Confessions
Light!
The second Kira has sent Sakura TV another message for Kira.
This time they've sent a video and a diary.
I thought that I'd better let you know...
A diary?
I bet that idiot's gone and done something stupid again.
Can't they just sit still and wait?!
They're saying to show the diary on TV?
Yes, this is it.
May 2006
1st: Even though I said I wasn't going to attend the circle activities
____with GW High, my friends still rang and asked me to go.
4th: Went to see "Morning Musume" with my friend at the Saitama Super Arena.
5th: Last day of the holiday, but I just lazed around at home.
7th: School started, but I'd divided the notebooks for different classes
____with my friends, so I didn't attend.
10th: Got invited to a party by friends but turned it down. Yokohama is too far.
13th: A friend came to borrow a CD that I'd promised to lend them.
2006? Last year's diary, huh?
16th: Forgot about a report that was due.
_____Asked a friend to come over in order to copy theirs.
19th: Read "Jump" for the first time in ages.
_____Reading it all in one go was fun.
2006? Last year's diary, huh?
22nd: Met up with a friend in Aoyama. Looked at each other's notebooks.
Look at the entry under the 30th.
28th: Apparently they are going to release the PZ3, which will be more amazing than the PZ2. One to watch!
30th: Confirmed that there was a Shinigami present at the Giant's match in the Tokyo Dome.
Confirmed that there was a Shinigami present in the Tokyo Dome.
I can only imagine that they're suggesting that we do this on the 30th of May.
If this goes out on TV, even the public will realize their intentions...
In any case, the only way you can see a Shinigami is if you touch their Death Note.
How do they--?
22nd: ____Met up with a friend in Aoyama. Looked at each other's notebooks.
Hey, Rem?
Huh?
Even though I have the eyes of a Shinigami, I'm unable to see my own lifespan. Can you explain why that is again?
Amane Misa
Humans possessing a Death Note need only see the lifespans of the humans they are going to kill.
Shinigami are unable to see each other's lifespans, and the same principle applies to humans who have Death Notes.
22nd of May... at Aoyama, we looked at each other's notebooks.
If by "notebooks", they mean "Death Notes", then... that's something that only I, as Kira, would understand.
The police should be focusing on the entry for the 30th of May...
"Confirmed that there was a Shinigami present at the Giant's match in the Tokyo Dome".
I'm probably correct in assuming that the entry regarding Aoyama is the real message.
But in that case...
What do you make of it, Light-kun?
I'd better be careful not to say anything careless here...
It's best that I let him go first.
Right now, it just looks pretty stupid to me.
Yeah! It's obvious that they're attempting to meet up with Kira at the Giants's game.
Broadcasting this will cause a panic, and the game will be cancelled... don't they even realize this?
If I'm honest... this is so dumb, I'm not quite sure how to deal with it.
If we broadcast this diary, we'd also have to make the announcement that the match on the 30th will be cancelled.
Yet, if we don't broadcast the diary, the second Kira won't make their move.
Plus, if we cancel the game, they may get angry, and who knows what they'll do...
It'll be okay. The second Kira appears to worship Kira.
We should be fine in believing their promise to our fake Kira that they won't take innocent lives.
Anyhow, first of all, we need to broadcast this diary and announce that the game is cancelled.
Then we'll announce that on the 30th, all the roads surrounding the Tokyo Dome will be controlled by us.
Lastly, we'll send a reply from our fake Kira, agreeing to the meeting.
Don't tell me... you think that they'll show up, despite how tightly the security around that area will be monitored?
I doubt that the real Kira will show, but I don't know about the second Kira...
We don't know how stupid they really are... or even if they truly are as stupid as they seem.
I'll try and see if I can figure out any other hidden messages.
If they're using a code that only those with a Shinigami's power would understand, then I won't be able to break it.
But... we'll need to ensure that we keep a close surveillance on all of the locations that are mentioned.
The 22nd; met up with a friend in Aoyama.
The 24th; met up with a friend in Shibuya.
Realistically, we can't expect any results, but we'll need to pay attention to anyone that's in Aoyama with a notebook, and anyone shopping clothes in Shibuya.
Just as I thought.
If the second Kira is caught, then I have to ensure that I get their notebook at the very least,
and in the worst case scenario, kill them and anyone else that's there.
I'll arrange to increase the number of surveillance cameras around Shibuya and Aoyama as much as possible.
In addition, on the respective days, we'll need to have as many plainclothes policemen as possible at each location.
Well, I'll go, since I'll easily be able to blend in with the crowd at Aoyama and Shibuya.
I'll go as well.
Light!
It'll be okay, father.
I occasionally go to Aoyama and Shibuya.
Besides, I'm the least likely to look out of place wandering around there with Matsui-san.
Moreover, the only person the second Kira is interested in, is Kira.
Well, Matsui-san, let's leave the plans for Aoyama and Shibuya until tomorrow.
Okay, got that. Light-kun, take care.
As soon as I get back outside and switch my phone back on, this always happens...
Yes?
This is Ryuuzaki.
I need you to observe Light-kun carefully during those two days as well.
This is confidential, so please keep this to yourself.
Yes... I understand.
"As long as my suspicions aren't at 0%, be suspicious of his every move"... is that what he's saying?
I'm home.
Light! You're home late.
Yeah.
They told me to keep my assistance with the investigation a secret...
I've got a girlfriend at the university now.
Oh!
What?! Onii-chan's got a girlfriend?!
Incredible!
Hey, hey, I'm an 18 year old university student; it's only natural, right?
Sayu, you've got to try harder too.
Eh?! I-I don't want to try hard!
Light? What about dinner?
I had room service at the hotel, so I'm fine.
Onii-chan! What do you mean by "hotel"?!
What? What? What kind of scandal have I unearthed?!
So, Ryuk... there's something I want to ask you.
Ah, I thought so.
If you're able to answer, please do.
Are Shinigami on Earth allowed to talk to one another?
Not too sure.
I think that from the moment I possessed a human, it became against the rules for me to do that kind of thing without the human's permission,
but there isn't really a law against talking, so the other Shinigami may come and talk to me.
So, you mean that there's a possibility that when the second Kira's Shinigami sees you, they'd be allowed to tell them that I am Kira?
Normally, they wouldn't. It depends on their personality.
So, is is safe for me to assume that your personality is what I believe it to be?
Yup. If I saw a human with a Shinigami, I wouldn't tell you.
Well, I think that's the right choice, Ryuk.
Thanks.
Huh? The fake Kira's already thought it through this far?!
What is it?
Aoyama is a huge place. I was doing some research on how to go about looking for them, and I found this...
On the 22nd, there's an event at the "Note Blue" nightclub.
Aoyama...
Aoyama literally translates to "Blue Mountain"
"Blue"...
and "Note"...
Seems that they've put a bit of effort into this.
It's possible that they're smarter than I thought.
Although if that's true, I may have to be more careful.
Right now, it seems that going to this "Note Blue" might be worth a shot.
But you don't want them to find out that you're Kira, do you?
Err... Light-kun...
What's this?
These are my friends at the university.
Nice to meet you.
This is my cousin, Tarou-san.
It's his first time in Tokyo, and he says he wants to have fun somewhere like Aoyama or Roppongi.
So, let's do our best for him.
He's also looking for a girlfriend, any applicants?
Hey, Light-kun!
Just what I expected from Light-kun!
No one would think that there are police present in this group of young people.
If I move around in a group, even if Ryuk gets seen, they won't know who he's possessed.
In addition, it'll act as a wall against L's surveillance cameras.
It's not bad for investigative purposes either.
All that remains is to watch the entrance of "Note Blue" prior to, and after the performance.
Found you!
Yagami... Tsuki-kun, is it?
月 = "Tsuki" (moon). Read as Light in this case, but this is not shown by the written form.
You're the only person whose lifespan I can't see!
That settles it! He's Kira!
I didn't think that it'd be this easy to meet you!
Hey, Rem, let's go home.
Huh, already? After all the effort you've put into meeting him?
It'd be bad for me to go up to him with all these people around and say something like, "I'm so happy to meet you, Kira-san!", wouldn't it?
Now that I know his name, it'll be easy to find out more.
It's an unusual name, after all.
Oooh! So it's written "Tsuki" but pronounced as "Light"!
Blood type:
Weight:
Height:
D.O.B.: _____February 28th, 1989
Oooh! So it's written "Tsuki" but pronounced as "Light"!
That's kinda beautiful!
Still, he's pretty amazing, isn't he, this Yagami Light...
Apparently, while he was in his second and third year at Junior High, he was the National Tennis Champion!
Also, for Toudai University's Entrance Ceremony this year, he gave the speech as the freshers' representative!
There's no photo, but it can't be anyone else with a name like this.
I'd never guessed that Kira would be so young and handsome...
Everything is far better than I'd imagined it would be!
There are places unashamedly selling registers, too.
This world is such a twisted place.
Now I know his address too!
In the end, on both the 22nd in Aoyama and the 24th in Shibuya, there was no evidence of any suspicious activity occurring.
All that remains now is the Dome on the 30th.
There was no one suspicious at "Note Blue" either...
Don't tell me that it's really going to happen at the Dome?
Ryuuzaki! Sakura TV have received another message from the second Kira.
It's postmarked the 23rd.
I was able to find Kira.
To everyone at the TV station and the police force, thank you.
I-Impossible?! Where? At Aoyama?
Did their Shinigami see Ryuk and tell them that?
No... In the crowd, it should have been impossible to tell who Ryuk was possessing...
I took every precaution to ensure that I wasn't followed...
If this really is connected to the diary... and was really posted on the 23rd... the only date it leaves is the 22nd, in Aoyama, as a corresponding date.
The only people to have gone from headquarters were Matsuda and Yagami Light.
So, is Yagami Light Kira, after all?
Yet there's absolutely no proof that it happened in Aoyama...
This is bad, they've found them.
Does this mean that Kira and the second Kira have joined forces...?
No, we don't know for sure that they've joined forces yet.
The second Kira only said that they'd "found" Kira.
They may yet have to make contact.
Now that we've progressed this far, the only thing that we can do is have the police appeal to the second Kira.
Appeal to?
Yes. The police will need to offer the second Kira a favorable deal if they tell us who Kira is.
Things can't get any worse for you, can they?
This isn't good... I have absolutely no idea how this second Kira may react...
Yet, there's no way that I can stop them...
If Kira doesn't already know who you are, it's not too late.
You mustn't approach Kira purely for the fun of it.
If you come in contact with Kira, you will almost certainly die.
You'll only be used!
All you should do now, is to think carefully about the value of human life.
Give us all the information you have on Kira, and atone for your crimes.
Save the people of the world from the fear of Kira.
Where are you going?
To confess.
Oh, so this is the choice you've made...
I wonder if that's Dad...
Coming!
Welcome home!
Eh?
Good evening. My name is Amane Misa.
I've come to return an important notebook that Light-san left behind at university.
P-Please wait for a moment.
Onii-chan!!
Notebook?!
Don't tell me?!
Pleased to meet you. I'm Amane Misa.
I was watching the TV, and I thought that you might worry about me, so I just had to come here.
This notebook...
Death Note?!
A Shinigami!
It's the fake Kira...
Come in.
Oh, are you sure that it's okay? I'm so happy.
Mother, she's gone through all the effort of bringing this over, so could we get some tea or something?
Yes, yes of course.
I've told you about this before.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
How did you know?
Ah, you really haven't traded your eyes, have you?
If you trade your eyes with a Shinigami, you're able to see people's names and lifespans,
but you're unable to see the lifespan of someone who has a Death Note.
Oh, I-I didn't know that much about it...
Okay, I've understood that much, but if you'd been caught, Kira's secrets would've been revealed.
It's okay. So far, I haven't been caught, and if I do as you say from now on, I won't get caught.
I'm right, aren't I?
And then I'll see L's name.
I'll be your eyes...
so...
So?
Please make me your girlfriend!
G-Girlfriend?
Yes!
If I handle this the wrong way, I could end up dead, but...
Impossible.
That day in Aoyama, there were triple the usual number of surveillance cameras operating.
If you went to Aoyama that day, you would have been captured on tape somewhere.
I'll be there as well.
If we were to become close after that...
Even meeting each other now is risky.
At least try to understand that.
These are photos of me on the day I went to Aoyama.
There's no doubt that she's unrecognizable.
So, what about fingerprints?
All those things you sent to the TV station were covered in the same fingerprints.
But those aren't my fingerprints!
Even I think through things a little before I act!
Until recently, I was living in Kansai, and I had a friend there who was interested in the occult.
I made a fake video containing footage of spirits and approached her about sending it to some TV stations.
She was really into the idea, and I got her to dub ten copies.
Then I copied the "Kira" over to them, without getting my own prints on them, and added the audio.
So, what's your friend doing now?
If you told me to kill them, I'd do it right now!
If you still refuse to trust me, you can look after this notebook.
As long as you only look after it, I'll still be the owner, so I should still be able to use the power of my eyes.
Right, Rem?
That's true.
This way, I won't be able to kill you, but if I become useless to you, you can kill me.
Why is she willing to go this far...
But you could already have torn out a page of the Death Note and hidden it somewhere.
Why do you have to be so suspicious of me?!
I don't mind if I really am just used by you!
Please, believe me...
How can she say such things?
A year ago, my parents were murdered right in front of me by a burglar.
I couldn't forgive that... yet the trial dragged on and on. Eventually they judged that he'd been falsely accused..
But then... Kira passed judgment on him.
To me, Kira is an absolute being!
No matter... no matter what, I wanted to meet you!
I wanted to say thank you.
You went through all this trouble for the sole purpose of meeting Kira?
She was able to implement the bare minimum of countermeasures against surveillance cameras and leaving fingerprints...
She's not as stupid as I thought...
Plus, she's saying that she'll do as I say from now on...
I understand...
I can't be your boyfriend, but I can pretend to be one.
Those eyes of yours, which you traded half your remaining life for in order to find and aid me, will be a great weapon.
Thank you. I'll try my hardest to make you love me.
To be continued