Friend
I understand. I can't be your boyfriend, but I can pretend to be one.
Thank you. I'll try my best to make you love me.
I'll show her L's face and find out his name, then I'll erase him along with his investigation team.
Killing her can wait till after...
She's the one person that knows Kira's true identity.
I can't leave her alive for too long.
"Pretend to be", huh?
I guess that'll do for now.
Anyway, let's get to the point: will you show Misa your Shinigami?
I guess I'll have to if I want her to trust me.
Okay... turn around for me.
Okay!
You can turn back now.
Heya!
Wow! Even though you're a Shinigami, you and Rem are completely different types!
I've heard about you, if only by name, Ryuk!
Nice to meet you!
Yes, nice to meet you too.
Oh yeah! Light! Do you know how Shinigami die?
You're already using Light, my first name?
Well, can I call you "Knight" instead of "Light", then?
To Misa, you're like a knight on a white horse!
"Light" is fine.
You're not seriously going to check all the video footage from Aoyama on the 22nd all by yourself, are you?
Yes. There is a real possibility that Kira and the second Kira made contact there.
I'd like to check all of these.
Also, Yagami-san...
Ah, yes?
Have Mogi-san keep a close eye on Light-kun's movements.
Light's movements?
If by any chance he really is Kira, the second Kira may try to approach him in some way.
I understand...
I wonder when Ryuuzaki actually sleeps...
I caught him sleeping, just like that, in his chair once...
Huh?
No, really...
So, you're saying that if a Shinigami has feelings for a specific human, and kills another human, in order to prolong the lifespan of the one they have feelings for... they'll die?
That's right.
I can't imagine that any Shinigami would do something like that.
Well, you'll certainly never do anything of the sort.
So, where have you been sending the video tapes to the TV station from?
Well... the first one was from Osaka, then from Tokyo, and the last one was from Nagano.
I tried to ensure that they couldn't pin down an exact location, so I used the shinkansen.
So, you still have tapes and envelopes with your friend's fingerprints, right?
Yeah.
You better destroy everything you used to make those videos...
That is, after we send the final tape from yet another different location tomorrow.
What should it say?
"I have decided not to reveal myself to Kira. To the police, thank you very much for the warning.
However, I will join Kira in purging the world of evil, and will gain their acceptance through aiding them.
I will begin by passing judgment on all criminals that Kira has not judged already.
Then, I shall proceed by sharing these powers with people that I find worthy and would like to continue making this world a better place."
"Share these powers"?
It's simply a line to confuse the investigation.
Since there are already two people who have this power, it's not inconceivable that there may be more.
If they believe that this figure could increase, they'll become more impatient.
Can you do this?
Don't say "Can you do this?". Just tell me to do it!
I will do whatever you ask of me.
There's one more important thing that I've got to mention...
Yes!
If we get caught by the police... even if we get caught as suspects... we can't mention anything about each other or the notebooks.
Unless they have the notebooks, there is no proof.
Can you swear to this?
I swear!
So, this concludes the boyfriend-girlfriend contract, right?
I guess so.
Then, now for my stipulations:
At minimum, there must be at least one date a week.
She doesn't get it after all...
That's not possible.
Why?!
It seems like you won't understand unless I spell it out for you.
L already suspects that I am Kira.
Wow, this "L" is really impressive...
Most people believe that he knows nothing, or that he's an idiot, when in fact he's already...
I won't say it's entirely thanks to that, but I've managed to get in direct contact with L.
L and Kira are in contact?! Both of you are amazing!
I'm getting a little excited...
L thinks that even if I am Kira, as long as he keeps his name hidden, he's safe.
So, to investigate me further, he revealed himself to me as "L".
But, the only proof he has, is that he has no other suspects.
In fact, if I act naturally around him, I expect he'll trust me and we'll investigate together.
So, all you have to do is take Misa to L?
It's not that easy.
It was hard enough for me to try and get close to him...
But more importantly, if someone suddenly starts to make contact with me, while at the same time,
Kira and the second Kira's attitudes towards society are changing, that person will be suspected of being the second Kira.
The suspicions of me being Kira will then deepen.
We can't allow them to think that we've suddenly met and started to go out with each other.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Sort of... is that why you're saying we won't be able to go out on dates?
You can't see me because it'd make them suspicious?
No... it'd probably be better if you start thinking carefully about how you're going to see L's face without him discovering your existence.
Yeah.
In order to get rid of L, I need you.
As much as possible, I'd like to meet you in person to pass on information...
Oh good!
...so, to ensure that our meetings remain unnoticed, I'll aim to go out with lots of different girls.
Huh? What do you mean?
You'll be dating other girls?
That's what it'll come down to...
No way!!
If I see you doing that... I'll kill the girl.
Scary...
Hey, Misa-chan...
It's "chan" now, is it?
...this is not a game.
We're going to change the world, remember?
I know, but... Misa loves you more than the world...
What are you talking about?
Your feelings for me should be those of a supporter.
Besides, this is the first time you've ever spoken to me.
You've never fallen in love at first sight?
No.
It's true that I wanted to meet Kira out of gratitude and sympathy, as opposed to love.
But Light, from the first time I saw you, I...
What the hell is wrong with this woman?
Popular as ever I see!
Well, if you love me, you can obey me, right?
First, you said that you didn't mind if I used you, and that you'd do as I say, didn't you?
But I can't forgive you if I see you with another girl!
These are two completely different issues!
Right now, both Death Notes are in my hands.
If you don't obey me, I'll kill you.
I won't let you do that... Yagami Light!
If you try to kill this girl, I'll write your name in my own Death Note... and kill you.
I can see this girl's lifespan.
If she dies before her time, I'll assume that you were responsible.
If you use the Death Note to kill me, in order to save her, wouldn't you die?
That's right. If you do that, Rem, you'll die!
You're correct... but that's fine by me.
What's with this Shinigami... is she serious? Then from this point on...
Light?
What is it, Mom?
It's already 11:30. You shouldn't have a girl here so late...
Ah, that's true. We were busy talking.
Sorry, Mom!
I apologize for intruding on you all till such a late hour.
Light, I'll see you soon.
Yeah.
Light, you should walk her to the station.
Right now, walking around outside with her would be...
I'll be fine! Good night!
She's a cute girl.
Yup, yup. I wasn't too sure about her at first, but she's cute.
She's my type!
If I kill the girl, she'll kill me?
Does that mean I'll have to remain on Rem's good side until she dies?
In addition, I'll have to protect her from getting caught by the police.
Thanks to you, Rem, Light truly is my "knight" now.
Seems so.
But you know, you can't really kill him.
To kill a Shinigami, you have to make them use their Death Note to save someone they like.
Yet, I can't try to kill her first by manipulating someone via the Death Note to attack Misa.
If Misa gets intro trouble, I'll be the first person she'll suspect, and I'll be killed straight away.
Currently, Rem's an even bigger threat than L.
S-She's... doing something as high profile as this?!
Amane Misa
Real name: Amane Misa
Hometown: Kyoto
D.O.B.: 1987 December 25th
Size: 152 tall, 76 bust, 51 waist, 75 hip
Blood type: AB
What will happen if they find out that I'm seeing someone like her?!
Damn it! No matter how I look at it, she's just getting in the way.
What can I do...
Wait! More importantly, I need to think of a method of using Misa's eyes to kill L.
If only I could get rid of L...
Onii-chan, good morning!
Good morning.
Mom, Sayu, can you not mention Misa-chan to father?
Okay, okay.
Actually, it's not just father either. I'd like you not to mention this to anyone.
She's an up-and-coming model, so she's not really supposed to have a boyfriend or anything along those lines.
Eh?! Really?! No wonder I thought she was cute!
Just what I'd expect from a girlfriend of yours.
I'll keep your secret... for 5,000 yen!
Moron.
Toudou University
The final message from Misa will arrive today.
It should be passed directly to the investigation, instead of going to the TV station.
I should stop by Investigative Headquarters and check L's reaction.
Yagami-kun.
Yagami-kun... you said that you'd go out with me, didn't you?
Yeah, I did.
And here we are, sitting together in lectures.
Yeah?
Yet, you don't seem the least bit happy about it. You seem distracted.
That's not true.
I was just thinking that going out with "Miss Toudai" means that many people will be saying things about me.
And truthfully, you are extremely beautiful, Takada-san.
Please don't dwell upon such matters.
I don't like fickle things such as "Miss Whatever".
Ah, you're right.
Yet, she clearly didn't mind...
Let's just go at our own pace without worrying about others, okay, Takada-san?
Yes.
'Evening.
Light-kun, you've arrived at a good time.
We've just received another video from the second Kira.
Again? That was fast.
Yes. They state that this is the final one.
Well, take a look.
I have decided not to reveal myself to Kira.
To the police, thank you very much for the warning.
However, I will join Kira in purging the world of evil, and will gain their acceptance through aiding them.
I will begin by passing judgment on all criminals that Kira has not judged already.
Then, I shall proceed by sharing these powers with people that I find worthy and would like to continue making this world a better place.
Having watched this, I get the feeling that Kira and the second Kira have made contact.
Why do you feel that they've made contact?
Didn't you feel it?
I assumed that you would get the same impression as I did.
It's the fact that their insistence on meeting Kira has completely changed.
Also, the fact that they now want to judge all the criminals Kira hasn't yet judged in order to be accepted by them.
Why hadn't they done that from the start?
It's because they hadn't thought so far.
Presumably, they've managed to make contact with Kira, who told them to pass this judgment.
Kira has also asked to conceal this link between them.
In that case, Kira is acting without thinking too much then.
Yes.
Has something happened to stop them from thinking so clearly?
Perhaps they're trying to confuse me by making the connection between them obvious.
Realistically, this connection is a huge threat... but due to this, my suspicions towards Light-kun have lessened.
What do you mean by that, Ryuuzaki?!
If Light-kun was Kira, instead of sending a tape like this, I believe that he'd get the second Kira to make another threat forcing L... that is, me, to appear on TV.
As long as we assumed they hadn't made contact yet, it would be the second Kira's responsibility...
Then all he'd need to get them to say is:
"I stopped once when Kira told me to. But I no longer believe that that warning came from Kira. Kira should be pleased if L dies.
There's no way that they would try and stop me."
Ryuuzaki...
Yes?
If I truly were Kira... I wouldn't do that.
Why?
If you genuinely are L, then I know your character.
No matter how you're threatened, there's no way that you'd actually appear on TV.
You would never consider taking the fall for someone else.
Without a doubt, you'd have some sort of plan to get out of it.
So you knew?
Light, even if it's purely theoretical, I want you to stop with this "If I were Kira" talk.
Ah, I'm sorry, father.
But I want to express my thoughts clearly to Ryuuzaki.
I want the case to end quickly, and then my name can be cleared.
Besides, the reason I can say "If I were Kira", is because I'm not Kira.
That's correct... Light-kun isn't Kira.
Or should I say, it'd be a problem if he was, because... Light-kun is... the first friend I've ever had.
You're a friend that I really get along with as well.
Thanks.
It's lonely with you being absent from university.
I'd like to play tennis with you again at some point.
Yes, by all means.
"Friend"?!
"Friend", huh? Well, good for you, Light.
Ryuuzaki... he's easily managed to deduce the connection between Kira and the second Kira.
Looks like I'll need to get rid of my enemies as soon as possible.
Oh, right...
It'll be even more dangerous to meet Misa from now on.
Light!
I couldn't wait an entire two weeks, so I was just on my way over to see you!
This is the first time in my entire life that I seriously wanted to hit a girl...
I just really wanted to see you...
Well, you'd better come to my house.
A girl... again?
Misa-san, welcome!
I've seen a lot of magazines with you in them!
Welcome.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Mom, can we have some tea?
Rem?
Huh?
You're Misa's ally, right?
Yeah, well, I've seen this girl a number of times from the Shinigami world, and due to certain circumstances, I've got some feelings for her.
You've got feelings, despite being a Shinigami?
Seems like you don't like the fact that I said, "If you kill this girl, I'll kill you".
So, does this mean that if Misa is happy, you're happy?
Yeah, that's how it works.
I don't want to see her sad.
Misa really... likes me so much.
Light?
Misa?
Yes?
Is my happiness your happiness too?
Yes.
Can you ask Rem to kill L?
Rem wants you to be happy, yet if one of us is caught by L, that happiness will be threatened.
Although Shinigami aren't supposed to tell humans other people's names, there's no rule that stipulates who Rem can and can't kill.
Yeah. If you kill L, I'll have even greater feelings for Misa, and I'd be thankful to you too, Rem.
More importantly, we'd both be happy together.
Rem, I want to be loved by Light.
Both of us will be happy... I'll be happy.
Okay...
Okay then, Yagami Light.
I don't like you, so even if I end up prolonging your life, it won't kill me.
I'll kill L. He means nothing to me.
Yay, Rem! Thank you!
I knew you'd do it!
L is going to die... just like that?
To be continued