Ally
Ah, you can't go through with this belt...
Huh? Still doesn't work?
Hmm... we really don't have a choice but to accustom you to the security measures around here, no?
How about... this?!
Good day!
What's happened to your forehead?
Oh, this?
Well, I had a fight with my wife.
My kid is still young, so it looks like I'm going to have to commute here.
Yes, it would be better for you to go home.
What a waste! The rooms here are incredible!
You should just move in yourself, with the family and all.
Don't treat me like I'm a single, easy-going guy such as yourself.
Where's Ryuuzaki?
A date.
He's gone on a date, along with Light-kun, in Misa-Misa's room.
Surveillance cameras, eh?
Well, I guess it's unavoidable considering Amane is somehow connected to the second Kira.
And Matsuda, stop calling her "Misa-Misa"!
Oh, okay...
Hey! You know, for me, this just isn't feeling like a date.
Please, don't mind me.
Anyway, aren't you going to eat that cake?
Sweet things make you fat, so I avoid them.
As long as you use your brain, you won't get fat, even if you eat sweets.
Ah! You're making fun of Misa again!
Fine. How about I give you the cake if you leave me and Light alone?
If I leave you alone, I'd still be watching you on the surveillance cameras; it'll still be the same.
Pervert! Will you just quit with all this tasteless stuff, already?
Whatever you say, I'm still taking your cake.
That's okay. We'll just close the curtains and turn off the lights.
The cameras detect infrared as well.
More importantly, despite moving into these headquarters filled with equipment, Ryuuzaki, you seem to lack the motivation to do anything.
Motivation?
I don't have any.
To be honest, I'm pretty depressed.
Depressed?
Yes.
Because I've always thought that Light-kun was Kira, the idea that this theory may be wrong has come as quite a shock.
Still, I have my suspicions...
Hence the reason for these.
But then again, Kira can manipulate people's actions.
In other words, Kira was manipulating you in such a way that I would suspect you...
Both Light-kun and Misa-san were being manipulated by Kira.
If you think about it this way, it does seem to make sense...
By that reasoning, even though Misa and I were being manipulated, we were still Kira.
Yes, there's no doubt about it.
You're both Kira.
According to my theory, Light-kun was Kira when I imprisoned him.
And from that moment, criminals stopped dying.
Until then, the theory that Light-kun was Kira still worked.
Yet, two weeks later, criminals started dying again.
So from here, we move to the next assumption...
Kira's powers can be passed from person to person.
That's an interesting theory, but if that's the case, then catching Kira will be no small feat.
Yeah, that's why I'm stumped.
Even if we catch those being manipulated, their power will just pass to someone else, and no memory of it will remain.
No matter how many people we manage to catch, it'll be pointless.
But none of this has been confirmed yet. Try and rouse some motivation.
Motivation?
I don't have much.
In fact, it's probably better if we don't try too hard.
If we chase them too desperately, we'll just be placing our own lives at risk... don't you agree?
Ryuuzaki...
That hurt.
Don't fuck with me.
You have no motivation because your little theory about me being Kira was wrong?!
Perhaps I phrased that badly. I meant that making the first move might work against us, so--
How are we supposed to catch them if we don't even chase them?!
How many innocent people do you think have already been entangled in this?!
Besides, weren't you the one who imprisoned both Misa and myself?!
I know... but no matter what reasons you had, my motto is...
An eye for an eye.
It's not that my theory was wrong, merely that "Yagami Light is Kira" and "Amane Misa is the second Kira" wasn't enough to solve the case.
That's why I'm depressed.
Is it so wrong for a human to feel this way?
I'd say it was wrong.
The way you're talking, it sounds like you won't be satisfied unless I really am Kira.
I'm not satisfied unless Light-kun really is Kira?
You could be right.
I've only just realized... I wanted you to be Kira.
Remember, an eye for an eye.
I'm fairly strong you know.
W-We should contact them and get them to stop.
Yes?
Ryuuzaki! Get this!
Misa-Misa was voted top of the Eighteen readers' popularity poll!
Oh, I see.
This means that she'll be the star in Director Nishinaka's next movie!
What's wrong?
It's just Matsuda being his usual dumb-ass self.
Well, Matsuda-san is a bit of an airhead by nature.
I can hear you both...
Two Months Later
Ryuuzaki, I know you've got no motivation for anything, but can you take a look at this?
Look at this carefully. It seems like this might be hinting at something.
All three of them held important positions within enterprises that represent Japan.
Name
Death by
Date
Tamiya
Rokuhei
Heart
attack
Aoi
Kouji
Heart
attack
Moriya
Takeyoshi
Heart
attack
Ashimoto
Koutarou
Traffic
accident
Tanikan
Kenji
Traffic
accident
Kawashima
Tatsuya
Traffic
accident
Sudou
Hitoshi
Illness
All three of them died from heart attacks.
As a result, Yotsuba's share prices have risen, while those of other enterprises have fallen.
Simply put, all these deaths have benefited Yotsuba.
If you search a little deeper, there have been thirteen incidents like this over the last three months.
What do you think?
The only conclusion I can draw from this, is that Kira is backing Yotsuba.
Yes, but if this is true, killing criminals isn't Kira's primary objective.
Yes, it's possible that they're using the act of killing criminals as a camouflage for killing people for their own profit.
So, how's that? Feeling slightly more motivated now?
It's impressive that everything is going this smoothly; nobody suspects anything at all.
Both Yotsuba's share price and profits have gradually been rising without gaining attention.
Yes.
Everything is going exactly according to our calculations.
There's just one thing that's been on my mind... the three we killed last week... why did they all die of heart attacks?
For one of them, I thought we decided on an accidental death?
It's probably because we specified the place of death as along the Wangansen.
However, at the time of his death, he wasn't at home, but was secretly with a woman in Italy.
So, if there's an impossible element in the cause of death we provide...
Kira will merely kill them with a heart attack.
That's why I said last week that if we just request for a death either via an accident or illness,
he'll eliminate them in the fastest and most natural way possible.
Anyway, the police should already have their hands full investigating the deaths of criminals.
If there was someone who was able to trace these civilian deaths back to us, they would have to be some sort of god.
Furthermore, it's all been taken care of already.
Chief! Ah, Mogi-san! Thanks for all your hard work.
It's amazing! Thanks to Light-kun's work, there's a real possibility that Kira is connected to the Yotsuba Group.
Yotsuba?
Er, that's right...
That's probably it, Matsuda.
Just now, I heard from the Deputy Chief that Kira has been sending bribes to politicians.
This is what Kira is promising... in return for the police simply ceasing their pursuit of Kira, they would leave the politicians untouched.
The police have sold out to Kira.
Mogi has already made his decision.
Aizawa, Matsuda, if you still want to pursue Kira, you'll need to follow Mogi and myself, and hand in your resignations to the police!
Unless we decide to resign from the police, we'll no longer be allowed to investigate Kira seriously.
W-What's the meaning of this?!
It's very simple. They said that if I continue to investigate with L, I'll be fired.
S-So, Chief, what did you do?
In a few hours, I'll no longer be the Chief.
But you have your own lives, so think carefully before you decide what to do.
You're right, especially those with wives and children...
I think that all of you should return to the police force.
I originally began alone...
I'm grateful that you've all managed to stick with it for so long.
But I'll be able to do this alone.
And I promise to visit you all with Kira's head as a present to the police.
Ryuuzaki, as long as I'm here, you won't be alone.
I've made this promise as well.
That's correct. Until Kira is caught, I'll need Yagami-kun to stay with me.
However, the rest of you should return to the police force.
Didn't you once say that you needed the cooperation of the police with this case?
That was because then, the police, as an organization, was prepared to disobey Kira and maintain its stance on this investigation.
But help from a few civilians who have quit the police can't really be said to be with "the cooperation of the police".
The police have decided not to catch Kira. You've done enough.
Well, it's true that if we leave the police, we may not be of much help to you,
but what about our feelings?! We've put our lives on the line for this case!
We should have the right to decide by ourselves: do we want to continue investigating, or return to the police?
I guess so... in that case, please make your own decision.
B-But Chief, by quitting the police we'll be without a job.
Even if we manage to catch Kira, what are we supposed to do after that?
After that? I hadn't really thought of that, but I'm guessing that once we've caught Kira, we'd have to... find new jobs.
I've decided! I'm going to quit the police and continue chasing Kira!
I've got a job as Misa-Misa's manager, besides, if I return to the police, I'd feel like a loser--
Watch what you say, Matsuda.
Is it possible to return to the police, and help out in my spare time?
No. If you're planning to return to the police, please don't come here again.
I swear I won't reveal a single thing from this place!
I definitely won't give you any information from here.
If you want to pursue Kira as a lone policeman, then that's up to you.
I don't think it'd be right for you to quit as a police officer, and then go chasing Kira to the point of causing your family concern.
It's exactly as Ryuuzaki says. If you decide to stop now, no one will blame you.
That's right. We won't think of you as a traitor!
But Chief, you also have a family...
Our circumstances are completely different.
This is so unfair. I wanted to stay as well...
I approached this knowing that my life was going to be at risk...
And if I quit now, how can I face Ukita?
Damn it! Why has it become wrong for a police officer to chase Kira?!
Ryuuzaki... didn't you make me promise that if anything happens to any member of the investigation, including being fired by the police,
I would provide them and their family with sufficient financial aid for a lifetime?
Why are you reluctant to tell them this?
Mind your own business, Watari.
I apologize.
What? You've even acted to protect our livelihood?
Isn't that great, Aizawa-san?!
Ryuuzaki, were you testing me to see whether I'd leave the police and continue here?
I-It isn't like that, Aizawa! Ryuuzaki just hates to say things like that himself.
T-That's right!
No.
I was testing him.
I wanted to see what choice he'd make.
Ryuuzaki...
Fine, I get it! I'm leaving this investigation and returning to the police.
Aizawa-san!
I was unable to make an instant decision like you, and was leaning towards returning to the police.
There's no reason to be stubborn...
No! I quit!
I've just realized... I hate Ryuuzaki, his methods, all of it!
You know, Aizawa-san, I like people that are like you...
That's the other thing I hate! The fact that you can say that with such a straight face!
I'm out of here!
Thanks for all your hard work.
I've found another one!
A branch manager from one of Yotsuba's biggest rival banks.
September 7th - slipped on the stairs at home and died.
September 7th, that makes it a Friday.
Taking a look at this again, it just occurred to me that all the deaths which benefit Yotsuba happen towards the end of the week.
Eh? Really?!
At first the times of death were random; however, they've gradually begun to cluster around the time from Friday evening until Saturday afternoon.
That's an excellent observation, Chief!
I keep telling you that I'm not "Chief" anymore.
No. To me, you'll always be the Chief!
This is an excellent lead, father!
I'm not planning to lose to you and Ryuuzaki just yet.
I don't want to be a dead weight around here.
Dead weight...?
Is Kira a part of Yotsuba? Is Kira merely using Yotsuba?
I've got no idea which it is, but we can assume that Kira is behind this.
It's time that we investigate Yotsuba thoroughly.
I've finished compiling a list of all Yotsuba's employees, both here and overseas.
Thank you.
Over 300,000 people! How did he manage this so fast?
That's amazing, Mogi-san!
There was always something amazing about Mogi-san, right from the start.
R-Ryuuzaki, is there anything else I can do? Other than being a manager?
You want to make yourself useful?
Yes!
Then, can you bring me another cup of coffee?
And don't forget our guests as well.
Who are they?
When did they get in here?
They're our new members.
I'm Aiber, a con artist. Nice to meet ya.
I'm Weddy, a thief by trade.
A-A con artist and a thief?!
That's correct.
Aiber acquires and learns what is necessary for every social discourse, and is guaranteed to form an intimate connection with his target.
We'll be using him as our spy.
Weddy is a thief that can crack any safe, key or security system.
As proof, she was able to infiltrate this place without anyone noticing her.
W-We'll be investigating with criminals?
They're criminals, but not the type that appear in public. Kira will not be able to judge them.
Try to think of them as professionals from the underworld.
I get it. In order to investigate Yotsuba properly, we'll need such people.
Let's all work together on this.
Yeah!
Okay...
It's Papa!
Papa!!
Yumi... Eriko?
What are you doing in such a place?
If you're going to come home, just say so. I haven't bought you any dinner.
I'll give you half of my croquettes!
Yeah... I haven't had a lot of rest, so they've given me some leave.
"Leave"? You have time off?
Yup, that's right.
Yay!
From now on, I should get some time off every week.
That means we can come to this park... even the zoo... or theme parks...
What's wrong?
Mama... papa is crying.
To be continued