Makeshift
Well then, let's begin this meeting.
Given that there's only seven of them, one of the eight must have...
I suppose they've most likely... killed him.
In order to advance the Yotsuba Group's development further, whom should we kill?
See! It's exactly like I said!
This is bad... at this rate...
But before that, there are a few things we need to discuss.
Firstly, we need to address Hatori's death.
It was unavoidable.
Besides, if I'm honest, I'm kind of relieved that Hatori is dead.
Kira has clearly shown us what will happen to those who try to leave this group.
I believe everyone here has understood the significance of Hatori's death.
Let this be a lesson to us all.
Next, Erald Coil's report...
One of their members has died, and that's all they've got to say?!
So, this report is what our $5 million paid for?
He hasn't uncovered any vital information, such as L's face or name.
Is this guy, Coil, really going to be of any use?
Wait.
At the end of the report he warns us not to underestimate L's existence.
"Given your current pace... particularly the fact that the deaths which benefit the Yotsuba Group occur every Friday and Saturday...
it's possible that L will connect this to Kira."
To be able to figure this much out about us, Coil's a pretty capable guy in my book.
At any rate, we need to reconsider our current plan of killing off people towards the end of each week.
T-This is incredible. The confessions just seem to keep on coming.
Surely, with this recording, we'd be able to arrest all seven of them?
Just as I thought, this is bad...
Kira's not being very versatile with this, huh?
They should at least attempt to spread them out over the course of the week.
I think that since Coil's realized this, it's going to be too risky to carry on killing at our current pace.
From now on, we've got to be more discreet, and ensure that no one else finds out about this.
Alright then, moving on to the main issue; whom should we kill?
The launch of E.L.F. Insurance in Japan... if we don't stop that,
then the Yotsuba Group, among other companies, will lose a lot of clients.
Agreed.
So, with regards to E.L.F., shall we go with accidental deaths for those on this list?
No objections.
What on earth?! Just like that?!
Another target is the one who's opposing the Yotsuba Group's plans for a resort.
Mr. Zenzai Santorou of the Kugisawa Group.
Zenzai suffers from high blood pressure, so we can specify a date for him to suffer a stroke. How's that?
No objections.
Kira, accidental death, death through illness, specifying exact times...
It's exactly like we thought! There's no mistake about it!
No, unfortunately, until said people actually die, we can't say that for sure.
From what these seven have disclosed at this meeting,
as long as we closely monitor the actions of those seven until those mentioned at the meeting die...
if we always closely monitor these things from now on... without a doubt, we'll catch Kira.
Ryuuzaki!!
What's up with both of you?
I can't go along with your plan! It's wrong!
I knew it...
It's apparent that your plan is to allow those seven to continue killing in order to catch Kira, but I can't do that!
He's right! The seven of them are clearly murdering people!
Surely we can prove this with Matsuda's testimony and these video tapes?!
It's quite a dilemma... if we do arrest them now, everything we've worked for will be ruined.
So, we'll request Kira to kill the E.L.F. people in three weeks' time, and Zenzai this weekend.
How's that?
No objections.
This weekend?! There's no time left!
Light, do you have the phone numbers for all seven?
Yes.
It doesn't matter who, we need to contact one of them and force them to call off the murders.
Wait a minute please. If we do that, it'll mean that they've been discovered just three days after Aiber got in contact with them.
It'll look suspicious.
Most importantly, it's extremely likely that doing so would make it impossible for us to figure out who Kira is.
After all this work, we'd be back at square one.
In order to catch Kira, we need to be able to prove that they are Kira.
Ryuuzaki, if Kira really is one of those seven, is it fair to assume that if we call one of them,
the chance of them being Kira is one in seven?
I was thinking that there'd be two at most, so I'd say two out of seven.
If we're already prepared for them to find out that they're being investigated,
then it's worth betting on the two out of seven.
I'm going to borrow the title "L", Ryuuzaki.
Someone who, from the conversation, looks unlikely to be Kira, yet is still influential... that would be...
Ooi!
Namikawa!
If you're going to call, use the phones in this building.
They can't be traced or tapped.
Ideally we would just wipe out all the executives of our rival enterprises, one after the other.
That would be the fastest method, but I guess it doesn't work like that...
Is this the Director of the First Trade Department, Namikawa Reiji-san?
Yes? That's right.
Please give out natural responses while listening to me.
I am L.
Cameras and bugging equipment have been set up in that meeting room.
The entire meeting has been recorded by us.
You began the talks with Hatori's death, and then went on to discuss who you should kill.
Am I right?
He's seen everything!
If you're not Kira or negotiating directly with them, I can make a deal with you.
A deal?!
Postpone the murders of the E.L.F. president, and Zenzai by a month.
I doubt that will prove too difficult for you.
I see...
And then?
If you do this and cooperate with us from now on, you will...
no, in fact, all except Kira will be considered as attending these meetings under duress, and will not be charged.
Oh, really...
Now I've got no choice but to side with L.
No, if Kira finds out that I've sided with L, they'll kill me... what should I do?
If you tell people about this phone call, it'll just cause a panic.
It'll do you no favors, and you'll all be caught.
However, my aim is to go head-to-head with Kira.
Listen carefully... if L beats Kira, you won't be charged; if Kira beats L, you get to continue your affluent life.
You should just play along with both sides and see what happens.
L or Kira, whoever wins, you can't lose.
The only way for you to lose... is if you're caught right now.
He's already figured out what my final decision has got to be.
Well then?
Fine, on Monday.
What is it, Namikawa? Who was it?
One of my men has messed up. I'll have to deal with it on Monday.
Sorry for the interruption. Let's get back on topic.
As for when we're going to kill the E.L.F. members and Zenzai...
How about we give Coil a month, and if he still hasn't discovered L's identity by then, we'll kill them off on random dates.
Then, we'll give him another month, and repeat.
Once L is out of the way, we can resume killing two or three each fortnight.
Basically, our main priority should be to deal with L.
I see. It's true that if we deal with L, we'll have no one left in our way.
Until then, we should tread carefully.
That might work.
Well, it can't hurt to play it safe.
In that case, we'll give Coil a month.
No objections!
L should be satisfied with this...
However, we'll continue to meet on a fortnightly basis.
Meeting closed.
It seems to have worked.
Yeah...
Yagami-kun, you really are amazing.
Not only did you manage to postpone the killings, but we might even be able to obtain information from Namikawa.
Your methods are similar to mine, and you managed to think of this before I did.
In that case...
If I die, you may be able to carry on the name of "L".
What are you talking about?!
We have a month to deduce who Kira is, and to find the proof.
The challenge begins now.
Yes...
However, since you were the first to notice the Yotsuba Group, it's fair to say that you may be more capable than I.
It's possible that you may be able to handle it, Yagami-kun.
If I were to die...
...would you succeed me as L?
If I were to die, would you succeed me... with the name of "L"?
If he's Kira, and is putting on an act, he'll definitely answer "yes".
What are you talking about, Ryuuzaki?
As long as we're wearing these, we'll die together--
Oh, I get it...
Ryuuzaki, I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to speak your thoughts aloud to everyone else here.
Ryuuzaki is thinking that if I were Kira, then either I still am Kira right now and just pretending otherwise,
or Kira's power have passed to someone else, and right now I have no recollection of being Kira.
Those are the two patterns.
If it is the former, and I am just acting, then he can never take these handcuffs off.
No, even if I wasn't acting, he probably wouldn't remove the handcuffs.
He's thinking that I was Kira, and even though that power may have passed to someone else,
I might have set things up so that the power will return to me.
Basically, it's not that I was simply being manipulated,
rather, I may have transferred the power to someone, and have planned to regain it once the suspicions against me had been lifted.
Amazing... he knew exactly what I was thinking...
Ryuuzaki was thinking that, "after L's position is his, Yagami Light will become Kira".
Correct.
To gain the same status as L and be in a position to even manipulate the police... while secretly being Kira.
I would be invincible.
And you think that I'm capable of achieving this... no, in fact you are saying I would do this.
Yes.
But what do you think now?
If nothing else, you must have realized that I'm not acting, right?
You mean that if you were putting on an act to take my position you wouldn't be revealing your plan to everyone, am I right?
Ryuuzaki...
Do you truly believe that after catching the current Kira, I'd go on to become Kira... A murderer?
Do you really see me as that kind of human being?!
I believe so.
I can see it in you.
A-Again...
Okay! An eye for an eye!
Let's just call this a draw and be done with it!
Yeah, that's right. For now, we've got to catch the Kira that's right in front of us.
As long as we're wearing these handcuffs, you can't have any complaints.
You're right, we've only got a month left.
Ryuuzaki?
Yes?
If we can use the footage of that meeting as evidence to arrest those seven, won't the judging of criminals stop as well?
Again...
Unfortunately...
"Unfortunately"?
...we can't be certain that Kira is among those seven.
If Kira is only connected to them, and we arrest them, then all that will happen is that those seven will be killed.
Unless we know for sure that one of those seven is Kira, there's no point in arresting them...
and even if Kira is among them, it's difficult to say who it is right now.
It's still too early to tell.
B-But if we can't say that Kira is definitely not among those seven,
there's a possibility that if we arrest them, the murders will cease.
It's as my father says. There is that possibility.
Umm, I think I'll chase Kira on my own after all.
I'll let you use these headquarters and I'll continue to use them myself as well.
Yagami-san and the rest of you can continue to pursue Kira as you wish, using your own methods.
I'll investigate using my own methods.
Unless we do this, it'll just end in arguments.
Let's just go our separate ways.
In other words, you insist on narrowing it down before you pursue Kira?
Yes.
We can't solve this case unless Kira is caught.
I'm not saying that there's no point in stopping the deaths of the criminals in front of you,
but unless we expose all truths to the light, Kira will appear again, and consequently, the victims will increase in numbers.
That being the case, it's my belief that we need to confirm Kira's identity through those seven.
I'm against the arrest of those seven, so if you're planning to do it, it's your responsibility.
I'll pursure Kira by myself.
We have a month. It'll depend on which of us is fastest.
Ryuuzaki! Where are you going?
To Amane's room.
I'm sorry. Light-kun, I know you're on your father's side, but I'll need you to come with me as I can't remove the handcuffs.
Light! Is it okay if we go on a date today?
Even if Ryuuzaki-san has got to come...
Misa-san?
Do you love Light-kun?
Y-Yes... very much.
And yet, you also admire Kira?
Yes...
So, if you had to choose between them, who would you pick?
Huh?! Light, of course!
It's true that I'm grateful to Kira and I've wanted to meet them in the past, but that isn't love!
It'll definitely have to be Light.
And Light-kun, you want to catch Kira. Don't you, Light-kun?
Yes, of course.
He wants to catch them. Now, what do you think of that?
If Light wants to catch them, then I want them caught too.
So, if it was possible, you would want to be of use to Light-kun, and help him investigate, correct?
R-Ryuuzaki!
Yeah! Misa would do anything for Light!
-_-
Just wait a minute! What are you planning?!
We'll get Erald Coil to report to those seven that he's got a lead that suggests that Amane Misa may know L in some way.
And that "Amane Misa was interrogated on suspicion of being the second Kira".
That's true too.
If they think that there's a chance that Amane Misa knows L,
they'll definitely employ her to be in their commercials, and attempt to question her.
That time Matsuda messed up, he did ask for her to be hired for a commercial, after all.
Yup, yup!
No way.
Why?
Because that would put you in danger, of course.
You're worried about my safety? Yay!
But Misa would do anything for you. This is nothing.
Listen Misa, if they think you know L, they'll try any means possible to get you to admit it.
It'll be fine! No matter how much they torture Misa, she won't say a thing!
Yeah, that's right.
We know that Kira can manipulate people before their deaths.
There's a real chance that they'll manipulate Misa into talking before killing her.
In fact, if they kill L, they'll no longer have a use for her, and will kill her in order to silence her.
I wouldn't want that...
Light-kun...
as long as we win, Misa-san won't die.
Also, as long as we're connected by these handcuffs, we'll share the same destiny.
If I die, you'll die too.
And if that happens, the saddest person will be Misa-san.
Either Light-kun and I die, or we catch Kira.
So, which is it?
Catch Kira! I can't live in a world without Light!
That's correct!
Hey, Ryuuzaki! You're going too far!
We don't have time. I'm in a hurry here.
Besides, Amane Misa's willpower and love for Light-kun are beyond comparison in this world.
R-Ryuuzaki-san...
Misa may have been misjudging you until now!
Calling you a pervert and so on...
But in reality, you actually understand me!
Yeah, Misa-san is an excellent lady, completely worthy of Light-kun.
Thanks, Ryuuzaki!
I might fall for you...
Erm, I'm not so keen on that... how about we say "we're friends", Ryuuzaki-san?
Yes.
I've made another friend.
Yup! All of Light's friends are Misa's friends too!
Let's all get along!
And Misa never sells out her friends!
The three of us will combine our powers and catch that Kira!
Well actually, Yagami-kun wants to approach the investigation with his father in a different way than I.
So, it'll just be the two of us: Misa-san and myself.
Huh?! What's up with that?!
You play pretty dirty, Ryuuzaki... you're giving me no choice but to join this investiga--
No. We're fine.
What are you talking about?!
Light's joining too! It's decided!
No, that's not it! I'm against the methods used in this investigation itself. It's too dangerous for Misa.
Light... thank you so much for thinking of me.
But let me do this. Misa wants to be useful to you, Light.
I want to be able to help you, so that you'll love me even more.
Besides, Misa will quite happily die for you.
As I thought, given the current situation, it'll prove difficult to arrest those seven.
Any good ideas, Mogi? Matsuda?
To be continued