Resurrection
Ryuuzaki, let me go.
Chief, I'm coming too!
Understood.
Remember that you're dealing with Kira.
Under no circumstances should you let him see your face, and exercise extreme caution while restraining him.
Watari, if Higuchi makes even one suspicious move...
I understand. I'll immobilize him without actually killing him.
Aizawa, did you bring something to obscure your face with?
Yes.
Back us up.
Understood! Thank you very much, Chief!
Higuchi, put both hands up and step out of the car!
Higuchi has been secured.
Mogi-san, as we planned, place the transceiver on him.
Yes!
Higuchi, how were you killing people? Answer me!
If you don't, we'll make you confess using any means at our disposal.
It's a notebook...
A notebook?
You probably won't believe me, but if you write the name of a person whose face you know in that notebook, that person will die.
A notebook...
Yagami-san?
Yes... I've found it in his bag.
It's true there are names written here, but there's nothing unusual about this note--
What's wrong, Yagami-san?
M-Monster!!
Calm down. Yagami-san, you aren't carrying a gun at the moment.
Yes... yes, that's right.
Are you okay, Chief?
M-Mogi! Can't you see that thing?!
Chief, you're very tired at the moment--
What's happening, Mogi-san?!
A-Ah... I-It looks like only those who've touched this notebook can see this... this monster!
Please bring that notebook to the helicopter.
R-Right...
What can you possibly be planning, Yagami Light?
By touching a Death Note that you previously owned, all your memories associated with it will be recovered.
However...
Ryuuzaki, here it is.
I-It's a Shinigami... they really do... exist...
Yagami Light...
Notebook...
Showed each other our notebooks in Aoyama...
Love at first sight...
The second Kira...
Ryuuzaki, give me the notebook!
Kira's method of killing...
Kira... the second Kira...
Two notebooks...
More than one notebook exists.
It's not over yet...
I am L...
A-Are you okay? Anyone would be petrified if they saw that monster.
Ryuuzaki?
Yes?
Firstly, we've got to compare the names written here against the list of victims.
Erm... yes... I suppose you're right...
I've won.
Just as planned!
I'm relinquishing all ownership of this notebook.
The ownership of this notebook now returns to Rem. Correct?
Correct. Your point being?
Okay, now give that notebook to Ryuk.
Fine.
The owner of this notebook is now Ryuk.
Ryuk, next, I want you to drop that notebook here, onto the ground of the human world.
Huh? Well, guess it's okay...
And so the ownership returns to me.
So the ownership has gone round in a circle; nothing has changed.
Maybe...
But there'll be a time when this will be of use.
And the first notebook that I received from Ryuk...
I'm giving it back to you, and I want you to give it to Rem.
Here.
Rem, I'll need you to pass that to someone who has a reasonably high status, yet remains greedy for success.
Someone who'll undoubtedly use the notebook to further those goals.
Doing this will guarantee Misa's release from imprisonment.
If she still hasn't been released after several years, kill me. How's that?
Yagami Light, what are you planning?
This is all to save Misa. Trust me.
Understood... if this will help Misa, I'll do as you say.
Next, I'll manipulate the situation so, like Misa, I'll be detained and under 24-hour surveillance.
While in detention, I'll relinquish all ownership of the Death Note and it'll erase any associated memories I've got.
During that time, the judging of criminals will recommence, and if that continues, at some stage, Ryuuzaki will be forced to release us both.
And then, with my memories gone, I'm sure I'll attempt to catch Kira.
It's just the type of person I am.
So, you plan to find the person Rem gives the notebook to before L can, and reclaim the notebook?
Exactly. And I'll kill whoever has ownership of it.
But there is one problem:
If you hold no ownership over that Death Note, your memories will only return as long as you're physically touching it.
The moment you let go, all your memories will be erased once more.
I need to kill Higuchi without letting go of this notebook.
That way, the ownership will pass to me, and my memories won't disappear.
If I pull this four times with less than a second between each...
Success! I knew I'd be wearing this at the time.
Old habits die hard.
Yagami-san, please escort Higuchi to the car.
O-Okay... understood.
This notebook... if analyzed scientifically, I wonder if we'd discover anything.
Yagami-kun, that's not like you. That thing is beyond science.
I guess you're right.
This is the longest 40 seconds of my life...
Higuchi! Ryuuzaki! Higuchi is...
What?! What's going on?!
Hey, Higuchi?!
What are you doing, father?! If Higuchi dies now...
T-This isn't possible... but I think he's...
Yeah, he's dead.
The next, Ryuuzaki... will be you.
"How to use"...
"The human whose name is written in this note shall die."
"This note will not take effect unless the writer has the person's face in their mind when they write his/her name."
"Therefore, people sharing the same name will not be affected."
"If the cause of death is written within 40 seconds of writing the person's name, it will happen as it is written."
"If the cause of death is not specified, by default, the person will die of a heart attack."
"Should a cause of death be specified, a further 6 minutes and 40 seconds are granted to write any further details."
Furthermore, in the "How to use"-section at the back, it states:
"If you make this note unusable by tearing it up or burning it, all the humans who have touched the note till then will die."
What?! Is that true, Aizawa-san?
Yup, it's written right here.
There's no doubt that while that rule exists, they won't destroy the notebook, and there's no danger of me losing my memory.
Aw.. that's just shit... why didn't you tell me this earlier?
Rem, I won't get in trouble with the old man for writing in fake rules, will I?
No, there are no rules regarding that.
Alright then. But Light, I'm counting on you for more apples.
Maybe I shouldn't have said "I want to see the Shinigami too", and touched that...
If you hadn't, you'd be the only one in the investigation not knowing what's going on.
Is that what you want?
N-No, I want to be on the same level as everyone else in this investigation. Really!
And this final sentence...
"If the person using the note fails to continuously write names of people to be killed within 13 days of each other, then the user will die."
Oh! This means that both Light-kun and Misa-Misa are completely cleared!
It's true.
Light-kun and Amane were imprisoned for over 50 days, and even now are under surveillance. If either were Kira, they'd no longer be alive.
That's great news, isn't it, Chief?
Yes.
Rem-san... wasn't it? The white person over there.
R-Ryuuzaki, that's rude! You can't go around calling them "white".
Correct.
There are other Death Notes in the human world, aren't there?
Not sure. Maybe there are, maybe there aren't.
If other notebooks did exist, would the rules be the same for all of them?
It's no use, Ryuuzaki. There's no way that Rem will let you cast doubt upon these rules.
Yes, they'd be the same.
There are many notebooks within the world of Shinigami, but the rules are all the same.
Those notebooks under human possession also share a common set of rules.
Ryuuzaki, the suspicions surrounding Light-kun and Amane have been cleared.
It's time to end their surveillance.
He's right, it's obvious.
You're right...
I understand.
I apologize for everything up until now.
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
But the case is still far from solved.
Although these handcuffs will be removed, I'll continue to investigate from here, if that's alright.
Yes.
Now Misa and I are 100% clear of suspicion.
Rules written by a Shinigami in a Death Note... you'd have to believe them.
Thanks to the fake rules I created, Ryuuzaki has nowhere to go from here.
Understand this Ryuuzaki: in any world, rules are something that are made by the gods.
You will bow down to the rules I've created.
You tried to oppose me, the new god of this world, and for your transgression, you will die.
Light! Promise me that you'll text me every single day.
I can't believe that I finally have to part with Misa-Misa...
Oi, Matsuda, leave them alone.
See ya, Misa-Misa!
Hey!
Even if we can be seen on the security cameras, from this angle, they shouldn't be able to see my mouth.
Misa, when you're certain that no one else is around, I want you to go to the place I'm about to tell you and dig up something for me.
Light! Your memories have returned!
Don't worry, Misa will do good!
Light, I remember! Everything that happened back when I was using this notebook... You must have buried this notebook so that I'd remember too!
Misa, if you're reading this, it's likely that your memory has been restored.
A letter from Light!
Do you remember a friend of mine, from Todai University, who introduced himself as "Ryuuga Hideki"?
I want you to write his real name in this notebook and bury him.
Then, as soon as possible, burn this letter.
Take only a few pages from the notebook, and re-bury the notebook itself.
The next time you see me, touch me with a piece of paper from this notebook as naturally as you can.
If you can obey me in all this... I'll love you, forever.
________________________...love you, forever!
Yay!
I see. This is all Light's plan.
For me to obtain this notebook and regain my memory... and kill Ryuuga Hideki... Ryuuzaki...
This should remove another obstacle for Light, and I'll have helped him!
It's no good, Light. I can't remember his name.
I used to see tens, hundreds of names and lifespans every day...
There's no way I can remember! Stupid Misa!
Finally! I'm back!
Ryuk! It's so good to see you again!
How have you been?
Erm, sorry but... being male and all that... that kinda makes me blush.
Oh, yeah!
Here you are!
Light told me to bring it along.
Is it that good?
Yeah. Apples in the human world are... how d'ya say it? "Juicy"?
In any case, they're damned good.
You wanna try eating one?
Huh?
It's an apple from the world of Shinigami.
Doesn't look very tasty...
Take a bite.
Oh, yeah, Ryuk. I want to trade eyes with you.
Sand!!
You wanna make a deal, huh?
You realize that you've already made a deal with Rem once, right?
Your remaining lifespan has already been halved once; you sure you wanna do it again?
It can't be helped I guess.
I've completely forgotten the one name that I needed to remember.
Light will be mad at me unless I go and find it out again.
Well, that's fine by me.
It's Misa-Misa!
Poor thing. We can't switch our cell phones on in here, so Misa-Misa has to come all the way here, just to see Light-kun.
Light, hurry up and go see her.
You shouldn't keep a lady waiting.
Sure.
Ryuk! Why is he with Misa?!
Misa's lifespan has halved again!
Surely she didn't trade eyes with Ryuk?!
Light.
Long time no see, Ryuk.
L-Light, I'm so sorry. I can't remember Ryuuga Hideki's name, no matter how hard I try!
I see...
Well, that's a shame...
B-But I traded eyes with Ryuk!
It's all going according to plan, huh?
You idiot! That means your lifespan has...
It doesn't matter. I want to help you!
Misa, I want to be with you in an ideal world for as long as possible.
That's the way I feel, right now.
Light! I'm so happy!
Misa, let's build a new world together... a world without criminals, filled only with kind-hearted people.
To be continued