December 2007
What did you--?! Roger!
Say that again!
L has died...
Died?!
Why?!
Was he killed by Kira?
Is that it?
Most likely.
After saying he was going to sentence Kira to death, he got killed himself?!
Is that what you're telling me?!
Mello...
Unless you win the game, or solve the puzzle... you're nothing but a loser.
So, who did L choose? Me or Near?
He hadn't decided yet... and since he's dead, he can no longer choose.
Mello, Near, how about it? Why don't you two try joining forces?
Hmm, fine by me...
That's impossible, Roger.
You know that Near and I don't get along.
We've always been rivals...
Always.
That's fine, Roger.
The one who'll succeed L will be Near.
Unlike me, Near will handle things calmly and objectively, like he's solving a puzzle.
I'm leaving...
I'm leaving the orphanage as well.
Mello!
Besides, I'm almost 15.
I'm going to live my life my own way.
At the time of Higuchi's arrest, a policeman overheard him say:
March 5th 2012
"If you write the name of someone whose face you know in the notebook, that person will die."
And that's this "notebook of death"?
Yes. It should currently be in the possession of the Japanese police force.
A boy who goes by the name of "Near",
armed with three years' worth
of independent research into
the Kira investigation,
approaches the President accompanied by the Head of the FBI.
Mr. President, the current L is a fake created by the Japanese police force in order to avoid disorder.
The real L is dead.
Director Mason, who is this?
Well, let's just say he is L's true successor.
The United States of America...
SPK = Secret Provision for Kira
established the SPK,
a brand-new counter-Kira organization
with no links to L,
comprised of selected agents from the FBI and CIA, in addition to Near.
Abduction
However, under the present circumstances, controlling information on the Internet is impossible,
and the investigation into Kira has been at a standstill for far too long.
Those who post the names of the people they want dead on the Internet are the ones I really want them to kill!
But because Kira requires information from the Internet, there's no way they'd kill them.
You're completely contradicting yourself, Matsu!
Well, certainly, the conclusion that as long as you don't do anything bad...
Or rather, that for law-abiding people in general, the world has changed for the better, will be an easy conclusion for some people to reach.
You're a fine one to talk.
No, soon everyone will see it this way.
You're all talking about that again? Give it a rest, darling. Same with you Light.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Welcome home, Sayu.
Onii-chan, Misa-san, it's a surprise to see you two here.
Welcome back.
Please excuse our intrusion!
It's "Matsuda-san", right?
Y-Yes!
I haven't seen you in a while.
I'm indebted to you for always taking care of my dad.
S-Sayu-chan...
Wow, you've really grown up... umm, you've become even more beautiful... erm, the last time I saw you...
Matsu's face has gone bright red!
No! I didn't mean--
I'll never let Sayu marry a police officer.
You're right. There's no way I would allow that.
Huh?! No way... I haven't even asked her out, let alone proposed!
Father... Mother...
Mo--
Fath--
Oh, but I think Matsuda-san is lovely.
R-Really, Sayu-chan?
Yes, and if you were maybe ten years younger, I might even have considered dating you.
Seems like you've learned to handle yourself.
Yeah, she seems so much more mature than Matsu!
But you haven't changed at all. You've always been this wonderful from the moment I met you!
Onii-chan, you've got a job too now. Don't just live together, hurry up and get married.
Too right!
Such a unfortunate family playing "happy families"... this is too funny.
What is it, Aizawa?
Understood.
Matsuda, Light. Come with me.
An abduction? Who's abducted who?
The Chief of the Police Force, Takimura... We have no idea who the culprit is yet.
Damn it! Why now, when the Kira investigation is in this state...
Deputy Chief's Office
Are you certain of this?
We received the call at 6:12pm; around 45 minutes ago.
We've traced the call back to the Chief's cell phone.
Has the culprit made any demands?
Well... they'll exchange the Chief... for the murderer's notebook.
Who's doing this and why?!
Could it be Kira?
Not necessarily. If people found out about the notebook there would be countless people who would want it...
Father, how much does the Chief know about the notebook?
Information regarding the notebook was supposed to be kept to the people in this room.
That's right. I swear I haven't told the Chief anything.
Someone knows about the existence of the Death Note, and that the police have it... and they're coming after it.
Notify all police departments of the abduction only.
Okay!
Have the culprits made contact?
No. There's someone here to see Takimura-san.
What?!
I'm FBI agent John McEnroe.
It's not my real name of course, but I'm here regarding Kira, so please forgive me.
Kira... I'm afraid the Chief isn't available right now, but you can discuss the matter with me if you like.
I guess that's fine.
Let me get straight to the point... the Japanese police force can't be depended on.
In order to solve the Kira case, we'd like you to hand the notebook over to our country.
So it was the FBI!
Where have you hidden the Chief?!
W-What are you talking about?!
Don't act as if you don't know!
You realize this is a serious crime?!
We have nothing to gain by abducting the Chief of the Japanese police force!
Then, how did you find out about the notebook?!
What's going on?
Seems that someone has abducted the Chief of the police force, and their aim seems to be to obtain the notebook.
Commander Lester, steer the conversation toward assisting them with the rescue of the Chief and apprehending the culprit.
And if we get the chance, we'll seize the notebook.
Understood.
Has he said anything?
That the Japanese police backed out of the Kira investigation,
and in reality, the only ones working on the case with L were Yagami Souichirou, Mogi Kanzou and Matsuda Touta. Is that right?
Yes. There was another man called Ukita, but he was killed...
So, that explains why the Chief of the Police Force didn't even know of the notebook's existence.
The Japanese police are useless.
Out of all them, the one with the highest rank was Yagami, the guy in command of headquarters, right?
Y-Yes.
According to my theory, there should be two notebooks.
Kira has one, and the Japanese police has one.
We'll take them both!
As long as we do as Mello says, nothing will go wrong.
In the year and a half Mello's been here, has he been wrong about anything?
But why would someone like you, who joined us by bringing the head of a mafia boss that even Kira hadn't managed to kill,
be so hung up over a notebook?
I don't just want the notebook...
I'll kill anyone who gets in my way, and become number one!
I'll do whatever it takes to beat Near to it.
Boss!
What is it? Keep it down.
S-Sorry... Eddie and I were kinda dozing off and...
Takimura has managed to kill himself using his necktie.
You idiot! This won't work without a hostage!
No... it's alright.
If this is Kira's work, it means they don't know our names or faces, so they killed Takimura instead.
In short, Kira is someone who knows about this abduction.
What should we do, Mello?
Next up, we'll abduct Yagami Souichirou's daughter, Yagami Sayu!
There are no clues regarding the whereabouts of the Chief...
The culprits haven't made further contact since abducting him. What does this mean?
Light. That FBI agent called himself "John McEnroe"... His real name is Rally Connors, there's no doubt about it.
Really? Good.
The investigation is real too.
The Head of the FBI himself offered his assistance in rescuing the Chief... I guess we can trust him.
The Chief should already be dead... why haven't they said anything?
He's dead, so they're just giving up the exchange? Is that the kind of opponent they are?
Father... no, everyone else that's here too. You all need to be careful.
Even if the Chief doesn't know about the notebook, he knows who was investigating alongside L.
If he reveals that, there is a chance that they'll come after us--
Light!
I'll go to bed by myself tonight, like a good girl.
Yeah, goodnight.
Goodnight!
I'll stay here.
The people here aren't the only ones in danger! Our families and--
The Chief's cell phone number... it's from the culprits!
Aizawa!
Yes!
Trace the call!
This is Yagami.
Deputy Chief... about the deal regarding the exchange of the Chief for the notebook... that's now off.
Takimura is dead.
What?! Y-You bastard!
The deal is only off as far as the Chief is concerned. Instead, we'll now exchange the notebook in return for Yagami Sayu.
As the Deputy Chief of the Police, we know it's pointless to tell you not to contact the police, but we would like you to act alone.
If we see any big movements by the police, we'll kill your daughter, without hesitation.
Just as we did with the Chief.
I'll be sending you images of Takimura's corpse. Take a good look.
I'll contact you again tomorrow.
H-Hey!
They got me! They've manipulated Takimura's death to their own advantage, and now Sayu is...
Light, things are getting interesting again, eh?
The Chief...
Why did they have to go this far?!
Damn it!
YAGAMI
Yes, yes...
Darling? Isn't this rather unusual of you? Calling from your work cell phone...
Huh? Sayu?
Now that you mention it, she's pretty late.
Sayu...
Are you okay, Father?
The way I figure it, the kidnappers didn't kill the Chief; Kira did.
Huh?!
They probably did that to prevent the kidnappers from acquiring the notebook.
Kira prefers to think of themselves as just, so they wouldn't want the notebook falling into evil hands.
If Kira did kill the Chief, then we've got to assume that they have some way of accessing police information.
We're better off if we act by using only the people here. If we don't...
Kira may try and kill the hostage again.
That's correct.
Near, the abducted Chief of the Japanese police has been killed.
By whom?
By whom? By the people that abducted him.
It would be interesting if it turns out that Kira was the one who killed him.
You're right. If the hostage dies, then they'd be unable to exchange him for the notebook.
And if it was Kira, it narrows the list of suspects.
By the way, Commander Lester, any news on his whereabouts?
Well, it's certain that four years ago he was at the orphanage you mentioned... after that, we have no idea.
So, it's decided.
Mello, you always get too emotional and neglect what's really important.
Or do you really have nothing to do with this?
It's strange that you'd leave a photo of yourself behind...
This is Yagami.
Your daughter has finally arrived here.
"Here"?
You must have an idea as to where we are by now.
We'll do the exchange here.
Alone. With the notebook. Within two days. In LA.
There will be no exchange unless you guarantee that my daughter is safe!
Let me hear her voice.
I get it, I get it. I'll mail you a picture of her.
Sayu...
Deputy Chief! We've narrowed it down to Los Angeles' Fifth Avenue.
The TV program pictured in the background is currently airing in the US.
They've taken it on purpose to let us know she's okay.
T-Thank god... at least we know she's alive.
I'm going to take the notebook to LA.
I'm going as the Deputy Chief of the Police Force, and also as Yagami Sayu's father!
I'll make all the decisions and accept full responsibility for them!
Father! Wait until we've worked out a plan.
He's right, Deputy Chief.
But I've got to get to LA within two days. There's no time.
So, you're saying that the kidnappers didn't kill Takimura; Kira did?!
I'm just mentioning it as a possibility.
And if that's true, Kira somehow managed to obtain information from the Japanese police.
Yes?
This is L...
It's L... the current one.
I've heard what John McEnroe, or Agent Rally Connors, had to say from Deputy Chief Yagami.
Will you assist us in the investigation into the murder of Chief Takimura?
Let's see...
The phone...
Second-generation L... it's a pleasure to meet you.
"Second-generation"? What are you talking about?
Who are you?
There's no point in hiding it.
We're a newly established organization especially created to investigate Kira independently of L, called the SPK.
The seven main members of this organization all know about L's death.
L's death? Who and where?!
And I am the one at the center of the SPK...
Let me see... I'm N.
"N"? Is this a joke?
And yet... this feeling... what is it?
To be continued