Given the rather "convenient" interaction between Kira and the Japanese police during this incident,
I can conclude that Kira and the Japanese police are working together.
"Working together"?!
And if that's true, Kira is... the second-generation L.
To all of you at the Japanese Investigative Headquarters: have you ever thought, even once, that your "second-generation" L might be Kira?
Near... I've got no choice now but to kill you!
This is terrible! Live on TV, Demegawa is...
I, Demegawa, have finally tracked down the base of an evil organization that seeks to capture our God, Kira!
And along with my brothers, we have them surrounded!
Transfer
Supporters of Kira!
Don't enter the building all at once!
The opposition may try and blend in with the crowd and escape!
Obey my orders as Kira's spokesman!
We must corner them, expose them to the cameras, and offer them to Kira!
I definitely won't overlook you!
Near... for now, you'd better get out of there.
You've got a lot of nerve advising me, considering you're Kira.
I can't believe you're still saying that!
There are other organizations out there hunting Kira, and yet this attack happens immediately after I start suspecting you.
The timing is far too convenient.
Near, you're jumping to far too many conclusions from a misunderstanding.
To them members present at the Investigative Headquarters, at best, Kira is in your midst...
Please think about it.
Light-kun is Kira... that idea is being reinforced yet again.
The previous L also suspected Light-kun...
First squad, break down the door and the first twenty, make your way in!
Second squad, hold!
Leave that to us! We're the first squad!
What the--!! We were here first!
Near, unless we get out of here quickly...
What foolish people...
I don't find it strange that there are people who are willing to support Kira,
but that only applies to those that genuinely want Kira to judge criminals.
The people besieging this place are different.
They are truly worthless human beings.
As long as they're having fun, it's all that matters... they're selfish.
I-I realize that, but for now, we need to...
Let's use L's inheritance and those people we employed that oppose Kira.
But once we use that plan...
Let's do it. The preparations have already been made.
This should be interesting.
M-M-Money!!
I-It's money!!
Money?!
There's so much of it!
Amazing...
I should have gone...
Matsuda...
Gee, humans really are amusing.
But, you can exchange that stuff for apples, so I guess I can understand.
Bastard! I got that first!!
Outta the way!
Shit! Near, you're planning to escape amid the confusion, aren't you?
But if you do, Demegawa's cameras should be able to...
P-Pilot! Head toward the floor where the money is coming from!
Damn it! Deme-chan, what the hell do you think you're doing?! You can't buy love and peace with money!
In Lower Manhattan, New York, a vast amount of dollars are...
The police squads have arrived!
Police squads?!
As expected, given the panic that's ensued here, the police squads have arrived!
This isn't looking good...
Let's do this.
At this precise moment, we're safe even if we walk right out the front door.
I guess in this kind of situation, the police had no choice but to act.
Shit! So this is how they're intending to counter it.
They'll emerge, disguised as part of the police squad.
Telling Aizawa and the others to keep a close eye on the police is as good as telling them that I'm Kira.
There are police exiting the building!
Where is he?
He's got to be among them...
Where?!
Damn it...
I wonder just how much money was involved...
Matsuda...
Ten million dollars maybe?
How many apples is that?
Near!
Near?!
This is Near.
We've completed installation of communication circuits, so we thought we'd better get in touch.
Near, you're safe?
To all at the Investigative Headquarters, I believe it won't be long before you each come to a definite decision regarding Kira.
The timing of this attack is as good as saying that Kira is among you.
And if none of you suspect the second-generation L, then you're all worse than nursery school kids.
I've reinstated the phone number I gave you all a few days ago.
Feel free to give me a call anytime.
Well then, I'll be waiting.
What confidence... or rather, he's being pretty aggressive.
Everyone, if any of you feel like you want to help Near, please go ahead.
Given the current situation, I won't be offended.
It's my belief that, ideally, the SPK and ourselves should understand and cooperate with each other.
Near's the one that's holding us back here.
When I think about Deputy Chief Yagami, I don't want to suspect Light-kun.
However...
Dad?
Welcome back. You came home tonight?
Yeah. Why are you still up?
I've got exams soon.
I see... Just don't work yourself too hard.
You too, Dad, okay?
It won't be surprising if someone does contact Near.
What matters is what follows.
If I leave this even a single step too late, it could turn into an irrecoverable situation.
I've got to do it now!
Wow! An emergency command from Light!
Let's see now... number three...
No way...
Yes? Near speaking.
I'm with the Japanese Investigative Headquarters. I'm Aizawa.
The time has finally arrived... this is so that I'll be completely safe, and a normal wife to him.
This is what Light wants... for me to find true happiness in being a woman.
Light, thank you...
I see... that's very interesting.
So, L detained two suspects for over 50 days, and the "13 days" rule cleared them both.
Yes, but of course, that on its own doesn't mean that they are Kira.
And L had no problems releasing them?
No. He had Mr. Yagami, who was Chief at the time, play a trick on them.
The Chief informed them that they had been confirmed as Kira and the second Kira, and that they were being taken to an execution chamber.
Along the way, the Chief pulled a gun on the suspects and said he'd kill Kira and then himself.
It was believed that if they were Kira, being pushed so far, they would have killed the Chief.
That's how the judgment was made.
Kira's quite a guy...
Kira used their detention to prove their innocence.
Did the suspect offer to be detained?
I have to admit, Light-kun did volunteer to be detained...
If they did, then this settles it.
So, who were these two suspects?
I can't tell you that much.
Despite this, I'm still working under L, as a member of the Japanese Investigative Headquarters.
I understand.
Thank you for your valuable information.
It's the first time I've heard of people with the eyes of a Shinigami being able to see the names of others. That was helpful.
Well then...
Near, is that enough? You aren't going to question him further?
At this point, it's best to leave things as they are.
Besides, we've learned something vital.
Deputy Chief Yagami and the suspect were father and child.
There's no other explanation for him saying "I'll kill Kira and then myself".
Thus, the second-generation L, and the person I believe to be Kira, is... Yagami Light.
Light-kun.
Yes?
I'm going to be honest with you... I contacted Near.
Don't worry about it. It's something that I encouraged myself.
So, what did you talk about?
No... I won't ask you that. It might be strange for us to have a discussion about that.
I want to establish with absolute certainty that you're not Kira.
I'm sorry that you have to go through the same thing twice, but until Kira's caught, I'd like to keep a close eye on you.
I'm sorry, but the same goes for Amane Misa. I'll have to check her room.
There's always the slight possibility that she has a notebook.
Wait a minute, Aizawa-san...
No, please go ahead.
You'll all become witnesses to the fact that I'm not communicating with Misa in secret.
Mogi?
I want this cleared up too.
Light-kun not being Kira would be the best outcome, but if evidence incriminating him as Kira turns up in Amane's room... then...
Aah! Mochii and Monchicchi!
Long time no see!
Since Light never seems to come home from investigating Kira, I've got nothing to do!
She can't possibly have the notebook on her in that outfit...
Misa... there's been a report that a bomb has been planted at L's house.
It's most likely a false alarm, but we'd like to check your apartment.
Huh?! Is Light okay?! I better call him!
You can't call him!
Why?!
Light-kun is fine. He's got some important business to attend to, so he sent us.
That's right! Light loves Misa so much, he'd probably be even more worried if he heard my voice.
Search all you want, Aizawa... you won't find the notebook.
I don't want it to get awkward around here because of this...
This isn't a friendship club. Aizawa and Mogi can do as they please.
It's time for Kira's Realm to start.
Kira's Realm
Greetings, supporters of Kira! I am Demegawa, Kira-sama's spokesman.
Behold! The construction of Kira's Realm, named after this show, is progressing well thanks to all your support!
And once this is completed, let us all meet here, and welcome Kira-sama to his temple!
Wow... such bad taste...
Hey, is everything alright?
Yeah. Guess it was a fake report after all.
But as a precaution, one of us better stay here over the next few days.
Sure, thanks.
Mogi, you can go back to headquarters.
I'll stay.
Eh?! Mochii's not staying, but Monchicchi is?!
I'm not dependable enough for you?
That's not it... it's just that, without your old hairstyle, you just don't seem like Monchicchi. It's not cute!
Mogi!
Yes! I'm sorry!
You stay...
In order to complete Kira's Realm, we beseech you to donate a million yen!
Sounds like a scam to me.
Yeah, they're no different from a shady establishment.
It's just so unlike Kira...
Demegawa... he's acting on his own impulses... at this rate, people will start turning away...
I don't need him any longer... but...
Welcome back.
We didn't find anything in Light-kun and Amane's apartment, but...
I understand. You can continue observing Misa and me until you're satisfied.
At this point, I'd like to introduce you to the key members of Kira's Realm, which I myself handpicked.
First up is...
Eliminate.
We will join Kira-sama in...
Eliminate!
Eliminate!!
H-Help me...
Eliminate...
Please wait a moment
W-What the hell just happened...
Why is Kira after their own followers?
Maybe they're stopping someone that's gone too far.
You could be right, but this is so cruel...
What's going on?!
Neither Light-kun nor Amane Misa have had the opportunity to use the notebook.
Mikami... I can really use him. Selecting him was not a mistake.
Even without orders from me, he understands Kira's thoughts, ideals, desires, and what's no longer needed. And he acts upon it.
I had Misa relinquish ownership of her Death Note.
I had her lose all memories of the Death Note, and send it to someone else.
They can ask her anything, and she won't be able to answer.
She is nothing but a woman.
The issue now is the next owner, a man who's already appeared on TV to appeal to Kira.
Someone who genuinely worships Kira, a man who understands that just by being given the notebook, he is the chosen one.
Occupation
Prosecutor
I wasn't mistaken...
Mikami Teru... he is worthy of doing my bidding.
Thank you for coming, Shinigami. I can now carry out judgments reliably.
What do you think of Kira?
God.
To be continued