Eliminate.
Eliminate!
Mikami Teru is a person who can distinguish good and evil far better than the average Japanese adult.
His sense of justice is strong.
And unlike the average Japanese adult, he has seen much unhappiness, and faced death many times.
Selection
In this world you are either evil or on the side of justice.
This is the truth I discovered when I was a child.
Humans are either good or evil. Everyone is divided into these two categories.
Even though Junior High was a small part of the world, it became that way.
As class representative, even though I aimed for high goals, there were always enemies.
Hey, stop it! Stop it!
I couldn't help but fight against evil.
Even though it looked like justice would lose at times.
But no matter how I suffered, I was happy.
Thanks.
Just hearing that word from the victim, made me want to help them every time.
During those times, my effort paid off.
It was verification of my own justice.
Don't do something you regret.
See, see!
But, that was only true in the world of children.
Come Junior High, fighting against evil only increased my enemies.
The victims became assailants, even spectators went on the side of evil.
Justice cannot help change things all the time.
At those times, we have no choice but to eliminate evil.
The only person who understood me, my only ally, was a woman. My mother.
No, it used to be my mother.
Teru, in this world, there are things you cannot change.
Please stop it already. They have no reason to torment you.
There's nothing to prove by acting this way.
You only look like an idiot.
What can you accomplish by working this hard by yourself...
My mother was wrong. She wasn't on the side of justice.
There were people who needed to be eliminated.
And then a miracle happened.
Four of the bullies were driving recklessly, all of them died.
One passerby died as well. That person was my mother.
The people I wanted eliminated were eliminated all at once.
I was probably afraid at first. My heart rejected it.
But the elimination should make some people happy.
The victims definitely... no, the entire class deep in their hearts...
I wasn't wrong.
Soon after, the classroom became peaceful.
Evil deeds will be punished, this is something that should be.
Evil must be eliminated.
Furthermore, are there any mistakes in this book?
Yes, I'm really sorry.
After I became an adult, my beliefs became firm.
Everywhere there are people who have no worth.
No, because of these people, evil exists.
And as they approached adulthood, they no longer wished to be reformed.
There's no choice but to eliminate them.
It's a mysterious thing. The people I passed judgment on were eliminated one by one.
Was it coincidence, or was I special?
Those things didn't matter.
Divine punishment was brought down upon evil.
If it wasn't, someone would have to pass judgment on evil.
For that purpose, I became a prosecutor.
Prosecutors are figures of justice passing judgment on evil. It was my calling in life.
That's what I believed.
And at that time...
God descended!
All those people didn't die by coincidence.
It was God's judgment.
God was watching me!
God was passing judgment for me, who stood up against evil.
I realized this, so I went to as many places as possible where God was watching.
And then...
God was definitely watching over me.
Not only that, he found me worthy of his power.
With this, it's fine if I don't get a response from him.
I'll do what he desires. I'll carry out Kira's duty.
Eliminate.
Mikami killed Demegawa before I instructed him to.
Now there isn't a spokesperson to speak Kira's thoughts.
I can't make a move in this situation.
What will you do, Mikami?
Kira hasn't sent any messages.
He must be in a position where he can't make any moves.
But this is an important moment. A spokesperson for Kira is essential.
Then, I'll take the initiative.
Extra, extra, a new development!
Kira will be choosing a new spokesperson to replace Demegawa.
Please watch!
This woman...
Takada Kiyomi.
Good evening, this is Takada Kiyomi from News Six.
Starting today, I'll be bringing everyone Kira's word quickly and accurately...
So it's NHN's best announcer.
Picking Taki, Kira has good taste!
There's no mistaking it. She was Light-kun's girlfriend during college.
You've dealt with this quickly, Mikami.
But they will find a connection between us immediately...
No, his choice isn't bad at all.
She knows me. I can't send her anything.
On the contrary, I can get her on my side easily.
I can definitely use her. I need to contact her as quickly as possible.
Takada Kiyomi. I talked to her once when I was in a debate program.
She was a regular moderator, but when asked a question about Kira, her expression changed.
She detests criminals and those that bring misfortune to society.
She spoke so profusely about it, you could tell the intensity of her beliefs.
After that, I talked to her in private many times, and she was undoubtedly a supporter of Kira.
She was the perfect person from the media to use as Kira's spokesperson.
Takada Kiyomi.
It would be reckless to choose her as the spokesperson.
And there haven't been any signs of messages from Light-kun.
Am I thinking too much?
Everyone, what do you think of using Takada Kiyomi for the investigation?
She was actually my girlfriend during my college years.
To suggest this himself... so he isn't going to keep this hidden?
Kira gives her his instructions, and makes her read his message...
Using her would be the best method to catch Kira.
But Taki is only doing this because Kira must be threatening her. Won't she be afraid to cooperate with us?
That's right.
That's not an issue.
I have her cell phone number, and if I want to see her, I can make it happen.
You have an amazing confidence. That's Light-kun for you.
But, it'll definitely be difficult to get her to cooperate in the capture of Kira.
I talked to her about a lot of things during college, but she is definitely... a Kira supporter.
But we can still use her.
Right now, the police are claiming they support Kira.
But in reality they aren't doing anything.
So, I'll let her know I'm working for the police, and ask her for Kira's instructions on what the police should do.
For someone who supports Kira, that won't be an unappealing conversation.
Will that go well?
I don't know, but we can only try.
It's true... We can observe what goes on.
Then, I'll call her right now.
Light-kun.
I want you to let us listen to your conversation with Takada.
All right, I don't mind.
No, I want you to listen.
We don't know if there will be any hints about Kira in what she says.
Y-Yeah...
Hello?
Takada-san, this is Yagami.
Yagami-kun?
It's been a while. Why the call?
Takada-san, I have something important to say to you.
Can we meet sometime? I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
Yeah. I know you're in a position where the world pays attention to you, so meeting might be impossible.
But even if that's true, you haven't kept in touch with me.
That's true.
During college, I didn't get to talk to you as much as I wanted to.
But thanks to our jobs, we are able to meet each other again.
This feels like fate.
Because of our jobs...?
Right now, I'm working in the police, and there is something I want to talk to you about.
Currently the police aren't defying Kira.
All right, I'll listen to what you have to say, but I don't know if I can help you.
Thank you. First, let's meet up and have you listen to what I have to say.
Anywhere you want, just the two of us.
OK then. We'll meet after tonight's news is over.
I understand. I'll get a hotel room.
But is that really OK?
I recall that you live together with Amane.
Things are going well now, aren't they?
No, that's...
She lacks the intelligence to be my partner.
Mochii!
Yes?
Mochii's cooking is good, can do everything, and Misa is living comfortable, but it's been five days already!
Yes.
Let's keep this a secret from Light, even though it makes Misa feel bad.
Yes...
No matter how much Light trusts Misa, this much trust shouldn't be normal.
Light would definitely be jealous!
I heard from Near that this woman could be the second Kira.
But can this airheaded idiot of a woman really be...?
Even now Kira hasn't contacted me.
If Kira wanted to contact me but couldn't, he would use Takada first.
Good evening. This is the nine o'clock news.
The words of Kira I am about to speak now, will become the way of life for the world.
Besides those who cause harm, those who have ability and live without using it will not be forgiven.
Eh, so he's going to kill lazy people?
That has to be a lie!
You're overdoing it, Mikami.
No, it's too fast for him to make these decisions.
Either way I need to get in contact with him.
How is it, Matsuda?
Sound and video are working properly!
There are no blind spots. The nine o'clock news is over now.
Light-kun, I'm heading back now.
Yes.
I wanted to see you...
That was rude of me. Please, have a seat.
Somehow, it doesn't feel like it's been a while since we've met.
What is Light-kun doing!?
Why isn't he saying anything? He needs to hurry or she'll become suspicious.
Ide-san, haven't you ever been in love?
What?
How's it going?
The mood is great!
I wasn't asking about that...
Sorry.
Kira!
Is it Mikami?
She said Kira just now!
It can't be... direct contact from Kira?
It'd be better if you answered that.
Yes.
Hello?
No, I'm with my friend. No one else is here.
It was fortunate for the phone to be answered.
Mikami, are you going to rely on luck?
He wanted to see me suddenly.
A person who summoned Kira's spokesperson in private...
Give the phone to that person.
He wants to talk to you.
Choosing you was definitely the right decision.
Light-kun has the phone!
If he's the real thing, it's dangerous!
I'm on the phone now.
Who are you?
November 26th? Five pages? What are you talking about?
God!
Good, Mikami. How much of my situation can you discern?
Is God unable to act freely right now?
Yes.
Are you under surveillance?
Are you really Kira?
He wants me to judge someone!
Look at Sakura TV!
Sakura TV you say?
Sakura TV.
At all costs, to call out Kira!
He died!
This is bad, he's the real thing!
Mikami, you've exceeded my expectations.
Yes.
What? Uninstall all the bugs?
We have no choice.
What is the meaning of this?
It should be safe now.
Listen carefully, Kiyomi. I am Kira.
That's right. I am Kira.
That's all I wanted to say.
Yagami-kun is... Kira!
If you ask Kiyomi about my identity, I will not forgive you.
Yes, as you command, God.
Do you understand?
I'm Kira, and this man is the person with Kira's power.
That's... that's great!
You're the only person I ever admired in my life... The only man I had a connection with.
And you are Kira... this is too wonderful!
You are going to follow me.
And become the new world's goddess.
Yagami-kun!
Light-kun, are you safe?
Yes, Takada-san was able to smooth things out with Kira.
I'll be acting as her boyfriend, and we can go after Kira like this.
Eliminate.
Eliminate!
To be continued