L, I want to meet you.
Daikoku Wharf, also known as Yellow Box.
The 28th, at 1pm. How is that?
Understood.
Take off everything you're wearing and put them in there.
You can use this blanket.
Takada-san, are you okay?
Yagami-kun.
I've done everything you said, placing my own life as the top priority...
I've done it all! Hurry and come, save me!
Takada Kiyomi. On 26th January 2013, at 2:32pm, burnt all her belongings and anything written down before burning herself to death.
It brings me great sorrow to tell you that among the two bodies found at the scene,
one of them has been identified as announcer Takada Kiyomi, as confirmed by forensic detectives.
Inside the church that burned down was a 2-ton truck carrying a motorcycle inside.
They suspect the cause of the fire to be the ignition of gasoline.
What worries me now... relates to choosing the next spokesperson.
The word of Kira-sama is something that cannot be stopped.
We deeply regret announcer Takada passing away, but it seems she didn't really have the qualifications as a spokesperson.
As expected, this is no task for a woman.
Kira-sama, please choose us as your spokesperson!
No! Return to Sakura TV--
This is awful...
Isn't it?
The second the dead body was confirmed as Takada, the fight to become Kira's new spokesperson has erupted again.
Last night's judgment unfolded perfectly.
That could only mean that Takada and Mikami kept in close touch.
There is no problem.
It's Near!
L.
Yes?
I know I'm interfering, but regarding our meeting...
The 28th at 1pm is alright?
Yes.
As expected, it hasn't changed.
It's just as I thought.
Now there isn't a single doubt.
Alright then. The day after tomorrow, on the 28th.
Correct.
So it's the day after tomorrow, huh?
Things are getting pretty exciting!
Yeah.
Who knows what Near wants to show us though...
Matsuda... Ide...
All of us might be killed that day...
Do you understand that?
Gevanni.
Yes?
Are you able to make it?
Yes.
I'll be fine.
Commander Lester. Lidner. Gevanni.
Let's do our best.
28th January, 2013
Everyone, good morning.
G-Good morning.
First...
I've released Amane.
Please call her to confirm it.
I dunno what's going on. Maybe it's a compensation... I ended up in a Teito Hotel Deluxe Suite though! Feels so good!
Oh, really? I see.
Please stay there for a while.
Okaaaaaaaay~
Near, please switch over to Mogi.
We keep the notebook locked up, and need everyone's security number.
Understood. I'll connect you.
Mogi here. The number is... 62-324.
My number is the only one left...
The murderers notebook.
"How to use:
The human whose name is written in this note shall die.
The note will not take effect unless the writer has the person's face in their mind when they write his/her name.
Therefore, people sharing the same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written within 40 seconds of writing the person's name, it will happen as it is written.
If the cause of death is not specified, by default, the person will simply die of a heart attack.
Should a cause of death be specified, a further 6 minutes and 40 seconds are granted to write any further details."
Near, I have the notebook. I will definitely be the one holding onto it.
Is it alright with you if Mr. Aizawa carries it, L?
Near, I've already considered that it would be best for you to have Aizawa carry it.
Thank you very much.
Very well then. See you there.
With this, everything ends.
No...
It begins today.
Kira's perfect world.
All who know of the notebook... will die.
Near is inside, no mistaking it.
So, let's go.
Near, you're very much inferior to L, you are not qualified to wear his mask.
L, those four are from the SPK.
And the one wearing the mask is Near.
B-But, I can't accept this!
You freely accuse someone of being Kira, yet you are the one wearing a mask to save only yourself!
It is a precaution. There's a chance that everyone's face here, excluding mine, has already been seen by Kira.
That means that their name may already have been written down.
That's why, for one hour--
No, for thirty minutes, allow me to see if anyone here is being manipulated and dies.
W-What's that all about? To wait and see if we die or not?
No. If Light-kun is indeed Kira, I can't say it won't happen.
Especially now that our existence no longer has any meaning.
From here on, it's just wasting time.
Near...
I never thought holding back my laughter would be this hard.
He's waiting for him to come.
I can see through it.
Near!
It's been over 30 minutes and nothing has happened!
Of course not.
Because Kira isn't here.
Very well. Everyone seems to be okay.
I'll take off my mask now.
What is it, Near?
Are you still waiting on something?
Waiting... That's exactly it.
I am waiting... for the one who will complete our circle, to come.
The one who will complete the circle?
He'll be here shortly.
That's what we are waiting for.
This building is a sealed room. You can't see inside without opening that door.
He will surely come through that door.
Or at the very least, peep through it.
Who are you saying is coming?
The one who is currently carrying out the judgments for Kira; X-Kira.
He'll definitely bring the notebook and come.
And then, he will see my face and write down my name.
No, he'll kill everyone here who knows of the notebook.
I-I don't understand! What are you saying?
This other person will come with the notebook to kill us all?!
And we're just gonna sit back and watch?!
Yes, now listen...
If that person comes through the door, only greet him.
And if you see the door open slightly, pretend you didn't notice.
T-That's just foolish!
He's already here!
God!!
Eliminate!
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate!!
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate!!!
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate...
Please, don't move!
It's okay, we won't die!
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate!
How can you say that we won't, Near?
I modified the notebook.
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate!
I replaced the pages when I was in direct contact with the notebook.
The one currently outside, when judging as Kira, wrote exactly one page per day.
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate!
Even if he writes our names now, we won't die.
Because I replaced the page set for today!
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate!
Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate! Eliminate!!!
X-Kira is on the other side of the door, and he will take another look inside here to confirm our deaths.
You may restrain him then.
From there, we seize the notebook, and whoever's name isn't written down, is Kira.
I-It's true that... the one whose name isn't written down would be Kira.
It's just...
Just as planned! Just as planned! JUST AS PLANNED!!
The modification of the notebook... I knew about it.
Near, you have completely and utterly lost!
The notebook you altered was a fake, one I had Mikami prepare!
And so, the notebook that Mikami is writing in, is the real one, which had been hidden until now!
I had Mikami create a fake notebook... While sending pages to Takada from the real notebook.
Therefore, the one doing the real judgments was Takada.
As for Mikami, there were times he deliberately wrote names in the fake note to be witnessed by his tail.
Except during those times, the one really judging was Takada.
This made it look like the real notebook was in Mikami's hands.
Mikami's schedule is precise; he leads an exceptionally punctual life.
He writes exactly one page per day; no more, no less...
Near, you must have noticed this and made your plan.
That is, you could easily determine which page would be used for the day we meet.
Then all you had to do was to replace the page for that day.
By doing that, those whose names are written in the notebook will not die.
That was your plan!
And that's why you couldn't change the date of our meeting.
But seeing how we knew that the notebook would be modifed, I had Mikami check the fake notebook every day.
I have confirmed it.
At that moment, I knew I had won.
The one Mikami brought with him today, is the hidden, real notebook!
But Near... you did have a chance to win.
You're too soft.
And far inferior to L...
If it were L, he would've thought of the possibility of a fake notebook, and tested it.
You had the chance...
I'm rather disappointed in you.
You're no rival to me.
You tried to win too beautifully...
Oh well, because of you... everyone dies.
And as for me... This will be my absolute win as Kira.
The one outside... are you done writing down the names?
God!
Yes, I'm done.
N-No, I can't laugh yet... I gotta hold it back!
Everyone will die in 40 seconds.
35 seconds...
35 more seconds and I get to declare my victory!
Don't you find it strange?
Why does he answer your question, "Are you done writing down the names?", so honestly?
Who knows? Maybe he's an honest guy.
Or no, perhaps he left himself plenty of leeway?
Or just maybe your plot has been seen through.
Then we really might be done for!
Mikami Teru. If you don't mind, would you please come in?
I know you are currently taking over Kira's judgments.
If you wrote down our names, there's nothing to fear.
Please, enter.
Mikami Teru? Right. Don't just hide out there, come inside.
God!
Mikami... you did well!
How much time has passed since you first wrote down a name?
30... 31... 32... 33... 34... 35... 36... 37... 38... 39...
Near, it's my victory!
40!!
To be continued