...it was just the two of us, after all!
Eyeshield, go for a touch down!
What's wrong? You can't get the six points if you don't go for the touch down!
Eyeshield?
I've been hiding it from you up till now, but my true identity is...
S-Sena!
Yeah!
Ya-ha!
Eyeshield 21's true identity is top secret! You'll go to hell if anyone finds out!
It hurts!
I accidentally fell asleep!
But that dream sure was realistic.
Yay! I finished making our communications network!
Deimon Devil Bats Communications Network
It goes from me to Kurita, Komusubi, Monta, Yukimitsu,
and then all the way to Sena.
Hiruma is last, huh?
It's here! It's here! It's here! It's here!
Yay!
Before...
Communications Network Kurita -&gt; Hiruma -&gt; Done
I'm going to contact Komusubi right away!
You're too loud, Ryokan!
I'm sorry!
Let's practice some tomorrow! What time's good for you?
What is it, Daikichi? You're so excited!
I know! I bet something good's happened!
M-Master! New pupil!
What? You found a master in American football and got to become his pupil?
How could you figure all that out?
Stupid! Two powerful men can understand each other even when they're silent!
Yeah, right.
Okay, Daikichi, sit down.
Listen up.
Since you've been accepted as his pupil, you've got to make your master proud!
Hm? I feel like I'm forgetting something...
Come to think of it!
How to get in contact with Eyeshield 21?!
Crap...!
Sena? Sena, did you hear me?
No...
You don't know how? You're the team manager so you're supposed to know these things!
Fine! I'll ask Kurita! Later!
Wait a sec!
How to contact Eyeshield?
I asked Sena, but he didn't know.
And you don't know either?
Y-Yeah...
Like we'd know!
They didn't know either...
Which means I've got no choice. HE'S the last person I can ask.
Ya-ha!
I'll be the one to personally contact Eyeshield 21.
After all, he IS our secret weapon!
I can't tell you any more than that!
What's with everyone?!
Come to think of it, Eyeshield has to be a student here at our school...
They're definitely hiding something from me.
Okay! If they're going to hide something, I'll just have to work hard to figure it out!
I've got a bad feeling...
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Find Eyeshield!
How cool...
Oh, Manabu! You're going to school this early?
No, I'm...
I have morning football practice! I passed the tryouts!
What did you say?!
You have to study!
You don't have time to join some team or club!
This is why you were only able to get into a school like Deimon!
That's what would happen...
Um... Well... I thought I might be able to study better at the school study hall than at home.
Oh, okay. Well, that's wonderful.
Right now is a very important time for preparing for your future, after all.
Y-Yeah!
And here I thought you had joined a club or something!
But that would never happen!
That was close!
I'm the least physically fit so I have to get pumped up and practice the most!
Let's do it again!
They're early!
Hey!
Yukimitsu! We were so super excited that we started practice at 2 A.M. last night!
Okay!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Mamori...
MAX super-speed get up and dressed!
Max! Max!
Hey, Sena! Let's go to morning practice!
Sorry! I didn't sleep well last night.
Rushing to the max!
Yeah!
You're late, Butt-monkey, Manajerk!
Okay ladies, we're going to run through cones!
Hey, Manajerk, hurry up and drag Eyeshield 21 over here!
O-Okay!
Wait, Sena!
I'll go, too! I have some business with Eyeshield.
I have to ask for his phone number!
I said to wait!
Really!
I should be able to see Eyeshield if I keep close to Sena.
I'm definitely going to find him!
This is getting pretty serious.
Let's go!
Eyeshield, running through!
You're amazing!
No, not really!
Speed isn't everything.
What are you looking for, Manajerk?
Where's Sena?
That's strange. Eyeshield's never around when Sena is,
and Sena's never around when Eyeshield is.
Is that just coincidence? Or is it...
I see! Those two don't like each other!
Okay, Eyeshield 21, you still have 50 laps left!
Okay!
His speed goes down with each lap he runs, but his short-time power is okay.
So stamina's his problem...
Hey, Eyeshield!
Class is about to start!
Geez!
Club time! Club time!
Club time!
I feel like someone's watching me...
You're too obvious, Mamori.
At this rate, you won't be able to transform into Eyeshield!
All righty, then! Leave her to me... Max!
Mamori quit worrying about Sena so the two of us can...
SPARKLE!
I'm sad...
What should we do?
At this rate, Sena will never be able to dress up as Eyeshield.
How interesting! I guess I should go all out on her!
Kurita, what's wrong?
This is Kariya's latest dessert! Let's eat them together!
S-Sure...
Come on! Help yourself!
Th-Thanks.
Change into Eyeshield while you can!
Open up! Open the door!
I'm sorry...
Ya-ha! Hey, students from Deimon High School!
I've got some big news from the football team!
Bluntly put, find Eyeshield 21! Catch Eyeshield 21 before the day's over!
What do you think'll happen if you don't catch him?
How stupid! Let's go home.
Yeah.
The pictures...
That's no joking matter!
It'd be horrible if those pictures got out!
We'll catch Eyeshield!
H-Hiruma?
There he is!
Wait!
Eyeshield 21!
What's the deal?!
Football Clinic!
What's under the uniforms?
Shoulder pads and other forms of protective gear is attached to them.
It's so players can tackle the enemy without getting hurt! Ya-ha!
Wait, Eyeshield 21!
Anyway, I've gotta run!
Eyeshield 21, as a member of the track team, I'd like to invite you to join.
We'll talk about it later!
But-!
Wait, Eyeshield 21!
Ouch!
I won't give up, Eyeshield 21!
He's doing a great job running from them.
Now then, next I'll...
What?! You'll forget all about us being your slaves if we catch Eyeshield?!
It'll take a lot of stamina for him to escape those guys from Zokugaku.
He's here!
That way!
We'll sandwich him in!
Darn it! Search over there!
Why's stuff like this always happening to me?
So this is where you were!
Why are they here, too?!
Outta the way! I, the great Rui Habashira, am going to kill Eyeshield 21!
Darn! I lost sight of him.
And here I was planning on landing my Evil Kick on him, too!
That jerk's as fast as ever.
I wonder where he went...
"To Eyeshield 21,"
"I've got your manager."
"If you want her back, come to the warehouse on the outskirts of town."
"From, Rui Habashira."
Mamori!
Catch him!
I wanna do whatever I feel like
It's no big deal RIGHT NOW
Holding my overflowing emotions with MY HANDS
I'm sentimental BABE BE SURVIVOR
We hurt each other as if we lacked any feelings
I can't see!
We work hard spending our days trying
to get a step closer to our ideals
Like I give a damn about what's right
Since the path opening before me is clear,
I want to believe in DREAM MAKER
Hey, you gonna throw it away? You gonna avoid it?
I can feel my mission
Love for Life, Drive for Light ultramarine-colored sky
Please give Mamori back!
Cry for Fight, Smile for Bright let's tear through it
Love for Life, Drive for Light
I think I can see tomorrow
Cry for Fight, Smile for Bright shaking your heads
I can't see again!
I wanna do whatever I feel like
It's no big deal RIGHT NOW
You keep scurrying around like a rat!
Holding my overflowing emotions with MY HANDS
I'm sentimental BABE BE SURVIVOR
Don't you care about what happens to this girl?
You coward!
How pathetic, Eyeshield 21!
Let go of me, you coward! You... You-!
That hurts!
Let go of Mamori!
Fine! But first take off your helmet.
What should I do? He'll find out who I am...
Hurry up!
Okay!
S-Sena?!
My, what a surprise!
So the Lightspeed Running Back, Eyeshield 21,
is really that wimpy gopher, Sena Kobayakawa, who is always getting rescued by Mamori.
What a joke!
Right, Mamori?
Sorry to let you down, but he's a fake!
Look up! Up!
Up?
The real Eyeshield 21 is right here!
I'm here!
I'm the real Eyeshield 21, to the max!
And he's right here, too!
So which is the real one?!
But this one's not him!
It's impossible for you to be him, Kurita! Learn how to tell people no!
And this one's a dog! Look over here! Hey dog, quit eating and participate with everyone!
You makin' fun of me?! Huh?!
We were supposed to be trying to catch Eyeshield, so why do we gotta do this?
We don't have a choice!
It's better than those pictures getting out!
The real Eyeshield is among us!
Catch him if you can!
And if you can't, you'll be my slaves for an extra three months!
You're Hiruma, aren't you?!
Run, Eyeshield 21!
Go!
Secret Technique, Eyeshield Clone Technique!
Are you okay, Sena?
Can't breathe...
Darn it! I'll catch all of them!
Chameleon!
Is it him?! Or him?! Or him?!
Nope, nope, and nope!
Chameleon!
Is it him? Or him? Or HIM?!
Nope, nope, and nope!
That's enough already!
What'll you get out of doing something as cowardly as this?!
You want to know who Eyeshield 21 really is too, don't you?
I don't care anymore!
I don't care who he really is. Don't do stuff like this if you really like football.
Fight against Eyeshield fair-and-square on the field!
We'll finish this in a football game sometime!
Later!
Ya-ha! You can't catch the real Eyeshield that easily!
Hiruma!
Too bad, chameleon freak! Now you're my slave for even longer!
Mamori!
I feel drained now that everything's over.
Are you okay?
I wonder who saved me in the end...
Was it you?
No!
As if that'd happen, huh?
In the end, I never got to find out who Eyeshield is.
But I believe that when our dreams come true and we go to the Christmas Bowl someday,
he'll tell me who he really is.
For now, just getting to see him run on the field is enough for me.
Yeah...
I may have been against it at first, but I'm glad that you joined the football team.
Yep!
I'm really surprised. I was so brave when I wanted to protect Mamori.
But I just can't forgive that Hiruma!
Hey, Manajerk!
That's Eyeshield's lap time for today.
Put it in his file.
Unlike normal, his speed went up instead of down.
He got in some good practice thanks to those Chameleon jerks.
I-I wonder if Hiruma planned for all of this to happen...
You plotted this from the very beginning, didn't you?!
We got a new way to practice!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Kurita, why are you so down?
I'm putting everyone through a lot of trouble!
So I'm going to quit football!
What are you saying, Fatty?!
What about your dream to play at the Christmas Bowl?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Farewell, Kurita?! Ya-ha!
From Togano to Hiruma and then lastly to Eyeshield 21.
All done!
But, I feel like... we're missing somebody.
I wonder if I caught a cold...
Where are you, Eyeshield 21?!
I wonder who it could be?
Where am I?!