Bando Spiders vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Okay, come on!
- Ya-ha!
Listen up, Taki.
Don't try to beat Akaba by pushing him down.
You couldn't handle it.
First you've got to accept that.
We're up against the Tokyo MVP, Hayato Akaba!
He's a top player who can't be pushed around!
But you see,
you've got your own way of fighting as the underdog.
You've got your own weapon that will enable you to win!
He caught him!
But will you end up on Hayato Akaba's
dinner plate, Natsuhiko Taki?!
I won't let you get near Sena!
You're wasting your time.
That's right!
This is my one and only weapon
I have for defeating you!
What?!
This heavy-pushing hard-rock type man!
Now's your chance, Sena!
Yeah!
Touchdown!
- Hooray!
Suzuna, I can't believe he stopped Akaba!
Taki's amazing! Truly amazing!
Yep...!
The extra point kick made it!
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 29
Deimon's just six points behind!
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 30
Now don't you dare get cocky!
We're still a whole six points behind!
T-That's right.
And we don't have much time left...
Bando's offense...
...HAS to be stopped!
Yeah!
Don't let them eat the clock.
Pour on the pressure!
- Yeah!
We're going to win this game!
We WILL win!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Time-Up of Light and Shadows!
Well, we're down to five minutes left
and Deimon is kicking off!
Musashi kicked the ball deep into enemy turf!
We're running out of time!
Hurry!
Defense! Defense! Defense!
- Stop him!
Deimon's got another enemy
they're stuck fighting against now: time.
But going by their fierce determination...
I know you'll make it to the Kanto Tournament, Sena!
Deimon's squashed Bando's offense again!
They sure are on overdrive!
That's the only way I can describe what we're witnessing!
Sweet! We're gonna make it!
Yep!
This is when we're supposed to stand our ground!
Bando failed to steal their first down
and still have a whooping 41 yards left to go!
Next up is their fourth down!
Kotaro, I know you can-
I know!
If I make a smart kick and get three points,
this game is as good as ours!
Kotaro...
We've gotta stop him!
They're down to 41 yards!
Bando's going to stick with Kotaro's field goal kick as their final offense!
His rhythm's different from normal!
Oh no!
The ball went soaring up high!
Will it make it?!
It missed!
Kotaro's kick didn't make it!
The tip of his toes got caught in the grass,
throwing off his timing.
Darn it!
We have to win this game and prove to the world
how powerful kicks really are!
How could I goof this up?!
Dang it!
He got a little nervous
because of all this pressure over him
having to make this kick.
That's all it took to throw him off.
Now it's Deimon's ball!
H-How much time's left?
Four minutes!
Okay! It's attack time!
We're down to one minute and thirty seconds!
Man...!
We're so close, but they aren't budging an inch!
It's not a problem.
Kotaro will kick the ball right in front of their goal posts.
That way Deimon won't have enough time
to grab the ball and steal a touchdown.
Yeah!
We're counting on you, Kotaro.
Right.
I won't let you down!
I'll get it right this time!
Kotaro...
W-What is it?!
I just gotta kick it over there, right?!
I'm sorry...
Throughout this game...
...we've been relying on you and your kicks.
- Let's win.
- Huh?
The two of us...
No, all of the New Bando Spiders' players will play to win!
Akaba...
I hate to admit it,
but without out you,
we couldn't have brought this team back to life again.
I have to confess...
I think you're the smartest dude out there!
Oh gosh, you two!
Good luck, Bando Spiders!
Allegro!
Coach!
He was watching the game!
Listen up, everyone!
Let's use Allegro! Allegro!
Man!
The offensive team
gets like three times as much practice time as we do!
It can't be helped.
They're the ones playing the lead melody, after all.
Akaba! You don't have anything to do with kicks!
Take my smart spit attack!
But a team without a kicker is like a rock band without a guitarist.
Football and guitars have nothing to do with each other!
Guys!
Did you know that "allegro" is actually a musical term?
All-gross?
No! ALLEGRO! Allegro!
Huh?
Normally it just means "fast," but its true meaning is different.
It really means "lively and fun."
I may be a newbie at football,
but I still want to enjoy playing it.
Everyone gathered up around here loves football!
So quit being so glum!
Let's be lively and have fun!
Great!
I'll have fun, cut loose and make a totally smart 200-yard kick!
There's no way you could kick THAT far!
- He's right...
- Allegro!
Allegro!
The New Bando Spiders is the best team in the world!
And I still wanna keep playing football with this team!
- Yeah!
The entire atmosphere around them's changed.
Man! Sideburns has completely regained his cool!
But the same goes for us!
We promised each other
that we'd make it to the Christmas Bowl!
It's not just the three of us anymore.
All of the Deimon Devil Bats...
...will make it there!
To the Christmas Bowl!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what's important when making a punt!
The hint is pushing them back.
When you fail to get a first down and decide to make a punt,
make sure it's a long kick so that it will force the opponents back.
Send it flyin'! Ya-ha!
Spiders! Spiders! Spiders!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
The crowd has flown into a cheering war between
- the Spiders and the Devil Bats!
- Oh, calm down.
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 30
There is a six-point gap with 1:21 left to go!
Will the final seat of the Kanto Tournament
- go to the Bando Spiders?!
- Rock and Soul!
- Or to the Deimon Devil Bats?!
- Ya-ha!
Who will the goddess of victory smile upon?!
We're going to beat Akaba!
We'll defeat that Spider's Illusion!
I will definitely defeat you with our Spider Illusion.
The game's up and going again!
What will Bando do now?!
Set, hut!
Kotaro, kick it as far back as you can!
Deimon won't have enough time to get a touchdown that way!
Yeah, Akaba, leave it to me!
Deimon, you're finished!
Go!
That kick's... a monster!
I'm so smart!
Now we're sure to win!
He even factored in the wind!
Kotaro's kick was absolutely flawless!
They've practically dug Deimon's grave
and stuffed them in the coffin!
Why's there already someone where it's supposed to land?!
Stupid Sideburns, your kicks are TOO perfect!
You're practically telling us where the ball's gonna land!
Good going!
- Sena!
Nice Max Catch! Now run!
- Yeah!
Deimon Devil Bats!
The game's almost over!
All of their blockers are relying on this punt return!
Sorry, but you're up now!
Please stop him, Akaba!
Run!
We're finished if you get stopped!
- Stop him!
We're going to the Christmas Bowl!
I won't let anyone stop me!
- Sena!
- Yay!
He's using his super lightspeed!
Forty yards in 4.2 seconds!
It's the world of lightspeed...
But this is... a trap!
He's completely surrounded!
He fell for Akaba's run force!
I won't stop running!
I don't care if my legs give out on me!
I can't let our journey to the Christmas Bowl end here!
It's an ongoing Devil Bat Ghost!
What?!
I'll keep this speed up until I reach the goal line!
Use Spider Poison!
Oh, that's right!
We can't lose, either!
Spider Poison!
Not again!
They're getting pushed back!
Darn it!
Crap!
Man, this really ticks me off!
Yeah, our stupid Chinfuzz here...
...figured out how to counter this play before us!
No matter how hard I push... he isn't giving in!
I won't let you near the ball, not matter what!
That's it!
Keep putting yourselves between them and the ball!
No matter what, don't slow down any, Sena!
Get through or else!
Let's WIN!
The Christmas Bowl...
...is ours!
Go at them like you're gonna kill them!
Yay! He got through!
But the time...! Hurry up!
My muscles...!
They feel like they're being jabbed by needles!
I feel like I'm gonna die...
I can't... move my legs...
But there's no way I'm stopping!
I'll never stop!
I'll make you stop!
Bando will be the ones going to the Christmas Bowl!
Akaba!
Which one of them is the real Eyeshield 21?
This game will unveil that truth to us!
Run, Sena! Faster! Run faster!
Surpass your own limits!
He's using his Spider Illusion!
There's ten seconds left!
Sena, I'm gonna win!
I WILL get by you, Akaba!
We're definitely...
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Sena?!
You...
Sena Kobayakawa got a touchdown!
- Yay!
He broke through Akaba's Spider Illusion and scored a touchdown!
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 30
Deimon's finally tied with them!
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 36
Sena!
You okay?
Leave the rest to me.
Yeah!
S-Sena, you should go rest on the bench...
No, please.
We've come so far in the Tokyo Tournament
and I kinda want to stay on the field until the very end...
And now, and now-!
They're going to have Musashi kick for the extra point!
Musashi's finally come back to us.
I know... this kick'll make it!
He did it! Game over!
It's 36-37!
The Deimon Devil Bats totally, totally, totally flipped the scoreboard!
The third team representing Tokyo is the Deimon Devil Bats!
They're going to the Kanto Tournament!
- Boo-yah!
We did it!
Yay, yay!
YA-
HA!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Yay!
Deimon flipped the scoreboards and won the game!
Now the Tokyo Tournament's over.
It feels like it took forever and a day.
And now the Kanto Tournament's about to start!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Strongest Warriors in Tokyo! Ya-ha!
Yay!
Let's start practicing our cheers
for the Kanto Tournament, Deimon Mascots!
Let's go, Cerbbie!
Piggyberus!
Go, go! Deimon!
Omo, put your heart into it!
Go... go... Deimon!
- Go... Go... Deimon!
- I said to put your heart into it!
I'm only human!