- Eyeshield 21!
- Keep watching!
Okay, we've all gotta believe in ourselves, and all the training we've done!
We're gonna open a path for Sena no matter what!
- Right!
Deimon can't out-muscle us.
We're gonna ground them once and for all!
- Right!
Sakuraba...
Monta...
No one beats me in a catching match.
I'll neutralize your skills with my height.
Shin...
I'm coming at you with everything I've got.
Then come, Eyeshield 21!
Whichever one of them comes out on top will, more or less, determine who wins the game.
It's finally here...
The ultimate final showdown.
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Opening Fanfare!
The rematch of the century will kick off in mere moments!
Will it be Deimon's offense or Ojo's defense?
It will be an epic battle between sword and shield, until one finally breaks!
Listen up.
We need use the boost we're getting from removing the masks and score right away.
Especially you, Peewee.
You need to run the opening kickoff in at top speed.
B-But...
What do we do if they kick it to the other side, to Ishimaru?
Who's faster, you or the track star?
OBVIOUSLY there's an 80% chance they'll kick it to Ishimaru.
Then we should all gather around Ishimaru's side...
And he and I switch places right before they kick?
We'll give 'em a taste of a super-light speed kickoff return.
Right!
Sena... They're going to use him right from the start.
I wonder.
Even Sena will have it rough if they leave themselves too open.
I want to know...
...how effective will Eyeshield 21's light speed legs be against Shin?
And...
...how far Shin will go after having mastered my Rodeo Drive.
Go, Deimon!
C'mon, Kakei, take it off!
You gotta get in the spirit!
I will never... ever strip.
This'll be smart.
Deimon vs. Ojo...
They both beat us to get here.
This better be the smartest game I've ever seen, or they'll get it!
Indeed, who will play the hottest beat and wrap up this session with a win?
I'm telling you, guitar metaphors don't make sense!
As expected, the crowd is pumped up!
Seibu, Kyoshin, even Bando!
It's an all-star gathering of Kanto's top players!
Don't cry, Onihei!
Once again, Deimon and Ojo will clash!
Let's review their respective tournament performances thus far!
Riko?
All right... we'll start with the Deimon Devil Bats.
In the quarter-finals of the Tokyo Tournament, they faced the Kyoshin Poseidons.
Somehow, they stood up to their overwhelming height and managed to win.
But in the semi-finals, against the Seibu Wild Gunmen,
they managed to keep pace with Seibu's explosive offense for most of the game,
but in the end, they came up short.
Deimon's last chance would come in the third place tiebreaker game.
And in that game,
they faced the ultimate kick team, the Bando Spiders.
They had a tough time against Kotaro Sasaki's kicks and Hayato Akaba's Run Force,
but they squeaked out one last touchdown and beat Bando,
which earned them a ticket to the Kanto Tournament!
Then, in the Kanto Tournament,
Deimon ended up facing the reigning champs, the Shinryuji Nagas.
Even though they were down 32-0 at the end of the first half,
they pushed back against their seemingly invincible opponents,
and pulled off a miraculous comeback victory!
Then we have the Ojo White Knights!
With Shinryuji eliminated, they are the current favorites to win it all.
Yes, their record is incredible.
They beat Bando in the Tokyo Tournament semi-finals,
and Seibu in the finals to take first place.
And in the opening game of the Kanto Tournament,
they obliterated the Sado Strong Golems!
As always, their most incredible stats are on defense.
Aside from a single field goal by Bando,
they have not given up a single point throughout the whole tournament!
Simple, ain't it?
The football royalty of Ojo versus the still-evolving Deimon.
Yeah... there's no telling how this will end.
You scared with all those eyes on you, Peewee?
Oh... no...
How should I say this...?
It's like... we're responsible for all the dreams of everyone we've beaten... or something...
That's why...
That's why... we have to play our best today, in front of all of them!
Enough of this wuss-talk, let's roll!
You need to show your best stuff to Ojo, too.
Yeah!
Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
-Ya-ha!
- Oh!
Oh ho! Sena catches a kick on the opposite side!
Okay!
Eyeshield?
He got it way out there?
I knew it...
- Go, Sena!
Blaze a path down the field!
Too naive... we planned for you to be the runner.
Here they come! Ojo's proud, iron defense, the Five Knights!
Have they already closed in on Sena?
Find it... even the smallest crack... and blow through it!
Nothing!
Sena!
Smash a hole in 'em!
Guys...
Don't underestimate them, Deimon.
This is the great shield that defends Ojo...
The Grand Scutum!
King Kuroki will shut you down!
This guy's... heavy!
You can't match Watanabe's power! Use speed on #70!
The Swim?! That's my move!
You're not the only one who uses it.
It's a tall lineman's move.
T-These guys...
The Delinquent Deathblow!
Hang on!
- You won't get through!
They all...
They got squashed...
They are Ojo's Five Knights!
The game has just begun and they've flattened Deimon's line AND Sena!
N-No way...
Shoot...
How did those jerks...
...manage to stop us?
Don't take Ojo lightly!
Shin and Otawara aren't the whole team!
You get that now?!
This is Ojo's defense...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What do you call the thing that holds the ball up for kicks?
Think about Musa-shan's kicks!
The item used to hold footballs up for kicks are called "kick tees."
You need 'em for kickoffs! Ya-ha!
Woohoo!
No one beats Ojo's defense with the Five Knights on the field!
They call their iron defense the "Grand Scutum!"
That's Latin for "grand shield," folks!
And what an appropriate name,
these five are like one giant, living shield!
All five of them were chosen as all-star
defensemen after the Tokyo Tournament.
Be careful, everyone!
We don't lose one-on-one fights!
We got this.
That's the spirit, guys!
We'll stop them in their tracks this time!
- Yeah!
Can Deimon break through Ojo's defense this time?
Deimon goes with another Sweep!
Here they come!
Don't look down...
...on the Deimon line!
You won't get through this time!
- Now, Sena!
There's a way through!
I can make it!
Wait-!
He made it!
Sena!
No, not yet...
Uh oh, now it's Otawara standing in Sena's way!
If everyone could imagine for a second,
the terror of facing down a heavily armored knight charging forward at top speed.
Otawara's really fast!
Otawara uses his massive bulk to knock Sena aside!
We finally opened a path...
How'd they...?
That was no opening.
That gap in the Ojo line may have looked like a good route at first,
but they were positioned to lead him to Otawara.
The Run Force.
They controlled Deimon's blockers and only left Sena a route they could defend.
Talk about un-smart.
Just when he got through, he hit another wall.
What're they gonna do?
Man, they use the Run Force, too?
Yeesh.
This stinks...
Man... they totally owned you guys, huh?
We couldn't help it!
You don't notice the Run Force unless you're looking for it!
Your guy took you down, too!
Say what?!
Guys!
We've got a game to play here!
No yelling!
G-Guys, no-
Stop fighting!
Eesh...
A-Anyways, the game's just started!
Until we can really stop those five, Sena won't be able to get through!
Kurita...
Let's come up with a way to counter the Five Knights!
Easy for you to say...
The guy who got me, #22 has crazy good technique.
#70's really freaking strong.
#92's way taller than I am, and he uses the Swim, too.
#25... f-fast!
Can't match speed.
What?
'Sup, Komusubi?
I couldn't use my power 'cause of his speed!
You couldn't use your power because of his speed...
You can't match Watanabe's power! Use speed on #70!
That's it!
They're using technique on Togano, power on Kuroki, and speed on you two!
They're matched up perfectly to stop us!
So they figured out which one of us they should target according to our weaknesses...
And then totally controlled us!
Yes!
Then if WE choose the matchups...
WE can control THEM!
Yeah!
If we know the trick...
...there's nothing to fear!
Guys!
Take it to the max!
Good thinking, Komusubi!
Now let's get 'em!
- Yeah!
What a crazy bunch.
Still, the only way we'll last against Ojo is for them to figure things out for themselves.
Set...
If we don't make a good showing this play, Ojo will have all the momentum.
Everyone... stay focused!
It's okay... trust in everyone's ability!
Things won't go your way this time.
Tackle!
Hut hut!
Deimon runs a third sweep!
Now, everyone!
I'll take the power guy, #70!
I got the speed guy!
I got the technique guy!
Heavyweight...
...power!
- Double Belly Press!
The third time's the charm as Deimon blue-skies the Five Knights!
So many routes!
Now, Sena!
Right!
Eyeshield 21 leaves the Five Knights behind!
You're not getting through!
Everyone worked to get me this far... I can't let him stop me!
- The Devil Bat Ghost!
It's not over!
Here it comes.
You're headed right for the guillotine!
Now it's Shin who bars Eyeshield 21's path!
Here comes Shin!
It's time for the ultimate showdown!
Eyeshield 21 versus Seijuro Shin!
The star players of both teams are on a collision course!
This isn't the Devil Bat Ghost he stopped last time.
Come, Eyeshield 21!
I'll use the same technique I used on Agon, and use my arm to block him and get through!
I'll beat you, Shin!
Start the Devil Bat Ghost...
Wha-! He's too fast!
- Sena!
A-Amazing...
The Trident Tackle struck a moment before the Devil Bat Ghost began!
That was Shin's power...
It's not over...
You're better than that!
Stand up, Eyeshield 21!
A prodigy who trains incessantly,
Seijuro Shin.
He's a monster with a capital M.
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
H-He can't be... "Prison Chain" Ikari?!
Huh? I dunno what happened between you two, but this's no time to be scared!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Ikari's Prison Chain!
Ya-ha!
Stopping the Devil Bat Ghost before it starts... Shin's totally smart.
Deimon's allegretto offense is no match for Ojo's perfect defense.
If this keeps up, it'll be "al fine" for Deimon.
Guitar metaphors...
- ...don't make sense!
This isn't the time to be synchronizing with the audience!