Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
Beware! The Demonic Chameleons!
What're we gonna do...
We've got no time left before the Kyoshin game!
What do they want us to do, play naked?
Who the heck did this?!
Hey, this's...
A red uniform, #21...
He's the only one it could be!
What's wrong?
Don't try to stop us, boss!
We're gonna wreck that runt!
What's with them?
Boss!
They must've seen this and gotten mad...
You gotta be kidding me!
If they make a big scene they'll get us disqualified from the tournament!
Rrgh!
Uh...Can I help you?
We said we're here to say hi.
Get out here, Eyeshield 21!
They want Eyeshield 21.
W-Why?
They said they wanna say hi, but...
Say hi?
Maybe the found your wallet, or need directions...?
I seriously doubt it.
Ain'tcha coming?!
Don't make us drag you out!
A-Anyways, you should at least see what the problem is.
Y-Yes.
Yep, you should go.
W-Wait, why do I-
They want Eyeshield 21!
You really want to blow my cover?
Have to.
I don't want to!
Get your butt out here!
Y-You're...
The king of evil...
...Yoichi Hiruma!
You sure you're allowed to do this?
Zokugaku doesn't sit around and take it when people sneak in
and try to mess with us!
Then maybe you should double check.
You boneheads, are you all insane?!
H-Habashira...
What?!
What's beating him up gonna do for us?!
You get me?
B-But-
Habashira-
Clam it, just get back here!
You hear me?!
You tell this to Eyeshield 21:
We'll be nice and back off THIS time.
But this ain't over.
Hiruma, your phone!
That was yours.
When did you take it?!
Sena, don't tell me you really did it?
There's no way!
Then maybe it means someone tried to take Deimon out of the picture by framing Eyeshield 21?
Wha- Really?
Stop getting involved in these stupid plots!
It's time for practice!
- Okay!
What a waste of time.
- I'm going home.
- Yeah.
Later.
Wh-Who are you-
E-Eyeshield...
Again?! Eyeshield attacked us again?!
Another sneak attack, too.
Do we really have to sit around and take this?
I can't stand it anymore,
- we have to get him!
- Let's go!
You three still don't get it, do you?
B-But, boss-
Silence!
You know Rui's putting everything he has into this tournament!
We'll get our revenge!
But until the time comes, don't any of you do a thing.
Got it?!
I can't believe we're just letting this happen...
What the heck is wrong with Habashira?!
Back in the day things were quiet,
and if anything happened, he finished it right away.
Maybe Habashira's losing his edge.
Well well, I see we have us some Zokugaku students!
Ah, I see. You must be the one that got jumped, right?
N-None of your business.
You know who did it, don't you?
But you're just sitting around twiddling your thumbs.
Zokugaku's gone down the toilet.
Or maybe you'd like us to take care of him for you?
Since you boys don't have the guts to do it yourselves!
Shaddap!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
Mess with us and you'll pay!
Now you're talking!
Let's see what you've got!
When are you numbskulls gonna learn?!
Get out of here, now!
Hold up, Habashira.
You pick a fight and then you just leave?
Our bad... Just leave us alone, okay?
Stop talking like a sissy!
Y-You lousy-
No!
H-Habashira!
- Why?
- We gotta fight back!
So wait, if there's an impostor...
Hey, Habashira's...
Something's fishy over there...
Sena, hide!
Come on, Habashira.
You chicken or what?
No...
Then wake up!
I told you to fight!
No.
If you wanna hit me, just get it over with.
What...?
Man, forget this chump.
C'mon.
Chump!
Wuss!
Baby!
W-What happened, Habashira?
Why? Why don't you fight back?!
Is football really that important to you?!
No way... He got beat up!
Hey!
Habashira.
Huh?
Oh, Deimon's manager.
You saw that?
...Yes.
Sorry, you saw me at my worst there.
No, you weren't...
This tournament's MY last one, too.
We got booted from the spring tournament because I punched a ref.
Losing's bad enough, but being disqualified is a million times worse.
It killed me.
So...
So I wanted to get us to the Christmas Bowl.
To give us something we could be proud of.
I... I see.
Tell Hiruma this.
Tell him I'm gonna take care of this personally!
Y-Yes!
Football Clinic!
What is a "route?"
The course a receiver runs!
Learn all the routes so you can execute your plays perfectly! Ya-ha!
Why're you all spaced out?
Are you worried about something, Sena?
I bet you're thinking,
"we really need to do something to find the culprit."
Y-Yeah...
Find the culprit?!
Whoa, that sounds fun!
No way, that's too dangerous!
Habashira said he would take care of it personally...
But he...
Hiruma?
Who stands to gain the most,
by eliminating Deimon and Zokugaku in one fell swoop?
Think about it.
Deimon and Zokugaku...
W-What, Sena?
It couldn't be.
Eat that! Die, Zokugaku scum!
I got a question for you.
The Dokubari Scorpions?
Yes.
See...
The team that would gain the most by eliminating both Deimon and Zokugaku
is Dokubari.
I see.
It makes sense.
O-Of course, this is all just an assumption.
But you came all the way here to tell Rui this?
Y-Yes...
I completely understand why Habashira's
so focused on the Christmas Bowl.
You're a good boy, aren't you?
Well...
C-Can I help you?
A red #21 uniform...
You bought one, exactly one, complete with an eye shield...
What for?
W-What're you talking about?
You bought it at that sporting goods store.
I don't understand...
I know what you're up to, kid!
What's up?
Deimon's manager?
I figured he'd show up.
Right... Send the freshmen to Dokubari?
Got it.
Uh...
Take it.
Right...
Hello?
Did Hiruma send you?!
I told him to keep his nose outta this!
N-No, I came on my own...
Whatever... Do me a favor, then.
Yes?
Bring Eyeshield 21 there, too.
Huh? Who're they?
C'mere...
Okay, I got it.
Which one of you is Kanagushi?!
That would be me!
Can I help you gents with something?
Trying to pit us against Deimon and get ourselves booted...
You really put some effort into this, huh?
What's that?
I have no idea what you're talking about...
Don't play dumb with me.
We've already gotten a confession.
K-Kanagushi...
He told us everything.
He says YOU used him to set up Eyeshield 21.
I don't know this person!
I mean, he doesn't even go to our school.
K-Kanagushi, you backstabbing-
You're something else, acting innocent in the face of all this proof!
I assure you it's no act!
I haven't done anything wrong.
Eyeshield 21's the real culprit, isn't he?
You little...
Why don't you go find him?
No need. He's already on his way.
You mind setting this stooge straight?
Tell him "Eyeshield 21 never plays dirty," or something.
It was you, wasn't it, Eyeshield 21!
Say something, Eyeshield 21!
Well?
That's right. It was me.
W-What?
What'd you say?
See? What'd I tell you?
I'm telling you Eyeshield 21 never would've done that!
This guy's a fake!
What proof do you have of that?
Sorry, pal.
You don't know what Eyeshield looks like, do you?
How can you prove he's a fake?
If you want proof, I've got it right here!
E-Eyeshield 21?!
Are you the real one?
Yes.
I am the REAL Eyeshield 21!
What do you say to that, Kanagushi?
He's the fake!
A fake that Zokugaku dressed up to goad us into a fight!
Everyone catch that phony!
Oh man!
Those dirty rats!
You dirtbag!
No! Back off.
He... The REAL Eyeshield 21 could never be caught by bums like Dokubari.
Eyeshield, Shmeyeshield...
I'll take him down.
Go!
W-What?
He's getting blurry!
Ya-ha!
Way to go, real one!
H-He disappeared...
Habashira, from Zokugaku.
Don't mess with us!
Awesome...
Habashira...
You really did a number on me!
He can't cause any big scenes right now, either.
Get him!
Stop!
We're going home, guys.
Habashira!
You're sure about this?
Yeah...
We'll let HIM make this loser pay out on the gridiron.
Don't get me wrong, Eyeshield 21!
I'm not grateful, and I'm not on your side.
R-Right...
The one who finally stops you will be ME!
I'll see you on the field, Habashira!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Yay! The Chameleons and Poseidons go head to head!
But wait, something's wrong here.
It's like Habashira and the freshmen players
aren't on the same wavelength.
Which one will survive?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Clash! The Chameleons vs. the Poseidons! Ya-ha!
"I'm not grateful, and I'm not on your side."
"The one who finally stops you will be ME!"
That was pretty awesome.
Yeah, I really hope we get to play Habashira's team...
But Zokugaku's next opponents are the Poseidons, right?
Oh... Yeah...
And the Poseidons completely demolished Onihei and Hashiratani...
You think they'll be okay?
I know they will!
Habashira... He'll do it...