I reserved it for the whole day!
Wow... He's amazing!
Yahoo!
Nice!
Eyeshield 21!
Good work!
You guys played great!
Quit acting so happy.
Why in the world are we even out here?
You guys did it, congrats!
Quit messing around, go get changed!
Eyeshield?
Yes?
I'm so impressed.
You were great, I mean really great!
Th-Thanks!
Can I... Can I still join the football club?
O-Oh, of course-
Thank you so much!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Scorching Hell Tower!
The Devil Bats won 46-28!
The fearsome Rui Habashira never even got close!
Football might be kinda fun.
I don't know the rules or anything, though.
Football, huh?
Well at any rate, Eyeshield 21's running was still cool, no?
Oh yeah, that was something else!
We'll be interviewing by position!
Please come in when we call your number!
There's so many people!
Okay, we'll go ahead and ask them the position they want,
but mainly we'll decide what they're suited for.
The easiest thing to see is if they belong on offense or defense.
How can you tell?
By the way they enter the room.
For example...
Guys like this are professional and will execute a strategy with precision and efficiency.
He belongs on offense.
On the other hand, this guy's a wild animal who'll use his instincts to catch his prey.
He goes on defense.
So I guess that means I'd be put on offense?
Then I'd be on defense.
What are you all talking about?
You're a team manager Sena, you don't go on offense OR defense!
Th-That's right!
E-Excuse me?
Hey, I saw him yesterday-
Offense.
U-Um, I'm Manabu Yukimitsu, from class 2-4.
A second-year?
I guess I don't belong, after all...
Oh, no, no!
What the heck am I supposed to ask for interview questions?
Come on Sena, ask him something.
W-What's your favorite food?
You stupid Manajerk, that had nothing to do with anything!
Of course it did!
But what about asking why he wants to join, or something like that?
Right, that's what I meant!
As I watched the game against Zokugaku yesterday,
it felt like a fire had been lit inside me.
I've been going to cram schools ever since first grade,
and I've never been allowed to join any clubs.
Next year will be dedicated to college entrance exams.
I get depressed thinking about how my time in high school will end if I keep going like this.
I... I just want one memory of-
Memory?
Memories?!
We're here to win games, Baldini!
But if I were to play, I would play to win!
Freakin'...
I know I'm not in very good shape,
but seeing how someone as small as Eyeshield became a hero from Notre Dame
and how he stands up to anyone in his path without fear or hesitation...
I want to learn from him!
Umm, there's no need to make such a fuss over Eyeshield 21...
No, he truly is incredible!
But-
I hope you'll consider me.
Could Sena and Eyeshield be...
...angry at each other?
Next! Number 2!
Defense.
Mm-
Class 1-1, D-D-Daikichi Komusubi!
P-Pupil!
Pupil?
P-P-Pupil!
Are you saying you want to be Kurita's pupil?
You mean you want to be on the line?
Hooray! A new friend on the line! Let's both work extra hard!
Another teammate, another teammate!
I think Eyeshield 21 is the man!
I wanna be just like him...
And maybe be on TV, too, so girls will like me...
I wanted Eyeshield 21's autograph...
Oh, but the passes is cool, too!
Your throws were all, "Whoosh!"
I swear I'll become a hero!
Down with Eyeshield!
We're teammates and rivals at the same time.
I'm Miyake from class 1-3.
I'm pretty good at most sports, right now I'm kind of bouncing from one team to the next.
Oh, really?
Clearly you don't have many members, but perhaps you can convince me to play now and then?
I really admire you, Hiruma.
So much money in your treasury, so many people at your command...
I'd be honored to help lighten the load.
Whew, it's finally over!
That reminds me...
Those three didn't show up.
Maybe they hated playing in the Zokugaku game...
We don't need people with no drive.
I wish we could use everyone who came today.
There's too many of 'em.
We need to have tryouts.
Tryouts?
I heard Eyeshield's gonna be here!
What're we doing?
They said climbing stairs.
Sounds exhausting...
They're all freshmen...
I must be the only second-year, but they all look so fit!
Everyone here?
Something going on down there?
The football club?
Freeze, kid!
All aboard!
Huh?! Where to?
We're not climbing stairs here at school?
We're getting on, we're getting on!
Get back here!
Stand still!
I'll strangle you!
I knew you'd come back!
Hey, where's Mamori?
I don't see her.
She's already on-site.
What site?
It's right out there, take a look.
No way!
Are you for real?!
Football Clinic!
What does a team manager do?
Team administration!
They support the players and set up games and stuff! Got it? Ya-ha!
To-To-Tokyo Tower?!
How does he do it?
See you at the top!
We got ice yet, Manajerk?
Tons of it.
Listen up, ladies! The rules are simple.
The goal's the top viewing platform.
Fatty's up there waiting to have himself a snow-cone,
so bring him some freakin' ice!
You can carry as much ice as you want.
And if it melts, you're free to come back for more.
The point is, if you manage to get any ice to the top, you make the cut.
Are we clear?
This stuff seems to melt really easily...
We put sugar in it so it would melt quicker...
Hey Manajerk!
Where's Eyeshield?
Huh? I was gonna stay down-
Find him and drag him over here!
Today's also a demonstration, so I want him running with everyone else!
Okay...
We gotta climb this?
How long you think it'll take?
Maybe I should take more ice?
No way, it'll weight you down.
Taking a light load and rushing all the way up's the easiest way to get first place-
He's the real ace!
Max catch!
Oops, it melted.
Let's rumble, Eyeshield 21!
I can't beat you in a footrace, but my jumping ability will get me to the top before you!
We're teammates and rivals at the same time.
You think you can beat me?
Go, everyone! The Hell Tower awaits! Ya-ha!
They're fast!
Ow- Hey!
Why are we trying out, exactly?
We'll ditch this place first chance we get.
I'm too slow, I have to carry as much ice as I can.
The Hell Tower isn't as safe as it looks.
I hope everyone makes it up here in one piece.
We're finally at the Grand Observatory!
That means we're halfway there!
This is easier than I thought it'd be!
Huh?
C-Cerberus!
W-We're fine, there no way Cerberus will wanna eat ice!
We put sugar in it so it would melt quicker!
Barrier #1: The Hellhound!
Run, Monta! Cerberus is after the ice!
Wha?!
We're not carrying sherbet!
This thing'll eat anything that has a flavor!
He's gonna chomp us!
That was close...
Here.
To replace what you threw.
You don't have to-
I don't wanna owe you any favors.
I'm just keeping our race on the up-and-up.
Got it.
Not again!
We actually got past Cerberus...
What the-
It's so hot!
What the heck is this?!
Can't you make it a little easier?
Barrier #2: The Caldron of Hell!
It all melted!
Mine too!
Nuts, now we gotta do it all over again!
Good luck, guys!
Careful, we're almost to the heaters!
We're fine!
Grand Observatory
Almost to the goal!
Special Observatory
We're up high!
I'm gonna win!
First place.
Your last one melted.
One for Sena!
And one for Monta!
Th-That was fast...
No one's gonna make it up in one shot... They're all coming back.
Yeah, keep at it, guys.
Let's give it one more shot, quit halfway, and go home.
What's your problem?
That little punk!
He's mocking us!
Great job, Komusubi!
M-Master...
I'm trying!
Sena, are you busy up there?
No, not really...
Can you come back down? We're almost out of ice.
Got it, I'm on my way!
Oops, I'm still dressed as Eyeshield! Gotta change...
That was too close!
I finally made it halfway... I need to hurry.
Sorry, Baldy. There's nothing in the rules about stealing someone else's ice.
Man, we are so smart!
You said it. Carrying ice all the way from the bottom is a fool's errand.
See you, Baldy. Thanks for the ice!
Forget him.
Are you okay, Yukimitsu?
I-I refuse to quit.
I'll do it as many times as it takes!
How horrible... Those two stole Yukimitsu's ice!
I'm going to tell them off!
Piece of cake.
Aww yeah.
The elevator's-
The Guardian of Hell!
This is...desiccant?
Hot!
Get bent!
You think you can just-
M-Master!
Great job, Komusubi!
Fatty Jr. makes the cut!
The three Ha-Ha brothers make the cut, too.
We are NOT related!
Wait, why did we actually pass?
I've had enough.
This is totally impossible.
Let's go home.
Yukimitsu, are you all right?
I'm fine...
Oh, Sena, we're fine on ice.
A lot of people gave up and went home.
There's no one else downstairs.
'Kay, guess it's time to pack up, then.
Huh? Where's Sena?
He went up a little bit ahead of me...
He's not here.
How strange...
I can't do this...
I'm not cut out for football after all-
I skip cram school for the first time in my life, and for nothing.
Next year are exams.
Before school ended, just once...
Just one time, I wanted... to do something for myself.
This is my last chance!
Are you injured?
Eyeshield!
S-Seeing you is what made me decide to try out for football!
So I... So I could...
Keep climbing, Yukimitsu.
I'll be waiting for you at the top!
R-Right!
Eyeshield's waiting... He's waiting for me at the top!
Sena, where were you?
Uhh, nowhere...
Let's go home. Clean up, Manajerk.
C-Can't we wait a little longer?
Someone might still be climbing!
No one else is coming.
B-But...
Yukimitsu!
You made it, Yukimitsu!
Yukimitsu, I'm so proud of you!
You rock, dude!
Yeah!
Bah... It's all melted.
No way!
And he finally made it to the top...
Yukimitsu...
Oh? There's one last cube left.
Baldini passes!
That's awesome, Yukimitsu! You made the cut, you made it!
I owe it all to Eyeshield...
Yukimitsu...
I'll work extra hard!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Has Mamori uncovered the truth about Eyeshield's identity?!
Oh, man! If she finds out, Hiruma will-
Uh-huh! You'd better run as far as you can!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Find Eyeshield! Ya-ha!
Yummy, isn't it Komusubi?
What are we still doing here?
Fine, we'll out-binge him!