- Drown!
- Ya-ha!
Set, hut, hut!
Hiruma really is their key to victory.
It's all up to Yoichi Hiruma!
He's the Deimon Devil Bats' secret MVP!
Ya-ha!
Touchdown!
We're gonna keep going with this flow!
You're up next!
Okay!
You're the key!
I'm... the key?
Course you are!
You're Deimon's ace player, after all.
I'm the ace?!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Promise Made on the Field!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
You can do it!
Set, hut!
Get 'em!
They're pretty good!
Not good!
Stop Eyeshield, Ohira, Onishi!
You shouldn't underestimate us!
The Kyoshin defense is the tallest defense in Japan!
Kurita and Komusubi opened up a path!
I'm only up against two guys...
That running style...
Yay!
He did it!
It's the Devil Bat Ghost!
Eyeshield 21 scored a beautiful touchdown!
The first half's over!
Not a bad way to end it, either.
They've got a good chance at victory if they keep this up during the second half.
Kyoshin Poseidon 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
We've definitely gotta win!
Great, just a two point gap!
Let's go full throttle!
Yeah, yeah! We're definitely pushing them back!
You did it, Sena!
Yep! Let's keep up the pace!
Everything depends on how long our Wishbone play keeps working on them.
I seriously doubt Fox-eyes over there is going to keep quiet much longer.
That's... Eyeshield 21.
We're doomed if we go one-on-one with him.
There's no stopping him!
I'll stop him one-on-one.
Do you have a counter-attack for their Wishbone?
Well, of course I've been thinking up something,
but I thought it'd probably be best to let my underclassmen state their opinions...
Deimon's Wishbone
is strong because it allows them to quickly determine
the weak points in our defense formation and send someone to run through it.
I see!
So if we decide beforehand where the weak point will be,
we'll have complete control over Deimon's run.
That's perfect!
We'll let the shrimps run their hearts out!
Amazing, Kakei! You got it totally right!
You thought up the exact same thing I did!
So, who'll you let run?
Eyeshield 21.
Mizumachi and the others will hold back everyone but Eyeshield.
That shouldn't be too hard.
Well, that's true, but...
In other words,
you wanna use THAT technique, huh?
That technique? You mean THAT?
Okay, cool.
So all we've gotta worry about is stopping those guys in the back.
Deimon's Wishbone won't work anymore
if I can defeat Eyeshield one-on-one!
The Kyoshin Poseidons are barely winning with a two point lead.
The Deimon Devil Bats have been pushing them hard
since the end of the first half!
How will the Poseidons defend against the Devil Bats' Wishbone?!
Well, at long last,
we're bursting into the fateful second half of the game!
They stepped over me...
All three of them did!
And it was easy for 'em!
But we'll be okay.
Komusubi's already proved that to us.
Height doesn't really matter.
As long as everyone blocks for me,
I can use the Devil Bat Ghost to blast through a one-on-one confrontation!
No, I WILL get through!
C'mon! Let's work hard in the second half!
Guys, fight!
There's just 30 minutes left.
We're gonna flip the score and go to the semi-finals!
Stop everyone but Eyeshield!
- Yeah!
We'll take the lead at this rate!
Go!
Eyeshield!
No, wait!
They're intentionally drawing out Eyeshield!
I'll get a touchdown if I get by Kakei...
It'd put us in the lead!
Devil Bat Ghost time!
Kakei won't lose!
It's not like there's any other Japanese
who went to America and became aces there!
Your running truly is impressive.
You go from running straight ahead at full throttle
to making a sharp turn in zero seconds without losing speed.
But if I can cover that distance in zero seconds...
Let me show you that merely running around isn't enough in a real game!
Go, Eyeshield!
He's here!
What pressure!
I've gotta turn here!
No way...
Impossible!
Th-The Devil Bat Ghost has been... DEFEATED!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to throw the ball!
The main point's your wrist?
The key points when you let go of the ball
are to put your pinky finger on the laces and not move your wrist.
Keep an eye on your pinky and wrist! Ya-ha!
Ka-ke-i! Ka-ke-i! Ka-ke-i!
The Devil Bat Ghost...
...didn't work.
No way!
So that's Shun Kakei...
He surprised me...
His killer tackle was explosive!
But what exactly was that technique?!
Kakei's Moby Dick Anchor really is super-duper!
Anyway, it's great!
Got it?
A fake can never get by me.
It's clear who's going to win this game.
He stopped... the Devil Bat Ghost?
I'll expose you for the weakling you are!
Snap outta it already!
The game's not over yet!
Right!
Curse that fox-eyed jerk!
He really was hiding a great technique!
We're not done yet!
There's still time! There's still time!
I'll get by this time!
Set, hut!
I don't need anyone to cover from behind me.
Push forward like mad!
Stop everyone but Eyeshield!
They found the Wishbone's weakness!
Monta and Eyeshield's running combo is powerful when it's completely synced.
But because of that, our pass offense is on the weak side.
The enemy knows that,
so they're going to do everything they can to stop them from running.
And now they've even managed to stop the Devil Bat Ghost!
There's no way the Devil Bat Ghost can't work!
Poseidons! Poseidons!
The Devil Bat Ghost has been stopped again!
The result will be the same no matter how many times you try!
Don't worry, don't worry.
It's okay. You'll get by next time!
What should I do?
The Devil Bats don't stand a chance if I can't get by Kakei...
Wow! The Deimon Devil Bats are doomed if Eyeshield 21 can't get by!
This time!
Set, hut, hut!
Huh? I don't get it?
Max Dash!
I thought that would happen!
Onishi!
Deimon failed to get their first down!
He even stopped Monta!
Keep at it! Fight!
It looks like your friends have given up on you
the way they didn't let you have the ball.
They did it! They got a field goal! It's now 17-12!
Kyoshin Poseidon 17 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
All right! We did it!
The Poseidons are overpowering them.
Have the Deimon Devil Bats reached the end of the line?!
They're facing the greatest pinch of their lives!
He didn't give it to me again...
It's no good!
This's bad!
We've completely fallen into the palm of their hand!
What should we do?
We don't have time for this!
Shoot!
We aren't moving forward at all!
This is bad.
Now do you understand, Fakeshield?
This is a piece of cake with you outta the way!
Sorry, but this will be your last game!
Got that right!
It's no... use...
Stand up...
Stand up!
Stand up! Stand up! Stand up! STAND UP!
Show 'em what you've got!
Didn't you say you'd keep winning?!
You said you wouldn't let the fall season end!
You said that you'd keep winning until everyone in
the Deimon Devil Bats is standing on the field together!
Yuki...
We play Amino High in the first round!
If we beat them, we'll get to keep playing!
Right, Monta?
You got it!
The tournament won't end if we keep winning, Sena!
Until EVERY Deimon Devil Bat stands on the field together, we won't lose!
EYESHIELD!
You aren't playing football by yourself!
You aren't the only player on the Devil Bats!
Sena, let's work together to crush them!
Monta...
Let's work hard together!
You're right! I'm not alone!
It's just like Yuki said.
The Devil Bats don't have to lose...
...just because I lost to Kakei.
We're all in this together!
That's right. I even made that promise to Yuki!
We can't lose, no matter what!
We can't give up!
You bet!
Deimon Devil Bats, fight!
Okay!
That's it!
Look!
The Poseidons always invert their safety
on third and short after a run like this.
Huh? I totally didn't get what you said.
You're right!
Which means that those Kyoshin guys
aren't worried about a long pass whatsoever.
We've got to tell them!
But we can't use any more timeouts...
Mamori...
After the run, the safety on third and short is...
No, no, no it won't work.
I don't think gestures like that
are gonna get such a complex strategy across...
Is she dancing to show her support?
- I'm a good dancer too, ya know!
- We'll use max effort!
I don't get what you're tryin' to say, Manajerk!
Hey, guys!
Since we've backed them into a corner,
they'll use their specialty: offense.
In other words, they're definitely going to use Eyeshield.
If the Deimon Devil Bats fail to get their first down,
the Poseidons will take over on offense!
Eyeshield?
You're annoying!
You can't get past Kakei!
Are you going to use the same pattern like idiots who can only learn one thing?
Yeah, it's the same thing.
I'll definitely stop him!
What?!
It's the same play, minus one stupid idiot!
Speaking of idiots!
What a way to be remembered...
Ya-ha!
It's totally open!
Oh no!
Sorry to make you wait, all of my fans!
The long pass was a success!
They're down to just seven yards!
The Devil Bats are about to get a touchdown!
This is bad!
I didn't know they could make passes like that!
Have they incorporated passes into the Wishbone?
Fox-eyes, quit thinking you're safe just because you stopped Eyeshield's run!
Deimon doesn't have any useless weaklings in it!
We're different from those teams
that have one or two genius players that pull everyone along for the ride!
Hiruma!
Now then, what should we do next?
Shoot!
Set, hut, hut!
#80! Stop #80!
- The ball!
- He doesn't have it!
Eyeshield, go for it!
- Go, Eyeshield!
- Eyeshield!
They're all the reason I'm even here!
Touchdown!
It's 18 to 17!
- Hooray!
- Yay!
The Deimon Devil Bats have finally, finally taken the lead!
Kyoshin Poseidon 17 - Deimon Devil Bats 18
Great!
A true ace believes in his friends and they believe in him!
Got that, Peewee?
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Yep!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Deimon's finally taken the lead!
But the Poseidons are finally getting serious!
Hey! The real fight's just starting!
But what's the deal with that Mizumachi guy?
Sena, don't let your guard down till it's all over!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Obsession with Victory! Ya-ha!
The game's not over yet!
We're aiming for the top, after all!
Mizumachi...
Just kidding! Did I sound cool?
Hey, I was pretty mature-sounding, wasn't I?
Sorry, Mizumachi.
But it's just like you said.
Oh?! So you're finally getting serious!
It's scary when Kakei gets serious!