Shinryuji Nagas vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha!
Shinryuji's kickoff flies through the air towards the uncovered corner!
Good kick.
Yeah, they don't want Eyeshield 21 running the return.
That's the best spot to aim for.
It's common sense.
Lions must show no mercy.
Huh?!
What incredible speed...
Amazing!
Eyeshield got there all the way from the other side of the field!
Nothing less from the "Lightspeed Running Back," Eyeshield 21!
R-Riko, you're...
- Go, Eyeshield 21!
Oh no, they're already on him!
No way!
Shinryuji impresses with an overwhelming block.
They're already going at full throttle!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Devils vs. Dragons!
Nice going, Sena!
I can't believe you caught that!
All the way from the other side!
Yeah!
Against Shinryuji!
We're gonna be all right to the max!
Yeah!
Devil Bats, Devil Bats! Devil Bats, Devil Bats!
Nagas! Nagas! Nagas!
Set!
Okay, time for me to make an awesome max ca-
Ikkyu...
I remember, monkey-man.
You said you'd get even with me today.
You could try for the rest of your life, and you'd never win.
We'll see.
Before this game's over, I'll beat you
and keep my promise to Honjo!
Pass, run... What's your plan, Deimon?
Hut!
Run, Butt-Monkey!
I WILL become the best receiver!
Then it's time to put up or shut up!
Wow...
He's keeping up with Monta running backwards...
It looks like a magnet being repelled!
A cornerback that runs the 40 in 4.89 seconds BACKWARDS.
This is why they call Ikkyu Hosokawa a prodigy.
Running backwards is a basic strategy
that lets you react instantly to the receiver's movements.
But how can anyone run backwards that fast?!
He must be the fastest in Japan...
...maybe even the world!
He won't win!
I ran for 2000 kilometers on the Death March!
I'll make a quick juke to the side...
He can't get away...
Monta...
I thought so...
Two feints!
The zig-out pass route...
The juke was a fake?
Hiruma, pass it to the max!
No way!
He had no options!
With no open receivers, the pass play fails!
Nuts!
How did he get in front of me from over there?!
I knew you couldn't do it.
We could play for a hundred years and you wouldn't win once.
Hiruma!
Gimme... gimme another shot at that route.
I'll do it... I'll do it this time!
Sorry.
That one play told me everything I needed to know.
You're not good enough to shake off Ikkyu.
Even if your brain doesn't wanna admit it,
your body understands, Butt-Monkey.
Monta...
That's why...
...we'll use you again.
We'll run a hitch.
It's 2nd and 10,
so we'll run you to an open spot and use a super-short pass!
We can turn that last failure into a setup for this one.
Make sure you catch this one.
Yessir!
Here comes Deimon's next attack!
Set hut!
Here!
They're running a hitch!
A quick short pass!
He'll get it this time!
No one's behind me...
Even if I make a diving catch, if I don't go down,
at this short distance I can turn right around and run!
All right!
Don't slow down! Jump for it, you Butt-Monkey!
I-I-Interception... Shinryuji's ball!
N-No way...
H-He got it...
That dude's unreal...
Only 20 yards to Deimon's goal line!
A dangerous spot for Shinryuji to be on offense!
Finally.
Here comes the evil genius.
Agon... Kongo.
I'm sure you all realize that we can't do anything
until we neutralize Mop-Head over there.
Of course!
And you're gonna take him on, Eyeshield 21!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
And you're gonna take him on, Eyeshield 21!
But, umm, Hiruma...
Don't you think the gap between Sena and Agon's
so wide that he'd be in serious danger?
Are you STILL whining about that, Fatty?!
His speed's the only chance we have, you dingus!
Stop! Stop, Hiruma!
Him getting caught and beaten to a bloody pulp
is better than us keeping him back and having our offense paralyzed!
H-How can he say that so casually...
That's the deal, Peewee.
Bump him outta the way and run!
B-Bump HIM?!
The ball has fallen into the hands of Shinryuji....
And the once-in-a-century natural talent of Agon Kongo!
This is his first time playing from the start in a year,
but will we see him going all-out?!
I have to ATTACK HIM? This is too scary!
Sena's so smart!
He's pretending to back up
so it doesn't look like he'll be running in to bump Agon!
Umm... no, I think he's just really scared...
Come on, Sena!
We're counting on you, Sena!
I'm scared... but I have to do it!
The bump is a straightforward attack that ruins the target's balance.
But my real weapons aren't my arms!
Set, hut!
He's so fast!
He's flying to Agon's left... to his heart!
Okay... this...
...will knock him off balance!
What're you trying to pull?
Agon shakes off his defender and catches the pass!
Don't let him score!
Someone stop Agon!
All right, Lucifer over there figured him out!
Take him down!
A garbage player like you wants to fight a prodigy one on one,
without any of your little tricks?
Please.
He chopped his arm like he did to Sena!
No!
Remember, Mop-Head.
When you have 11 of the same player,
they all do the same thing in the same situation!
Hiruma used the arm that got hit to grab onto Agon's leg!
All right, Hiruma!
You say something, loser?
Shinryuji Nagas 0 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
T-Touchdown...
Shinryuji Nagas 6 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Agon Kongo's ability is overwhelming!
Hiruma!
Are you all right?
I just got cut on a pebble.
That chop...
I've never seen such an aggressive running style...
Something wrong, Agon?
Nah... It's all good.
I changed my mind.
I was just gonna rough them up a little...
But now I think I'll demolish the lot of 'em.
Set, hut!
Deimon runs it this time!
And the brothers are out front for the sweep!
- Smash 'em!
Shoot!
It didn't work?!
He's fast!
He broke through them in a second... I can't dodge!
Deimon's offense fails again!
He's barely even trying...
He-He is...?
We're not even close to the scary part yet.
Hey, what say we stop screwing around
and win this thing already?
Let's use the Dragonfly.
It's too early for the Dragonfly.
We can't reveal our best attack so quickly.
Stop being a such a wiener.
Why can't we just play our best card and crush 'em from the start?
We don't want a 99% chance of winning, we want 100.
I want at least a 20 point lead so that even if they get lucky, they can't win.
Are YOU telling ME how to play?
Fine.
The Dragonfly it is.
Considering how difficult it is to score on Shinryuji to being with,
and with Agon now playing on both offense and defense,
Deimon can't afford to let them increase their lead!
How will Deimon defend this time?
Four and out, guys!
Don't let them get a single point!
We'll stop them!
Huh? Agon moved...
Here comes the Dragonfly!
The Dragonfly?!
Set, hut!
Don't let him pass!
Sack the QB!
Unsui!
Stop, it's a trap!
What?!
They hiked it to Agon instead of Unsui?!
Works for me!
Let's tear those stupid dreads off!
THAT'S the trap, you morons!
Unsui's open!
The Kongo brothers complete the pass!
I have to stop him!
Sena manages to stop Unsui, but it's still an eight-yard gain!
Set, hut!
Get Agon!
N-No!
It's Unsui!
First down, Shinryuji!
From Agon to Unsui, and Unsui to Agon!
The amazing combination of these twin brothers appears invincible!
Their strongest formation, the Dragonfly...
...uses both Kongo brothers as quarterbacks!
We don't even know who's going to throw...
How are we supposed to fight this?
The Dragonfly...
Set, hut!
Stop them, we have to stop them!
Who do we stop, Agon or Unsui?
It doesn't matter, get them both!
Unsui's running it himself!
They can do that too?!
Hiruma saw through them!
A backward pass?
Now it's Agon!
Stop their run, everyone!
Now Unsui's a receiver?!
T-Touchdown...
Unbelievable...
What do we do...?
Ikkyu's backward running, Agon's super-aggressive attacks...
And now the Dragonfly...
They have no weaknesses!
The Shinryuji Nagas... they're too strong!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
The Shinryuji Nagas are crazy!
So this is why they're called invincible and godlike!
They keep scoring... Keep trying, everyone!
Don't give up! Deimon's still got HIM!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The 12th Athlete!
Ya-ha!
You'd better increase your lead,
or we'll blow you outta the water in the second half.
I guarantee out team'll score over 20 points.
- Based on what?!
Keep your shirt on, trash.
We'll have over 30 points by halftime - you'll be finished.
I wonder.
Hiruma's trying to get under Agon's skin again,
like he did with that leg tackle earlier.
He's trying to make him play harder and use up his energy.
Makes sense... Maybe that's our way to victory.
We walked 2000 kilometers on the Death March
instead of running around chasing skirts like him.
That's right, we're better than some playboy!
Yeah! All HE did was hook up with a bunch of girls!
I think their jealousy's making them stronger.
Guys are so dumb...