- Fire!
- Ya-ha!
I'll win!
I'll beat Riku!
Touchdown!
Just one minute left to play!
Eyeshield somehow overcomes Kaitani's Rodeo Drive
and scores an amazing touchdown!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 32
Deimon is only three points behind!
U-Unbelievable!
This is a game for the ages!
Is something wrong, Kumabukuro?
I'm just so moved...
They're both just amazing!
Talk about showing what you're made of...
Lightspeed legs...
The most frightening thing about Eyeshield 21
is that he's still a rookie.
And yet he still improves by leaps and bounds in every game.
It's impossible to gage the full depth of his potential.
A rookie?
Didn't he play for a Notre Dame affiliate middle school?
Eyeshield! Eyeshield!
Wow... I beat Riku...
Riku...
Riku!
Sena...
Riku?
You won that round, fair and square.
But...
I haven't lost yet.
Sena, the real winner of our battle...
...is the one whose team wins this game!
He's right.
I haven't truly beaten Riku, not yet.
Like he said...
Whoever wins the game wins our battle!
We'll do it!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Fateful Kick.
Y'all really hamstrung me.
When you start getting hopeful, you end up disappointed.
Hey, I warned you,
Eyeshield was gonna win.
I guess you were right.
Which must mean you're the better quarterback, too.
Going back to the humble act already?
The better QB is the one who wins the game.
Either way works for me.
This next play's gonna decide it.
Kinda funny, since it's gonna be totally primitive - no tactics, no tricks.
Couldn't have said it better myself.
Deimon will kick for the extra point.
Ya-ha!
And it's really, really wide!
Deimon's kick is no good!
We've seen their lack of a kicker hurt them many times before.
Yep... He just boots it.
I knew it wouldn't go in.
How come we didn't go for two?
Even if we made it, that's only two points.
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 32
That's not enough to win.
There's no point in wasted effort.
The one point that kick would've gotten us never mattered.
But we can come back if we score another touchdown.
We've got 60 seconds left.
The next play's gonna be the last one...
it'll be nothing more than a primitive brawl.
A primitive...
...brawl?
Exactly 60 seconds to go!
The moment Seibu takes possession of the ball, they win!
How can this be?!
That's right.
Once you're on offense,
you have up to 25 seconds to start a play.
25 times 3 is 75.
They'll use every second to run the clock to zero.
If Seibu gets the ball, they won't have to do a thing to win.
B-But we've gotta kick off to Seibu, don't we?
Then what to we do?!
There's no way to win!
That's why it's gonna be a brawl!
We'll do an onside kick.
Onside kick?
Uhh...
It's a special type of kickoff.
A special type?
For a regular kickoff,
you try to send it as deep into the opponent's side as you can.
In contrast, an onside kick is
when you try to keep it as close to your own side as possible.
Isn't it better to just bash it all the way to the enemy goal line?
You dumb butt-monkey.
It doesn't matter how far we boot it, once Seibu caught it, we'd lose.
But if we can grab the ball instead...
We can go back on offense and get a touchdown!
That's the theory.
We'll charge straight into the other team,
there'll be a huge scramble for the ball,
and we'll steal it back.
No plans, no tricks!
Whoever gets the ball wins!
No problem!
All 22 guys charge for the ball,
and whoever knocks the opponent away wins!
All right!
I'll use every move I have as a catching expert to grab the ball
and run it in for a touchdown!
No one expects anything outta your legs.
If you get the ball, hand it off to Eyeshield.
Scoring the touchdown is your job, Eyeshield.
Right!
Now! The rest of you can forget about trying anything fancy.
Just catch the freakin' ball.
Yeah!
No one beats me in a primate brawl!
No, not a primate brawl, a "primitive" brawl.
Seibu already knows what we're gonna do.
They'll be sending in all their big guns.
You guys ready?
-Yeah!
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
C'mon, one minute left!
Give 'em everything you got!
We're pioneers on the unsettled field!
Wild and tough!
And the game begins again!
This could be the last play!
Will it be Seibu or Deimon who comes away with the ball?!
Seibu's lineup isn't about offense or defense now.
They're sending in their all-stars.
Of course.
This onside kick's gonna decide the game!
Bang-bang 'em, team! Bang-bang!
Sena, you're really awesome.
You deserve to be called Deimon's running ace.
However...
I'm our catching ace.
I'll get the ball.
In the name of my idol, Honjo,
I'll beat Tetsuma!
Monta...
I know you can do it.
Now let's put Seibu away!
Hiruma...
Kurita...
35-32.
Only a three point difference!
Musashi, we won't lose.
Please... win!
The game has reached its climax!
The final...
...battle.
Here I come!
- Bring it on.
You're dead meat!
Watch me, Honjo.
I'll catch this if it kills me.
It's all come down to this last play.
We're all going to the Christmas Bowl, together!
He turned the laces in!
Pretty ironic that it's all coming down to a kick...
Musashi...
The fateful kick...
Ya-ha!
...goes flying!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Give us some catching tips!
The hint is "secrecy!"
When playing receiver,
it's important to avoid revealing the route you're running to your opponent
Use your eyes to trick the enemy!
Ya-ha.
Ya-ha!
It goes flying!
An onside kick!
Get it, Tetsuma!
He kicked it on the laces to make the ball bounce oddly!
That's it! Way to go!
- I got it!
Not happening!
Riku!
Yes!
I won't let you!
I can't move!
That's it, Tetsuma!
No one beats me at catching!
Monta!
They both...
No, they-
Monta and Tetsuma battle it out in midair!
Whoever gets the ball goes to the championships!
You'll have to kill me to take it away!
Butt-monkey!
Tetsuma!
His fingers...
...are on the laces!
It's a little easier if you hold it on the laces.
He went for the laces! How?!
In the middle of that craziness?! It's impossible!
He got it!
He did it!
He really did it!
Sena!
Monta!
Everyone up!
Get up and block!
Open a path!
Monta got the ball to me!
Now if I can just score a touchdown...
We'll win! We can still go to the Christmas Bowl!
Let's finish this, Riku!
Huh?
Why's he just...
W-What...?
What's going on?
Dead ball! Seibu's ball!
W...Why...?
Why? I'm the one who took it!
While both players were holding the ball,
Tetsuma touched the ground first.
Therefore, the ball goes to the receiving team, Seibu.
The ball was down and the play was over at that spot.
Seibu is now on offense!
Game over!
Advancing to the finals of the Tokyo conference
of the national high school football tournament
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 32
with a score of 35-32, it's the Seibu Wild Gunmen!
Too close... Too close...
We made more touchdowns than them...
If we'd just scored the extra points...
Three points... We lost on kicks...
Musashi!
It's... over?
All...
...over...
You came really close, Deimon.
One point,
or one hundred,
a loss is a loss.
Is this how it ends?!
Arrrgh!
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
Our chance at the Christmas Bowl...
...is gone...
Are you nuts...?
I had it...
Monta?
I had... the ball...
We didn't lose, we won!
We won!
I promised Honjo that I'd become the greatest catcher ever!
The game isn't over until both teams line up and bow.
Shut your pie hole!
It's not over!
We're going to the Christmas Bowl!
I won't let it end here!
I'm not gonna let some stupid blind ref take that away from us!
Go back and read the freaking rule book!
It's in there!
I got the ball!
Get your head out of your butt, you idiot!
Monta!
Stop!
You lousy-
Have you lost your mind, Tetsuma?!
Make sure you thank Tetsuma later.
Who told you to do that?!
Try to understand, Coach.
Monta...
I dunno why he saved us,
but thanks to him, we dodged a big bullet.
Wait, what?
What's that supposed to mean?
Strictly speaking, we've got one final shot.
The losers' bracket!
- Losers'...
- ...bracket?!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Wait, we lost the quarter finals, but we've still got one last chance?!
You mean we've still got a shot at the Christmas Bowl?!
Yeah, so you'd better not blow it!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Pact Between Rivals! Ya-ha!
We'll be playing Seibu in the finals...
Not until we beat Bando in the semi-finals.
Our most dangerous opponent is unpreparedness.
We can't afford to give them any openings.
You heard him, Sakuraba.
Make sure you tie your shoes tight!
Forget my shoes, Otawara...
For the love of God, pull up your pants!
Talk about unpreparedness.