Hey, they announced where the Kanto Tournament will be held!
It's gonna be at the Enoshima Football Field!
Isn't Enoshima... right near Shinryuji High?
Yep.
We've just gotta win our first game in the Kanto Tournament!
Ouch!
Don't get so stressed out over it!
B-But...
I've heard that Enoshima Field's
got a great stadium that's state of the art.
There's also a nice breeze since it's near the ocean.
If that's the case, let's scope it out to the max!
Yay!
I can see it!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Demon God Agon Kongo!
Where are you going, Agon?
Everyone's practicing!
How lame.
Agon, someone just called asking for an interview!
I've told you to turn those guys down.
They're annoying.
Tell 'em I caught a cold or somethin'.
But it's a high school girl!
Tell her to send me a picture...
...of her cute face.
Hey! Not gonna apologize after ramming into me?!
We're talking to you, Dreads!
I'm drenched in their blood!
Now I've gotta change into our lame school uniform. Man!
Y-You said that you'd give me an interview
if we did it at a local restaurant...
I-It's said that a genius like you
only comes around once a century, Agon.
T-T-Thank you for coming out here to see me!
No biggie! It's my pleasure, really.
Thank you so much!
I'm interviewing all eight teams participating
in the Kanto Tournament for Football Monthly and-
Forget about that.
I want to hear all about you first.
Oh, so you're Mr. Kumabukuro's daughter!
I don't really take after him.
B-But I realized that I wanted to follow in his footsteps
after helping him out some.
You're so cute, I just know you'll make a good reporter.
No, I'm not all that cute.
Does being cute even go along with being a good reporter?
Oops.
Made the wrong approach.
So she wants me to complement her talent...
Well, your positive attitude's so cute.
And you seem to have a real knack at interviews.
R-Really?!
Actually, I went all-out and invited
someone else to the interview, too!
I thought it'd be interesting to interview two teams at once.
M-Man!
Wait! Where are-?
I'm leaving.
Why?
It's a waste of time if we're not alone.
H-Hey, wait, Agon!
Oh, he's here!
Hello! Oh, what should I do?!
It's been a while since I saw you last.
Hey! Long time no see, loser!
Interesting...
Sit down, Dread Head!
Which means, Hiruma and Agon actually....
I mean, so, were the two of you... friends?
Huh?! Friends? With this loser?
He's just too weak for a title like that!
I just used him as an underling!
We used each other.
Since Dread head here's so violent,
filling my book of threats was a piece of cake.
Darn it! Don't let Agon escape!
Dread head, they went to the right.
Darn it! Where'd he go?!
Curse you!
A loser's a loser, no matter how many flock together.
They aren't worth the air they breathe.
That all depends on how you use them.
Oh, no! I may just be a part-time journalist,
but I can't back down now!
So then...
I'm asking all six teams in the Kanto Tournament
the same questions as part of my
"Sudden Questions by a High School Reporter" article.
First give me your name,
your team's name and your strong points.
Taiga Kamiya, Misaki Wolves.
I bet you can tell what my strong point is!
It's my long legs! My legs!
Seijuro Shin, Ojo White Knights.
I'm not a good enough player to disclose my personal strengths.
Kiminari Harao, Taiyo Sphinx.
My strong points...
I suppose that would be my ability to calmly search for a receiver.
Maruko, Hakushu Dinosaurs.
Well...
I'm afraid I can't do something as silly
as disclosing information about myself like that.
Ganjo Iwashige, Sado Strong Golems.
It's my rock-hard body!
Seibu Wild Gunmen.
People call me the Kid.
As for strong points... I guess that I don't dream too big....
Mine is that I never lose!
Mine is that I always win!
What's with these two?!
S-So then, who are you keeping your eyes on?
Me!
No dice?
Then Agon, I guess, since he won last year.
But I'm still stronger!
Eyeshield 21, Sena Kobayakawa.
Agon Kongo and Ikkyu Hosokawa.
Agon, Shin, Kid...
Whew! There's just too many to count!
Isn't it obvious?! Banba!
Seijuro Shin... and then... Sena, I guess.
Someone to look out for? No one...
Oh, Yoichi Hiruma!
But not in the same way you're thinking.
I can't believe a worthless loser like you started a football team!
What a joke.
And then you went into football, too.
This isn't good!
I've gotta keep the questions rolling!
S-So then, next question!
Why did you start playing American football?
Because I get to snap people in half!
Crushing worthless trash
with my great talent is just way too much fun.
A-And why are you playing football, Hiruma?
Because it's fun.
Depending how you play your cards,
even "trash" can defeat geniuses.
I get a real kick outta that.
Let's see, so then,
have you done any special training for the tournament?
Training? Haven't bothered!
I've got a secret weapon for Shinryuji.
Our plays will be unlike anything you've seen before.
Hope you're ready for us, Dread Head!
W-Well then, here's my last question.
What do you think is the most
important quality for a football player?
Talent and I mean raw talent.
Speed, technique, and...
...power!
Anyone lacking talent's just in the way.
Well, I suppose someone with Ikkyu's abilities
can be somewhat useful.
11 of me, now that'd make a dream team!
A team with 11 of the same person!
Talk about easy to crush!
I can see how much you hate mediocre players.
So you're just going to love the show
HE'S going to put on for you.
See here, you loser!
A thousand losers can't take down a genius!
And I'm going to prove it to you in this next game!
A team that relies on some speedy pipsqueak,
like Eyeshield 21, annoys me to high heavens!
You can keep playing with your powerless shrimp
and worthless punks until you keel over!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
Wow, this sea breeze feels great!
So this is the Kanto Tournament's stadium.
Yep.
Let's win, Monta!
Yeah!
They both seem so strong and reliable.
Oh, that smells good!
I'm hungry...
Let's get something to eat before we head back to Deimon.
Yeah, I'm just starting to get hungry, too.
Yeah, nice idea!
Gramps, I want fried squid!
Sea snail, clam, squid and octopus, please!
Geez! That's everything he's got!
Enoshima Shrine
I've got something I need to take care of.
I'll meet you at Enoshima Station, okay?
Huh? Where are you going, Mamori?
It's a secret!
See ya later!
Please keep everyone safe during the game.
And help them win their first game in the Kanto Tournament.
Same goes for the next game and the next!
Just help them make it to the Christmas Bowl!
You have to help them win!
Some charms and then... good luck fortunes please!
Good luck, good luck, good luck!
Bad luck
Bad luck?!
One more fortune please!
This stinks.
I bought three fortunes and they all said "Bad Luck" on them!
This doesn't really mean anything!
I just know that Deimon's gonna win! Yep!
Oh, no! It's so late!
Man, Mamo sure is late.
Yeah, I wonder what's keeping her...
I'm gonna go look for her.
You two stay here just in case we miss each other, okay?
Yeah!
Take care!
That jerk!
The loser!
It sure is late...
I wonder if they're waiting for me!
She's kinda cute.
Hey, you have a sec?
Do you know where Enoshima Football Field is?
Huh? You're from Shinryuji...
Oh, so you know who I am!
He seems kinda different from before.
But...
And you are...?
I-I'm the Deimon Devil Bats' team manager...
Oh, Deimon, huh?
I see! I thought I'd seen you somewhere before!
So that's it!
Sorry for forgetting where we met...
I-It's fine.
So, um, Enoshima Field's straight ahead.
Well, I've gotta-
C'mon, show me how to get there! C'mon!
It'd make me so happy!
N-No, I've got to...
Oh, please.
S-Stop it...
Get away from Mamori!
Sena!
You're that powerless shrimp...
I'm busy with this lady, so scram!
Stop bugging her!
You punk...
You're dead.
Don't hurt Sena!
Mamori...?
He vanished?!
I told you to butt out.
You little...
Everyone on your team drives me nuts!
There's blood on that!
Sena!
Mamo!
Monta, Suzuna...
What's going on?!
Annoying pests!
What's this strange feeling?
Mamo, are you okay?
Wasn't that Agon? What was going on?
I've met a lot of scary people in the past,
but Agon Kongo is different.
He terrifies me....
He isn't a punk...
He's pure...
...evil.
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
What's that?!
Hiruma, Musashi and even Kurita
were originally going to go to Shinryuji High?!
Yeah, and it's all my fault we didn't.
What on earth happened?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Shinryuji is the Enemy!
Na-ga!
Surprise Interview!
So, what type of girl do you like?
A kind, obedient girl.
A girl who takes pride in working hard for the team.
That's not your type, that's your manager.
Elegance above all else.
I have to love her.
Big boobs!
I don't really have a "type..."
I guess I'd like a girl I could open up my heart to.
A babe. Put the hounds in the kennel.
Someone useful.
That's your manager, you know!