Shinryuji Nagas vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha!
Kick a field goal?
Forget the whole "strategy" thing.
Just let me get another touchdown
and close the lid on the garbage gang over there.
We're kicking BECAUSE we believe in you.
Shinryuji Nagas 32 - Deimon Devil Bats 14
Shinryuji's up 18 points.
If we take the guaranteed three points from a field goal
and increase that to 21, then we've guaranteed our victory.
I guess finishing them off
with such a fail-safe plan's the cruelest option, in a way.
Shinryuji's kick is good.
Shinryuji Nagas 32 - Deimon Devil Bats 14
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 14
They're now up by 21 points.
Sena, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine... Monta...
As long as there's still a 1% chance we can win...
...I won't quit!
I know another guy who gets really stubborn in situations like this.
- Deimon, Deimon, Deimon!
The Deimon Devil Bats mount a desperate attack!
Monta is surrounded!
Leave Raimon to Ikkyu!
Close up the center!
Ya-ha!
The pass is complete!
Deimon gets the first down!
This changes our planned pass defense for Deimon...
We may have to start over from scratch.
Just having Yukimitsu out on the field...
...completely changes their play patterns.
Taki and his flexibility for short passes in crowded spots...
At moderate distances,
Yukimitsu's poor athletic ability is offset by his excellent judgment.
And for long bombs, their ace receiver, Raimon.
They've only got one more target,
but they've exponentially increased their offensive power.
Kurita charging up the middle,
Eyeshield's super speed along the sides,
and Musashi's explosive kicks...
Individually, they're all lacking, and yet...
...one could argue that Deimon...
...has the strongest offense in Kanto.
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Fighting to be Number One.
Their defense changed formation...
Guess you're no match for me after all, monkey-boy.
Crap!
How can this be?!
Incomplete!
What incredible organization,
changing strategies in an instant!
This is what's carried the Shinryuji Nagas
to nine straight championships!
We advanced the ball so far...
Sena...Yuki... They're all..
They're all worn down and they're still fighting...
What's wrong with me?!
But what can I do...
...against a natural like Ikkyu Hosokawa?
How... how do I...
Hiruma.
I have an idea to turn this around.
It's our only option.
What's the plan, Butt-Monkey?
You toss a long bomb,
like this, VOOM!
And I'll catch it, BAM!
Then POW, touchdown!
BOOM!
Everyone looks so... sad...
Don't get sucked in, Suzuna...
You're up against Ikkyu, man.
How're you gonna catch a long bomb
against a guy that runs faster and jumps higher than you?
I... How should I know?!
But... if I don't beat Ikkyu,
we won't get to be in the Christmas Bowl!
I'll win, no matter what!
That's all I've got, I don't have a good reason!
You're serious, huh, Butt-Monkey?
I don't mind guys who talk a big game,
but now you've gotta come through!
You'll be the only receiver.
This'll be a huge 35-yard touchdown pass.
You gotta overtake Ikkyu, Butt-Monkey!
Okay!
We're low on time, if we don't score on this drive...
Do something, guys!
Set, hut!
Hiruma's backing up...
That can only mean...
a long, high pass,
that leaves everything up to luck and the heavens!
A last-ditch prayer to God!
The Hail Mary pass!
Please!
Dear God, PLEASE put the ball in Monta's hands!
God can't help you now!
Does he really think you can outrun me?
Monta...
Him? PRAY?
You didn't know?
Devil's don't ask God for favors.
Ya...
HA!
What?!
It's not a high pass!
It's not a Hail Mary?
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
Eyeshield 21!
Max Catch!
Ya...
HA!
This...
This is a super-LOW pass
that will slip right below the midair battlefield,
a Hail Devil pass!
A battle of pure catching skill!
Will Monta score a touchdown,
or will Ikkyu deliver the final blow?!
It all hinges on this one pass!
Nice max pass!
It'll be close, but I got it!
Too bad...
If it's close enough for you to get to it,
it means the top aerial battler can, too!
Take out the prodigy with your unbeatable catches!
Monta!
If you don't get this, it's over!
Catch it!
Go!
Ikkyu's got the advantage.
Monta has to make the catch,
but if Ikkyu even gets a finger on it, he'll block the pass!
Ikkyu touches the ball first!
Knock it away, Ikkyu!
Ikkyu...
My job's not to win in the air, it's to catch the ball!
I'll catch it no matter how hard you knock it away!
'Fraid not.
Sorry!
He intercepted it?!
You came close.
Against anyone else, you probably would've won.
But I've got more catching talent!
Catching... talent?
I never even felt like I had any talent.
At first I couldn't even tell how far away they were...
Or catch a single fly ball...
But I... bit by bit, I got it.
I learned to keep my eye on the ball, even if I was scared...
To match the rhythms of my body and the ball's movement...
The ball's... movement...
When did he...?
How'd his hand get up here?!
The ball!
The ball...
...is...
...mine!
How'd he get his hand on the laces?!
Max Catch!
Touchdown!
Monta, Taro Raimon, knocks Ikkyu Hosokawa aside!
The long pass is complete!
He really beat...
Kanto's strongest cornerback...
He beat Ikkyu!
Way to go, Mon-Mon!
That was awesome, Monta!
I mean, it was... well...
Awesome!
No, it was AWESOME!
AWESOME!
Would you guys build your vocabulary?!
Anyway, that was totally awesome!
You always say it... you won't lose to anyone when it comes to catching.
When I met him in the hospital,
he was just another rookie...
Ikkyu's abilities are superior in every other way...
But at catching, and only catching...
He's the best in Kanto, even if he doesn't realize it yet.
It's 35-21, the Deimon Devil Bats are closing in!
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 21
Wait, that means...
If we score two touchdowns...
T-Tie!
No way!
Wow!
We can do it! Two more to go!
It was just one time.
They just made a single pass.
Let's pay them back.
One... time?
You get to be number one by beating every challenger else every time.
I'll never forgive myself.
Taro Raimon.
Monta's fine...
You won't catch another one of those ridiculous passes.
Don't forget,
I'm number one when it comes to catching.
Yeah, perhaps now you are.
But before these last eight minutes are over,
I'll surpass you and take that title for myself.
Ikkyu, the best cornerback in Kanto,
acknowledged Monta as a rival!
Complete!
The Shinryuji Nagas get three yards!
Shoot, I couldn't block it!
You're doing great, Monta!
You held a pass to Ikkyu to only three yards!
They've learned things get dangerous
when you're defending Ikkyu.
Their passes will keep getting shorter.
Right!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Monta's changed the flow of the whole game with one catch!
We can do this...
If we can just stop this drive, we have a shot!
I wanna crush these scumbags more than anyone else...
These pieces of garbage, with their little dreams...
Hut!
Agon's running it!
Tackle him, Peewee!
I'll stop you!
It's over.
Take a look at this, runt.
Don't tell me-
Amazing!
Agon whips out a Devil Bat Ghost!
Agon steals Eyeshield 21's signature move
and runs for 20 yards with the Devil Bat Ghost!
Sena worked so hard...
He practiced for 2000 kilometers... and Agon just...
- 20 yards?!
- We're in deep snot!
No...
we've got a much bigger problem on our hands.
Deimon takes their third and final timeout!
It's too much.
You need to spend some time on the bench.
If you don't...
you might never be able to run again.
N-No way!
You're playing.
Prepare yourself, Peewee.
Sit down!
What's your problem, you old geezer?
My stupid dad...
He knew he was pushing his body beyond its limits...
...and now he's past the point of no return.
I won't...
I won't stand by and watch it happen again.
Hiruma!
I'll stop this even if I need to knock you out myself!
We can't ignore Agon.
We can't bench him!
Go ahead and deck me if it'll make you feel better.
Nothing's more important than victory.
You're supposed to be the leader!
You've got no right to say things like that.
If Sena permanently injures his legs...
I'll never forgive you, for the rest of my life!
Set...
I'll give you credit for coming back out here
knowing you're about to get evaporated.
Even though you couldn't catch up with me after I nailed you last time.
Hut!
Taking a big risk, are we Deimon?
You had #52 abandon his post and come after me.
But Yamabushi will easily block him.
Meaning #52's area will be wide open!
Ikkyu blows past Monta,
can me make a diving catch in the wide open backfield?
*missing*
Impossible!
Who? Who could be running up the middle now?!
No, it doesn't matter, I've got the timing...
"Tranquil Reflections"
If I throw it with at full power, Ikkyu's got it.
I can make the-
What?!
Eyeshield 21 runs straight up the middle and intercepts!
Where'd Eyeshield come from...?
He didn't go after Agon...?
What a guy.
They left Agon undefended!
They completely ignored their prodigy!
That's WHY we ignored him.
And why you made me act like such a dork...
You deserved that punch.
You stinkin' scum!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Run, Sena!
You've gotta get past Agon this time!
But he's so fast... He's already on me!
That's not just a football!
Protect it with your life!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Will of a Warrior!
Ya-ha!
Eyeshield 21 runs straight up the middle and intercepts!
You stinkin' scum!
I've got a bad feeling about this...
I can feel a cold sweat running down my back.
Dobie...
Suzuna... let's just... keep quiet.