I'm gonna work twice as hard until Musashi comes back!
Wow, everyone's doing awesome!
I'll say!
They're all fired up for the Bando Spiders game!
Yeah!
There's a lot on the line,
we either go to the Kanto Tournament or our season ends.
I'll keep working too...
Good!
That's the spirit, Sena!
They're counting on us too,
let's not let them down!
We managers have plenty of responsibility too, after all.
Hey, manager!
Coming!
I thought she'd figured out I was Eyeshield...
How much longer are you gonna keep that a secret from Mamo?
Well, if I told her, she'd just get worried.
I think this is better...
Come on, Manajerk!
Quit your bellyaching
and go pick up the helmets and cleats!
Y-Yes!
Get the lead out!
Y-Yes, sir!
Wait, I'll help!
Careful of all the traffic!
Make sure you stay on the sidewalk...
Huh...? Sena...?
Sena, you're too fast!
We can't lose...
We'll beat Bando no matter what!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The True 21.
Excuse me!
Yo!
Hello.
Here ya go.
Hey, careful.
I got it...
- Ow...
- Yeesh...
S-Sorry...
This is...
...an eye shield?
So hyper.
H-Hey, you're-
Akaba from the Bando Spiders...
Last year's Tokyo MVP!
Those are Deimon helmets...
So you two are...
I'm a manager.
Cheerleader!
I'm afraid the field will be jamming to OUR beat.
Jamming?
Beat?
That reminds me,
Deimon has a player calling himself "Eyeshield," doesn't it?
You didn't know?
He's like, super famous!
Suzuna!
But he is.
Intriguing.
Akaba wears an eye shield too?
Maybe...
...the Eyeshield 21 Kakei met in America...
The real Eyeshield 21...
It couldn't be-
Wake up, Peewee!
Um...
- Hiruma-
- Okay!
Next play!
A Peewee and Butt-Monkey combo run!
Yessir!
Max teamwork!
Peewee.
You were saying?
Oh, uh... Nothing.
Are we gonna show 'em what Bando can do?
- Yeah!
Are we gonna face 'em down?
- YEAH!
That's it!
Very smart!
Go for the touchdown!
Yes!
What's up with the eye shield?
It ain't smart.
Aesthetics.
Aesthetics...?!
If I'm going to call myself the strongest,
I need to wear that eye shield.
Huh? Say what?
No solos!
Hold it!
Can't you two agree on anything?
Give it a rest, okay?
I'm just saying, it's not smart.
We march to the beat of different drummers.
There aren't any drummers in football.
All sports have their own rhythm.
Athletics is about notes coming together to compose a score.
That makes zero sense!
Enough already.
Look, you two are the keys to us winning.
Try to get along!
Yoichi Hiruma, the quarterback.
He's the brains behind Deimon.
Textbook game plans won't work on him.
As a fellow play-caller,
what do you think, Akaba?
He's interesting.
His results always seem miraculous,
but they're actually meticulously planned out.
As a musician, he's simultaneously bold and cautions.
Enough with the music stuff!
And next...
The mysterious unknown running back
who runs at the speed of light
and scores most of Deimon's points,
Eyeshield 21!
If he's calling himself Eyeshield 21
with such an amateurish playing style...
I'll rob him of his title!
See ya.
Let's go get soba or something.
Good call.
Bye bye, see you tomorrow!
Maybe Akaba really is the true Eyeshield 21...
What's the matter, Sena?
Something got you down, Peewee?
Akaba, the real Eyeshield 21?
It's not out of the question.
I-I knew it!
Knock it off!
Are you still obsessing over the whole "fake" thing?
"Eyeshield 21"
isn't just a single person's nickname.
Huh?
W-What do you mean?
He's a legend born from the famous Notre Dame...
A once-in-a-generation ace runner is given the number.
THAT is Eyeshield 21.
In other words,
the title of the greatest high school football player.
W-Whoa...
So you gave me that incredibly scary nickname on purpose?
It's just a name,
anyone could call themselves that if they want.
So quit worrying about it!
Wait, so...
...if Akaba's the real thing...
I've just been borrowing his name.
Look,
let's just ask Kakei and figure this out once and for all.
Huh?
Kakei's the only one who ever met the real Eyeshield.
If we're lucky,
he might even give us some insider info on him!
Sena!
Mon-Mon!
What are you two doing down there?
Oh ho, is this a private meeting?
N-No, it's nothing at all!
See, we were just about to go visit the Poseidons
and see if they had any tips that could help us beat Bando,
Mamori.
The Poseidons?
They know about Bando?
Cool, let us come!
You come too, Mamo!
Okay!
Let's roll!
That settles that, I guess.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to steal the ball from behind!
The hint is "punch!"
When you want to steal the ball from behind,
knock the ball away with a hard punch.
Smack 'em good!
Ya-ha!
Kakei's off at the nearby hot springs.
I see...
Ooh, hot springs?
- We gotta go, Mamo!
- W-Wha?
Thank you so much.
Wait up, Deimon!
Listen up.
Last time, the Poseidons fought hard, but we lost.
But Kakei and Mizumachi will be back next year.
Those two are uper-say ong-stray, you dig?
They'll get you next year!
This year, though, win it for us!
Make it to the Kanto Tournament!
Mizumachi...
easily nails the turn around!
Good thing we're the only ones here...
And he only kicked Ohira,
which is fine by me.
It's not fine!
Mizumachi will now swim the 800 meter!
He's as energetic as ever.
You guys...
Deimon?
- Deimon?
Whattup?
S-Splash...
We always come here to sweat things out after practice.
You have to be fully recovered for the next day.
Wish we had something like this near us.
Oh, wow!
Huh?
That's Suzuna...
Yours are so big, Mamo!
Mine are so small... See?
I'm like a little girl...
Wanna feel?
C'mon, go for it!
N-No, that's okay...
Wow, so soft!
Holy smokes, I've never seen anyone ACTUALLY
get a nosebleed from being worked up!
Your towel's just so big and soft, Mamo!
I love it!
Huh? What was that noise?
Y-You okay?
I'm still happy...
Akaba Hayato of the Bando Spiders?
Do you think the Eyeshield that you met in America
might be Akaba?
Eyeshield 21...
If I hadn't met him,
I wouldn't be who I am today.
He's finally here!
The superstar from the far east!
The Japanese miracle who became the MVP of Notre Dame!
Eyeshield 21!
He's Japanese?
I'll stop you...
I'll stop you Eyeshield!
Touchdown!
Crap!
Was I just too late?
I'll get you next time,
Eyeshield 21!
From what I've heard,
he's back in Japan now.
A player of his caliber
will definitely be in the national tournament.
Then it must be Akaba-
Hayato Akaba earned last year's Tokyo MVP for being the best lead blocker.
Lead blocker?
He runs ahead of his runner at top speed
and knocks down any opponents in the way.
The position of lead blockers are especially important during the kickoff.
But there's more to Akaba than that.
Look at this cute strap, Mamo.
Do you think Sena would like this shirt?
It might be too big...
Sena?
Yeah, I think it would suit him.
Uhh... huh...
He doesn't really care about his appearance,
if I left him alone he'd wear the same things all the time.
Hey, Mamo...
I don't think Sena's as immature as you think he is...
I mean, Sena's...
I want to tell Mamori myself.
Just wait for him, he'll show you... Please.
Suzuna?
Ooh, this one's adorable!
But so's this one!
Yep, he's Bando's best weapon.
Freakin' Vampiro... He's gonna be a pain.
As a play-caller,
Akaba is nothing less than a master conductor.
He's got a fantastic sense for coaching.
Finished. Now...
What's the meaning of this?!
Not on my watch!
Wha- Kakei, we can't just ignore this!
I can't refute or affirm anything.
But with his physique, speed, technique...
There's a strong possibility he could be the Eyeshield 21 I knew.
Wow, you didn't even flinch!
So Eyeshield 21 is Akaba...
Why didn't I realize it?
Akaba, the real Eyeshield 21...
However...
The issue at hand isn't whether he's the real one or not.
Huh?
Right?
If you lose this game, you're eliminated.
For Deimon to beat Bando,
you'll have to beat Akaba.
As DEIMON'S Eyeshield.
You knew?
You beat me.
With or without your eye shield,
I respect you as a capable athlete.
If Akaba IS the real thing,
you'll have to surpass him too!
Surpass... the real thing...
What was that for?
I was gonna use those as a pommel horse!
Huh? Guess I had the wrong idea...
Nothing like some light sweet coffee after a soak, huh?
We'll see you later Mamori, Suzuna!
Y-Yo, wait up, Sena!
When did Sena get so... fast?
Yes... Kakei and Hiruma are absolutely right.
This has nothing to do with who's "real" and who's "fake."
I have to surpass Akaba,
with everything I've got!
One on one? With me?
There's something I want to confirm.
Suit yourself.
Come on!
If you happen to run into Deimon's Eyeshield 21,
tell him I said,
"If Eyeshield 21 is the title of the best player in the high school football world..."
"Then I'M the only one suited to carry that name."
Be careful...
...Deimon Eyeshield.
This strength... he has to be...
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
We've got a critical practice for the Bando game,
where the heck is Sena?!
Does Mamori have him trapped again?
What's more important,
managerial duties or practice?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: They're Waiting for Me! Ya-ha!
Man oh man...
Who knew we had a hot spring so close by?
Make room for me, everyone!
Sorry... the water's all gone...