Keep going!
Everyone's pumped up because the Bando game is coming...
We've gotta work extra hard too!
Right, Sena?
Sena?
Geez, Sena's always running off...
Sena...?
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
They're Waiting for Me.
Everyone's working their tail off,
you need to be a responsible manager!
Right... I know, but...
I guess you still can't handle this kind of thing
without me to help you.
You'll be okay.
You just need to put your mind to it.
Be confident!
Put my mind to it...
Come on, I'm Eyeshield 21...
Gotta get changed before Mamori gets here.
There you are, Sena!
Mamori?!
Okay, let's organize the data on Bando!
S-Sure...
Okay...
I'll sort out the vital info,
you take notes.
Oh, sure.
Oh boy...
This is why I keep saying you should tell Mamo
that you're Eyeshield 21...
Mamori has Sena trapped?
Yeah, she's making him do manager stuff.
Then Sena won't be able to practice...
The Bando game's right around the corner...
Cut me some slack...
Being a manager's way more exhausting than practice.
I didn't even get to practice for a minute today.
I have to do something!
Sena got caught AGAIN?!
Uh-huh...
Not again?!
I'm home...
Oof...
I'm pooped.
How long are you gonna keep this a secret from Mamo?
Easy for you to say...
She's still concerned about me all the time...
If she knew I was Eyeshield 21...
Sena! Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
Hiruma, how dare you make Sena a running back,
it's too dangerous!
He quits as of this minute!
I doubt it'd be like that, but...
I wonder if Mamori's here already...
Yup.
Sena? Good morning.
G-Good morning, Mamori.
Sena...
It's been fun, hasn't it?
Oh, it's that picture.
Football is such a rough sport...
Sometimes I think about trying to make you quit...
Mamori...?
But I'm glad we joined the team.
We've made lots of friends.
You're a valuable member of the Devil Bats now.
Keep being the best manager you can be.
I-I will.
Manager...
Riku?
Your championship game against Ojo's almost here.
Yeah...
That monster Seijuro Shin will be gunning for me.
You and Shin are incredible people.
Not just you two... Akaba, as well.
Everyone amazes me.
But there are even more of them out there.
I want to play against them, too.
If that's true,
then climb higher, Sena.
To the Kanto Tournament, where the greatest compete!
Where the greatest compete...
Beat Akaba, beat Bando, and meet me there.
I'll see you later.
At the Kanto Tournament!
There's PLENTY of incredible players out there.
And you're one of them, Sena.
We can't lose.
I've gotta...
...keep pushing!
Sena, are you okay?!
Your mom said you have a fever!
Mamori...
I'm sorry, Sena...
I must have been overworking you.
No, you didn't-
Just rest up, Sena.
We'll all take good notes at the championship match.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What's the most important quality
for Eyeshield 21's position, running back?
It's all about "speed!"
A running back needs the speed
to get past anyone and everyone!
Blaze through the other team!
Ya-ha!
The championship match between the Seibu Wild Gunmen
and the Ojo White Knights is about to begin!
Stupid freakin' Sena...
It's gonna start any second now!
Sorry I'm late!
Huh? Where's Sena?
He came down with a fever...
He did?
Is he gonna be okay?
Huh?
Tetsuma?
Why's he in the audience?
I'll be blunt, without Tetsuma,
we can't beat Ojo!
We push too hard and we'll end up with injuries!
So bang-bang through this game carefully!
Golly...
He's really telling it like it is, huh?
There's nothing more disheartening
than your own coach predicting a loss.
Kid...
Let's go full-steam ahead.
For Tetsuma...
You said it.
Hey, you hear about what Tetsuma
did after the Deimon game?
Oh yeah, he smacked one of their players or something, right?
He got a one-game suspension as punishment.
Is that what happened?
Tetsuma.
I'm sorry!
I had no idea...
If you hadn't stopped me...
...I would've gotten disqualified.
But instead...
Instead...
You got yourself disqualified instead.
We'll fight again.
In the...
Kanto Tournament.
Remember...
It doesn't matter that our slot in the Kanto Tournament is secure.
We fight at full strength, with the pride of kings!
Show them Ojo's strength!
- Yes sir!
Glory on the Kingdom!
- Yeah!
Fire!
The game is finally starting!
Seibu's unstoppable offense against Ojo's impenetrable defense...
This promises to be an incredible game!
I'll get through you and prove that I'm the best.
Get ready, Seijuro Shin!
What am I doing here...
Shin and Riku are going at it right now...
I want to see who's better.
I'll squash whoever you throw at me!
They're running, stop him!
A run?
Is the loss of their top receiver, Tetsuma,
forcing them to rely on the run?
You shall not pass!
Stop me, if you can!
Rodeo Drive!
Kaitani is shut down!
The Rodeo Drive fails!
Wow...
So this is a championship game!
It's good!
The Everest Pass is complete!
What an awesome game!
I can't get a good shot...
I'm going to film from over there.
This should be good.
Sena?!
Sena...
Shin comes to meet Kaitani again!
Riku...
Riku has the ability to get past Shin...
I'm getting further... bit by bit...
The timing...
If I can just get the timing down!
The Spear Tackle resounds throughout the arena!
Wow...
Sena, are you okay?!
You shouldn't have dragged yourself out of bed...
You have to rest up and get better!
Let's go home, Sena.
Please... leave me alone...
This is getting good...
I've never seen Sena look so focused...
It's like he's not even himself...
Over and over, Kaitani rushes forward,
but Seijuro Shin is there to meet him every time!
Without Tetsuma, the key to Seibu's trademark Shotgun Pass,
they're forced to rely exclusively on Kaitani's running.
It's going to be a long, tough game for them!
Even Riku can't get past him...
I'll...
I'll get you next time.
With just a minute to go,
they're two touchdowns behind!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 3 - Ojo White Knights 14
Game over, huh?
What should we do?
Let me run again.
Even if our team loses...
...I won't!
C'mon, then.
Riku...
I just need to time it...
Riku Kaitani.
You are no ordinary man.
Spear thrusts can be sidestepped!
Yes!
But you won't beat me!
I almost made it...
And with that,
the Ojo White Knights seize the Tokyo Tournament championship!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 3 - Ojo White Knights 14
The world...
...where the greatest play.
Akaba...
You...
...give off the same vibe as Eyeshield 21.
But I'm afraid the final ticket to the Kanto Tournament...
...belongs to Bando.
I swear on my name as the TRUE Eyeshield 21.
Bando's not going to the Kanto Tournament,
Deimon is!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
It's time to play Bando for third place!
Akaba claims HE'S the real Eyeshield 21!
You gonna let him get away with that, Sena?
It's not about who's real and who's fake.
I am who I am!
Sena? You don't mean-?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Sena Kobayakawa! Ya-ha!
I'm kinda worried about Sena...
Wanna stop by his house on the way home?
Mamo?
Please... leave me alone...
I've never seen Sena like that...
It felt like he'd gone somewhere far, far away...