We're finally here! The manly state of Texas!
Time for some real rugged training to prepare us for the Christmas Bowl!
Can you believe we're having the camp in America?
The Wild Gunmen have never done anything like this!
It's all thanks to ME winning second prize in the Summer World Lottery!
Be grateful.
It was TOO lucky.
Too much good fortune spells trouble later.
I'm gonna catch some Z's.
Tetsuma, wake me up in about three hours.
Wait for me at the beach at 10:00... Hiruma.
Well, this is the beach, but...
Where did he mean?
We've still got two hours.
Why are we all meeting here, anyway?
What a pain.
Still, we have to grin and bear it, eh, Togano?
Shall we go look around for Hiruma?
Indeed, Kuroki!
Come along, Jumonji!
Oh dear... So be it!
They're gone...
Huh... and where's Kurita and the others?
I saw him going into this gigantic hamburger restaurant.
Yukimitsu, too?
Yeah, he was worried about what'd happen if it was just Kurita and Komusubi.
Sheesh, everyone's flaking out on us.
Y-Yes, they are...
So, what are those?
We DO have lots of time!
Works for me!
A real cowboy shop!
Sadly, you're the only one who can comprehend these manly topics.
Let's mosey, Kid!
Not like I could leave an old man in a foreign land on his own.
I wanna win the Christmas Bowl, no matter what it takes.
That's why I need you.
So get up, and don't give me any lip!
Ungh... You came all this way for THAT?
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Ultimate Combo! The Devil Gunmen!
Gotcha!
Mamori...
C'mon, charge! Charge already!
What's up with this bull? Must be stupid!
Hurry up and get mad!
Oh, no!
What crazy power!
Wow... He stopped a charging bull with a football...
Dang...
That's Kid, from the Wild Gunmen!
What's Deimon doing all the way out here?
Well, we're, uh...
Having training camp!
Something like that...
And you, Kid?
Same thing, right?
Yeah, that's the plan, but...
This guy's got the fire in his eyes.
That does it!
I'm takin' this little dogie to the Ben Ranch and makin' him a rodeo bull!
Not again... What is he TALKING about?
Yeah, it's time, it's time, it's time!
The 21st annual Texas Beach Football tournament is about to begin!
Beach football is a simplified version of football played in the sand!
It's just five-on-five, so small teams are a-okay!
Games are only ten minutes,
and you only have to tag to stop your opponent, so it's easy, safe, and fun!
Run, jump, and push your way to the front of the line! All entrants are welcome!
I see...
The winning team wins a $1000 prize!
AND as a bonus, this prime piece of delicious Texas beef!
That's the look! I can tell you're itchin' for a fight!
Kid! You're entering that tournament!
Everyone's already at the Ben Ranch.
We can't enter with just the two of us...
We have to! We're men, dangit!
Saving this bull is our duty!
We need more than two people!
I wonder what it's like... being on the same team as someone that good!
Registration is about to close, it's time to get our game on!
You all ready out there?
Sign us up, Kid!
We don't have enough-
Uh... Excuse me...
Well... If you want, we could play...
Sign us UP, Kid!
Why don't you team with us?
We'll be the Devil Gunmen.
What? Devil Gunmen?!
I like it! Deimon and Seibu teaming up to make the Devil Gunmen. Good thinking, boy!
Seriously?
Okay, let's fill out an entry form!
Huh?! You're gonna play too?!
Hey, without me, we're still short.
True.
She's got us there.
The first match is the Sexy Queens versus
the Old-Young-Boy-Girl mishmash team, the Devil Gunmen!
Oh dear... Our first game's against a bunch of tourists!
Those silly gooses! This will be easy as pie!
They're so unsightly.
No waist... Short legs...
Flat chests!
Now take a look at us! Check out our sexy bodies!
It takes some nerve to even step outside looking like that!
They're making complete fools out of us.
As long as we do the same to them on the field, it doesn't matter.
All that smack-talking will come back to bite them.
The Devil Gunmen'll shoot while they're making jokes and wrap the game up early.
Right!
Football Clinic!
What does a wide receiver do!
He catches the quarterback's passes!
He needs to be able to jump higher than everyone else and make catches! Ya-ha!
I can't believe I'm playing with Kid...
Set, hut!
The ball is snapped, and the game is afoot!
So fast!
Argh!
Oh man... The time between the snap and the pass was almost nonexistent!
Sorry, I'm too used to my normal timing.
I'll wait little longer-
N-No, that's okay!
Please, throw me another one at your regular speed.
You sure?
Yes!
You got it.
Go get 'em!
Nice! Perfect timing!
Max Catch!
Touch-in!
Nice job, Deimon.
We're a golden tag-team!
Yes... Now it's my turn.
Uh-oh! The Sexy Queens fall behind early!
The kid with the hat and the monkey are no amateurs!
Shall we take out the chimp, then?
Okay!
Dagnabbit.
Kid, over here!
Here goes!
Oh no you don't!
I can make it!
Hey! Don't gang up on Sena!
Shoot, with Mamori here I can't run for real!
Touch-in!
I figured this'd be tough, what with only two real players.
Coach, Manager, Manager?
It's all good!
If we just had Tetsuma!
He's on the bus with everyone else.
Tetsuma always follows orders. There's no way he'd show up-
Hmm...
I'm gonna catch some Z's.
Tetsuma, wake me up in about three hours.
Two hours, 59 minutes.
57 seconds.
58.
59.
Wake Kid up?
He's not here.
Whatever, Tetsuma isn't just gonna appear out of thin air...
That'd be way too...
Lucky!
Player substitution!
Set, hut, hut!
Tetsuma!
Holy cow, they're completely in sync!
Uh oh, even playing dirty isn't enough to...
...stop him!
Touch-in! Game over!
He's like a well-oiled machine... They can attack with any pass route they want!
The Sexy Queens go out sexily!
The Devil Gunmen throw the brackets into chaos!
They advance to the semi-finals!
Devil Gunmen?
I feel like throwing some bullets, Tetsuma.
I wish I was free to run my heart out!
Okay, Sena, make sure you don't rush in there!
It's no use...
What are those boneheads doing?
You know them?
The shorties are on my team.
And there's the world's fastest quickdraw.
Max Catch!
Not bad, butt-monkey.
Why isn't that other shrimp running?
He has his reasons.
Leave Sena alone!
Mamori!
Max Mamori catch!
Run, Sena!
I can finally run!
That guy's legs are crazy fast!
Wow, it's a sandstorm!
Touch-in!
And the Devil Gunmen advance to the finals!
This is a miracle!
Hey, kid, you're pretty dang speedy.
Thanks!
I like the cut of his jib.
It all comes down to this!
The tourist team, the Devil Gunmen, versus
the defending two-time champs looking to make it three, Too Tattooed!
Hey, Japanese team, you're da football team we're facing, right?
Yeah, you're one-pass style reeks of regular football.
Umm...
Regular football and beach football are different.
I'ma show you how it's really done.
L-Let's see what you've got!
The championship game is about to begin!
There it is! Too Tattooed's special play,
countless short passes called "The Dance of the Flea!"
Wha?
What're they doing?
W-We can't stop passes like that!
Touch-in!
Too Tattooed quickly pulls ahead by seven!
Our tourist friends simply can't keep up!
Yep, you regular football guys ain't used to da trick plays we use!
There's so many places to pass from, I can't get a bead on them.
They really are the best beach football team...
Too Tattooed are no slouches.
You know them?
They were a bunch of two-bit punks when we first met...
But I took them under my wing.
I'll consider your offer,
IF your gang manages to get past mine.
Then you won't mind if I join in, right?
Of course not.
Gotcha.
If we don't start throwing short passes too, we're toast.
B-But none of us can throw accurate passes...
We have no control...
Show some spine!
Hi-Hiruma!
W-Where'd you come from?!
Yo, Manajerk!
Geez...
I'm replacing you. Go find the rest of the Deimon team.
There ARE such things as MANNERS, you know!
Your overseer's gone.
Now start running at full tilt!
Right!
Now this is good! We've got Deimon's QB, too!
I assume you're cool with that?
Well, it certainly won't be boring...
What the hey.
All right! The five of us form the strongest pentagon.
Let's rip these jokers apart!
First, us two QBs will "pendulum" our way up, you dig?
I dig.
Me combined with your quickdraw... We'll be invincible.
You put too much faith in me.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime super tag team.
Let's rock!
Set, hut, hut!
Hey, when did he-
Crush their sub!
You're kidding! The two of them just instantly worked together in perfect harmony?!
It's the Dance of the Flea!
No, wait!
They're doing it with just two of them!
They're insane!
All right, they're all coming after me!
Tetsuma, zig out!
Pass to your left!
Max Catch!
Sena!
Wha- Him?
He got way better outta nowhere!
Amazing!
With Kid, Tetsuma, Monta, and Hiruma, no one can stop us!
They're unstoppable!
The five play styles of the Devil Gunmen really have formed the strongest pentagon!
Game over! The Devil Gunmen win it all!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
W-Wha?
A 2000 km "Death March" across America?
If I go home, I'll have an easy, carefree summer vacation.
But...
If you wanna get stronger, follow us into the depths of hades!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: At the Gates of Hell! Ya-ha!
We did it! We won!
Yahoo!
We really won!
Only those who taste the bitterness of defeat can truly grow stronger.
I've taught you all I can.
You've all grown a great deal.
I know you'll be all right.
Sensei!
Great job, Kid, Tetsuma!
They're both so incredible...
Remember.
We're going up against teams just like them.
Right!
Way to go, everyone!
I heard you won the championship!
Wh- It couldn't be... It's such a... coincidence-
It was no coincidence.
Finding him was the main reason we made this trip.
Coach Doburoku!
Who is he?
Coach Doburoku Sakaki!
Our middle school coach who taught us how to play football!
Coach?!
You gave me your word.
You're our new trainer!
Fine by me...
You sure you can keep up?
Our trainer?