Great! We're just 14 points apart!
Shuei Elephants 021 - Samurai Warriors 007
Let's work hard to flip the score!
Go, Sen- Oops, Eyeshield 21!
There's no way we'll let that high schooler do as he likes!
Touchdown!
Hey, what just happened?
Eyeshield's legs are so fast
that a normal person on defense can't keep up with him.
Why?
Why doesn't he use that diabolical running style?
Shin, I bet you wanna play!
You want to fight him, don't you?
Hey, do we have some back-up players here?
I have an idea...
Why don't we let those two play?
They're also high school students.
And I'd love to see them play against Eyeshield!
Hey, you two!
Huh?
How about it? Would you like to play, too?
For real?
We're in! We're in! Right, Shin?
Eyeshield... I'll stop you!
- We did it! Yay!
- Yeah!
Shin...!
I've waited for this.
I won't hold back, Eyeshield 21!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Ghost vs. The Spear!
Whoa! Eyeshield 21 verses Seijuro Shin in an explosive battle!
Seijuro Shin VS. Eyeshield 21
That's right!
I get to fight against Shin!
Set! Hut, hut!
I can use those three high schoolers.
Since we can't use our normal offense,
I've got to rely on them!
There's a reason why I can't lose this game, no matter what!
He got crushed!
Pass! Pass!
I'm trapped!
I can't make a pass!
Here you go, #21!
Okay!
Show me your diabolical running!
Shin!
The Devil Bat Ghost is our secret weapon.
We can't afford to start showing it off.
You're not allowed to use it outside of actual games.
Is that clear?
That's Shin's special move, the Spear Tackle!
It's been a while... since I've hurt like this.
The Spear Tackle... has become even more powerful!
You okay?
Yeah...
Why?
Why aren't you using the running style you used against Amino?
Do you really think that you can defeat me
without using that diabolical running style?
I... I want to try out the Devil Bat Ghost against Shin...
But I...
Set! Hut, hut!
Master's "HNNRABA" block!
That's nothing!
I'm awesome!
Pass over here!
Their pass course has been blocked again.
I guess we'll run.
Eyeshield's running again!
The Devil Bat Ghost is off limits!
I can't get through!
Show me your diabolical running!
What are you doing, Eyeshield 21?!
Why aren't you using it?!
Wait, S-Suzuna! Please calm down! Hey, c'mon!
Seijuro Shin...
He has the ability to make good decisions
and the physical strength to quickly respond to the opponent's moves.
He's truly an ideal line backer!
Sena, is it because of what Hiruma said?
Because he said not to use Devil Bat Ghost?
But you know... You-!
He's right.
Am I okay with things like this?
Don't I have to use my full strength when fighting against Shin?
But...
For some odd reason,
Eyeshield isn't using that running technique he used against Amino.
Due to their difference in height,
Komusubi's getting crushed from above by Otawara.
And Shin is completely preventing against anyone
passing to Raimon or letting Eyeshield run.
The game's just going to keep getting harder for the Samurai Warriors!
Oh, this is it!
They're playing a game!
So that's a corporate team...
But man, that one guy is pretty short.
If it isn't Sena!
Hey! So the brothers finally made it!
We're not related!
What on earth is going on here anyway?
You see...
Everyone, welcome to the Nagano Hot Springs Tour-
How can this be?
How can this be?!
If you're short a few players, why don't you ask them?
We play on Deimon High School's football team!
You kids know pass routes?
Of course!
Shuei Elephants 35 - Samurai Warriors 17
And that's that.
We're struggling with an 18-point gap.
The difference in their body mass is just too much.
They're lacking a good line.
They aren't putting their hips into it!
They need to make their hips explode more!
Huh? You can tell?
Football's all about the line, ya know.
And the line's about your hips, ya know.
And hips' gotta be explosive, ya know!
Wha-What...?
Hey, this is the reporter who was talkin' bad about us!
What?!
Can't let that slide!
We'll show you what we've got!
We're gonna settle this now!
I'm the cool hand line, Kazuki Jumonji
Playing dirty's my motto! I'm Koji Kuroki.
I'm the manga-loving Shozo Togano!
Be sure to watch us carefully!
Yay! The Deimon Devil Bats are teaming up!
Shin...
Yay! Football Clinic!
Does Japan have any arena football teams?
Arima's "Samurai Warriors" is a famous team.
They're literally samurai who have crossed the seas to fight! Ya-ha!
Make your hips explode!
Hip Explosion Ka-BOOM!
- They're holding up well!
- Yay!
Good going!
Max Catch!
We barely managed to gain a yard!
You can't get by me!
Defense's ball!
Running for it won't work after all.
Shin...
That pain you feel now...
is the result of me using all of my strength against you.
No matter who you are,
I'll always go at you with all I've got!
I'll never regret anything!
I... don't want to have regrets over my fight with Shin!
Sena?
Monta, I...
I know! Just do what you want!
I know you're dying to play with all you've got.
Just forget about what Hiruma said!
Monta!
After all, it's not like he's watching...
You look pumped up!
Quit holding back and do whatever the heck you want!
Don't hold back any!
Full power!
Yeah!
Shin, I'm going to come at you with everything I've got!
Shuei Elephants 38 - Samurai Warriors 17
Field goal!
There's a 21-point gap.
It'll be bad if they get any more points.
- Excuse me...
- Hmm?
Please give me the ball. I want to run.
But, running isn't...!
Please let me!
I'm asking you, too!
Same here!
Same with us!
Yeah! Sena, I mean, Eyeshield can defeat that guy!
We'll open up a huge path for him!
Guys!
Fine! I'll let you try running again if that's how everyone feels.
Yah!
Okay!
Set! Hut, hut!
This time I'll give it my all to get past Shin!
Hut!
It's open! Go now!
That's...!
At last! He's doing it!
He's stepping to the right...
He suddenly shortens his stride and steps forward with his left leg.
It looks like he's going to try to get past me from the right, but...
...he's not!
He's using his left leg as an axial so he can push his entire body to the opposite side!
I can do it!
It's a non-decelerating barrel cross-over step!
He truly is... a ghost!
Touchdown!
W-What was that just now?
Yay!
He... did it! That's his...
Devil Bat Ghost!
D-Devil Bat Ghost?
Right!
It's Eyeshield's secret weapon, the Devil Bat Ghost!
Great! You finally did it!
A silent kick means...
So that's it.
He got ya good, Shin!
I'll stop him next time!
Great! We got the extra point!
Shuei Elephants 38 - Samurai Warriors 24
There's just a 14-point gap! We can do it!
Good going! Keep it up!
Set! Hut!
Okay!
Once more... I'll get through again!
Right? Left?
The right!
I got through!
Touchdown!
What should I do?
What should I...?
Amazing!
He got through on the opposite side from before!
He can turn to the left and right as he wishes!
The Devil Bat Ghost truly is a diabolical running style!
We did it!
- ...Ojo!
- See that...
Okay, there's a seven-point gap now!
Shuei Elephants 38 - Samurai Warriors 31
Don't let appearances fool you.
The more I rely on my eyesight, the slower I'll get.
In order for my body to keep up with Eyeshield, I must...
...enter a state of selflessness!
I must believe in my own strength...
...and abandon all unnecessary thought!
Okay! Let's flip the scoreboard!
Yeah!
Set! Hut, hut!
Take the lead! Let's go!
State of selflessness...
Here I go! Devil Bat Ghost!
He lowered his arms!
I get it!
Seijuro Shin's amazing!
He's amazing...
You really are amazing, Shin...
He stopped the Devil Bat Ghost.
It won't work on Shin anymore!
I thought this might happen.
I thought I was gonna have to punish him for disobeying me, but...
Shuei Elephants 66 - Samurai Warriors 34
Game over!
We didn't make it...
Going up against a corporate team was hard on them.
But everyone did great!
Looks like we got a little big-headed after that game against Amino.
Yeah...
We're still not good enough to defeat Ojo or Seibu yet.
Feel regret!
Using the Devil Bat Ghost is pretty rough on my knees!
It's still not perfected yet.
I see!
Hiruma had already realized this,
so he didn't want me to use Devil Bats Ghost too much.
Well, I guess it's all good since they realized they've still got a long way to go.
I still got a long way to go!
I've got to work even harder!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Ah-ha! What's with those guys doing the bunny hop on the beach?
The Yuhi Guts!
They're our next opponent in the tournament.
They're pretty passionate! They're on fire!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Hot! Guts!! Fire! Oh, oops! Ya-HA!
Excuse me, but didn't you say that you couldn't afford to lose this game?
Something important must have been on the line...
Yeah, it was a promise between men!
Just what was it?
The Elephants get to use all of our cheerleaders in the next game!
How depressing!
That's it...?