- Okay, come on!
- Ya-ha!
Bando Spiders vs. Deimon Devil Bats
They've got a hole in their Spider's Web.
A... hole?
Where ever they are, the ball will follow.
That's their probem.
But even if we know where the ball's going to land,
we can't get by their annoying line.
And we can't push our way through to the ball, ya know?
No normal person could.
Huh? Me?
You're the only one here who can do it!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Truth Behind Red Eyes
So then, what will Deimon do now?
Will they be able to slip out of the Spider's Web
and hit hard on offense?!
We're so smart!
There it is!
It's Kotaro's monstrous kick!
Over there!
Yeah!
Push through!
We'll hold out...
...until he...
...gets here!
Who will steal the ball?!
Whoops!
Deimon's line has been defeated again!
It's ours!
Amazing! Deimon's Sena Kobayakawa stole the ball!
I have to get a touchdown no matter what!
I can do it!
Sena Kobayakawa was so close!
But he got crushed by Akaba's impregnable defense!
True...
I must admit that your lightspeed legs
have great musical sense.
But it doesn't matter how fast you are.
You'll never break my beat!
And here I thought we'd broken free of the Spider's Web....
Akaba stopped Sena!
Akaba fills in the hole in their strategy,
making it absolutely flawless.
What's wrong, Sena?
You depressed or something?
Get pumped to the max!
That's not it.
Then what is it?
I realized that he really is amazing...
I guess I'm a little happy
that we're going up against such an amazing player.
S-So you're impressed, huh?
But I shouldn't be acting like this, should I?
After all, we can't go to the Kanto Tournament
if we can't defeat Akaba.
And here I'm saying I'm happy he's strong?
He's so strong... that he gives me chills.
He's truly terrifying!
Sena, I've got a little secret to tell you.
You see, those chills aren't from fear.
You're trembling with excitement at the thought of defeating him!
You're acting like an ace, Sena.
Hey, peewees!
Looks like you're getting all nice and pumped up!
I've got an idea! Huddle up!
Well, as long as we've got my smart kicking,
there's no way Deimon could possibly defeat us!
You're right...
We're a team that's mastered kicking
because that's what we were born to do.
This wasn't coincidence or some random whim of ours.
We're the Bando Spiders.
So you're really transferring away, Akaba...
Yeah...
With your dad's transfer,
I guess it couldn't be helped.
You're going to Teikoku High in Kansai, right?
Honestly, it was a tough decision.
But Bando should be just fine without me here anymore...
I'm sure everyone
will work hard to win the tournament.
Akaba...
Why'd ya do it?!
I may not always understand you,
but I thought you were different from the others!
You stupid idiot!
H-Hey, what's going on, Kotaro?!
All of you...
...are so not smart!
Teikoku High School
They're all Bando players!
Why are they here at Teikoku High?
Hey, Akaba! You're late!
It's all thanks to your transferring to Teikoku!
They asked us to transfer, too!
Unlike Bando,
we can easily slide into university through their program.
And we'll get scouted by corporate teams
if we keep playing football even a little.
This has made the rest of our lives a cake walk!
- This's too cool!
What's the meaning of this?
We just asked the other members of your team
to transfer over after you decided to come here.
As long as we've got
the offense and defense teams that you created,
we're sure to go to the Kansai Tournament!
So that's what you were plotting.
Now we can rest at ease.
And life'll be sweet like a rose for you!
It works out nicely for both of us!
I don't like...
...the tick to your beat.
- Our beat?
I mean, you're horrible people.
How dare you talk like that?!
Hold it, you brat!
W-W-W-What're you doing?!
Even if you go back to Bando now,
you won't be able to participate in the fall tournament till it's almost over!
And you'll have nothing but a kicking team!
As I thought...
Our musical senses clash horribly.
"The powerful Bando Spiders have lost by 55 points!"
"Is their team in danger of falling apart?"
This is impossible!
We can't win!
I've never heard of playing football with just a kicking team!
Why is everyone giving up after losing just one or two games?!
That's right! Let's give it our all!
How are we supposed to fight?!
We're just a kicking team
and we don't even have a coach anymore!
How shoud we fight?!
A... Akaba?!
What are you doing here?!
You jerk!
How dare you show your face here?!
Y-You idiot! Why didn't you dodge?!
The team fell apart because I transferred away.
I heard that our coach quit as a result of that, too.
That's why I've come back.
I want to go to the Christmas Bowl with this team!
O-Our Akaba...
...bowed down to us!
I'd like... to play football with you.
Akaba!
You're going to come back?
What the heck?!
You think you can just waltz on back like this?!
You're so self-centered!
Enough, Kotaro!
It's not like this is Akaba's fault.
No, it's okay...
Y-You...!
Do you seriously think we'll make it
to the Christmas Bowl with nothing but a kicking team?
Yeah, I do.
Assuming we're a kicking team with an awesome beat.
Your weirdness never ends!
But... you're super smart-looking right now!
I just can't understand you.
You could have been the ace player
and lived in the lap of luxury if you stayed at Teikoku.
And instead you came back to this
weak-fragranced team that's falling apart.
Perhaps a weak fragrance matches my musical taste
better than the fragrance of a life as a celebrity.
Man, I just don't get you!
Ouch!
That hurt! What gives?!
What do you mean we're "weak-fragranced?!"
- Yeah!
I was just being descriptive!
Now face my Smart Spit Attack!
Ew, stop that right now, Kotaro!
Without his kicking abilities and passion,
the Bando Spiders you see before you would never have come to be.
That's why we have to win with our kicking!
That's our team's fate!
Is that really okay?!
But we won't be able to move ahead very much!
It's important for us to throw their defense into chaos.
Peewee will cover a bunch of distance! Got that?!
Yep!
My, what an unusual formation!
Three people are lined up behind Hiruma!
Crush #80!
Catch it!
A back pass?!
Oh my god! This's a no go!
But this was a piece of cake for a genius like me!
Sena!
I'll do it if you can't!
Taki's hugging the sidelines!
Deimon's gained three yards despite getting burned bad!
Just what I'd expect from the master tactitian, Hiruma.
He's using rugby-style passes in order to pass the ball around.
You can do a back pass as many times as you need to.
He's as tricky as ever!
It's a back pass, Kumabukuro!
Right.
Since Deimon's line keeps getting defeated by Spider Poison,
they've decided to gain yardage
by running along the sidelines rather than dash head-on.
But, Hiruma, that type of trick won't work on them for long.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What's an important trait for Eyeshield 21's position,
the running back?
The hint is "teamwork."
It's important for him to trust his friends
and dash through whatever path the blockers have opened for him.
Trust your friends!
Ya-ha!
Don't let them push you back, guys!
- Yeah!
Take your time and sing out your own phrases!
A change... in the center of gravity?
Right.
When the opponent goes to tackle,
they dig into the ground.
If you can push them right then,
even huge giants will...
Amazing, Akaba!
That's right!
We've got that awesome technique that Akaba taught us!
- Spider Poison!
Not again!
They suddenly...
...got stronger!
Good. That's perfect.
Curse you, Vampiro!
He taught them a formidable technique!
Tokyo's MVP, Akaba...
He's truly fearsome!
He must have studied their opposing teams
to figure out the timing for when everyone
shifts their center of gravity
and then taught it to his team.
- Crush #80!
B-Back pass!
I'll catch it!
Crush them!
They've gotten faster!
Deimon managed to pass the ball to Sena
while sending Bando's defense into chaos.
And now he's running along the sidelines!
He's heading for a touchdown, BUT...
Kotaro and Akaba are rushing to block him!
This team is definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Same here!
We have to go to the Christmas Bowl!
I'll stop you!
There it is! The Devil Bat Ghost!
This time I'll get a touchdown!
He easily outran Eyeshield Sena Kobayakawa and stopped him!
Hayato Akaba is terrifying!
No...
It wasn't a matter of Akaba being super fast just now.
It was more like he already knew what route I was going to take!
Akaba's going to try to stop Sena again!
Go, Chinfuzz!
I'll beautifully block since I'm a genius
and then Sena will have a route he can run through!
Taki's left is open!
Great! I'll make it through!
It's a trap!
That's just a dead end in a labyrinth!
I can do it!
Touchdown!
Amazing! Akaba stole the ball with his speedy tackle
and ran it in for a touchdown!
I've already told you.
It doesn't matter how fast you are,
you'll never get by me.
Run force, huh?
Interesting.
What's "run force" again?
Well you see, Mizumachi,
you control your blockers to create a human maze.
It's allows you to control the enemy's running routes.
It's a high-level technique.
My brother went to block,
but instead he ended up blocking Sena's path.
That's a killer technique that only an expert lead blocker
like Akaba could actually pull off.
He's a completely different type of player
than Shin and Kakei,
who take advantage of their physical attributes when they play.
This is what makes Akaba Hayato,
also known as the "Field Conductor" so fearsome!
With the extra point kicks,
they're way in the lead with a score 17-0!
Bando just doesn't stop attacking!
There's 40 yards to the goal post.
That's pretty far off...
I can do it! I'll look totally smart!
We can't let them get any more points!
Sorry, but we're going to win this game!
Kotaro!
Leave it to me!
I'm smart!
The field goal attempt was a success!
Deimon's in a pinch!
They can't stand up to Bando's offensive onslaught!
There's already a huge 20 point game separating them!
Arrgh! What should we do?!
We'll never catch up at this rate...
And we can't even stop their offense!
They're strong!
They're TOO strong!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
They've got Akaba AND Kotaro!
The Bando Spiders are way too strong!
Deimon, aren't you in serious trouble?
But... we still stand a chance!
We can't give up!
He's the only one who can save us now, isn't he?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Run! Musashi! Ya-ha!
So, what will you do, Deimon?!
Will Hiruma be forced to throw in the towel
when they can't even snag possession?!
No, he won't!
Those aren't the eyes of someone who's given up!
Those are the eyes of someone who is waiting...
...for even the slightest hope of victory!
Waiting? But who's... he waiting for?