He's using his Spider Illusion!
Sena, I'm gonna win!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Touchdown!
He did it! Game over!
It's 36-37!
The Deimon Devil Bats totally, totally, totally flipped the scoreboard!
The third team representing Tokyo is the Deimon Devil Bats!
They're going to the Kanto Tournament!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Strongest Warriors in Tokyo!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
- Boo-yah!
Yay! We did it!
We did it!
"Even if cheering,
some of the tears we see shed are not from happiness."
Hmm, I think I goofed up that Haiku poem somehow.
Are you upset, Yukimitsu?
I am.
Is it because you can't stand and rejoice
on the same field as everyone else?
Right...
That shows...
...that you're already a great warrior.
You'll get your spotlight.
You'll get it eventually!
Right!
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 37
A one-point defeat...
They flipped the score by getting three points with that one kick.
If only my kick had made it through-!
This stinks!
I wanted to show up those jerks that had abandoned us!
I wanted to make it to nationals
and show them just how powerful a kicking team can be!
But I...
But I-!
You kicked with all your might back there.
Anybody who saw today's game
learned just how important kicks are for a team.
Darn it! Just you wait and see!
I'm going to train harder and become the ultimate smart-looking player!
And next year...
Next time, the Bando Spiders will crush everyone...
...as a kicking team!
Sena...
Huh?
The title for best runner,
"Eyeshield 21,"
should belong to you after all.
No, no! I really didn't do anything all that great!
So a man who "isn't all that great" got passed me.
Is that what you're saying?
N-No, you got it wrong...
You're going to the Christmas Bowl, right?
Right!
Then you can't let anyone defeat you ever again.
Once I accept this...
...I can't let myself lose to anyone ever again...
If you seriously want to make it to the top,
you must bear the burden that goes with the title "Eyeshield 21"
and never give up.
I need the resolve... to never lose!
Kotaro...
What?
Our inner musical beats are completely different.
We never have been able to harmonize nicely together.
What brought this on?
But...
Huh?
But I'm glad we got to perform together.
I've never been able to figure you out!
But ya know...
You're super smart-looking!
That was an awesome performance, you two!
Coach!
I swear that next year
everyone here in our kicking team
will make it to the Christmas Bowl!
Yeah!
I'm going to laugh extra hard today!
Cut back on it some!
That's cold to the max!
Ladies!
Why the heck are you guys playing sissy water games?!
Shoot!
H-H-Hiruma! Today they earned-
Bottles just won't cut it, kiddies!
Ya...
HA!
This is the first time I've seen Hiruma so happy.
Yay! Everyone's so excited!
Hey, Sena!
That party's already started!
You were really great!
Towards the end-
H-Hey-
What's wrong?
Hey, you okay?!
Sena?
You did good...
Sena... did you get taller?
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us about Yocchie's position as quarterback!
The hint is "leadership!"
He must lead the entire offensive team,
so it's important that he's a good captain.
Lead your team! Ya-ha!
All-Japan High School Football Tokyo Fall Tournament Award Ceremony
Ouch...
Good morning!
D-Don't do that, Mamori!
We're suffering from max muscle fatigue.
We're completely covered in ice packs.
Sorry! Sorry!
Huh?! Sena!
Huh?
Look at your uniform!
Let's go a bit big since you're going to grow a lot.
Come to think it, it fits perfectly!
Huh?
Sena, when'd that happen?
Huh? Hm?
Seriously!
And here Sena used to be so tiny....
I guess he doesn't need me to babysit him anymore...
Huh? Did you say something?
No, it's nothing! Absolutely nothing!
We shall now commence the Tokyo Fall Tournament Award Ceremony!
A total of 36 schools participated in the Tokyo Fall Tournament.
And the grand championship goes to
the Ojo White Knights!
Congratulations, everyone at Ojo!
Whoops, there!
- I farted again!
- I swear Otawara will never change...
Y-Yeah...
I shall now announce the tournament's Best Eleven!
What's the "Best Eleven?"
It's an award recognizing the top players in each position.
Put together, they'd make the perfect all-star team.
We will start off with defense first.
For Linebacker, the Ojo White Knights' Seijuro Shin!
Amazing!
Shin really is amazing!
Followed by the Kyoshin Poseidons' Shun Kakei,
and the Zokugaku Chameleons' Rui Habashira!
For the line,
we've selected the Seibu Wild Gunmen's Buffalo Ushijima
and the Ojo White Knights' Makoto Otawara!
I farted again!
Now for the offensive team.
On the line,
there's the Kyoshin Poseidon's Kengo Mizumachi!
Well, that was a given!
The Hashiratani Deers' Onihei Yamamoto!
- Onihei!
He TOTALLY got that outta sympathy!
You shouldn't...
...say things like that!
No, I don't have the right to accept-
Mizumachi, he better not-!
What?
What are you talking about, old man?
You put up a pretty nice fight!
And coming from me, that means something!
He nearly gave me a heart attack...
Yeah.
But it's great that they're getting along now!
And the Deimon Devil Bats' Ryokan Kurita!
He's saying...
...that you won...
...ya hear?!
Kurita!
That's awesome to the max!
I-I'm so honored!
I can't believe I'm in the Best Eleven!
Kicker goes to the Bando Spiders' Kotaro Sasaki!
I'm so smart!
Receiver goes to the Seibu Wild Gunmen's Jo Tetsuma!
Hey, go on, Tetsuma.
It'd be a "slant" from here.
Yeah!
I'm so happy for you, Tetsuma.
And the Ojo White Knights' Haruto Sakuraba!
Sweet! Sakuraba!
No one's worthy of that award if Sakuraba's not!
You did it, Sakuraba.
Takami, this is for the both of us!
I didn't make it!
The tight end goes to the Bando Spiders' Hayato Akaba.
You know...
...guitars...
...have nothing to do with this!
The quarterback goes to the Seibu Wild Gunmen's The Kid!
Good gracious...
I personally think that a certain someone
is far better than me...
- Huh?
Oh!
Come to think of it...
You're not going?
The tournament's not over yet, you know.
And what about you?
It's not like I have to go.
I'll never... betray you again.
Got that right!
Running back goes to the Seibu Wild Gunmen's Riku Kaitani!
Riku, congratulations!
I always knew you were great!
They really did pick the best.
Yeah, they sure did.
And the last member of the Best Eleven for offense is...
...the running back...
Sena Kobayakawa!
M-Me?
In the Best Eleven?
Go on up there!
I wanted to stand up there with you, ya know!
Congratulations, Sena!
B-But...
I'm not really worthy of an award like this...
Everyone thinks you're great!
Sena...
You're the only one out here worthy of this award.
Riku!
You're the fastest man out there, Eyeshield 21.
If you don't hurry up, I might take that award for you!
C'mon. Accept the award.
You should be happy, kiddo.
Sena, congratulations!
Guys...
Shin...
You have earned that award.
Right!
Congrats!
Yay, Sena!
Sena, congratulations!
You really earned it!
Max congrats, Sena!
But I think I did pretty good too, ya know?
This doesn't bother me one bit!
After all, there's still-
That's right! There's still the MVP!
Yay, MVP!
And finally,
the Tokyo Fall Tournament MVP Award goes to...
The Chairman just looked at me!
No, he's looking at me!
Seijuro Shin!
Man...
Well, that's no surprise.
Congratulations, Shin!
Honestly,
we had a difficult time choosing
from the candidates for MVP this year.
Especially him...
But I want to see him improve even more.
I'm going to keep my promise with Shin
and fight him in the Kanto Tournament!
I can't lose!
I swear by my name as Eyeshield 21 that I can't lose!
This brings the Tokyo Fall Tournament Award Ceremony to a close.
We're going to have to train hard for the Kanto Tournament.
Join the basketball team!
No, you've gotta join the soccer team!
That's right!
Everyone found out who I really am during that last game!
Hey, there!
Don't harass him!
We'll discuss letting teams borrow him AFTER the tournament!
The football team did great!
The football team's awesome!
You better win now that you've made it this far!
- Eyeshield!
- Sena!
He's so cool!
Holy cow!
But t-they're kinda starting to make me nervous...
W-We'll be fine, okay, S-Sena?
Right!
It's a little scary, but...
I don't wanna question if we can win.
'Cause we've gotta win!
- S-Sena?
You've grown stronger, haven't you?
Probably...
Man, you just had to sound insecure at the end!
He's still got a ways to go...
Ya-ha!
Hey, kiddies, give me 100 laps around the river!
- Okay!
We're going to the Christmas Bowl!
Congratulations on making it to the Kanto Tournament, Devil Bats!!
The awards ceremony is over now!
So everyone's gotta focus on practicing
until the Kanto Tournament starts!
We've just gone through a bunch of tough games,
so it should be okay for us to take a little break.
There's no way Hiruma'll allow that!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Deimon's Half-time Show! Ya-ha!
Yoo-hoo!
We at Jari Pro want to award the Best Eleven
with new Sa-Ku-Ra-Ba brand spike shoes!
That so embarrassing, stop it, boss!
And we're giving the honored MVP a top of the line laptop!
Isn't it amazing?!
We're so generous, aren't we?!
Jari Pro-!
Yikes! Shin's so horrible with electronics.
I wonder why electronics always break the second Shin touches them...
There's no point worrying about the small stuff!