Okay, bring it on!
Here I go!
Whee-boy!
Nice catch, Monta!
Sena, weak throws like that are way too easy for me to catch.
Crank it up!
No more pansy passes, please!
Gee, Monta sure is going all out.
Don't let him show us up!
Yeah!
I wonder if this'll make it throw harder passes...
That idiot!
Why'd he aim it at us?!
Three Balls Max Catch!
- A-Amazing...
Perfect!
The Shinryuji Nagas'll be nothing
as long as I, Taro Raimon, am here!
He's so big-headed.
That monkey's annoying...
I won't lose to Ikkyu from Shinryuji!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
His Talent at Catching!
Okay!
Once more, Sena!
Wow!
Mon-Mon sure is pumped up.
Yep.
It's because one of the top three receivers
is a member of the Shinryuji Nagas.
Top three receivers?
Right.
There's the Ojo White Knights' Sakuraba,
the Seibu Wild Gunmen's Tetsuma
and the Shinryuji Nagas' Ikkyu.
All three of them are incredibly skilled,
so their called the top three receivers.
Monta wants people to recognize his skill
and change the title to "Top Four Receivers."
My catching competition with Ikkyu
is key to our defeating Shinryuji.
So I've just gotta win!
Yep!
I know that you'll do great, Monta.
We've gotta defeat Shinryuji!
Yeah!
But sorry for making you help me train all day today.
It's okay. No worries.
Really?
Then I've got one more favor to ask you!
Huh?
The pro baseball O.B. game?
It's the first game the master catcher Masaru Honjo
is going to play in since he retired from the Shuei Bears.
You're not a real fan if you don't watch this game!
But I'm not really a fan...
It's sky-high!
Honjo sure is amazing!
He still looks like he did during his prime!
C'mon, Monta. Calm down some.
There's no way I can stay calm!
Wow! He got a home run!
I can't lose to him!
Honjo, check out my catching ability!
Max Catch!
Oopsie. Wow-ow-ow!
Good going!
Nice catch!
Oh, well, thanks!
Uber-cool!
That was cool! Uber-cool!
I'm really surprised to see that you're a fan of Honjo too, Ikkyu!
Hey, that's my line!
What gives?
Monta and Ikkyu from Shinryuji became friends just like that!
I didn't know that you were a fan of Honjo, monkey boy!
Totally amazing!
He isn't even angry at getting called monkey boy.
Oh, back eight years ago on October 21, Honjo...
...was in the 5th Japanese series game!
Right, Sena?
Huh? You shouldn't ask me...
Hey now, you for real?
No. 80, Masaru Honjo, did a super great play in that game!
It's the game that made the Shuei Bears shine as the beast team in Japan.
O-Okay.
I'll keep that in mind.
Do you know Honjo's motto?
I bet you do!
You bet!
He always says it whenever he gets interviewed.
In baseball you need...
...99% effort and 1% talent!
That goes for football too, doesn't it?!
Yep!
Huh? Ikkyu's a Honjo fan?
Yeah, and then the two became friends.
So that's why he's working even harder today than yesterday...
Hey, let's go!
Go!
Bring it on!
There!
Yay!
Good!
I hope he doesn't wear himself out before the game...
Man, catching 1,000 balls wore me out!
Monta, I heard you met Ikkyu yesterday.
That's right, Mamori!
Man, he's a cool dude.
After all, all of Honjo's fans are nice, good people!
All righty then! Break's over!
Huh? Already?
I'm proud to have Ikkyu as my rival.
So then, let's work hard to the max!
Monta...
Right!
I've gotta work hard, too!
Taro Raimon, huh?
Max Catch!
Honestly, I never paid any attention to him before.
But going by that catch, he needs watching.
Ikkyu!
Why'd you have me come all the way out here?
Actually, there's something I wanted to show you!
This used to be Honjo's glove!
Honjo used to use this?!
Sure did!
Uber-cool!
Isn't it?!
I'm so happy you understand how cool this glove is!
Oh, no!
Monta?
Look out!
That was close!
I barely made it in time!
- Thank you so much.
Way to go!
That was cool!
Most impressive, boy.
N-Nah, it was nothing...
That was close...
That's all he's got?
Huh?
Ikkyu, please keep that glove.
It's a sign of our friendship!
Well, see ya at the tournament!
Let's go, Sena!
S-Sure...
Monta!
Hey, wait! Take this!
This stinks...
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
I just know that Ikkyu will take good care of my glove.
R-Right...
That's all he's got?
After all, Ikkyu understands just how much it's worth to me.
Right, Sena?
Sena?
Sorry... I've got an errand to run.
You go on ahead!
H-Hey, Sena!
He's acting weird...
I can't believe he said that about Monta...
I just have to know...
...what he meant by it!
What a pain.
What should I do with this?
That's Honjo's glove!
I dropped it...
Agon!
What are you doing?
Oh, nothing... Nothing at all!
Then watch where you walk.
Oh, sorry.
Agon, defeating Deimon's gonna be too easy, huh?
Too easy?
What are you talking about?
Those twerps aren't even worth mentioning.
We'll crush them in the blink of an eye.
Oh, right!
Agon, what do you need to be a good football player?
In football you need...
...100% pure talent.
That's my Agon!
You're uber-cool!
Yeppie-yep!
Agon is the coolest out there!
Let's see... I think it fell over here...
Found it!
Found him!
Ikkyu!
Here!
You found it for me?
But I don't need it,
so give it back to the monkey.
No way...
Monta said it was a sign of your friendship.
What happened between you two?
Well, nothing much, really...
But, Monta...
He couldn't even catch that pot!
He let that cat distract him,
which broke his focus, ya know?
That'll kill ya in a game.
But...
I thought he was really cool on the baseball field, but...
That monkey's a thousand years too early
if he thinks he can fight me.
I decided that I'm aiming for the top with Agon.
Later!
Ikkyu...
In the end, he wouldn't take it back.
What should I do with this glove?
Tomorrow I'll just have to tell Monta what happened
and give it back to him.
After all, all of Honjo's fans are nice, good people!
Here I go, Mon-Mon!
Go!
What a pain! I'm only human...
Okay!
Catch!
Double!
Triple Max Catch!
I see...
So that's what happened.
What should I do?
Why don't you hold onto that glove
until our game against Shinryuji's over?
Is that really what I should do?
I kinda brought it with me.
Ouch! Sorry, Sena!
I hurt my ankle!
I'm gonna borrow your spray!
Honjo's glove...
Monta, that's... Well... you see...
Why do you have it?
Well, you see, I...
What's going on here?!
Spit it out, Sena!
Actually...
Ikkyu!
That was outright cruel!
I thought you would like it!
What are you so angry about?
I thought that we could fight on par during the game!
On par?
Me, on par with you?!
You're way too weak for that!
Then, I challenge you here and now!
Me fight a monkey?
Fine.
Here I go!
Right!
Whenever you're ready.
I won't let you catch it!
What?!
He's running backwards?
So that's all the monkey's worth?
Darn it!
You jerk!
H-He caught it while running backwards!
I lost...
He knew right where the ball was going.
I didn't even stand a chance!
Monta...
Happy now?
Later!
Oh, right.
What was Honjo's motto again?
You need 99% effort and 1% talent, right?
How funny!
You don't even have 1% of talent!
Knock it off, Ikkyu!
You didn't have to be so cruel!
Even...
...if that's true...
Even... if I don't have 1% of talent,
I'll defeat you with 100% effort!
Monta...
Yeah, right.
Give it your best shot.
Monta...
I will!
I WILL!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
The Kongo brothers are so different,
even though they're twins!
Why does he put himself out for his little brother like this?
It's one of those complex relationships
that only people with siblings can understand.
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Talent Barrier!
Ya-ha!
"Don't cross this bridge"?
This is part of a racial joke, where different countries handle the "uncrossable bridge" in their own unique ways.
Hey!
This wasn't supposed to be taken literally!
Ikkyu! Ikkyu!