Against Shin, even Eyeshield's...
Like a scrap of paper.
No more...
It hurts too much!
All right, group around Eyeshield 21.
Just a little further.
What'd I just say?
Fighting until the end-
I can get past him.
A little longer... Just a little longer...
You wanna beat Shin?
I do!
I'm so close...
That's why... I don't want to quit yet!
Okay. Huddle up!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Never Quit!
All right, listen up, Eyeshield 21.
There's only one way for you to beat him.
5.13 seconds.
Good. Next!
Shin!
Shin's up. Wonder what his time'll be.
He's pretty fast, ain't he? You'd better believe it.
Ready...
4.37.
Holy cow!
You're something else, man.
It's like you run at the speed of sound!
Speedy ground?
The-speed-of-SOUND.
It's how fast sound waves travel.
So it means he's a real speed demon, right?
I still have yet to hit the wall.
The absolute limit for humans
is a 4.2 second 40-yard dash.
Even most pros can't do it.
I see... So if 4.4 seconds is like the speed of sound, then 4.2 is the speed of light, huh?
That's how high the wall is.
Basically, you've gotta run at the speed of light!
But I...
That's easy to say, but lightspeed is-
You wanna win, don't you?
Hut, hut, hut...
I don't know if I can do it, but at this point...
Hut!
I've gotta go for it!
He's gotten even faster!
Does it seem like their quarterback...
...is intentionally setting his blockers so Eyeshield will end up against Shin?
Either way, this is rare.
Shin is never this spirited.
You know, they've been coming straight to your side for a while now.
Want me to give you a hand?
No. Please stay focused on blocking the others.
I would prefer everyone force Eyeshield to come to me.
He won't get through...
I'll never let him pass!
Okay!
Deimon's #21 appears to be down. We need a stretcher out here, on the double!
Huh? It didn't hurt as bad this time.
He hit me from a different angle...
Is Shin's tackle getting sloppy?
No, maybe... Maybe I'm getting faster?
You okay?
Oh, yes!
I almost made it...
Go get 'em!
I can do this!
I thought I had it...
Hut!
This time!
Are you all right?
You're not injured, are you?
Uh-Umm...
I want to outrun him... no matter what.
Looks like the battle of the MVPs goes to Shin.
Set, hut!
He's so amazing... He's in a different world.
Sakuraba!
Ace!
Ace Sakuraba!
No, I'm no ace...
I'm not even close!
That's my last sticker. Do NOT lose it.
Uh-oh!
He's going around the line again!
Whoops-
This time, I'll-WHA?
Don't insult the equipment with this garbage!
This kind of carelessness is what leads to injuries!
Sakuraba!
Doctor!
Sakuraba, no!
Please, calm down!
Stay back, please!
You can't die!
Running onto the field is dangerous!
He may have a broken collarbone.
Call an ambulance right away!
Is he all right?!
How are you going to fix this?!
Do you know how many appearances we have Sakuraba booked for?!
We can't wait for an ambulance, I'll take him in my car.
Quit gawking and help me!
What have you done to Sakuraba?!
You're evil! Dirty cheater!
It's nothing to get worked up about, Sena.
Well, duh. It's that moron's fault for jumping out on the field during a play.
Plus, he would've caught me that time, anyway.
If I get a little further next time... Yeah...
Now THAT'S how you take the field.
All right guys, get ready for the final battle.
Since they've had Shin and Otawara in the center this whole time,
we've had to make big, sweeping runs to the outside.
But this time, we'll come out of nowhere,
with a charge up the center!
Get the jump on them! Charge straight up the middle right after the hike!
Use all your power and speed to open up a path!
Hut!
You've got real guts.
Time to decide who's the strongest lineman once and for all!
He's gonna make it!
Nope, on that course, Shin wins.
It's no good, I can't outrun him!
Go!
No, it's not over. Everyone worked to give me this chance!
Blast off, Eyeshield 21!
A little more... Just a little faster...
And I'll escape... No... I'll win!
You won't get away!
Football clinic!
What's Sena's position!
Running back! They take the ball and run forward.
You need a fast athlete for this position! Ya-ha!
You won't get away!
Th-This is... The world of lightspeed...
Woohoo!
S-Shin couldn't...
Whoa...
You used all your energy in that one shot, huh...?
Sorry...
It was just once.
You only made it one time in dozens of tries...
But you beat him.
Here. Great job!
Settle down, change your voice...
Thank you, Mamori...
Don't tell me... Sena...
...told you about me?
I guess you learned up my name from him?
It's scary how clueless she is.
Oh, no, we just met at halftime-
Now that you mention it, I haven't seen Sena since he went shopping at halftime.
I wonder what happened...
He's up in the stands taking pictures.
With football, it's easier to figure out what's going on when you're up high.
Oh, I see.
If you see Sena later, will you tell him something for me?
S-Sure...
Tell him "You can accomplish a lot, even though you're small."
He's kind of a scaredy-cat, so I thought if he heard that from you,
it'd give him the courage to try things he's afraid of.
Ya-hagh...
Kurita...
We finally advanced past the first round...
And it's already over...
That's right... The tournament's over.
Well, we learned one thing.
Ojo's team this year isn't up to par with last year's.
They'll make it to the final four, at best.
That's true.
And surprisingly Deimon's really pulled themselves together, huh?
That's a good one!
I lost! I lost to Kurita!
Line up!
All right, come on.
Against speed you can't even touch, no amount of power is enough.
Ojo WILL play in the Christmas Bowl.
Huh?
What're you doing?!
Coach Shoji!
Will you give us a statement about today's game?
There were no winners in today's game.
But in this world, only those who endure defeat become stronger!
The season has only begun!
My joints are shot...
But now I can live without fearing for my life... I hope...
Good morning!
I'm sorry, Sena! Are you okay?! Should I call an ambulance?!
I'm fine... Just sore from the Ojo game yesterday...
Sore?
Well you know, I had to run all over the place buying things!
Oh, you had me worried!
You made it sound like you had actually played in the game.
Hey, Manajerk. You took care of editing the tapes, right?
I don't answer to that horrible name.
What was that?
What was THAT?
They're fighting again?
Oh yeah!
Where are the pictures you took, Sena?
You were up in the stands all that time taking shots, right?
Oh, I-
Already got them developed.
Wow, there are so many!
Make sure you get 'em sorted after school!
Now the clause at the end of this sentence, particularly...
It's weird, how things went back to normal so fast.
Here's your lunch, I ended up making enough for two.
Oh, and it's going to rain later, so here's my spare umbrella. Brown's okay, right?
Everything's back to the way it was before.
And to top it off, I'm not anyone's gopher.
I don't do anything. Nothing happens.
It's all uneventful and ordinary.
Okay, gotta sort the pictures.
There's a ton of them!
I was so absorbed in the game, it was crazy...
It really was a lot of fun.
It's all because I met him...
Ya-ha!
Don't chicken out on me!
Blaze a path down the field!
You only made it one time in dozens of tries, but you beat him.
The country's top high school linebacker, Seijuro Shin.
It's all over...
...after just two weeks. It was like a dream.
If our team had just been better we'd still be in the tournament, out on the field right now...
Don't tell me you're not done sorting the pictures, Peewee!
Sorry to rush you.
We're already getting ready for the Christmas Bowl!
Isn't the tournament over?
There are two of them per year.
One in the spring, and one in the fall.
The winner of the fall tournament goes to the Christmas Bowl!
Fall is the real deal. That's the only one we need to win.
Ojo WILL play in the Christmas Bowl.
So that's it...
At any rate,
we gotta do something about him.
If we're gonna win the fall tournament, we'll have to play Ojo at some point.
We still have fall.
The real battle is still ahead!
Everything's still out here...
Oh, I guess it's the manager's job to clean up.
In this world, only those who endure defeat become stronger!
Anyone who plays on this field will suffer that humiliation at least once.
Not one athlete exists who hasn't stumbled, fallen or failed at some point.
But the most elite athletes are those who stand right back up and keep working.
The average ones hesitate a moment, and take longer to rise.
And the losers are content to stay flat on their backs!
Kurita?
Pass!
Why don't you give this a try?
Sure!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
Yay! Sena, you say there's a catching master trying out for the baseball team?
Yes! His name is "Monta Kaminari!"
We absolutely have to get him on the football team!
Huh? You sure you want someone with such a weird name?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Catching Master! Ya-ha!
Wait, so who took all these pictures?
Yo!
Who wants some Sakuraba snapshots from this season?
Me, me!
Me, too!
Okay, then!
I'll trade them with whoever takes the most pictures of today's game that AREN'T of Sakuraba!
It's a deal!
You got it!
What am I supposed to do with a million pictures of myself?!