Hiruma, I just told everyone that they have the day off.
Okay.
Is that Ojo's formation?
Yeah. There are plenty of things we can still while letting our bodies rest up.
You don't have to shoulder everything, you know.
You don't have to hold up a strong front for everyone anymore.
They aren't lazy.
Quit your yacking, Manajerk!
Wanna make a bet?
Will they stop by the club room or not?
I wanna practice!
Why can't we have practice today?!
Yeah, our game against Ojo's coming up.
There's the Ballista and Everest Pass.
Ojo's prided itself on having the strongest defense.
And now its offense is max strong, too.
I can't just sit still!
Yeah! Let's go study our videos of Ojo.
Hey!
Hurray! Hurray!
Suzuna?
Kurita?
Huh?
What's the...
...special occasion?
Everyone's here...
See? I knew they'd come!
I'm impressed everyone came by the club room even though you've got the day off!
Everyone, look up!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
It's just, so we can win!
Hiruma, where'd you get this helicopter?
Doesn't matter. Just look down!
Hey, what's that?!
The field's broken up by color.
Look at the guys standing on the field!
It's Ojo and Deimon?
N-No, that's...
Why the heck do I have to do this anyway?!
We couldn't refuse since the orders came from HIM.
Darn that Hiruma!
Habashira!
Wow! Lookie, lookie! There's someone impersonating Sena!
Why am I a pig?!
That's taking things too far!
I don't even get a mask on my guy!
Listen up, kiddies!
You're looking at Ojo's ultimate defense.
Each player's defense zone is a different color.
It's been broken up perfectly to create a perfectly coordinated defense.
If we don't stick to the zones' seams, we're doomed.
The best place to see the seams is up here in the air.
Memorize them like your lives depend on it!
- Right!
Oh, so this is your last trick before the game, huh?
Then let's use THAT.
- Sakuraba!
- Look over here!
He's great!
You're ruining practice!
- You're bugging us!
- Oh, scary! Stingy! Jerk!
But those two are just as impressive as ever.
There's no way Ojo could lose to Deimon!
Do you really believe that, Ikari?
There's no guarantee who'll win.
Victory is merely the glory that goes to the team that worked the hardest.
Y-Yes, sir!
Listen up!
There's only three days left before the game with Ojo.
We've gotta do everything we can so we'll win!
So we'll use...
...these.
Masks?
Hey! Everyone, fight!
Five minutes left!
Five whole minutes left...
I'm getting dizzy...
Because of the mask...
...it feels like my lungs are being stretched out...
This is tough!
I know about this!
It's mask training. I did it with the baseball team.
It lessens the amount of air you intake.
It gives you the same stamina boost that high-altitude training gives.
Who said it'd be that easy?
You, too!
How's that?
It's on so tight I can't take it off!
I-I can barely even breathe!
It hurts...
Of course it does! For the next three days keep that wet thing on!
That wet mask will restrict your air intake big time!
You've got to develop enough stamina that you can handle playing Ojo!
Max stamina! Stamina...
This is really... hard.
Is there enough time for this to help with the game against Ojo?
Well, when you take off your masks
you'll feel light like you've just removed a heavy load.
This power boost just has to last for a day.
But...
...isn't this overkill?
We'll give out before the game!
Let's go, Sakuraba.
Got it! This is the first time I got above Shin!
Good job, Sakuraba!
Thanks!
Up that high, my fingers couldn't even touch it.
Shin...
But this was just practice.
In a real game, you wouldn't have stuck next to me and tried competing with me.
Yeah. But that's what puny Taro Raimon is going to do.
His catching ability was even able to surpass Ikkyu's from Shinryuji.
But... regardless, I'll use my height to win.
Hey, get going!
Max Catch!
- Amazing!
How was it?
Yeah, it's just like you said!
If you stick to him like glue, even Sakuraba will have problems.
Yep! I'll prove to everyone that I always win in a catching contest!
Right. I think you'll be just fine.
Now you can defend against Sakuraba's height.
His height...
But if I'm fighting with Sakuraba for a ball that's up so high I can't reach it...
Nah, I've gotta stick with my dream of being the number one receiver!
I can't lose to Sakuraba!
That's the spirit!
Yeah!
Are you okay, Yukimitsu?
Ju-Jumonji... I-I'm... just... fine...
But-
Hey, what's keeping you, Yukimitsu?!
Get going already!
O-Okay!
H-Hey!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What do you call it when you carry the ball over your opponents' end zone?
Wow! That's an easy question!
When you carry the ball to your opponents' end zone, it's called a touchdown.
It's okay to catch a pass at the end zone, too.
Cross over the enemy's turf! Ya-ha!
It's finally over...
I'm max exhausted.
We're doing this for three days....
I'll keel over!
Are you okay, Yukimitsu?
Practice is already over, so you can take off that mask now.
Don't take it off!
W-What's your problem?!
I told you! Keep that thing plastered to your face for the next three days!
Three days? You mean...?
That's exactly what I mean.
It's on during class, when you bathe, even when you sleep!
Will this test of will actually help us win?!
What, you don't want to win?
Of course I want to win, but-!
Then quit arguing and keep it on!
But only if you really want to win!
Thanks for the food!
I can't blow on it!
This sucks!
This mask is so annoying!
Seriously.
What's with them?
They look suspicious.
Darn it! Is there really a point behind doing this?!
Hey, give me 21 more laps! Keep running!
Here you go!
Max Catch!
Here's the next one!
Next!
Max Catch!
Yuki?!
Yuki!
Are you okay?
Yukimitsu, get up on your own!
Awake yet?
Quit goofing off and get back to work!
Let him take a break!
Enough is enough!
You're taking this practice way too far!
If this is all you can handle, then you'll never defeat Ojo.
Is a stamina boost really enough to help us win?!
There's got to be a better way to do this!
Take off that mask, and you're outta the game.
What?! You little-
Jumonji!
Calm down!
Stop it!
What the crap can this little mask do, anyway?!
Don't YOU want us to win?!
Practice is finally over...
Jumonji, thanks for what you said today...
I'm not done yet!
I'm not through with him yet!
Where the heck is Doburoku?!
Dobu said he's got an errand to run by Enoshima and left.
Enoshima? Fine!
H-Hey, wait!
Jumonji!
Jumonji...
I knew it.
I thought you'd be here.
Doburoku...
Deimon's strong now.
But Ojo's still better.
Doburoku and... Ojo's coach?
Deimon's stronger!
NO, Ojo is!
What are they doing?
But isn't this ironic?
To think that we're back on Enoshima Field together, but this time on opposite sides.
Yeah.
I still have dreams about it.
Geez, I guess I'll never stop regretting that game.
We were called the Twin Blades.
We put our lives into these games,
and this is the very field where
our last game brought an end to our fleeting dreams when we lost by one point.
I was just a few centimeters too short to throw a good pass...
And I was just a few centimeters too short to catch it.
I know that's why you waited so long for that tall Sakuraba boy to shape up.
Thanks to Sakuraba's height, Ojo is no longer just a defensive team.
Is that...
...Ojo's coach?
There's Dobu.
Looks like they're talking about something.
But what?
G-Guys...
But there's no guarantee who'll win.
There's no guarantee, but with an insane amount of hard work and determination,
you can come pretty close to it.
Yeah, that's why I swore an oath.
I don't care how much they hate me for it,
I'll do anything to help them win!
Considering you, you're putting them through an insane regiment.
Pretty much. But as a result, our receiver's been improving with amazing speed.
Our line's improved a lot.
Thanks to Otawara's increased speed, the new line is fierce!
That goes for Deimon, too!
Togano's got power, Jumonji technique and Kuroki speed.
And Komusubi's got determination.
They may not be master linemen, but their strong fighting spirit is helping them to improve.
And Yukimitsu is definitely toning up.
Our offense has grown just that much stronger because of his hard work.
But... in the end, the key battle is between those two...
Yeah.
I want them to win no matter what.
I feel the same way.
But...
...one of us...
- ...must lose!
This sake is meant to cleanse the field for tomorrow.
This is... the finals of the century.
Coach Doburoku...
Wow!
Let's go!
H-Hey!
Jumonji?!
We're running outta time! We've gotta get in some more practice!
Geez, Kazu's...
...not honest with himself.
I'll go, too!
Looks like they're all right now.
Yep.
Enoshima Field...
The finals are coming up.
Yeah...
We've gotta win the Kanto Tournament semi-finals no matter what.
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
A surprise interview before the game with Ojo?!
But Sena's so nervous he's as stiff as a stone!
This is my time to shine!
You're just as bad!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Demon vs. The Lightspeed Man!
Ya-ha!
Dobu sure was cool today.
He seemed so mature!
Manger, could you cover these with the team funds?
Oh, sure.
Hey, Dobu, lookin' cool!
Later!
Mask fee, sake fee, sake fee, sake, sake fee...?
Coach Doburoku!
Crap!
Aside from the mask fee, we're not covering any of these fees!
Why not?! It was to purify the field!
Not happening!
Knew it.
Ew, how lame.