It's a full house!
And we're gonna be on TV... I'm really getting psyched up!
At long last, the day has come.
Everyone's been anticipating this game!
Will we see the full power of X High, a premier American football school?
Or will the quintessential anti-hero, Eyeshield 21, lead a stunning upset?
It's finally time!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Blitz! Japan vs. USA!
Representatives from both teams come out to greet each other!
I'm scared! I'm gonna lose! Help!
Still acting like a child, I see!
I figured you'd be playing in diapers, you're so immature!
I think you're hallucinating.
You going senile, at your age?
Maybe YOU oughtta be wearing adult diapers.
Get over yourself, kid.
I trust you haven't forgotten our wager.
If you don't beat us by ten points...
We'll leave Japan the same day.
But if you don't beat US by ten points...
You can never go back to America!
What?!
When did they make such a huge bet?!
Men!
Show no mercy.
I want them knocked out on the first play!
Yes, sir!
One small step for man, one giant leap for the NASA Aliens!
Panther's not dressed...
They're gonna come at us full blast.
Tackle their QB before he throws, like we practiced!
Blitz him!
You lead the charge!
Wha- Already?!
Set! Hut, hut, hut...
Tackle Homer...
Hut!
...before he throws!
They're blitzing!
Eyeshield 21-kun charges forward!
I have to make room for Sena to get through!
Ah, but they can't do anything against the NASA Aliens' Muscle Barrier!
Th-That's...
In the Taiyo game, it felt like the line was too heavy to move...
It's more than weight, it's tenacity!
These are real American physiques!
In other words...
Massive mounds of mighty muscle!
Hey, cool it on the alliteration.
Three... two... one... Zero!
If he catches that, it'll be a touchdown!
Shoot, he's just a little faster than me!
Eyeshield, cover him with me!
You're all the way back there?!
I was trying to blitz them...
Arrgh!
It's good! A successful Shuttle Pass! Touchdown!
Oh no!
You see that?
A touchdown on the first play!
That's our Shuttle Pass!
The blitz is a gamble where you ignore covering the backfield to charge into the pocket!
If they do manage to throw a long bomb, the receivers are wide open!
They scored outta nowhere.
We need to defend their long pass-
Double up on the blitz.
We blitz again!
What's up with Jumonji? He's all jacked up.
Kurita, Komusubi and Jumonji made some key plays,
but Kuroki and Togano were practically useless?!
Kazuki.
Are you still friends with those lowlifes?
"Throw away your trash."
That's a little rule we have in the corporate world.
They'll never say that again.
They'll never say anything like that again!
They aren't trash!
They can take their shuttle pass and shove it. I WILL stop them!
Deimon's offense ends with no score, and the Aliens take possession again.
Will another superior supersonic shuttle pass sail across the sky?
You're really having fun with that, huh?
Set, hut, hut!
Th-They're-
Blitzing with three men!
Now! Blitz 'em!
Eyeshield charges at Homer!
I've gotta hit him straight on!
Yes! We stopped the Shuttle Pass!
Not yet! Don't let up!
Three... two... one...
Zero!
Touchdown!
We practiced blitzing so much!
How could he still throw it from that position?
The Aliens are already up 14-0!
Their bodies make all tackles moot!
This is elite! This is "American Muscle!"
Their plan to stop the shuttle was blitzing?
If that's the best they could come up with, we're on easy street!
What a bunch of monkey-brains!
Deimon is in deep trouble early on!
Can they find a way to ground the Shuttle Pass?
Deimon's got it rough.
There's a big power difference between them and the Americans.
The quarterback's method for stopping them is flawed.
Method? I always just try to smash as hard as I can.
Well, I think most of us put a little more thought into it...
Power is important to a blitz, but not as much as speed.
Eyeshield 21, you may very well be the key.
Can the Devil Bats mount a comeback?
Set, hut, hut!
I'll use Ishimaru as a shield...
He knocked the shield and the carrier down in one shot...
Looks like you boys are getting deported.
Is that all there is to your running, Eyeshield 21?
This way, I have a slight chance...
Eyeshield gives up on charging through and makes a dash for the edge!
One more time...
Let me blitz him one more time.
There's something I want to try.
Football Clinic!
What happens in a blitz?
The secondary defenders behind the line charge forward!
It's a power move where you sacrifice defense to stop the opponent's play! Ya-ha!
The Aliens are back on offense!
Will the Shuttle Pass launch again?!
You're gonna ground the Shuttle Pass by hitting Homer's weak spot?
Yes.
Rush 'em with speed they can't defend.
You up for this?
I'll do my best.
Set!
Hut, hut!
Sena's so motivated; I won't let anyone near him!
This time...
It's hopeless!
Now!
What the-?!
The moment you underestimate Eyeshield 21, you lose.
Let go, let go!
No matter how talented he is, he can't pass if I've got his throwing arm!
The launch has been scrubbed!
It's #21, the shooting star!
There.
That's the real Eyeshield 21.
Stop him!
The muscle's coming!
He's surrounded!
It's wasn't quite a touchdown. Is this it?!
Big-
and useful!
Change of Pace...
He changes his speed in an instant,
Then just as you think he's about to stop, he switches to his top speed just as quickly!
THIS is Eyeshield 21.
That's the sharp running I saw!
He's always been that way.
His speed's variable.
Just when you think he's about to pee his pants, he hits his top speed, even faster than Shin.
So that variation's... the Change of Pace!
It must've been very helpful in his former life as a gopher.
A scared little kid forced to run errands becomes a football hero.
Touchdown!
Yay!
We're hosed.
Even Watt, our fastest guy, couldn't catch him.
No one on our team...
No one...?
What am I doing stuck on the bench?
Eyeshield strikes again.
He's something else!
He'd better be.
I can get past them with my speed.
Their strength's nothing to fear as long as I have speed!
Formation number 5!
Set!
Hey, no fair, we're not done yet!
A no-huddle offense.
Without time to plan, Deimon's organization will collapse!
Your biggest weakness is your lack of a coach on the sideline.
But a veteran team that can act without needing time to think of a plan is different.
Eyeshield, Track Team, the two of you are blitzing.
I heard that.
Two rushers coming up the center. Okay.
Hut!
Watt rushes up the middle!
He'll make the completion easily on a two-man blitz.
Now pass it down the center, just like in the playbook.
A four-man blitz?!
Homer gets sacked! The pass is incomplete!
Yeah, right according to plan!
If they start a no-huddle offense, everything that comes out of my mouth will be a bluff.
Pay attention to the secret signs!
Yo, Manajerk! Are you so hungry you needed four of those things?
Four?
Of course not! I was still coming up with a play.
Four sticks... A four-man blitz...
OH, NO!
But even if our defense holds the rest of the game, if we don't start scoring points...
Time for the Sweep, bros!
Sweep?!
You guys and Eyeshield lump together and the three of you sweep away any blockers.
No logic, no planning.
Force your way through!
Make sure you protect Eyeshield.
If this doesn't work, we'll never manage to score.
This is where we sink or swim.
Sink or swim...
Our chance to prove we're not trash!
Eyeshield... we're not veterans like you.
Oh, well, I'm a freshman too...
You're incredible.
You can slip through even the tiniest gap.
Compared to you, we all have a long, long way to go.
We're not good enough to take those Americans down.
But we...
"Throw away your trash."
We want to make people rethink their opinions of us!
Please!
Kuroki, Togano and I will find some way to block them...
Please get through!
I'm begging you!
Set, hut, hut!
Everyone's got a reason to stay in the fight.
For their pride...
To prove something...
To protect something...
Or to gain something!
We all have our own reasons... But...
We have to hold them here...
We...
...are NOT trash!
The Muscle Barrier's breaking up!
Now, Eyeshield!
I can make it!
But we all have the same goal... Winning!
First down, Deimon!
What tenacity!
Last time, I wrote that Kuroki and Togano were worthless.
I'll have to apologize to them next time!
Kuroki! Togano! Jumonji!
Huh?
They're cheering for us?
All you have to do is win, and they'll all love you for it.
Quitters are even lower than trash!
So win!
That's how you get what you want in football.
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
The Devil Bats are coming back!
But... Sena, you're in a weird mood!
I want to face him... Panther!
I want to take on the "Zero-G Legs!"
Oh ho, looks like Sena's pumped!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Caged Black Panther! Ya-ha!
Look at that massive mountain of muscle!
They can't beat this!
Would you PLEASE pull up your pants?
Oh, my bad.