Wild Wild Gunmen!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 107 - Uraharajuku Boarders 16
Bando Spiders 9 - Mitama Mariners 6
Keep those cameras rolling!
The Sengoku Samurai are about to make their mark by destroying Ojo,
and me, the coach, is here to present his take!
We'll start with their stiff of a coach,
and my fellow Sengoku alum, coach Shoji.
He's still an overzealous slave driver,
just like he was back in our Sengoku days!
But today, I'll teach him that being rigid and harsh doesn't always win games!
Stretcher! We need a stretcher!
Ojo White Knights 34 - Sengoku Samurai 0
The Ojo White Knights, the Seibu Wild Gunmen,
The Bando Spiders, and the Kyoshin Poseidons.
That fills four of the "best eight" slots.
And our next opponents are...
- The Dokubari Scorpions.
You again?
Who are you?
Mamori, this guy's a massive cheater from the Dokubari Scorpions, Kanagushi!
What do you want?
I thought I'd give the Deimon Devil Bats fair warning.
Warning?
The game has already begun.
The scorpion's stinger is poised above your heads.
Especially for Yoichi Hiruma and Eyeshield 21.
Without those two, Deimon will collapse.
Make sure you tell them to stay on their toes!
W-What?
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Fearsome, Venomous Scorpions!
Let's see... The Dokubari Scorpions...
Their record this year...
10 wins and 1 loss?!
- Whaa?!
A-Are you sure?
Yes...
They're not in the same league as Ojo or Seibu, but...
Even still, that's impressive!
The problem is HOW they won.
How they won?
Take a closer look at the scores, Manajerk.
What is it this time?
Half their wins were from forfeits!
In other words, they won without even playing.
Another odd point is how right before game time,
their opponents would start fighting amongst themselves,
or their best players would suddenly be injured
and they'd be forced to give up.
VERY convenient.
The scorpion's stinger is poised above your heads.
He's got some kind of evil plan!
...Yeah.
Even in the first round,
their opponent's best running back hurt his leg in an accident,
and the Scorpions routed them 13-0.
Don't bother me.
If they've got their sights on us...
We'll just shoot first!
N-No, then we'll just be disqualified!
We'd be playing right into their hands.
Then we're just supposed to hang out and let them jump us?
Forget that!
Violence is prohibited! Right? Right, Hiruma?
Hiruma...
If we gotta fight, we fight!
N-No!
Violence is prohibited!
- Too heavy!
We have to be very careful!
I don't want anyone to get injured-
- WE'RE getting injured!
At least we don't have to worry about you, Sena.
You're just a manager.
Huh? Oh, yeah...
Especially for Yoichi Hiruma and Eyeshield 21.
Are we gonna be okay?
Spikes!
What happened, Sena?
Who put thumbtacks in there?!
A shot put?
Who'd be throwing those all the way out here?
It couldn't be!
Look out!
You all right?
There's no way this would've just collapsed.
You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine...
A bolt's missing.
I know they were locked in tight yesterday.
I dunno who did this, but they're trying to hurt someone from Deimon.
Watch your backs.
W-W-W-What do we do?!
YOU need to keep calm!
Deimon's still a young team.
If the founding players don't act rational,
the group will fall apart like this scaffold!
Then again, what do I care?
Musashi...
Something bad might happen if we're alone,
so we should stick together as often as possible!
We ain't in kindergarten, man.
What is this, the buddy system?
Lame.
Oh yeah. Manajerk!
I am SICK of that name!
What is it?!
Hang on to this.
Our game plan for Dokubari.
Why do you want me-
Just take it!
Okay!
You'll need it after the first quarter.
Don't open it before then!
That's Hiruma.
Wandering around on his own...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how you score in football!
The hints are "six" and "three!"
A touchdown is six points, a field goal is three.
Those are the two ways to score points.
Everyone get that? Ya-ha!
The stadium is completely packed!
And everyone is eagerly awaiting the Deimon Devil Bats vs the Dokubari Scorpions!
That includes me!
Both are considered dark horses in this tournament!
Both also hold victories over the Zokugaku Chameleons,
and will go on to face ANOTHER dark horse team, the Kyoshin Poseidons!
What kind of football do those Deimon midgets play?
I can't wait to find out.
Hiruma's late.
What do we do?
The game's about to start!
Wonder if everything's okay...
Oh, no!
What if Dokubari did something to Hiruma?
Huh?
To Yocchie?!
No way... Not Hiruma!
But for him to be missing right before the game...
That's never happened before!
Those dirty rats!
- We'll show them!
Whoa, Jumonji, what're you planning?!
What do you think?
We're gonna go beat a confession outta Dokubari!
Yeah!
But if you get in a fight-
I'm not gonna take another minute of this!
Please, guys, just hang in there.
Fighting will get us kicked out of the tournament!
Do you really want to end our journey to the Christmas Bowl?
Hiruma will be here.
Right.
Yes.
We need to keep calm and figure out how to play without Hiruma.
As our balding friend says...
This is another trial for you all.
How far can you go without Hiruma?
But who's going to play quarterback in Hiruma's place?
Well obviously I'll-
Ohh, noo!
The sun has disappeared!
- It's the end of the world!
- Stop acting up.
C-Coach Doburoku, what do we do?
With Hiruma gone, you're in charge.
M-Me?!
O-Okay. You're right.
Umm... Okay... Ishimaru.
Who?
W-WHAAT?!
How come, Kuriton?
We all have about the same level of passing skill,
so long passes are out of the question.
But since Ishimaru can run,
he can carry the ball himself, too...
I'll be quarterback?
Me? In such an important position?!
Both teams take the field!
Oh? What's this, now?
I don't see Hiruma in there.
What did you do to him?
Huh?
What are you referring to, now?
Don't play dumb!
You're a cheating scumbag!
We're gonna make you pay!
Scary!
But if you try anything funny,
YOU'RE the ones who'll be disqualified.
N-No, don't fall for his taunts!
I'd appreciate if you didn't accuse me of things without any proof!
- That stupid grin is all the proof we need!
I still don't know what you're talking about!
But I'd be cautious during the game, too.
How despicable.
No matter how badly you want to win,
things like this are unforgivable!
Why isn't Hiruma out there with Deimon?
What will Deimon do?
As planned, their team's heart, Hiruma, is gone.
Now let's really mess them up.
E-E-Everyone, just s-s-stay calm.
We'll play just like always, okay!
That weasel...
We'll destroy him on the first play!
Yeah, just you wait!
R-Rip their heads off... Ya... ha...
That was... kinda weak.
It's game time!
How will Deimon function without Hiruma?
This will be a true test for them!
Those three linebackers will be gunning for me.
I'll run a fake scramble...
Set, hut, hut!
Get him!
The quarterback's carrying the ball himself, it's a scramble!
No, look!
Kanagushi doesn't have the ball!
- The ball's...
Shoot!
Dokubari Scorpions 6 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Touchdown!
Nice work by the Dokubari Scorpions!
Kanagushi executes a brilliant play!
Football's all about up here.
Hiruma's absence is hurting them more than expected.
Eyeshield 21 and Kurita can try all they like,
but Hiruma is the key to the Devil Bats as a team.
So, what should we do next?
Uh, right...
Eyeshield will be marked,
so let's try a short pass to Taki.
Okay... A pass.
Their quarterback's not used to the position.
It'll be either an Eyeshield run or a short pass to the tight end.
We'll focus on those two...
Now's it's time for Deimon to go on offense!
What a noob!
Licking your fingers is a dead giveaway you're going to pass,
because it helps keep the ball from slipping!
It'll be a short pass.
Set, hut hut!
Get the tight end!
Oh, no! Help me!
He caught it!
The Scorpions intercept and run it in for a touchdown!
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
They can read us like a book...
An early 14-0 lead!
The Devil Bats can't seem to get in gear!
Dokubari! Dokubari!
The Devil Bats fail again!
Their passes, their runs, nothing they do is working!
It's no good...
Come on, what's happening?!
They're predicting all our offensive plays,
and without Hiruma, everyone's completely lost confidence.
We don't stand a chance.
How can you say that?
They're the ones out on the field.
Them and only them.
We've gotta figure out a plan with who we've got!
We can't wait for a miracle!
They have to do this themselves!
What do we do...?
At this rate...
This game's getting sticky...
W-What do I do...?
Everyone's getting frustrated...
YOU need to keep calm!
That's right...
With Hiruma missing, I've gotta take charge.
Argh, I can't take this!
I'm gonna clobber that shrimp!
Don't try to stop us, Jumonji!
I won't!
I've had enough, too!
No, guys!
Move it!
That weasel!
Freeze!
Kurita...
Move it!
I'm not moving!
Listen, Hiruma WILL show up.
And until he does, we need to do our jobs!
Yeah... Hiruma will make it.
We've suffered through so much, just for a shot at the Christmas Bowl.
We can't lose now!
Not to those cheaters!
Right...
If Hiruma's not here, we need to make up for his absence!
Yeah!
If we don't, the Yuhi Guts and Zokugaku will never forgive us!
Win!
Yes.
I've been thinking about what Hiruma would do.
If Hiruma were here, he'd say,
"Wake up, their line's not that tough!"
That's true...
Compared to Amino, they're not as heavy or as strong.
So if we hit them with a full frontal attack, we can open a path
and Eyeshield can run it through!
Okay, everyone?
Yeah!
Right!
We got this!
Okay, let's go! One, two...
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
Ya-ha!
I see they've got their heads back on.
We can do it... We can even cover for Hiruma!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Yo! They've got our offense figured out,
and with Hiruma gone, we're in deep trouble!
We've got to keep trying... We can't lose!
Can you really win this without Hiruma?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Missing Leader! Ya-ha!
E-Everyone just relax...
It's our big brother!
Our boy, our boy...
He's in the spotlight!
We'll celebrate with red snapper, WITH the head left on!
Yahoo!