You're all benched!
I don't need people who refuse to follow my directions!
I... I can stop Eyeshield.
Please, give me one last chance!
If I can't hold him back...
I'll quit the team!
You don't get... anymore chances...
W-What's the meaning of this?!
We're asking you, too!
Please let Panther play!
Please trust us as a team!
Please!
Give us a chance!
Please let Panther play!
Fine...
For this game, and only this game...
Stop Eyeshield at all costs.
That's your only role!
Yes, sir!
Moonsault formation!
Run fast and free like you were on the moon, Panther!
Moonsault formation?
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
A Real Beast!
Deimon leads 26-21!
Can the Aliens turn things back in their favor?
That's-
What the heck are they doing?
Is this their Moonsault formation?
They've got it all planned out.
They're gonna unlock the cage and release Panther into the wild.
Ya-ha!
Deimon kicks off and the game resumes!
Panther's got it, stop him!
Komusubi, we've gotta get him!
Go for it, Panther!
Show 'em what your legs can do!
He's so fast!
He ran... right though them!
W-What was that?!
Who is he?! There aren't any records...
Such light feet!
Ah, we've finally received some data!
He's known as "Panther, the man with the Zero-G legs!"
Unbelievable... Who is that guy?
Someone special.
Watch me go, Grandma.
I'm running down the field wearing an Aliens uniform!
Tackle him, Eyeshield 21!
You're the last line of defense!
Bring it, Eyeshield 21!
Get ready, Panther!
And there it is! Eyeshield 21's patented explosive speed burst!
It's nothing like when I run alone.
I have a powerful foe charging in to crush me!
THIS is football!
I'm playing football!
I've never felt anything like this...
The spirit-crushing depression of watching your opponent pull away,
even as you run at your top speed.
Touchdown!
E-Even Sena couldn't catch him...
What incredible legs...
It was inevitable.
Eyeshield 21 can only hit his top speed in small bursts.
On the other hand, that boy maintains his top speed while simultaneously avoiding tackles
by using his gravity-defying light step.
The extra point is no good!
But the Aliens have begun their counter-attack!
It's pure innate athleticism.
He was born with that gift.
Born to be a sprinter.
I was born to be a sprinter!
Don't matter who comes after me, I never lose!
Hate to say it, but none of the other guys'll ever even get a shot.
That's the reason I never used Panther...
Was I using that one little act of disobedience as an excuse?
Did I subconsciously resent him all this time...
Because he's a natural sprinter, like Morgan?
Ah, we've got the replay.
Here it is.
Komusubi came in for the tackle first.
He made a small cut at the last possible moment and slipped by.
And then the same thing for Kurita.
Thus, he originally appeared to simply pass straight through them!
His movements are completely different from Eyeshield's sharp cuts.
You could even call him the polar opposite of Eyeshield!
A one-point gap,
with nine minutes to go.
The game's just getting started!
Set, hut, hut!
Sweep him!
Panther makes the block!
The Devil Bats' sweep has been swept away!
Panther's a great defenseman, too!
He's too fast for me to avoid!
Okay, the real problem is the Aliens' offense.
They're more than just the Shuttle Pass now.
The Shuttle Pass and Panther's run...
Which do we defend against-
What do you think?! Both!
The Shuttle Pass lands, and the Aliens gain 20 yards!
Aaaaargh!
I can't focus on the pass with Panther out here.
Again! Panther shoots through like an arrow in flight!
And it's now a man-to-man showdown!
Panther scores the touchdown! Eyeshield has failed!
The NASA Aliens extend their lead to seven points!
We managed to stop the extra point, but...
I was so full of myself... To think I WANTED to face Panther...
His legs are as flexible as a whip, and his steps as light as a feather!
Can anyone bring Panther down?!
Football Clinic!
What is an "interception?"
When the defense catches a pass in midair.
It's a big play that puts the defense back on offense! Ya-ha!
Panther! Panther! Panther!
Eyeshield is stuffed again!
His arm.
Panther gets through by using his arm.
That's how he makes those small cuts without losing speed!
Their muscle compositions are too different.
That man's running style comes from his limbs being tough, but supple.
It's impossible to imitate.
So it's something innate to him...
In other words, Deimon is in a tough spot.
We humans are not born with equal ability.
There is always a barrier...
...that effort alone can't overcome.
Amazing!
Morgan is incredible!
The MVP of the Armadillos!
That's what a natural-born sprinter can really do!
Panther must be having the time of his life.
He's just happy to be out there, playing football again.
Happy...
How long has it been...?
The last time football was fun was in my school days...
I'll show you...
I'll create the ultimate team,
one without a single superstar!
A systematic, methodical team.
One full of faithful pawns who follow their coach's plans!
I thought the Aliens were the epitome of that ideal.
Eyeshield is caught again!
Can Deimon close the seven-point gap?!
Just two minutes...
They must all be exhausted.
It's getting to be too much.
Hey! Remember, we can't go back to America unless we win by ten!
It's all good!
Coach Apollo!
I'm stopping Eyeshield, just like you told me to!
Go ahead, give me another order!
So, Coach, do you know why Panther never quit, even though you wouldn't let him play?
Actually he gave us all a big lecture about you.
If you're not gonna stand up for yourself, the rest of us will chew the coach out for you!
Yeah, it's messed up that he just makes you the ball boy!
You only disobeyed him once, it's not that big a deal!
If we all talk to him, he'll have to listen!
H-Hey, hold up, guys!
Coach Apollo will... Look, if I'm really good, he'll use me, I know it!
I'm just not there yet.
Yeah right!
If you don't ever play, you'll never make it in the pros!
Panther's dream is to make the pros and so his grandmother can have an easier life.
He decided to play football...
...after watching a famous, respected player from his hometown team in action.
A second-string running back who put in three times the effort of his teammates:
Leonard Apollo.
No matter how badly you treated him, to Panther, you've always been a man worthy of great respect!
What's the plan, Coach?
Kee... Keep it up.
Yes sir!
Set, hut, hut!
Big and useful!
I'm the real deal.
Nail him!
Panther!
It's not just Panther... They're ALL having fun.
My ideal football team...
...might just be complete.
It's no good... I can't beat him.
Is he done?
Your running's pretty cool.
But you're not using your full power.
I'm gonna be the greatest running back in history.
So I have to hit guys like Seijuro Shin and Eyeshield...
...with all I've got!
You sure you're trying your hardest against me?
That's right...
Panther came all the way from America to face me.
I have to give it 100%!
I want to beat Shin, too.
I may not be able to run like you, Panther...
...but I still want to win, with my own style!
Now you're talking!
Less than a minute left! Both teams muster all their remaining strength!
Heads up, butt-monkey!
GO!
He intercepted it!
Panther rushes towards another touchdown!
Everyone's wiped out!
A touchdown here and we win by 14 points!
I have to stop him.
No good... When he uses his arm...
His arm?
How could he push me like that?
He's got both hands wrapped around the ball...
I get it!
He leaves himself vulnerable during that brief moment he pushes off,
because he has to take one hand off the ball!
He's a black panther, released from his cage for the first time.
He doesn't understand the real wilderness.
Eyeshield's running, developed from years of being a gopher...
...is the REAL beast.
Even a timid herbivore, when backed into a corner...
...can momentarily gain unimaginable power.
I won.
Now!
THAT is Eyeshield 21!
Instantly hitting the 4.2 second level...
The world of lightspeed!
I refuse to lose!
Touchdown!
H-Huh?
Nuts!
W-What was the final score?
Game over!
Deimon went for a two-point conversion on their final play, but the Muscle Barrier fended them off.
They didn't stand a chance without Eyeshield.
We can only wonder why they didn't try to tie it with a kick.
Ah yes, perhaps because Deimon doesn't have a kicker?
Even that one-point loss is miraculous.
In their current state, Deimon never stood a chance in the first place.
But that new batch of players made some great strides in that game.
Perhaps that was Hiruma's aim?
Eyeshield 21.
You beat me at the end.
Panther...
Nice game.
Coming in at the last moment gave me too much of an advantage.
Next time we'll start on even ground.
And you won't get past me again!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Yay! We're finally in America!
So why're you freaking out, Sena?
I'm in deep trouble, we lost Cerberus at the airport!
If he's on the loose, he'll eat all the meat in America!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Take Back Cerberus! Ya-ha!
I hate to break up this tender moment,
but you're gonna keep your end of the bargain.
Our passports!
And what about you?!
You all have to leave Japan immediately, remember?!
Ah, yes. I guess you don't need your plane tickets home anymore, right?
D-Don't tell us!
Ya-ha! We're getting special training in America!
Seriously?! Training in America?!