ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Blaze a Path Down the Field!
They're late...
The tournament starts today. My debut game as manager!
I wonder if Sena will be okay...
Sorry! I'm here, Mamori!
Morning.
Good morning!
Thanks for yesterday. Let's get 'em.
Glad to have you on board.
Hey! Is everyone here now?
Say what? You were the last one to show up.
Umm, Kurita's still not-
He's paying the price.
Oh yeah, what was the penalty for not finding any new-
Hey, Man-Pig! You finally made it!
This isn't as heavy as it looks!
Thank God... Thank God I recruited someone!
Sena, do you have the Tokyo Tournament match-up list?
Yes.
Are our first-round opponents any good?
Nah, they're actually pretty wimpy.
We might even squeak out a win!
The Devil Bats' first victory!
We ain't squeaking nothing, we're WINNING.
How many wins do you need to be Kanto champion?
We're here to win TODAY'S game, stay focused.
So our first-round opponents are...
The Koigahama Cupids.
Is it nummy?
Very nummy!
Yay! It's my mommy's recipe, I've never made it before!
This's the Koigahama Cupids' third year as a team.
Every member has a girlfriend, and they're famous for taking said girlfriends with them to games.
Whoopsie!
Hatsujo!
You'll have to forgive the angelic sounds of their cheering.
She wanted to come root us on so badly, she wouldn't take no-
Oh?! You gents don't have a single lady with you?
How odd... Is Deimon an all-boys school?
Can we go, please? I don't wanna catch loseritis from these dorks.
Oh, of course.
We've gotta beat them!
Let's do it!
All right! The team's been united!
Hey, manager! Where're OUR cheerleaders?
I thought we were supposed to have a whole bunch of 'em!
Uhh, real soon... Actually, there aren't any...
H-Hiruma!
Hey, that's...
Do we really need to bother taping such a low-tier game?
Stop that nonsense.
This is one of your bad habits, Sakuraba.
No matter who the opponent, there is no such thing as a guaranteed win.
Yeah, yeah.
I knew it, that's Haruto Sakuraba. What's a male model doing out here?
Sakuraba!
He's here, he's really here!
I told you! My sources are never wrong!
Sakuraba!
Hey, don't cut in front of me!
Hang on!
I wanna be first!
Are you okay?
Yes...
You all right?
It really IS you, Sakuraba!
Sakuraba!
That's Sakuraba from Jari Productions.
He's on his high school's football team, the Ojo White Knights. They're really tough.
That's really cool.
He still plays football even though he's a celebrity.
Sakuraba's a nobody.
He's our REAL enemy.
The White Knights' Shin.
The fastest, strongest high school linebacker there is.
He's way too tough.
Linebacker?
It's a defensive position.
A key player who has to stop both runs and passes.
Seeing him reminds me...
...of our scrimmage against Ojo last year.
You played them?
We managed to keep the final score to 99-0!
Did you win?!
Oh, they scored 99 times...
Oh, no, one goal in football is six points.
Learn the friggin' rules or you won't be any good to us on the field!
I'm telling you, I'm-
I should've gotten the other one.
I warned you not to regret it.
So you didn't buy anything, huh, Mamori?
N-Nope...
Well, good for you. I buy everything I see and I always wish I hadn't later.
Hey, are you guys hungry?
I'm starving!
How about burgers?
C'mon, Mamori!
Right!
Okay, football in a nutshell, you just have to run the ball into the end zone!
Then you get six points.
The end zone's right there.
So the goal's not those posts.
You can send it through them, too.
But that's only three points.
So it's better to run it, because that's six points.
When you can run it.
But the opponent will try to stop runners by tackling them, like this!
I say we put him in today.
It's too soon! And you're forcing him!
He can stay on the bench if we're ahead.
No reason to reveal our secret weapon if we don't have to.
But if we're down, even by one point, you're going in!
Huddle up!
That's right, as long as we win, I don't have to play.
Do your best, Devil Bats!
All right, ladies, if we lose, we're out of the tournament,
so don't even THINK about playing nice.
We're gonna destroy 'em, and that's all there is to it.
Rip their heads off! Yeah!
It's time for the Deimon Devil Bats vs. the Koigahama Cupids!
Football clinic!
How do you score points?
A player scores by carrying the ball into the end zone.
That gets you six points! Ya-ha!
Don't let them through! Stop that fatso!
Great rush!
Kurita did it again!
I'm starting to get a grasp on the rules.
You STILL don't know the rules?! I'll fix that!
First everyone lines up on their side like this,
and the center person for the offense hikes the ball through his legs!
That's the exact moment the game starts.
Bingo!
Then you can pass it, run it, or kick it!
The offense tries to make it all the way to the end zone.
And the defense does everything they can to smash the ball carrier before he gets there.
You get all that?!
I understand!
The second quarter is coming to an end.
Neither team has scored yet.
The Cupids do have some offensive prowess.
But they can't stop Kurita at all.
Well, Kurita even gives US trouble.
As for the Devil Bats' offense...
Incomplete pass!
You butt-munch!
That was a perfect pass.
Everyone but those two are amateurs.
Same as last year for them, huh?
Hiruma and Kurita are two good players surrounded by a mish-mash of random students.
You can barely even call them a team.
They need at least one more...
If they just had a solid running back, things would be completely different.
Well, they don't have anything close.
4th quarter with 20 seconds left.
Looks like it'll be a tie...
Uh-oh, we're really close to the goal!
All right, we're close enough for a field goal!
If we make the kick, we'll be up by three with just a few seconds to go.
This game's in the bag!
We HAVE to block that kick!
Yeah, I noticed.
The fastest one here is... the track guy, Ishimaru.
Man-Pig here will clear a path up the middle.
You've gotta rush in there before they can kick it.
Okay.
Set!
Miss!
Get in there!
It's good, with just a few seconds to go!
There's almost no time left and we're down by three...
Are we going to lose?
Is the tournament already over?
Ishimaru's hurt!
Ishimaru!
Shoot... I twisted my ankle...
What the...!
These spikes are for astroturf!
No wonder he slipped!
What idiot gave him these shoes?!
Ow ow ow ow!
For use on artificial fields...
You worthless excuse for a manager! Can't you even tell which spikes are which?!
I'm so sorry!
"Sorry" doesn't cut the mustard, that's why we have cops! Now c'mon!
Please forgive me!
The game's still not over...
See? Sagittariuses will have bad luck this month.
But it says that it's also the chance for O blood types to make their move!
The tournament starts today. My debut game as manager!
For some reason I have a really bad feeling...
Gotta go, I just remembered something!
What do we do? Who'll replace Ishimaru?
Heroes always show up...
...when they're needed most.
Lemme introduce the "Lightspeed Running Back..."
Eyeshield 21!
Your brought this on yourself, now take responsibility!
Who's that?
Tinted eye shields are against the rules, right?
Yes, they cause eyestrain, among other problems.
Of course, if he has permission from the association, it's another story.
Wow! Did you decide you want to play after all, Sen-
What? Playing CENter hurts your back?
Here, lemme kick out the kinks for ya!
You stupid Man-Pig! What're we gonna do if the other clubs find out who he is?!
They're here to try and borrow our members!
And plus,
I don't wanna give them ANY information on him.
We have to hide everything we can, even if it's just his identity.
Oh, I see.
I guess I'd better get rid of Sakuraba.
Get rid of him? How?
Huh? Isn't that the famous male model, Haruto Sakuraba?
Uh-oh. Sorry, you'll have to finish the video!
Sakuraba!
Sakuraba?
Whoa, it worked on Shin too!
Okay Eyeshield 21, you're free to run at top speed. There's nine seconds left!
This is our last play, you can laugh or cry when it's over!
The Cupids are gonna kick the ball to us.
There's no way you'll be able to make the catch, so I'll receive.
Then I'll toss it to you, and you dash it into the end zone!
We'll get six points and have us a killer 6-3 comeback win!
There's no way that will work out...
All ya gotta do is get past 11 guys!
"All" I have to do is-
That's our only chance!
You don't want it to end here either, right?
Well, I...
This is the last play. We have to shoot them down!
I'll NEVER get past all of them without getting knocked down!
You'll be fine... Probably!
I'm not strong enough, and I can't push them aside, Kurita...
What're you thinking about pushing people for?!
No one expects anything outta those spindly little arms.
That's right! You've got fast legs instead!
Blaze a path down the field!
Nine seconds left...
Here comes the Cupids' kickoff!
Nice kick!
Go!
The OTHER way!
That sack of crap, not the spikes AGAIN!
The ones for astroturf?!
No, The ones for sneakers...
If he fell, it's over.
You've got fast legs instead!
Blaze a path down the field!
11 opponents... That was one...
Two, three, four...
Who's that?!
High schoolers don't run that fast!
Blow past 'em!
Five, six, seven!
Is the game over, Ishimaru?
Not until this play ends...
Either he goes down, and we lose...
...or we come from behind.
Smash him!
Go!
There's no one left!
No one can stop me!
Ya-ha!
The Devil Bats' first win!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
YAY! The Devil Bats got their first win!
Their next opponents are the famous Ojo White Knights!
Hmm? But is Sena going to have to quit the football team?
Being a manager is hard work, and I don't want Sena anywhere NEAR Hiruma!
What's going to happen?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: What I Hold In My Hands!
Ya-ha!
We need him on the baseball team!
I dunno who he is, but he NEEDS to join the soccer team!
Man-Pig, block!
If they find out who you are, they'll ALL try to drag and pull you into to their clubs.
They'll run you ragged, and you'll go through all of high school without a second of free time!
But hey, maybe you'd like it.
You can't tell a single soul that you're Eyeshield, you go it?!
Y-Yes!
Sena? Sena!
I wonder where he went...