The money situation's worked out, so everything's perfect!
I just want to lay down in a real bed!
Seriously! I'm so exhausted!
There ya go!
Just THREE?!
Hiruma, there's only three rooms?
How the heck are we supposed to sleep with this many people in three rooms?!
I've got something I need to go look for, so I'll heading out. Later!
A-Anyway, let's figure out how to split the rooms!
I think Anezaki needs her own room.
The three of us will get one room.
You can't decide that!
Really! They're so selfish.
Are you okay? Sena, wanna share a room with me?
Nah, I'm okay. I'll sleep with everyone else.
Man, why do we have to stay at this cheapo hotel?!
Sorry there's not much room.
I'll try to take up as little room as I can when I sleep.
I wonder what Hiruma's searching for?
Ya-ha!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
American Football Downtown.
Where should we go to buy stuff for breakfast?
Our budget's pretty small.
It'd be great if we could find a grocery store and get everything really cheap.
Found one!
Excuse me, Ms. Police Officer.
Yes? What is it?
Thief!
Someone, catch him!
What are you two doing? Hurry up and get over there!
Wait!
America's scary!
I wonder... where we are...
Don't tell me... we're lost.
Maybe we should call the hotel and have everyone come get us.
Nice idea!
Huh?
You're heavy! Hurry up already!
Sure thing!
Huh? That's strange...
Hurry!
I wonder if it's the wrong type of money...
I don't get it!
Not done?
Monta, hurry up with the phone!
"Hurry" he says!
That HURTS!
I'm sorry, he's such a klutz.
Whatever, just hurry!
I'm in a big hurry!
Go on ahead!
We're sorry!
It's me. Sorry I'm late.
I'll go get you now.
Set, hut, hut!
It's sandlot baseball, I mean, sandlot football.
Just like I imagined!
They're practically one with their sport, football.
I kinda wanna play now!
Yeah!
Max Catch!
Ow!
Ouch!
You're pretty good.
Are you two Japanese?
Yep!
Can you play football?
Well, you see...
We play it a lot!
We're short on members.
So would you be a doll and play?
The game with the neighboring town's team
will determine who gets to march first in the parade next week.
Who marches first in a parade?
No matter what, we don't want to march behind them!
Could you please help us?
Lucky! Let's do it, Sena!
Huh? Yeah, but...
He'll be your running back!
Okay! Let's go!
We're counting on you.
Sena's taking too long!
I wonder where he went to go shopping?
Guys, these are our fill-in players Sena and Monta!
Nice to meet ya!
Thanks man!
Do you think they're losing?
Looks that way.
Okay! We've gotta win since we're playing!
Papa, good luck!
Bob, remember that your placement in the parade's on the line!
We're counting on you, our fill-in boys!
"Boys?"
Well, let's go!
Right!
Leave it to us!
Wow, there's a bunch of Kuritas!
Set, hut!
I wanna do whatever I feel like
It's no big deal RIGHT NOW
Holding my overflowing emotions with MY HANDS
Oh, no!
I'm sentimental BABE BE SURVIVOR
Max Catch!
Great!
Nice going, Monta!
Good going, Monkey!
I'm not "Monkey," I'm "Monta."
We hurt each other as if we lacked any feelings
We work hard spending our days trying
Sena, make a touchdown!
to get a step closer to our ideals
Like I give a damn about what's right
We'll crush you!
Since the path opening before me is clear,
I want to belie in DREAM MAKER
Hey, you gonna throw it away? You gonna avoid it?
I can feel my mission
Love for Life, Drive for Light ultramarine-colored sky
Touchdown!
Nice catch! Nice run!
Cry for Fight, Smile for Bright let's tear through it
We'll be able to rebound if we keep this up in no time!
Love for Life, Drive for Light
Okay! I'm totally on fire!
I think I can see tomorrow
Yeah, let's give it our all!
Cry for Fight...
Hey, sorry I'm late. My bad.
I had to go all the way to his house to pick him up.
That's the guy...
...from the phone!
Hey, Bob! Let's put an end to this once and for all today!
Well if it isn't Big Bear.
I thought that you were taking a break because your wife's having a baby!
Sorry, granny! The due date isn't until next week!
And what are you two doing here?!
Well...You see...
Fill-ins from Japan have come to help us.
Fill-ins from Japan?!
We'll teach them how strong we Americans are!
Darn it! If only Panther was here...
Panther?
Do you mean Panther from the Aliens?
What, you know him?
Yeah!
Of course we know him!
We just recently played against the NASA Aliens.
Is that so?
Does Panther sometimes play in games with this team?
Yeah, of course!
Panther learned how to play football here.
If Panther were here, he'd easily be able to slip past Big Bear.
I'll give it a try!
Do your best on his behalf, too!
Okay!
Football Clinic!
What does the running back do?
He gets the ball from the quarterback and runs into enemy territory.
Run with all your might and dodge all of the tackles! Ya-ha!
Set, hut, hut!
Hut!
Don't tell me they got involved in a violent crime or something.
Don't say weird things like that!
We need to watch out for those brats' passes and running.
They aren't as good as Panther, but that one guy's a pretty fast runner.
Leave them to me!
I'll squash those little brats!
Darling, you can do it!
If Panther was here, he'd easily be able to slip past Big Bear.
Hey, over here!
We won't let you pass!
They figured it out!
He's running! Stop him!
I have to work hard for Panther, too!
You're pretty good, but this is the end of the line!
C'mon!
Sena!
You can do it!
Well then, let's drink to District 35's victory and the good fight District 36 put up! Cheers!
Cheers!
We did it!
Good job! You really did great.
We won today all thanks to you!
No, thank you for letting us play.
It was a lot of fun!
I realized why Panther wanted to go to Japan when I watched you two play.
I'm so glad I let him go.
Take this as a symbol of my gratitude.
What is this?
It's my special oatmeal.
It's full of nutrients and Panther loves it!
How sweet!
Let's dig in!
It's nasty...
It's nastiness knows no bounds.
You forgot this at the phone booth.
Thank you very much!
You're pretty good.
You beat us big time.
Nice run, Japanese boys.
Th-Thank you!
He was actually a good person!
Yeah...
Hey, hang in there!
Hurry and get her to the hospital!
Hey, everyone, I'm counting on ya!
I'm sorry, by the O.B. isn't working today and the head doctor is at the beach.
What?! You're a doctor, so do something!
I am, but I'm just an intern.
Then we've got to go to the beach to get the other doc.
The road leading there's under construction and there's a huge traffic jam.
It would be quicker to run there.
Can you do that?
No, I don't know the roads or anything...
Once you hit the street, you just go straight until you hit the ocean.
You'll see an old man with a mustache out fishing by himself. That's him.
You're without doubt the fastest person here. We're counting on you!
Please!
Please go for us!
It's for Big Bear!
Please!
All right.
Hey!
Obey the traffic signals!
What should I do?
It's scary...
So scary...
You're without doubt the fastest person here.
Please go for us!
Please!
It's for Big Bear!
It might be a bit hard for us to find two people in this big crowd.
Excuse me!
A boy with hair-
Mister Spider!
Spider!
Amazing!
That's really amazing!
America sure is an amazing country.
Sena?
Huh?
It couldn't be, right?
Are you okay?
You can do this!
The doctor will be here soon!
Doctor! Doctor!
You did it, Sena!
Max Ca-ouch!
Thank you, Sena, Monta!
Doctor, I'm counting on you!
Good job!
YES!
It's a healthy baby boy!
His eyes look like he'll make a strong-willed football player.
Congratulations, Big Bear!
Since you're Japanese, you recognized this, right?
It's the pose for Dogeza!
Thank you so much!
That's not how you do a dogeza!
Big Bear!
I-I'm sorry...
I finally found it!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
First sandlot football and now beach football?!
Really! There's no need to make Sena play in such a dangerous game!
But The Kid and Tetsuma from the Wild Gunmen are supposed to play!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Ultimate Combo! The Devil Gunmen! Ya-ha!
We're going to sleep on that bed, no matter what!
Quietly now!