[Amino Cyborgs 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 18]
Without Eyeshield, Deimon's losing to Amino by a whole seven points!
First down! Deimon's counter-attack begins!
Yah!
Boo-yah!
H-How?!
Our data on Deimon from this spring didn't show them half this strong!
Don't worry, Aoyanagi.
Our data didn't focus on just their power.
In fact, it should be even easier for us
to attack Deimon than we had previously predicted.
Huh?
Deimon's fatal flaw lies in...
That's it! Their offense!
Eyeshield 21 and that monkey boy score over 90% of Deimon's points.
In short, if we could seal them off somehow,
they'd take a dramatic hit in their ability to score points.
I see!
And now Eyeshield 21 isn't here.
If we can stop that monkey boy,
Deimon will have essentially lost all of its offense.
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Devil Bat Ghost!
Listen up, butt-monkey!
The enemy's going to try to crush you!
So w-what should I do?
There's nothing you can do!
Catch that ball even if it kills you!
That's your job!
R-Right!
Crush all our opponents!
'Cause we're going to the Christmas Bowl!
Right!
Those Amino guys... Are they going to go after their receiver?
That would be the obvious thing to do with Eyeshield gone.
Set! Hut, hut!
I used a motion capture device to create the perfect running form.
There's no way my speed could lose to yours!
You sure yap while running!
What?!
I ran this pass route like nuts during the death march!
Catch it, butt-monkey!
Wow! Hiruma throws an intense pass!
But it looks a bit too intense!
It's too far.
Even I couldn't catch it.
No way! It's impossible.
Wow! H-He caught it!
Whether the words "give up" crosses your mind or not...
...determine who's stronger than the other.
I can go a bit farther.
Since Sena's not here, I need to run as much as I can!
What?!
Do you think you can get past me?
You bet!
What?!
Oh, no! Deimon got crushed!
They failed to get their first down!
See that, gentlemen?
My analysis was flawless!
Right!
Your analysis?!
You're Raimon, aren't you?
From here on we'll have several men mark you
and tackle you hard the second you catch the ball.
Butt-monkey!
Don't chicken out.
If you freak out now...
I-I know!
This is bad.
Coach Doburoku...
There's too big of a difference in their body mass.
There's no way Monta could stand a chance against those Cyborgs with his build!
Th-Then what should we...?
There's nothing we can do.
Where on earth is Eyeshield 21?
Deimon's losing!
Monta...
Without you, he's their main target.
I can't watch this...
Hurry... We've got to hurry!
Amino easily made a touchdown!
- Good going, Amino!
- Good going, Kadoguchi!
Monta...
They're even killing our defense...
I almost stopped him!
Well, it's just about time to put that monkey out of his misery.
Hey, scrap metal!
There's something I need to tell you!
Tell me?
You're making a huge mistake.
A mistake? Me, make a mistake?
You can't control the game through knowledge alone.
Do you honestly believe saying that would provoke me?
Despite getting good grades, you lack common sense.
It's pretty obvious.
Preposterous!
Set! Hut, hut!
I'll go straight for the goal!
How am I mistaken?!
Wow! Munakata stopped him!
Deimon's got eight yards left until their first down!
Next time... I'll destroy you next time!
Ow...
M-Monta! Are you okay?
I-I'm fine. I can handle it!
At this rate, he'll...
But what can we linemen do about it?
Quit your daydreaming!
Take up your positions already!
Y-Yeah.
Set! Hut, hut!
Max Catch!
You're finished!
You're through.
He crushed Deimon!
You did well,
but Deimon was never a match for Amino's sports medicine from the beginning.
Just take it easy, now!
Hey, scrap metal!
It looks like you were the one mistaken.
We'll see.
We're not done!
We're still on offense!
I-Impossible!
Is he still going to play?!
Like I said, scrap metal...
Your calculations didn't take into account the power of his determination!
Max cracklin' recovery!
He's...
M-Monta...
Go for it!
V-Very well...
I'll admit your power of determination is impressive.
But if he keeps this up, it may shorten his life as an athlete.
Is that okay?
There's no way we're gonna lose!
What?!
Since he's not here...
I'd hate to be told we can't win since Eyeshield 21's not here...
There'd be... no point for me, or any of us, to be here playing football!
I see... First you were going on about determination and now pride...
Can't you think things through logically or scientifically?
Ain't happening!
After all...
...our grades totally stink!
Very well. Show me what you've got.
Let's see just how well your determination and pride does against Amino's sports medicine.
Looks like he's pretty ticked off.
I guess it's about time I bring out my trump card.
Trump card?
It's Deimon's greatest trump card... the Shadowless God of Death!
Football Clinic!
What's a "sack?"
It's when you tackle the quarterback!
Crush the person giving the orders to seal off the offense! Ya-ha!
We've gotta make up for the time lost at the stop light!
Hang on tight!
O-KAY!
Set! Hut, hut!
The entire line's going to guard their receiver?
Crush them!
I don't have the ball!
What?! Stop him, Kadoguchi!
What?!
It's a Deimon touchdown!
Amino Cyborgs 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
They got six points!
Who's that?!
Where on earth did he come from?!
P-Player #30?
I-I don't even remember him being on Deimon's team!
If you're gonna completely rely on data then remember who all the players are!
His name's the Stealth Running Back, Plain Ishimaru!
I didn't notice him at all!
He's so plain that he's hardly noticeable at all!
Deimon touchdown!
Amino Cyborgs 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
They're catching up!
They're catching up even though Eyeshield 21 isn't there!
They're completely different from this spring!
Deimon's strength is the real deal, but...
There's nine minutes left!
At this rate, they'll catch up to us!
Don't worry!
Panicking is just what they want you to do!
Yeah... B-But...!
I have a way to stop their offense!
What is it?
Listen up. Lead both the monkey and the plain guy to me!
I'll stop both of them on my own!
Right!
Oh, Ishimaru's dashing down the center field!
He's going one-on-one with Munakata!
Shin from Ojo and Panther were already doing this naturally.
I just have to veer off the axis a little to guide which direction he'll go.
I allow the runner a moment to stop and turn before jumping out at him!
It's finally happening...
Deimon was pushing forward so hard earlier,
but now they're at a standstill.
We can't...
We can't lose before Eyeshield 21 gets here!
That's right...
There's no way we can lose!
There's a two-point gap with five minutes left.
Just a bit more! We've almost caught up!
You can do it, everyone!
There's just a little bit of time left!
Will Deimon be defeated by Amino in the end?!
What will you do, Deimon?
Hey, hey! Are you okay with this, Deimon?
Amino's sports medicine truly is great!
You're finished, gentlemen from Deimon!
I praise you for having fought us thus far.
You've done well in that regard.
It's not over till the fat lady sings, scrap metal!
I can hear the sound of a demon's footsteps!
A demon?
A bike?
T-That's...!
Could it be?!
Our star actor's made the stage!
He's here! It's Eyeshield 21!
Yay! He made it in time!
H-He's cool!
What a flashy entrance.
Thank goodness he's here!
M-My, h-hello...
- It was horrible!
- You're LATE!
You jerk!
Stop that! We don't have time for it!
Let's go, Peewee!
I want you to make up for your lost time!
Right!
Um...
You were a real life-saver!
Thank you very much!
Go kill that newbie line backer if you've got the time to be thanking me!
He's from Amino, the elite school that conquers a different sport every year!
Don't let him make a fool of us!
Okay!
Yeah!
Eyeshield 21's going to start playing now?!
Don't worry.
After all, we've completely analyzed how he moves.
I'll stop him without fail!
How interesting! It'll be a battle between the aces!
Defeating that hunk of scrap metal is our way to easy victory!
Then it's our job to open up a route to him.
Now you're getting it!
Everyone, attack!
We're using the "Sweep" strategy!
Great! We're going to see Eyeshield 21's first play of the season!
Everyone got stronger because of the death march.
Even our "Sweep" is more powerful now!
He told them!
He said they're doing a sweep!
Great!
What should we do?!
It doesn't matter! Stick to the plan!
We'll open a path through brute force!
Knowing our strategy beforehand isn't gonna help them any!
Eyeshield 21!
I won't ask you to squeeze through a small opening this time!
We're going to make a huge path for you to dash through!
Set! Hut, hut!
Crush them!
It's huge! It's bigger than ever before!
Go, Eyeshield!
Amazing, Eyeshield 21!
It's him! It's Munakata!
Be careful! He does some sorta strange movement!
You'll definitely break in the end.
For 2,000 kilometers I practiced breaking without dropping speed!
At long last, we're unveiling the Devil Bat Ghost!
Go, Eyeshield 21!
I suddenly shorten my stride and start zig-zagging!
Huh? He's not breaking?
He's coming straight...Wait, what's with this sudden chill?
Wha-What?!
YA-HA!
He vanished!
He easily slipped by and got a touch down!
He easily...?
It's 14-to-18! Deimon's finally turned the tables!
Amino Cyborgs 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 36
No human could turn like that...
He used the barreling cross-over step,
which lets him maintain that super high speed of his.
But what happened to that stupid jerk Munakata?
He's just standing there.
Ikari, have you ever seen a pro runner come straight at you?
He's like smoke vanishing before you.
Great! Let's keep up the pace!
Game over!
Deimon wins!
I've already hit my limit even though we swapped members for offense and defense!
How come Deimon can maintain such stamina with so few players on the team?!
Sports is more than just pumping up your muscles and reading a technique how-to manual.
That's right!
You've got to work on the simple drills and repeatedly go over your basic training.
By doing that,
you'll have developed a mentality that allows you to overcome any situation.
What's wrong... with my Amino's sports medicine?
There's nothing wrong with sports medicine.
But that alone won't let you win.
Deimon's gotten pretty strong...
This should be fun!
The Deimon Devil Bats blasted through the first round!
Sh-Shin!
I won't let anyone get passed me!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
I think I've seen this guy who suddenly showed up somewhere before!
He's the Bando Spiders' kicker, Kotaro.
His kicking has a 100% success rate!
And who's that?!
Huh? He's MUSASHI?!
Oh, the rest is a secret!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Legendary 60-Yard Magnum! Ya-ha!
Go! Take the train to the stadium!
Your driver's license!
OK! Thank you, my friend!
Where's... this?
How can this be?!