Shinryuji Nagas vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha.
It's Unsui!
From Agon to Unsui, and Unsui to Agon!
The amazing combination of these twin brothers appears invincible!
The Dragonfly...
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The 12th Athlete.
The Shinryuji Nagas demonstrate their overwhelming superiority
scoring 14 points on Deimon a mere three minutes into the game!
Shinryuji Nagas 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
It doesn't matter if they stop us now.
We'll keep targeting Agon and wear him down!
That's right.
If Agon's playing offense, defense AND special teams,
maybe he'll run out of stamina...
No chance.
I've never seen Mop-Head get exhausted, not even once.
Then why's him playing both sides such a big deal?
ALL of us are playing both sides!
If they ALL saved their stamina by only playing half the time,
we'd have no chance.
However... there IS a way.
Eyeshield 21!
You're gonna take Agon Kongo out with your speed!
Right!
Shinryuji kicks off, and the game continues!
They...
Oh, is this a mistake?
The ball is heading right towards Eyeshield 21,
Sena Kobayakawa!
We did it on purpose
because we wanna wrap this game up.
I'll show you what it means to have real talent.
Watch this, you piece of trash!
I'll get through with the Devil Bat Ghost!
There it is!
Even against Agon-
It's the Devil Bat Ghost!
I made it!
You sped up from last time, huh?
Yeah!
Yay!
From the Devil Bat Ghost to the Devil Bat Hurricane!
This time!
Then again,
when faced with a level 100 opponent,
going from 10 to 15 still doesn't make much difference.
Oh no! Get it!
Yes!
He recovered the fumble!
Deimon Devil Bats, safety!
Oh my, Taki was tackled in Deimon's end zone!
Shinryuji Nagas 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
That gives Shinryuji two points for the safety.
Shinryuji Nagas 16 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
The Ghost, the Hurricane...
He beat both of them...
Now, would you mind analyzing Agon's moves
during that play, Riko?
Oh, yes.
From the eyes to the mind, and the mind to the muscles-
we send impulses!
Err, electronic signals.
It only takes 0.11 seconds for Agon's impulses
to fire and reach their destination!
The lower limit for human reaction time is 0.10 seconds.
In other words,
it's virtually impossible to have faster reflexes than him!
It's... it's just not something you can achieve with training!
He's been blessed with extraordinary natural gifts...
There's no other way to put it!
And now Deimon will have to kick off
from just in front of their own goal.
They're in dire straits!
I won't let it end here!
It's my job as a kicker!
That's some uber-kick!
With their backs against the wall,
Deimon tries to turn things around!
It's not over!
Max comeback!
Before this game, everyone out there thought the same.
What power!
No matter how strong Shinryuji is, they might just pull it off.
Kurita!
Go to sleep, tubby!
Agon makes a big play on the return!
They're already at Deimon's 40-yard line!
Like we were praying for a winning lotto ticket...
"They can do it."
But as soon as the game started, reality hit.
Shinryuji Nagas 22 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Touchdown! Shinryuji leads 22-0!
The air's too dangerous, we'll have to fight on the ground.
We'll run the Wishbone like we did against Kyoshin.
The Peewee/Monkey combo run.
- Right!
- Okay!
Set, hut, hut!
It's no good, no matter how fast our feints are,
he reacts too fast to get by!
They can only stand by and watch the gap widen...
Touchdown!
...and learn their place.
The strongest are called so for a reason.
Luck can't win against skill.
Shinryuji Nagas 32 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
The first half ends at 32-0!
The relentless gods of Kanto
aim for their ninth straight tournament victory!
What'd I tell say?
At least a 30 point lead by the end of the half.
Wait, what were you talking about?
"The Christmas Bowl?"
You losers have nursed that stupid dream for four years.
And now it's game over for you, guaranteed.
What is it, Sena?
I dunno...
What is this...? I've never felt like this before...
He can call me trash or a runt or whatever he wants...
But...
Hiruma, Kurita and Musashi's dream
has always been to play in the Christmas Bowl...
...and I won't let you mock it!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
All right, Sena!
Let's turn it around in the second half!
Listen up, guys.
Just make sure you don't get yourselves injured.
We don't have a chance of winning this, not anymore.
What...? H-Hiruma...?
Against Agon, Ikkyu and Shinryuji,
we'll never come back from a 32 point deficit in one half.
W-What're you saying?!
What about the Christmas Bowl?!
We all swore we'd make it-
Butt-Monkey...
Don't talk like you're in charge - you're not.
B-But...
They were never an opponent we were gonna beat
with effort and training alone.
End of story.
Hiruma...
You guys still have next year.
Didn't think he'd get discouraged so quickly.
Still, a leader shouldn't be talking like that
right after the second half opening kickoff...
What's that sneaky piece of garbage trying to pull?
Is this another trick?
But look at all his depressed flunkies...
This... can't be an act.
Our dream ends here.
Since we can't win this game,
we'll focus on keeping you all safe for next year,
and avoid risky plays where you could get injured.
Hiruma...
Because...
Deimon's chances of winning
are down to about one-bazillionth of a percent.
W-What happened to Yocchie...?
Mamo...
Deimon prepares to kick off again!
He...
The game's not over until our chances are at zero!
Hiruma would never say something like...
Hiruma never gives up...
...as long as there's still the tiniest chance of winning!
That's right!
We all swore we'd go to the Christmas Bowl together!
Just make sure we don't get injured?
You're not a nice guy,
just HEARING that gave me the creeps.
L-Lie...
You're telling us to go nuts, even if we might get hurt.
We're marching towards victory, right?
Mamo...
It's just... just barely noticeable...
But they're backing off a little bit each time.
Musashi's huge kicks
must be forcing them to reposition themselves.
With Agon all the way in back...
We've got a good shot at stealing back the ball.
It's now or never.
But if we chance our strategy now,
they'll realize we're reacting to their positioning.
That's a risk we have to take.
Please, everyone...
That's it... I get it!
"We can't take back the pace unless we all charge in!"
Did you really just change the plan without saying a word,
you insane demon?!
I've gotta believe that everyone else is still...
- ...shooting for the Christmas Bowl!
We're doing it!
Everyone's going towards the ball!
An onside kick?!
Get the ball! Move up!
Grab it!
Uber-catch, Yamabushi!
Yes!
- Komusubi!
The onside kick worked!
Deimon regains possession!
Th-They're out of this world...
It's too early to flip out.
Deimon's still got its trump card ready and waiting.
You warmed up during halftime, right, Baldini?
You're in.
Y-Yes!
R-Riko, do you know this player?
N-No, none of my data has-
Anyway, he's never played in a single game!
Reality is harsh.
He never had a chance at playing from start to finish...
Not after spending 17 years hunched over a desk.
But, Yukimitsu,
if save all your strength for the second half,
and just stick to playing offense...
You should be able to go at full strength like no one else!
That's all you've ever trained for!
I've always been on the outside, on the sidelines, looking in.
So close, and yet a universe away...
Finally... I'm finally...
...crossing this line!
Th-This is the field...
...it's totally different when you're actually on it!
He just fell on his butt.
Yuki!
You all right?
Sena, Monta...
Until EVERY Deimon Devil Bat stand on the field together,
We won't lose!
That's right...
I can't let everyone down, I've gotta do my best!
I'm fine, Sena, Monta.
Yuki, now every Deimon Devil Bat...
Our best members are all on the field!
Look at his build... They're gonna use a newbie?
Look closely, Yukimitsu.
You spent six whole months on the bench honing your best weapon,
your observational skills!
Set, hut!
I've been waiting half a year for this...
I've watched how each Shinryuji defender moves...
Even Agon and Ikkyu, with all their talent...
I know where they are, and where they're going.
Those 17 years you spent studying weren't wasted.
There! Hiruma will definitely throw the ball there!
You'll definitely notice that spot's open!
They didn't decide on a pass route beforehand,
he's just watching how the opponents move
and making the same judgment as Hiruma!
Outsmart those so-called "geniuses!"
This is your ultimate move, you bookworm of a receiver...
The option route!
YA-HA!
It's open... Please don't notice yet... Agon, Ikkyu!
Agon's hyperspeed reflexes!
Ikkyu's coming too!
Yo yo! You enjoy your one moment of hope, cueball?
They're catching up!
Look out, Yuki!
Now I'm uber-pumped!
Let's see who gets him first, Agon!
Even you won't beat me in the air!
I can't even dream of standing up to the two of them...
All my hard work, and I'm still nothing but a gnat to them...
Run, Yuki!
Don't lose!
- Don't quit on us!
I have no talent...
I've done nothing with my life for 17 years...
I haven't accomplished anything because I never TRIED anything!
But this year...
...is different!
He jumped!
It's too fast.
He'll never make it.
Don't quit, Baldini!
I have to catch it!
If I don't...!
Touchdown!
The Deimon Devil Bats... their first score... their first points...
...come from the guerrilla player, Manabu Yukimitsu!
- Yes!
- You did it!
- Yuki!
I did it...
Yuki...
The Deimon Devil Bats
are all mustered on one side of the field,
clearly preparing for another onside kick!
I've figured out Deimon's plan.
They're going for another quick score with an onside kick.
If you think so Onihei, then it must be true...
They switched back to a standard kick formation
right before he got to the ball!
That means you're wrong again, Onihei!
Watch out, watch out! Musashi's kicking!
Go back, go back!
STOP!
That's how Hiruma operates!
He puts pressure on his opponents
and then confuses them with trick plays
while they're trying to regroup!
Oh ho! Agon zooms straight to the ball's landing spot!
This's why 11 of me would make the ultimate team!
Smooth as butter!
As usual, Agon blasts straight up the middle for a big return!
Guess they're not that dumb...
We... we have to do something!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Way to go, Yukimitsu!
Now it's your turn, Sena!
Knock Agon for a loop!
Me, blitz Agon?!
I guess I have no choice!
I have to!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Power of the Rank and File!
Ya-Ha!
What's the plan?
If Agon and Unsui come at us with the Dragonfly again,
it'll be the first half all over again.
Peewee!
Yes?
From now on,
you're gonna blitz Agon at lightspeed on every single play.
It doesn't matter if he's carrying the ball or not.
You've thought this through?
If Sena runs that much on defense too...
...his legs will give out after a few minutes.
Of course I've thought it through, you old fogey.
If they even score one more point, the game's over.
It's our only hope.