He zoomed past Eyeshield and scaled the goalpost so quickly...
That #21 is amazing!
Whenever Panther sees someone like him...
...he always gets like this.
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Caged Black Panther!
We can win if we stick to the plans I made!
You don't belong on the field if you can't stick to it!
You're off the field if you ignore my orders! Got that?!
Yes, sir!
I better do some warm-ups.
For someone like me who doesn't have a uniform, all I can do is wait.
I want to compete against Eyeshield 21!
I want to compete against Panther!
Do you really wanna see Panther run that badly?
Remember what Hiruma said?
If there's something you want, win!
Monta...
We just have to kick their butts.
If we're in the lead by tens of points, they'll HAVE to let Panther play.
But we're running out of time!
Deimon's gotta win big time!
We're going to stay here in Japan!
How's that? Pretty simple, huh?
Well, it's easy to say all that, but...
It won't be that easy.
There's no way we can get that far in the lead...
It doesn't matter if we can or can't!
If you're serious about this, then I'll help with everything I've got!
Monta...
It's just like when I fought against Shin.
My legs won't sit still.
I want to compete against Panther!
Set, hut!
Max Catch!
Sena!
I'm going to play against Panther!
It's Eyeshield again!
Crush him!
Sweet! They got a first down!
Set, hut!
I can fight!
First down!
Go!
I can fight!
First down!
I CAN fight!
Ya-ha!
Touchdown!
He did it!
Great! Amazing!
Eyeshield's awakened!
The Aliens just can't compete against that speed of his!
There's a two-point gap now!
Who knows who will win!
Darn...
Curses!
Panther...
If I had of been there...
Panther?
Coach...
What?
I'm begging you!
Please let me stop him... Let me stop Eyeshield 21!
Panther...
Please!
A ball boy has no right to say that!
Huddle up!
The enemy is trying to make this a battle of who can score the most points.
And that's just fine with us!
If you follow my instructions perfectly, the passes will definitely work.
Got that?!
Yes, sir!
Set, hut, hut!
Number 8!
Number 8! Roger!
Confirming landing point!
Three... two... one... ZERO!
Landing point is OK.
Darn it!
They did it!
They got a touchdown with their Shuttle Pass.
That's perfect.
Their kick is also perfect!
The Aliens have regained the lead!
Little Brother Gonzales, it's your turn!
Okay!
Well, it looks like the Aliens are swapping out one of their players!
Big Gonzales and his brother Little Gonzales are both of the field together,
along with their irredeemable tattoos!
What?
They're irredeemable...?
I want a kanji tattoo!
I want it to say "Big and useful" because I'm a big man who is very helpful!
You're very helpful, huh?
How about this?
Here's the first kanji from "useful," so we'll just throw the character for "big" in front of it.
In Japanese, the characters for "Big" and "Useful" mean "Poop" when combined together.
I'm big and useful!
It says "poop!"
No way!
It's "Big Poop Man!"
How lame...
That really is irredeemable.
Sure is.
Set, hut!
Deimon's doing another sweep!
Big and useful!
What power!
Eyeshield was able to dodge him in the blink of an eye!
It's his Change of Pace.
He's fast!
Little Gonzales stopped Eyeshield!
Don't underestimate me because I'm little!
The big brother holds back the enemy with his strength
while his little brother covers him with his speed.
They're our Gonzales Brothers!
A single player with incredible ability doesn't lead a team to victory.
It's important that each player fulfills the role that has been assigned to them.
My players just need to be pawns, obeying my every order.
The Aliens are as formidable as I had thought.
So, what will you do now, Deimon?
They're probably going to try for more points!
Set, hut!
Crush him before he can throw the ball!
Deimon's quarterback, Hiruma, was thrown down!
Hiruma!
A-Are you okay?!
I'm not going to let them have their way!
Panther...
Football Clinic!
What type of technique is a bump?
It's a technique where you shove aside the receiver
so that you can prevent him from successfully catching the pass. Ya-ha!
Okay, ladies, listen up!
We're almost to the end zone.
Got it?!
Yeah!
Now it's time for Deimon to start up their offense again!
Set, hut, hut!
They went for a sweep!
Don't underestimate me!
He's empty-handed!
Hey!
What?!
Hiruma faked them out!
Don't let that pass get through!
Max Catch!
Touchdown!
They did it! Deimon got a touchdown!
Good going, Deimon!
Okay! Let's keep on going like this!
I'm sure Panther will get to play if we do!
Yeah!
What are you doing, #30?! Switch out!
They got an additional two points with their conversion.
Now there's only a one-point gap between them and the Aliens!
Set, hut!
Number 3!
Roger! Confirming landing point!
Three... two... one... ZERO!
Great! RUN, #25!
It's Deimon's ball!
Yay! That's our Eyeshield!
How pathetic! You're all pathetic!
#25, swap out! Get your butt outta there!
It really wasn't that big of a mistake...
They're swapping out again?
This is getting good!
They're starting to go downhill because they don't accept it when someone makes a mistake.
It's all because they're being forced to switch out if they make even the slightest mistake.
It's just going to get them all shaken up!
The Aliens are getting nervous.
Really? They look the same to me.
If the Aliens are going to focus in on passing,
then all Deimon has to do is focus on defending against their passes.
And Deimon's got Hiruma's devious strategies and Eyeshield's fast legs on their side.
No one on the Aliens' team can stand up to those legs.
Set, hut!
Don't underestimate me!
He faked the handoff again!
Butt-monkey!
All right!
It's their receiver! Crush #80!
Deimon can do more than just passes!
When I'm on the defense...
Eyeshield will take the offense.
What?!
Go, Eyeshield!
Shoot!
It's useless. No one can stop Eyeshield's legs.
Touchdown! Ya-ha!
They did it!
Eyeshield really is great!
At last... Deimon has turned the tables at last!
It's their first time taking the lead!
You guys are pathetic!
Time to swap out!
I don't need players who can't follow my instructions!
You little-!
I'm begging you!
Quit doing that! I'm-
I... Please give me my first and last chance to hold Eyeshield back!
What?!
If... If I can't hold Eyeshield back...
I'll quit the team!
What?!
Panther!
Please give me my first and final chance!
That's the man.
Leonard Apollo, huh?
It looks like he really does practice three times more than everyone else.
It may not sound that great, but he's a mediocre athlete filled with wishful thinking.
It looks like you may get to play as a starter this year!
What was I...?
I can't believe I'm reminiscing over my days as a pro now of all times!
He's Morgan, the ace runner from the famous 46ers.
He's transferring over to the Armadillo's right away?!
We don't need Apollo if we've got Morgan with us.
What a pity.
It doesn't matter how hard he tries...
Their innate abilities are leagues apart!
This isn't a world where effort alone counts for something.
Let me play in one game before you fire me! Just once!
Can't you compare Morgan and me in a game?
Please give me my first and last chance!
And if I'm not as good as Morgan, I'll leave the team quietly.
If you please, give me a chance!
Please!
If you please, let me play in just one game!
Sorry, but there's no need to.
You don't get any more chances.
You don't get... anymore chances...
W-What's the meaning of this?!
We're asking you, too!
Please let Panther play!
Guys...
We're not just saying this because he's our friend.
Going by the way things are, it would be tough for us to win by ten points without Panther's legs!
Do you think you can just go out there and play when you've never even practiced?!
No, he's been practicing.
What?!
He's been practicing with us whenever you're not around.
You've been practicing on your own?!
Right. We have a formation we thought up on our own, too.
We call it the "Moonsault Formation."
It's a formation that lets Panther run free.
Panther's been practicing three times harder than anyone while being the ball boy.
Please let us try it out in this game!
We can only do this formation if Panther's there!
Please!
Please trust us as a team!
Please give us a chance!
Please!
Give us a chance!
Please let Panther play!
Guys...
If you please!
A chance?
Very well.
But just this once!
We did it, Panther!
I get to wear the Aliens' uniform...
Thank you very much!
Quit yapping and get out there... before I change my mind!
Hold Eyeshield back, no matter what!
That's all you have to do!
Okay!
Panther!
It looks like the enemy's finally going to use their trump card.
Shin?
Moonsault Formation...
Let's see just how good it is.
Eyeshield 21, I kept my promise!
We can fight each other on the field!
Panther... I finally get to...
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
The wild beast has finally been set free on the field!
It's the Black Panther vs. Eyeshield 21!
It's Zero-G Legs vs. Lightspeed Legs!
Sena, show him how strong you are!
Be sure to watch this showdown!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Real Beast! Ya-ha!
Don't underestimate me because I'm little!
I'm helpful even though I'm short!
D-Don't tell me...!
In Japanese, the characters for "Little" and "Useful" mean "Pee" when combined together.
I knew it!