Mamori...
Huh?
Sena...?
Sorry I didn't tell you sooner, Mamori.
But I have to go.
Because... I'm...
And now at long last Eyeshield 21 is removing his mask!
It's the Lightspeed Running, Back Eyeshield, no-
Sena Kobayakawa!
Yay! I've been wanting to tell for so long!
Sena!
Mamori Anezaki!
That's right!
I can...
I can help the Devil Bats...
...as their manager!
How wise of you to realize that you don't stand a chance against me
and abandon your title as "Eyeshield."
That's not it.
I don't care about who's "real" and who's "fake."
I will go at you with everything I have!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Greatest Kicking Team!
The fateful battle for the third and final ticket
to the Kanto Tournament is about to begin!
The powerful kicking team, Bando, is going up against Deimon,
which doesn't even have a kicker!
These teams are truly the opposite extremes!
Kotaro!
Let's go with Kick Code D Flat Seven.
I-I was going to do that even if you kept your mouth shut!
Come on, let it drop.
Deimon's starting with the ball
and the Bando Spiders are kicking off!
We're the greatest, smartest kicking team and we're declaring war!
That's...!
All of the Bando players are moving to the right?
Move up! They're gonna do an onside kick!
Akaba and all of the Bando players
have moved to one side of the field!
I can't believe they're going to use such a risky play!
But the game just started!
Shoot! Are they really going to kick the ball over there?
Here it comes!
It's going to be a dribbler!
Even Tetsuma couldn't snatch up the dribblers before I could!
Perfect.
It's not a dribbler!
It's a soft floater!
Take that!
It's ours!
It's perfect.
It's going to land at exactly D Flat Seven.
- We won't let you get it!
Deimon's line is doing a great job blocking Bando!
Y-You can't have it!
Do it like Akaba showed us!
Now!
What?!
All of a sudden...
...their blocks got stronger!
There's a bunch of them!
I'll be your shield!
Sena, Monta, get the ball!
Roger!
Yay! Go, Kuriton!
Akaba...
Sena, let me show you just how strong the real Eyeshield 21 is!
Even Kurita...!
He got blown away!
Isn't that like impossible?!
Where's the ball?
The ball!
They got it!
He's so fast!
Good going!
Akaba!
A-Amazing!
Deimon was supposed to start with possession,
but Akaba has quickly stolen the ball!
Offense goes to the Bando Spiders!
Kotaro's kicks are perfectly accurate.
So all of Bando's players...
...already know exactly where the ball will land!
They got us good!
Just now...
...Akaba flew after the ball right after he blocked.
In other words,
pushing back the humongous Kurita was outright easy for him.
Did you see that, Deimon?!
We're so smart!
It's just what we should expect
from last year's MVP, Hayato Akaba.
He sure showed who's boss!
They're just 30 yards away from the goal!
Considering the distance, I bet Kotaro will try to make his move.
Kotaro's going for a field goal!
W-We can't get through!
Stand firm!
Yeah!
We can't let anyone beat us in a kicking game!
This is the Bando style!
When it comes to kicking games,
we're the greatest there is!
In American football there's offense and defense.
But there's a third type of team that never sees the spotlight.
But we're proud of being that third,
special type of team and have worked hard
to perfect our skills as a kicking team!
Hi-yah!
Kicking teams are smart-looking!
They are so not cool!
You're making the cool offensive team wait!
Hurry up and get off the field!
Who cares about some lame kicking team?
What do you mean "who cares"?!
Calm down, Kotaro.
Right, right. We ARE teammates, after all.
I don't care if we're teammates!
There's no way I can let what he said slide!
Kicking's nothing but a little bonus on the side.
What was that?!
Ouch!
Enough already, Kotaro!
C-Coach...
Hey, ladies!
Let's shout out with souls filled with rock and roll!
So our worthless coach has finally bothered to show up.
With us on the team,
we're bound to win just fine even without his help.
An amateur coach like him should just sit back and watch!
You jerks!
Well, it's true that I'm an absolute amateur
as far as football is concerned.
But even I can tell this much:
your kick is beautiful.
It's like the ball is beautifully flying over sheet music.
Coach!
There's no rush.
There'll come a time when we can prove to everyone
how powerful a kicking team can be.
If offense and defense are vocalists or lead guitars,
then the kickers are the plain yet important
bass guitar or drums that keep the rhythm.
Exactly.
There's no way that a band
made only of an offensive soloist will do well.
Kickers are part of the ever-important ensemble.
Somehow hearing that come from you doesn't make me feel better.
Oh, come on!
No matter how much you may bicker,
you two harmonize together perfectly.
Come on, calm down!
Rock and Soul! Rock and Soul!
This is awful...
All of our ace players have...
Good job, everyone!
Why are half of the lockers empty?
Everyone left us!
They transferred to Teikoku High School in Kansai!
Akaba!
Him, too?!
And here I thought he was different!
This stinks!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What's an important quality for being a running back?
The hint is having "good judgment."
When you're trying to dodge a tackle,
it's important to be able to quickly determine
whether to use a feint or dash to one side.
Don't get confused!
Ya-ha!
Man...!
The Sengoku Samurais won with a score 28-0!
We don't have time to get bummed out
just because we lost in the spring season!
We'll kick butt in the fall season!
We're so smart!
It's horrible, Kotaro!
The chairman said he's going to shut down the football team!
WHAT?!
The coach is trying to change his mind right now!
They're all trying so hard!
Please look beyond right now
and think of what they'll be like in a year or two!
But I know...
...you're down to nothing but a kicking team.
Can you even play like that?
All they'll do is sully Bando's name if they keep playing.
Even kicking teams can fight!
I think it's important for them to focus on improving upon
an area that they're already strong at!
Just give them a chance to get to that point!
They may have unique personalities and viewpoints,
but everyone's getting along
because they love football and desperately want to play it!
How could you ignore that?!
I'm begging you!
I'll even take responsibility for whatever happens if you like!
So please, don't take football away from them!
Hey! What's wrong, guys?
I finished talking with him about it.
You can keep playing football.
B-But, Coach...
Guys...
It's okay...
Don't worry about it.
Coach...
The rest is in your hands.
So please create a super powerful kicking team
so that you can shout out with all your soul!
And now we've become that ultimate kicking team!
He scored a field goal!
Bando Spiders 0 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
The Bando Spiders are already three points in the lead!
Bando Spiders 3 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Their kicking's really amazing!
T-That was supposed to be our ball...
But putting that aside...
We haven't even touched the ball once.
He's right.
They're ahead by three points
and we haven't even touched the ball yet.
So this is the strength of a kicking team...
Hey, Deimon!
You're trapped in the Spider's Web
because of our super kicking power!
It's the smartest strategy out there: the Spider's Web!
The Spider's...
...Web?
I don't have any problem with your musical sense
when you name our strategies in order to boost morale.
But I can't say that I approve of your singing
about our strategy to the enemy.
I've told you...
...football and...
...music...
...aren't related!
Why are you associating with the enemy, anyway?
This'll be the second time we're doing it, anyway!
Trying to keep it a secret isn't gonna change anything, ya know!
Let's do it!
We're doing another onside kick!
He outright told them.
I can't believe you...
Everyone's moving to the right again!
So they're definitely going with another onside kick.
Are they going to steal the ball again?
Quit making fun of us!
But aren't they...?
Just a thought...
This is just a thought, but...
What if they use the onside kick to get the ball,
get another three points with a field goal,
and then do another onside kick?
It'd be an eternal loop.
N-No way!
You're right.
So you figured it out!
That's pretty smart!
Sena...
Even if we went up one-on-one,
you could never defeat me.
But I've got an even simpler way
to keep those lightspeed legs of yours from getting in the way.
I'll never let you so much as touch the ball.
Here they go again!
It's Kotaro's soft floater!
I'll MAX CATCH it this time!
Don't let Bando get through!
Form a strong wall!
Amazing! Absolutely amazing!
Akaba's incredible lead blocking has flattened all of Deimon's players!
Bando's fearsome attack has stolen possession again!
And Deimon still hasn't even touched the ball yet.
No... way!
How can this be?!
I can't believe he blew us away when it was three-to-one!
That's not humanly possible!
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Guys!
- You can do it!
There's just 27 yards till they hit the goal line!
Kotaro is definitely going to make his move again.
He's gonna kick again!
Everyone pay close attention!
That's it! It's his field goal kick!
Get him!
The kick was a diversion!
Stop Akaba!
He's fast!
Leave him to me! I'll stop-!
How can this be?!
I've gotta stop him!
I HAVE to stop him!
Akaba scores a touchdown!
You're awesome, Akaba!
Bando's the best!
That run just now...
It wasn't the play he was originally planning on using...
What's that mean, Mamo?
They use different variations of their plays for different situations.
They really have trained hard to become a master kicking team.
Naturally, they scored the extra points with their kick!
Bando Spiders 10 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Bando's in the lead with a score 10-0!
And they've taken up the onside kick formation yet again!
It's impossible to escape from their web once you're stuck in it.
That's the true terror of the Spider's Web!
I can't touch the ball...
We've fallen smack into the palm of their hands.
W-What should we do...?
Their only option is to break through Akaba's invincible lead block.
Deimon doesn't stand a chance at victory if they can't pull that off.
Ah, but the fun's just beginning!
I bet Hiruma's got something up his sleeves.
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Hey, hey, hey!
It hurts to watch when you guys can't even nab the ball!
You're finished once you're caught in the Spider's Web!
How on earth can we escape from the Spider's Web?
Show them just how terrifying a demon can be!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Truth Behind Red Eyes! Ya-ha!
Hey! Did you see that, Musashi?!
You're totally wrong if you think that they can win without a kicker!
Quit hiding and get here!
What on earth are you doing?!
Seriously!
That was... not smart-looking...