I've picked our second Death Game opponent.
Wh-Who is it?
The Zokugaku Chameleons.
Zokugaku...
The Zokugaku that Habashira goes to?
Bingo.
Umm... will we be handicapped again?
Sure we will, don't worry.
- I knew it...
- "Official challenge?"
Go out there and wreck Zokugaku!
- C-Cut us some slack!
- If we go challenge Zokugaku
- they'll send us home in coffins!
You'll go home in a coffin if you DON'T go, too!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Chameleons Strike Back!
Keep going, get the touchdown!
You bums don't stand a chance
against Zoku U's Tokage Habashira!
It's smashin' time!
He's on Zoku U's football team...
Looks like a scrimmage...
Habashira's not around...
I guess he really did quit...
He got 'em...
This really... isn't like Zokugaku.
What're you doing out here?
I'm just the manager, why're you so scared?
"Official challenge?"
A challenge?
You two got guts, coming here on your own!
W-W-We're just the messengers!
A-And it's just for a scrimmage! Practice!
Read it.
To our dear friends the Chameleons,
We've picked you as the next opponents
for our Death Game, so be honored!
W-Wha?
O-Obviously we could throw a bunch of freshmen at you
and you still wouldn't stand a chance...
We're going to obliterate you,
you brain-dead dropout Chameleon losers.
Did you write this, Eyeshield 21?
You know, lately...
...you've been acting like a real big shot!
I'm not a big shot, I swear!
Death Game my butt, who do you think we are?
Let's mop the floor with 'em!
Yeah!
Time to go beat down Deimon!
Knock it off!
Rui?
Habashira...
Tell Hiruma we're in.
Habashira?
Seriously?
After they talked to us like that-
Clam it!
If you don't like it...
...get your revenge on the field.
Hold the phone, man!
If we lose we're quitting the Kanto Tournament, right?
And we're only using freshmen?
Why are you limiting us so much?
And against Zokugaku?!
If you don't wanna quit, you'd better win.
Without our second-years?!
Who'll be the quarterback?
Relax, I picked a suitable replacement.
You did?!
Natsuhiko Taki makes his debut as a genius quarterback!
- We may as well quit right now!
Look over there, you idiots.
- W-Weapons!
This isn't pro wrestling, are they out of their minds?
Looks like the challenge letter worked.
They're serious.
If you don't bring your A-game
you might be going home on a stretcher.
What do we do, Sena?
W-Well, if we charge in at full strength, we can... we can...
Think about this for a second!
We've only got 10 regular members as it is!
We lose, we have to quit!
What are we supposed to do?!
It'll be fine.
Just leave it to me!
Oh my God.
This idiot...
We're already...
...in deep trouble...
Oh yeah...
Zokugaku Chameleons vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha.
Deimon is playing their second death game
using only their freshman players!
A trial in and of itself!
A trial in every sense of the word!
Can we really play with only freshmen?
Everyone, do your best!
Set, hut hut hut!
What an odd throwing stance...
That's...
Kid's quickdraw pose!
Yay!
W-Wow, he really did it!
Wha... Buh?
- He passed it to the opponent!
Touchdown!
How can this be?!
Well, he got the motion right...
Look at your target when you throw a pass!
His throwing style's harder than it looks.
Who told you to try such a high-level move?!
- Easy! Easy, Kuroki!
- Just throw like normal, NORMAL!
Zokugaku Chameleons 7 - Deimon Devil Basts 0
The score is 7-0!
Why does he have to be such a thick-head?
The game's just started...
T-That's true, we'll be fine.
Right, Hiruma?
Yup. Chinfuzz will be back in his element soon enough.
Set, hut!
Here I go, Monta!
- Everyone on #80!
N-No way!
How can this be?!
How did they know who I was throwing to?!
What kind of idiot shouts out the name of his pass target?!
Keep your trap shut when you pass,
- you lunatic!
- Easy! Easy, Kuroki!
This time!
How can this be?!
Why would you ever pass it to me, you nutcase?!
- Easy! Easy, Kuroki!
I-Is he really going make it through this?
My brother...
Yeah, he'll be... fine...
Fine, I'll carry it myself!
Did the line fall asleep out there?!
- Come on, Monta!
- See if you can fall slower next time!
Maybe YOU should run somewhere
we can actually block!
What's happening to Deimon?
The game's barely even started!
They're having trouble working together today.
And you, you need to move quicker!
You trying to say I can't keep up?
- Yup!
- Exactly!
You lousy-
What'd I tell you!
All of you guys on the line...
- ...need to shape up!
- Same to you!
Shaddap!
Shape up!
I don't wanna hear this from you!
Just do your job!
Keep your feet planted!
The whole line needs to do better!
Quiet!
- You losers don't have any room
- If we're gonna be like this...
- to yell at me!
- ...we don't deserve to play
Say what?!
If we're going to be like this,
we don't deserve our spot in the Kanto Tournament!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what you need to be a lineman like Kuriton!
It's all about "blocking!"
You need to block the opponent from moving forward
so your team can advance the ball safely.
Steel your body and open up a path!
Ya-ha!
If we're going to be like this,
we don't deserve our spot in the Kanto Tournament!
What're you saying, Sena?
We're out here so we CAN play in the tournament.
You're not making any sense.
Yes I am!
We can't win if we're at each other's throats...
We'd never make it to the Christmas Bowl!
What's wrong with us?
We're all worked up just because the second-years aren't here.
Yelling at a first-time quarterback with no practice...
And then turning on each other.
We're awful.
We didn't make it this far on our own...
We got here together, as a team.
And now look at us.
Guys...
Lemme have it, Sena.
Slap me, you doofus!
Yeah, smack me one, Togano!
Then you hit me, Kuroki!
Come on, Komusubi!
Me, too!
- Let's do it!
Slap me, Sena!
Y-Y-Yes sir!
- Let's do it!
Let's do it!
Wait, I don't want to-
What are they doing?
They're smacking each other in the face...
We're finished.
- Let's do it!
- The passion of youth triumphs!
What's Deimon doing now?
They're taking turns hitting each other in the face.
Perhaps this is...
...a motivational technique to prepare them for a new strategy!
So now what?
We're not even gonna score if this keeps up.
Come on, we've been in tighter spots than this!
Yeah, as long as our chances of winning aren't at zero,
we're still in it, you wimps!
That's what he'd say.
I just thought of a good idea, too.
C'mere, Taki.
Okay, lay it on me, my brother!
Oh brother... this guy...
Sheesh...
What a goof.
They're laughing...
What are they doing?
Set, hut!
You're not going anywhere!
- Rip their heads off!
- Crush Eyeshield!
- What? Over there?
Deimon, 10 yard gain!
Yay!
We got a first down!
Good job, Monta!
There you go... If you can't pass, you hand the ball off.
High five!
Good one, Monta!
Our plan worked to the max!
You fool!
Pay attention, Arato!
You let him through!
What about you, fat boy?
You let him waltz right past you!
Put a sock in it!
They got through one time, don't get so mad!
Look who's talking!
Why don't YOU chill out first!
Those idiots, not again!
Set, hut!
#21?
#80? Which one?
Get them both!
- Neither of them?
- Huh?
- Him?
The goof-off?
A graceful touchdown!
Yay, bro!
Way to go!
Touchdown!
What a basic play.
Yup, but it becomes very effective with Sena involved.
So using Sena as a decoy...
...might be the way to win this?
21 seconds left.
There's no time left.
This might be our last offense!
Don't worry, it'll be okay!
We'll win, I know we will!
Why?! Why can't we get through?!
Their quarterback's not playing,
their center's not playing,
and there's only ten of them!
If they use Eyeshield on the next play,
we'll be in real trouble.
You guys ready?
You morons!
H-Habashira...
You still don't get it, do you?
Look at them.
Let's keep it up, don't quit on me!
What a spaz.
- We're only down by one!
- Seriously!
They're laughing...
How...
How can they laugh with such a tool playing quarterback?
Especially when they're down a point.
They believe...
...in their victory...
...and in each other!
You can't beat them, with or without weapons.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
My bad.
We can't let 'em get that last point!
We'll knock 'em outta the Kanto Tournament!
Yeah! Let's rock!
- Yeah!
When will they learn?
Set, hut!
Here they come, Hamaguchi!
Right! Stay focused, Arato!
Don't worry, they won't get me again!
What's up with them?
Suddenly their teamwork's a lot better.
It ain't as good as ours!
It's Eyeshield for sure!
Flatten him!
We got this!
Go, Zokugaku!
- Not happening!
Don't lose it now!
Deimon!
Touchdown!
It's all over!
Deimon wins 12-7!
Eyeshield 21 does it again!
Uh-oh, Riko, you've turned into your dad again!
You guys are the best!
We won!
All right!
Sheesh, they kept it suspenseful enough...
Two Death Games down, three to go.
-All right!
- All right!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Yay! Today's the Deimon School Festival!
Hiruma's not around, so let's have some fun!
A festival...
All I ever did at these was be a gopher.
Then you'll just have to make up for all that lost time!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Deimon School Festival! Ya-ha!
The deal was you work for me again
until the Christmas Bowl.
I never said-
Look close at the last part of the challenge letter.
The losing team has to be the winning team's slaves...
Hiruma, you freakin'- You wanna go right now?!
- Mister Hiruma...
He's Satan himself...