Bando Spiders vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Okay, come on!
- Ya-ha!
Sorry, but we're going to the Kanto Tournament!
The field goal attempt was a success!
Deimon's in trouble!
They can't stand up to Bando's offensive onslaught!
There's already a huge 20 point game separating them!
They're strong!
They're TOO strong!
So, what will you do, Deimon?!
Will Hiruma be forced to throw in the towel
when they can't even snag possession?!
No, he won't!
Those aren't the eyes of someone who's given up!
Those are the eyes of someone who is waiting
for even the slightest hope of victory!
Waiting?
But who's... he waiting for?
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Run! Musashi!
Spiders! Spiders!
At any rate...
We need to get some points to change the tide!
The winner of this game
will get the last and final ticket to the Kanto Tournament.
But bluntly put, Deimon's in trouble!
Their lack of a kicker has really hurt them.
Will Deimon's dreams of reaching the Christmas Bowl end here?!
Hiruma...
Kurita...
What was that "I hate football now" garbage?
That was nothing but a lie!
You're practically dripping with the desire to play football again.
So how long are you gonna keep hanging around the TV?!
Get the heck outta here!
How dare you talk to me like that?!
What?!
You can act tough like that in your cozy little bed,
but what would happen to all of our employees?!
Just how many mouths do you think we're feeding?!
What was that?!
Don't mess around with me, you impudent brat!
Dad!
Hang in there, Dad!
What's wrong?
What are you doing, Gen?!
You don't...
Dad?!
You don't know a darn thing!
Please try to calm down.
Gen, can you leave for a bit?
Please!
I'm sorry...
Deimon's getting backed into a corner!
Bando's kicking offense is just too much!
Yay! That's amazing, Musashi!
Your code name's gonna be the 60-Yard Magnum!
You already got the uniforms made?
We'll have an advantage when we're in high school if we start now.
We're going to the Christmas Bowl, aren't we?
Yep!
We've seen just how disturbingly powerful a kicking team can be!
Deimon's in a pinch!
They've totally got us figured out.
So this is why kicking teams are so fearsome!
I don't care if it's the Spider's Web or not,
we've gotta pull out of this eternal loop!
And to do that...
...I've got to break past Akaba's lead blocking.
But how do we do that?!
Let's change our positions.
Huh?
Bando's doing another onside kick!
Just how long will this one-sided offense continue?!
Go!
Both teams are rushing after the ball!
It's our first tag-play!
What's that?
That's-?!
It's a Sena-Hiruma combination run!
Hiruma has become the shield that will block Akaba!
He's reliable but scary!
Akaba's coming!
Yoichi Hiruma...
Sorry, but you can't defeat my Spider Poison.
He was effortlessly able to throw down Kurita,
Jumonji and the others, so...
I wonder how Hiruma's going to stop him?
Stop that!
Hiruma's willing to be my shield!
So I've got to trust him and dash forward!
It's fight between team leaders!
The true Eyeshield 21,
Hayato Akaba vs. the Demonic Tactician, Yoichi Hiruma!
Perfect! Hiruma's center of gravity shifted!
GREAT! Get him!
You feinted shifting your center of gravity?
Most impressive.
But, Hiruma,
you're forgetting something very important.
Unfortunately for you,
I'm more than powerful enough to push you down!
Yeah.
That's why you're such a pain in the butt.
Oh no! Yocchie!
A Bando player is running after the ball!
Nah, Hiruma knew beforehand
that he couldn't win in a match of brute strength.
But he was able to momentarily stop Akaba.
And that moment...
...was more than enough for him.
Sena!
- Sena!
It's showtime! It's not Eyeshield 21!
It's Sena Kobayakawa's first explosive run as himself!
Hiruma opened the path to this ball for me...
I've GOTTA get a touchdown!
Stop him!
Shoot! I'm the last person left!
Like I can stop THAT!
I'm just supposed to be the kicker!
Touchdown!
Peewee blew right on through!
Wow! He's way faster now!
He's fighting on his team as Sena Kobayakawa,
not as Eyeshield 21.
And that run proved that he's brimming with determination.
It's his first touchdown as Sena Kobayakawa
instead of as Eyeshield 21!
Bando Spiders 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
It's now 20-6!
Bando Spiders 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Deimon's finally scored some points!
My Sena...
Sena scored some points!
Guess that makes sense.
Sena was Eyeshield, after all.
But still...
It's amazing!
You're amazing, Sena!
Good job, Sena Kobayakawa!
Darn it! Was he really that smart-looking?
Now it's Deimon's turn to go for the extra points!
Set, hut!
Akaba quickly blew them away!
Since Deimon doesn't have a kicker,
the only chance they have at scoring anything
would be for them to run.
Their choice was a little too obvious.
You darn brat!
You're thinking,
"They could have gotten off a kick if I were there!"
Dad!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What's an important trait for someone sharing Musashi's position?
They hint is "confidence."
Kickers get to take the stage during important parts of the game.
So it's important that they're confident and don't cave in under pressure.
Don't be a chicken!
Ya-ha!
How long are you going to keep sulking around?!
Stop this nonsense, you impudent brat!
Get on outta here!
You don't know how it feels.
And I don't need you lecturing me about it!
This might be my last chance!
My dream might die today!
How many times do you think I've wanted
to leave you in the dust and run onto the field?!
But you see,
I worry about what would happen to all of our employees
at Takekura Construction if I left!
It's not like I can let some sickling take over the company
when he needs garbage like this to even hit people!
And Tamahachi's gonna have a kid soon!
I'll be fine, Gen!
Tamahachi... Guys...
I called them.
I knew you two would never be able to work this out on your own.
We can keep Takekura Construction afloat
without you there to help out.
I swear the company won't go under!
You need to stop trying to baby Takekura's workers.
Now go, Gen!
Gen!
Go on!
Gen, leave everything to us!
Go on now, Gen!
Gen, go!
You jerk...
Earlier you said you had thought about leaving us in the dust, didn't you?
Then go...
...and leave us in the dust.
Dad!
Gen, take this! I saved it.
You're gonna drop out?!
But why, Gen?!
Tamahachi, please...
Let's fly, Gen!
My stupid brat...
He better make it in time!
Otherwise I'll curse you!
Yay! Deimon's finally gained possession!
Now will they counterattack like mad?!
Set, hut!
I won't let you through!
What?! There's no ball!
Hiruma's got it!
Wow!
They made it look like Kobayakawa was going to run
but then had Raimon catch a long pass!
Uh-oh! Raimon's catch was incomplete!
Akaba had been anticipating this!
Now there's a scramble!
Hiruma's got the ball!
But Akaba was anticipating that, too!
Hiruma got thrown down!
Why'd this have to happen now?!
We won't make it in time if this keeps up!
Deimon still hasn't stolen their first down!
This is their third chance at offense!
So parlor tricks won't work, huh?
Go, Peewee!
You're the only one left!
Whoops! Kobayakawa's been squashed again!
Akaba's amazing!
He's like a soloist on stage!
Sadly, I've grown tired of listening to you guys play your melody.
Is he a monster?
Will Deimon get their first down next time?!
We're down to five seconds left in the first half!
They've got 45 yards between them and the goal.
This'll be tough...
Akaba's stopped both our passes and runs.
All that's left is kicking...
Like we've got someone here who can make a 45-yard kick!
Arrgh!
We desperately need a kicker with us now!
Bando's Kotaro is probably the only high schooler
who can make a 45-yard kick.
Deimon's out of options!
They're outta luck!
No, there may be one other person who could...
It's no good. We're not moving at all.
Gen...?
Hiruma...
Kurita...
I'll kick...
Guys!
Hiruma's Just-Smash-It-Kick won't work.
Then what should we do?!
Musashi...
This is the game that determines
who'll get the final seat to the Kanto Tournament.
It's the ultimate battle between
the Bando Spiders and the Deimon Devil Bats!
Will Bando win? Or will it be Deimon?!
The score's 20-6!
Bando's got a 14 point lead!
You're late!
You're 13,297 hours and 49 minutes late!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
He's here! He's here! HE'S HERE!
Musashi's finally here at last!
M-Musashi!
You've come back!
We don't have time for you to cry!
It's time for a counter-attack!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Time has Begun Again! Ya-ha!
Good luck!
Go for it, Gen!
We're with you!
Don't you lose!
I'll curse you if your kick stinks!
Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!