Yeah, c'mon everyone!
Trying... to the max!
Hold your horses!
Ah, Kotaro from Bando.
Where the heck's Musashi?
The Bando Spiders are too good for a kicker-less team to handle!
Ignore him, you'll catch dork-itis.
See ya.
Hey, don't ignore me!
Listen up.
I have a message for Musashi.
Kotaro Sasaki, i.e. ME, is the number one kicker!
I'm throwing down the gauntlet!
Holy cow!
One shot, from all the way back there?
And...
...it was full.
- What a dork.
Anyway!
Just make sure Musashi's there for the Bando-Deimon game!
Musashi...
I'll prove that I'm a better kicker than he is!
Got it?!
He's really confident.
He's also putting more pressure on himself.
Well, when you call yourself the best,
you're expected to win.
Which means he's ready to do whatever it takes to come out on top...
You all...
...need to be doing the same thing!
- Y-Yes!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Come back, Musashi!
The Deimon-Bando game is likely to be very close.
Yeah...
The Spiders' heavy emphasis on kicking
nets them an easy three points for field goals.
And a guaranteed extra point after touchdowns.
That's how they'll play.
But we...
Deimon doesn't have a kicker...
In close games, one point can make all the difference in the world.
A kicker...
But how can we...
Okay.
Follow me, Sena!
Follow you? Where?
Where else?
To see Musashi and beg him to come back for the game!
"You promised, remember Musashi?"
"You said you'd come back when Deimon proved itself to be a better team."
We made it to the Final Four.
Anyone would have to admit we've improved, right?
W-Why?
Look, Gen just said he has no intention of going back to school.
I'm sorry... You kids will have to leave.
Please, just let us talk to him.
He promised us!
Look, I understand, but...
- Musashi!
Beat it.
But...
I said beat it.
You...
You promised us, remember?
You said you'd come back when Deimon proved itself to be a better team.
Tama, we're done for the day.
Remember to lock up.
Gen!
Are you sure about this, Gen?
Those kids care about you, are you just gonna ignore them?
You WANT to go back, don't you?
I've seen you watching Deimon's games on TV.
Your dad's in stable condition,
and thanks to your hard work,
Takekura Construction's managed to get back on its feet.
We'll be fine, you can go back to-
Thanks.
But it's just too late.
I still feel the same way I did back then.
You're dropping out?!
Why, Gen?
What about your football-
Tamahachi, gimme a hand.
When a man sacrifices himself for others,
he endures it in silence.
I'm going to visit my dad,
take care of closing shop.
Gen...
Wanna go see Musashi again after practice?
You bet!
I'm not giving up on him.
Oh, Sena, Monta!
I've got big, big news!
Musashi's coming back!
My bro found this!
I'm such a genius!
This is...
...the starting lineup for the game!
That's Musashi's name!
See? That means...
...there's a 150% chance he'll be playing!
M-Musashi's coming back?!
Really?
Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray! Musashi's coming back! Yay!
But yesterday he told us to get lost...
Well, he was still at work, right?
If his name's on the roster, it's all good.
No more...
Hiruma... always does that.
He does?
Always?
Yeah... For the three of us,
time's been frozen since that day...
In middle school, Hiruma, Musashi and I
truly believed we'd make it to the Christmas Bowl.
Oh, the Mao Devil Bats are going for a field goal!
But at 45 yards, this will be a tough one!
No way, from all the way out here?
What morons, they'll never make it!
It's good! The Mao Devil Bats win!
The three of us graduated and were accepted at Deimon.
We absolutely believed we'd make it...
The idea that one of us would go away never even entered our heads.
But then...
Your father just collapsed!
He passed out while he was working and fell off a beam!
You gotta hurry!
I'm sorry!
Musashi never stepped back on the field.
He said he had to take over
Takekura Construction in his dad's place.
I had no idea...
Musashi's been through so much...
Why did you leave the Devil Bats, Musashi?
I abandoned Kurita and Hiruma.
Playing on a weak team is no fun.
I knew it, he was lying.
He wanted us to leave him alone...
But Hiruma and I still believe the three of us
will go to the Christmas Bowl.
That's why Hiruma
manipulated things so that Musashi's
considered to be on an extended absence
instead of having dropped out.
And putting his name on the roster every game...
so he can come back any time.
This kick tee's just like the rest of us.
Waiting for the day when its owner comes back for it.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to cut off a pass!
The hint is "arms!"
The trick to cutting off a pass is pushing your opponent with one arm
and hitting the ball with the other.
Use BOTH your arms!
Ya-ha!
Just waiting...
Just waiting's not gonna change anything!
C'mon, Sena.
I understand exactly how you and Hiruma feel.
Let's go shove this kick tee down Musashi's throat!
Hey, wait! Monta!
I'm comin' for ya to the max, Musashi!
The kick tee!
Truck Catch!
MONTA!
Gotcha.
You okay, Monta?!
I'm fine, but Musashi's kick tee's...
Excuse me!
Just in time...
Way to go, Sena, you did it!
Let's get moving.
Sena?
Maybe not going would be better.
What're you talking about, Sena?
Don't you want Musashi back on the team?
Of course I do!
But...
The Bando game's just around the corner!
We can't wait any longer, we gotta convince him!
W-Wait up!
Those two shrimps went to see Musashi?!
They're just gonna make things even more complicated!
Why didn't you stop them, you stupid fat lump!
I'm sorry, Hiruma!
Let's go.
You WANT to go back, don't you?
You promised us, remember?
You said you'd come back when Deimon proved itself to be a better team.
I promised...
Dad used to beat the Shinola outta me whenever I broke a promise...
Do you know what it means when a man goes back on his word?!
Please! Look who's talking!
What?!
You impudent little brat!
He didn't pull any punches even when I was young.
Until...
Dad, I heard you fell off a beam, are you all right?!
What're you doing here?
Men don't just abandon their position...
You impudent little brat!
Why was his punch so weak?
It was like he was swatting a fly.
I'm so pathetic...
Hey, Monta, I really think
we should just go home.
You can't be serious, we're already here!
But-!
You two?
Hiya...
Kurita told us all about what happened...
But...
Please, Musashi!
Please rejoin the Devil Bats!
We won't be able to defeat Bando without you!
If one guy's absence is all it takes to make you lose,
then go get it over with.
- Hey, wait up!
- M-Monta!
Does this kick tee
bring back any memories?!
Hiruma and Kurita are still holding on to it for you!
They've never stopped believing that you'd come back
someday to use it again!
Get lost.
Are you just gonna let them wait forever without saying anything?!
Shut up!
I don't know what Hiruma and Kurita have been telling you,
but I don't care what happens to them anymore!
M-Musashi...
Christmas Bowl this, Christmas Bowl that...
It's the same garbage over and over again.
I feel sorry a nice guy like Kurita has to go through this!
I may have been goaded into playing football by that jerk Hiruma,
but I don't have time to mess around with those two any more.
Mess around... You're awful...
Now he's got his lackeys to wave that kick tee in my face...
There's no low he won't stoop to.
I won't say anything more about him,
but if Hiruma's forcing you to play,
you're better off quitting now.
He's not!
Hiruma and Kurita...
They're not like that.
Sena...
I'm sure the situation with your father is a difficult one.
I understand if there's no way for you to return to Deimon.
But...
Don't badmouth Hiruma and Kurita,
they're putting everything they have into the team.
They're both playing because they love football!
I know...!
I don't need...
...to hear it from you two.
I know better...
...than anyone!
Musashi...
If...
If by some miracle my dad got better...
Then...
That night, the next morning, no, even in the middle of a game!
I'd start kicking again that instant!
That impertinent brat...
S-Sena, Musashi really DOES care!
Musashi still wants to play football with Hiruma and Kurita.
And they both know it...
That's why they're just waiting for him.
We should too.
We'll believe, and wait.
Right!
Forget Bando, we'll squash them!
Yeah!
Hiruma, they're great teammates, aren't they?
How long are you gonna bawl, Fattycakes?
Wait, Hiruma!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Time to train for the Bando game!
Hey, this is no time for running errands!
I still have to act as a manager
so Mamori won't find out the truth!
What a pain- Wait, what's this?
A Bando helmet with an eye shield?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: "The True 21!" Ya-ha!
Smart as always.
Hey, mister!
Kick this too!
And this!
Mine too!
Not smart...
Ah, who cares.
Okay, line up!
Who was here first?
YAY!