Yay!
Caps!
Megaphones!
Cheering sticks!
T-shirts!
Wow! You had all these made?
We've decided on our regular players now.
And the fall season's just about to start!
I do things right when I do them!
I'm trying my best to be a captain that pumps everyone up!
Hey, here's this month's issue of American Football Monthly!
"Closing in on Eyeshield 21's True Identity!"
"We asked a cheerleader what he really looks like."
"He's as hot as a Hollywood star."
Whatta lie!
That's a bit too much.
"Hype them up! Terrify them!"
"The bigger the bluff, the better!"
At least that's what Yocchie said.
Y-Yocchie?
I know who that is without having to ask.
Huh?
Suzuna, isn't Sena here yet?
Sena's...
Hey, I've been wanting to ask you this for a while now, but...
Why are you keeping it a secret from Mamo that you're Eyeshield?
W-Well...
Why?
It's horrible!
There's TV staffers over there who want to interview Eyeshield 21, right now!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Road to the Christmas Bowl!
There he is!
We're going to have a surprise interview with the highly rumored Devil Hero, Eyeshield 21!
We've gotta stay low for a while!
Why do you have to keep it a secret, anyway?
Because Hiruma told me to.
Who knows what he'd do to me if people found out who I am?!
Just thinking about it scares me!
You're weird.
Why are you even playing football when you're such a wuss?
Well... I guess... it just kinda happened...
It happened the day Deimon High announced who got accepted...
I spy fresh meat.
You passed! Way to go! Ya-ha!
Please, inform your dear parents about your success.
Hi, mom? Guess wha-
Hiruma!
He is the ONE student that is off limits!
So that's how you meet Yocchie, huh?
And then Mamori said...
I know, why don't you join a club?
That's what she said, so...
And to make a long story short, you always do what Mamo says, don't ya?
So you decided to join the football team?
Yeah.
It makes me so excited,
working together to reach a common goal,
running right over our opponents on the way!
You're also recruiting team managers?
U-Um...
Do you think I could be your team manager?
O-O-Of course!
Yahoo!
Let's shoot for the Christmas Bowl, together!
So at first, I had just joined to be the team manager.
The eyeshield looks neat!
We'll need to hide his face during games,
or the other clubs'll try to steal those legs from us.
Games? But I wanted to be manage-
During a game, you don't answer to "Sena Kobayakawa."
Your code name is...
...Eyeshield 21!
And then came our first game,
which was against the Koigahama Cupids.
I'll NEVER get past all of them and make it to the goal without getting knocked down!
Blaze a path down the field!
11 opponents... That was one...
Two, three, four...
Blow past 'em!
Five, six...
Smash him!
Go!
There's no one left!
No one can stop me!
So you got totally addicted to the sport!
It really left a big impression on me.
The weakling gopher got to be a hero for a while, after all.
But in football you get thrown around, fall down and even stepped on.
Sounds painful, ya know?
I'm amazed you never quit.
I'd thought about quitting once.
It happened... when I fought against Ojo's Shin.
It was the first time I had ever experienced just how great Shin's Spear Tackle is.
No more...
It hurts too much!
Mamori was right... I'm not cut out for this!
Everyone... I'm sorry!
I'm very busy and had to leave. Eyeshield 21.
Maybe he's abandoned us...
It's not just me.
Everyone's putting their bodies on the line out there.
Enough.
I have to stop running from pain.
I've had enough.
I won't give up until it's all over.
No matter how badly it hurts.
My chances of getting by Shin aren't zero yet.
It's no good, I can't outrun him!
Just a little faster...
And I'll escape... No... I'll win!
You won't get away!
Th-This is... The world of lightspeed...
Football Clinic!
How do you get points?
I've already explained this once before!
You get six points from a touch down.
Then you can kick the ball to get the point after.
Make sure not to forget this time! Ya-ha!
Wow! You got past Shin!
Yeah,
but only once.
I was really shocked back then.
I thought we wouldn't be able to go to the Christmas Bowl anymore.
Don't tell me you're not done sorting the pictures, Peewee!
We're already getting ready for the Christmas Bowl!
Isn't the tournament over?
There are two of them per year.
One in the spring, and one in the fall.
The winner of the fall tournament goes to the Christmas Bowl!
We still have fall.
The real battle is still ahead!
We still didn't have most of the Deimon members on the team back then, right?
Right.
Shortly after that Monta joined...
Komusubi and Yuki also joined up with us.
And then Jumonji and his buddies finally started to show a true interest in football.
YA-HA!
And then we won the game that would determine who would get to represent Japan!
Devil Bat Dive!
Touchdown!
There he is! It's Eyeshield 21!
Today I finally get to see your wonderful face!
Run for it!
Yocchie is always watching us, isn't he?
That's what makes him scary!
Hiruma's always thinking ahead.
So, then what?
Well, um...
My new rival, Panther, made his appearance.
Tackle him, Eyeshield 21!
You're the last line of defense!
Bring it, Eyeshield 21!
Get ready, Panther!
I couldn't catch up with Panther's gravity-defying legs.
Touchdown!
E-Even Sena couldn't catch him...
What incredible legs...
It's no good... I can't beat him.
Your running's pretty cool.
But you're not using your full power.
I'm gonna be the greatest running back in history.
So I have to hit guys like Seijuro Shin and Eyeshield...
...with all I've got!
You sure you're trying your hardest against me?
That's right...
Panther came all the way from America to face me.
I have to give it 100%!
His arm?
How could he push me like that?
He's got both hands wrapped around the ball...
I get it!
He leaves himself vulnerable during that brief moment he pushes off,
because he has to take one hand off the ball!
He's a black panther, released from his cage for the first time.
He doesn't understand the real wilderness.
Eyeshield's running, developed from years of being a gopher...
...is the REAL beast.
Even a timid herbivore, when backed into a corner...
...can momentarily gain unimaginable power.
I won!
NOW!
THAT is Eyeshield 21!
Instantly hitting the 4.2 second level...
The world of lightspeed!
I refuse to lose!
Touchdown!
But since no one won by 10 points...
I hate to break up this tender moment,
but you're gonna keep your end of the bargain.
Our passports!
And what about you?!
You all have to leave Japan immediately, remember?!
Ah, yes. I guess you don't need your plane tickets home anymore, right?
N-No way!
Ya-ha! We're all training in America!
Seriously?! Training in America?!
And that's how Yocchie was able to force everyone to go to America.
Yeah. While in America we found Coach Doburoku...
Here's the deal, Fatty and I are staying here in America to train.
Anyone who's sticking with us, cross the line.
No one has ever endured the death march and come out unscathed.
What's everyone doing out there?
But if you're willing to tempt death to get stronger,
rip up your ticket to heaven, and follow us into hell!
Taro Raimon, #80.
Position: Wide Receiver!
My favorite sport is now American football!
Studying isn't my favorite thing to do!
Manabu Yukimitsu, #16.
I... don't have a position yet!
Daikichi Komusubi, #55, line!
Let's roll, Jumonji.
You sure?
Win, and everyone will respect you.
That's what football's about!
What do you think, Toga?
Jumonji's all psyched up.
It's gonna be rough not having any manga to read,
but I guess American comics will do.
One, two...
Kazuki Jumonji, #51. Position: Lineman!
Koji Kuroki, #52. Ditto.
Shozo Togano, #53. Same here.
That's it... Everyone's playing football to become the men they truly want to be!
I know what I have to do...
I want the same thing!
I'll train hard with my friends and get stronger!
I want to win!
Sena Kobayakawa, #21. Position: Running Back!
Sena's Eyeshield 21?!
Then it's settled.
Participating in the death march across America is...
...the entire Deimon Devil Bats team!
We're all going to the Christmas Bowl... together!
And Mamo's the only one who doesn't know that you're Eyeshield
since she was on the airplane.
Hey, why don't you tell her in secret?
I bet she'd be surprised!
Mamori's always been the one to protect me ever since we were little
and I don't want to make her worry any.
Worry?
If she knew that I'm Eyeshield,
she'd be afraid that I'd get hurt or that I'm pushing myself too far.
So... you're gonna keep it a secret forever?
No.
I'll tell her myself.
I'll tell her when I'm a good enough player that she won't need to worry.
I'll be waiting at the finals.
I'll tell her when I'm good enough to defeat Shin.
Okay! I'll root for you until then!
Suzuna!
Yay! Yay! Deimon!
Yay! Yay! Devil Bats!
Yay! Yay! Devil Bats! Yay!
I've made such wonderful friends...
We're all going to the Christmas Bowl, together!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Yay! We've decided on the regulars now!
The waits finally over, Sena!
At last... The fall season's going to begin at last!
In this tournament, your finished if you lose once!
You've gotta be a man and fight!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Night Before the Game! Ya-ha!
I can't believe we haven't found him despite all of our searching.
Don't tell me that you're really Eyeshield 21!
Huh?