YA-HA!
Uhh, never mind me...
American football!
This all-out physical war comes down to:
Power!
Tactics, and...
...speed!
Touchdown!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Farewell Kurita?!
All right!
Let's get going!
The hell dash!
S-S-Save me-
Hell passes!
Max Super Catch!
Max Hero Catch!
Max Miracle Catch!
Max Special Rolling Galactica Catch!
Keep going, Monta!
M-Mamori!
Hell block!
Do it.
Do it!
Fine, we're going, we're going!
Everyone's working so hard...
That's not working, that's going way overboard-
Okay, my turn!
Ya-ha!
Is everyone okay?
Yes...
I must say, you guys really gave it 110%!
But of course!
We're all shooting for the Christmas Bowl!
Just wait and see how much it'll pay off!
The post-workout fatigue actually feels good, doesn't it?
I-I suppose so!
Oh, you're feeling it too, Sena?
Uh, well, I guess not, but...
Anyways, we've got a full team, so we need to keep at it!
This is so nice...
Before this year, it was always just me and Hiruma...
Practice was lonely, but now that we all do it together, it's so much fun.
Well, I've gotta go home now, so...
See you tomorrow!
That's right... Kurita's probably the most excited about the new members.
Yippee!
Ooh, there's a festival?
No!
C'mon, hang out with us!
No means no!
We'll all have a real nice time.
Please, leave us alone!
Please help me!
No!
C'mon, that looks fun, right? Come hang with us.
You look dumb!
I'm not going with you!
You're all weirdos!
Aww, don't run!
We just said we wanna to show you ladies a real good time!
We don't want to swing around!
Just let us go home...
Yahoo!
Ow! No NO-
Yikes!
Ouch!
What're they yelling about?
What the-
What happened out here?!
The festival decorations!
Oh man, cheese it!
H-Hey-!
Th-They're all broken!
Who in the world did all this?!
Was it you?!
We finally finished hanging them all up...
Umm... I, uhh...
You're gonna fix all this!
Hey, you!
Get back here!
Why me?!
Don't let him run!
That uniform was...
You hear about what happened at the station?
You mean by all the shops?
Every single festival decoration got trashed!
They were really expensive, too!
I heard it was someone from our school!
Really?
Who was it?
No one knows, but the person was wearing our uniform!
They didn't see his face, but they said he was this huge mountain of muscle!
I knew it, they think it's me!
All the store owners are really upset, they even filed a complaint with the cops!
Seriously?! If they catch the guy I bet he'll get locked up!
Well, at the very least, he'll get expelled.
W-Why me...
Every last one of 'em was wrecked.
Why would they do that?
How am I supposed to know?
Stress from exam preparations, perhaps.
No way...
I-I would never do something like that!
That's right, no one from our school would ever-
Are you kidding? I can think of plenty!
Why is it so hot today?
I know, it makes me feel sick...
Are you people insane?!
You think we're that stupid?
That's an insult!
You little-
Hey, chill out, no need to get angry-
YOU guys started it!
Everyone, please, enough.
No one on this team would ever do something like that.
We're all training for the Christmas Bowl, remember?
What's that got to do with this?
If our team was involved in an incident like this, we'd be barred from playing, right?
Oh, I see!
If they hear I was there...
Touchdown!
And the Deimon Devil Bats are the Christmas Bowl champions!
Oh my!
We've just been informed that Kurita used his immense power to assault two helpless foreign women!
He then sent three young men to the hospital and destroyed an entire shopping district!
T-That's a lie!
Athletic Commission
You are stripped of your title!
The Deimon Devil Bats are hereby disbanded!
Arrest him!
Stop, stop, stop!
I'm innocent, I tell you!
We must protect Earth! Fire!
Help me!
I'm-!
Resignation?
I'm going to turn myself in!
Football clinic!
What is this "Christmas Bowl" everyone's always talking about?
The All-Japan High School Championship Game!
The top teams from eastern and western Japan clash in one climactic game!
Ya-ha!
So if I stay on the team, I'll just end up costing everyone their shot at the Christmas Bowl...
I thought I should resign before you kicked me out...
This makes no sense!
Why should you have to resign, Kurita?!
Y-Yeah! It was those three losers, not you, right!
That's right, why do you even have to keep yourself hidden?
Well, if we don't have anyone else who knows the truth...
If I stay, everyone will have to give up their chance at the Christmas Bowl...
You lousy...
If you wanna quit, then quit.
But if you do, keep quiet so they don't start suspecting us.
H-How can you-
Hiruma!
The only witnesses are Fatty here and the two foreign chicks.
And from what I heard, the two of them are here sightseeing.
There's no telling where they could be by now.
But Kurita didn't do anything!
It doesn't matter how many of us claim he's innocent,
if we don't have the real criminals, the end result'll be the same.
So keep a lid on it.
You got that?
Yes... I will.
No! You can't let him-
We ARE going to the Christmas Bowl!
No matter WHAT happens!
U-Umm...
S-Sena?
I got kinda worried...
Oh, I'm fine...
Hey, what's-
Huh? Oh, this?
The three of us wrote this when we first made the football team.
"To the Christmas Bowl..."
We ARE going to the Christmas Bowl!
When you were freshmen?
Who's "Musashi?"
Oh... A lot happened...
Eventually it ended up as just me and Hiruma.
Are you really... just giving up on the Christmas Bowl?
As long as the rest of you make it, I'll be satisfied.
Kurita...
I'm going home...
Kurita. Kurita!
Looks like we've gotta find the real culprits ourselves!
But Hiruma's right, even finding them can't help if they won't confess.
That's true...
But we can't just throw Kurita to the wolves!
Yeah! Who knows, they might tell the truth!
Yes! We can't just let sit around doing nothing!
Then let's head out and look for people that match Kurita's description!
We'll split into two teams to give ourselves a better chance.
Wanted! Contact Demon High School's Football Club if you see them!
THAT'S how you're gonna look for them?
Won't that put the Devil Bats at risk?
Man...
It's perfect!
How soon?
I thought they'd know every juvenile delinquent in town...
This won't work...
Why would you even think it would?
Yep, that's that.
So when's the team being disbanded?
What's your problem?!
Please, calm down!
Chill out!
Zokugaku High School Academy
Say what now?
I didn't catch that.
I said, do you know anyone who was swinging on the ropes out by the Sanchoume Station-
Say what?
Okay, Sanchoume-
I dunno nothin'! Man, you're pesky!
I thought you hadn't heard a word I said-
We dunno who you guys are, either!
We dunno WHO you guys are!
It appears you fine gentlemen can't help us, then.
Please.
Hey!
If you know anything at all, please tell us.
Otherwise... we won't even get to play in the Christmas Bowl tournament!
I told you I don't know!
See? Let's go back, Sena.
Ya-ha!
Thanks anyways.
No luck at all.
Whattup, Deimon?
H-Hello...
Go check out that arcade.
Your rope-swinging guys are hanging out there.
They might know something.
Thank you so much!
Hey, umm...
Why are you helping...?
You're gonna get crushed out on the field by the great Rui Habashira, not Ojo's Shin.
Be ready for it!
Habashira...
Male bonding to the max! Now I'm pumped!
It's them!
They fit Kurita's description to a T.
All right, let's go... Er...
H-H-Hey! Wait!
Go, go!
I got it this time!
You... broke... the shops! You framed... master!
He's nuts!
He just accused them outta nowhere!
You want some of this?
Get back here!
You can't escape!
Why did it play out like this?!
Help us!
What're you guys doing?
Was it you three?
You sicced those little kids on us?
What kinda stupid garbage are you babbling about, losers?
The tables are turned! Now it's six-on-three!
You're the ones who destroyed all the festival decorations, aren't you?
You wanna rumble?
Run for it!
After them!
Man, they don't give up!
Stop!
So that's them, huh?
You're not getting away!
What the heck?! He's fast!
Eat...
...this!
Watch out!
Max Catch!
Don't...
...waste food!
I'm very conscientious.
This is insane!
I'll catch them... for Kurita, and the Devil Bats!
Distance is 40 yards away... The touchdown pass is 45 degrees to the right.
YA-HA!
Now we gotcha!
Not you too!
What're you doing? Get out there.
B-But if I go...
Just get moving, Fatty! You're owing them more favors by the second!
Kurita!
You guys did all this for me... Thank you!
These guys were the real culprits, right?
Yes...YOU were the ones who ruined the shopping mall.
You have to confess.
Wh-Who, us?
What're you talking about?
You got any witnesses?
You bet we do!
It was them!
They broke the display!
What was that?
It was you?
You wrecked out decorations?!
Please forgive us!
Then you're prepared to resolve this, right?
And fix what needs fixing?
Yes, whatever you want!
All right, we cleared your name, Kurita!
This is awesome to the max!
Then that means-
We can all go-
To the Christmas Bowl!
Yeah! Christmas Bowl, yay!
Christmas Bowl, yay!
Christmas Bowl!
Thank you, everyone!
Those women came all the way back here from New York yesterday!
Wow, why'd they come all that way?
I wonder...
It appears the Statue of Liberty is holding something!
Whoa, what-?
Get a close-up on that!
Deimon Devil Bats - Now recruiting members!
Hiruma...
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Now that the case is closed, it's time to celebrate with some Korean-style barbecue... Wait, what?
Hiruma would never let us eat our barbecue in peace!
Good point. Hey, where did those guys come from?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Kid and Iron Horse! Ya-ha!
Last year it was just me and Hiruma...
Hee hee,
hee hee,
hee hee!
I told you no one would come.
I think Kurita's having that dream again.
I guess Kurita really is the one most happy about the new members.