21st Annual Deimon School Festival
My first high school festival, I can't wait!
I've never really enjoyed them, to be honest...
I was pretty much everyone's gopher every year.
Hey, Sena, take these fliers, would you?
Okay!
Sena, pamphlets!
Right!
Sena, light bulbs!
Okay!
That's so like you!
Well, it's all in the past.
Let's have some fun this time!
Max fun!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Deimon School Festival!
Welcome, welcome!
Yum!
Woohoo! Yeah!
O-Okay, even though no one's listening...
Each year we award a one year
"all you can eat" cafeteria ticket
to the top three-person team.
The competition starts right now.
Please follow the rules.
And please don't let things get out of hand.
Even though no one's listening.
All you can eat at the cafeteria for a year?!
The three-person team
with the most points wins the tickets.
How do you get points?
Oh, there's lots of ways.
You can run a store,
put on a performance,
stuff like that.
How come no one cares, then?
Because last year one person took home all the tickets.
I can see him now.
Oh well.
We're doomed to failure with him around.
Yeah...
Everyone!
Big news!
Uh-oh.
Hiruma's skipping school today!
Oops, sorry.
Wh-
What?
Hiruma's taking the day off?
He said "I don't have time for baby games
with the Kanto Tournament around the corner!"
That means...
We've got a chance...
- ...at those tickets!
I'll beat...
...everyone else...
...and win...
...a whole year's...
...worth of food!
Team Kuroki!
- Hi!
Hi!
Team Togano!
Man...
Why am I stuck...
...with this doofus?
Team Jumonji!
What gives?!
I don't even get humans?!
This isn't fair!
Team Kurita!
One year of food!
I'll give everything I have for Mamori!
Team Boring.
What a boring team.
- Yeah...
Team Sena!
I hate team activities,
they're too much trouble...
I'm only human...
Right...
Umm... all right,
I'm sure no one cares,
but this year, we're adding
mango pudding
to the menu. Good luck.
M-Mango pudding?!
Sena, Suzuna, let's do our best!
For the mango pudding!
It's time for an anything-goes team battle
for the year-long all you can eat prize!
Wherever there's a battle, I'll be there to commentate
- I'm Machine Gun Sanada! And with me...
The high school reporter who can fill in at a moment's notice,
Riko Kumabukuro!
The first round is the team store!
Whoever draws the most customers earns 100 points!
Let the first round...
...begin!
First, we turn our attention to Team Kurita.
Oh ho, they've already got a huge line!
What type of store do we have?
Welcome, master.
Ahh, the always-popular maid cafe!
Mamori Anezaki shows us that pretty girls
always attract customers!
H-Hawt!
Mamori!
Enough! Someone save me!
Stay away from Mamori!
For some reason, Monta tackles the customers!
Well, that's no good!
Ah, it seems Kurita doesn't even care.
Welcome, everyone!
Suzuna is dressed as a manager.
What's your store?
A maid cafe!
Another maid cafe!
Step inside!
W-Welcome... master...
No amount of mango pudding is worth this.
This is too much... I'm only human...
Looks like their strategy failed.
W-Wow!
This huge building suddenly appeared out of nowhere!
And it's a casino!
Are we in Las Vegas?
A real man knows how to make an impact.
Hey!
Can I stop yet?
How big do you want this thing?
All casino customers get to come to my show!
Ignore him.
Why am I stuck with a dog and a pig?!
Next is team boring!
How are THEY faring?
Welcome.
They're very cute.
Boring. So very boring.
The second round is a stage performance!
The best team will win 100 points!
Riko and myself will serve as the judges.
First is Team Togano's "Taki one-man-show!"
How can this be?
They're doing great!
Okay, we both jump on stage when I give the signal.
You're sure we're allowed to interrupt another team?
This is about who makes the biggest impact.
We'll make a dramatic entrance and put on a magic show!
- Ta-da!
Yeah, that's right!
We'll make an impact!
There, now you're getting it!
After we come out,
Omo'll enter from the wings.
Got it!
Next is Team Boring's "Hatted Statues!"
Boring, so very boring.
Next...
Team Kuroki's Cheer Squad!
- Hi!
Kuroki and his cheerleaders are doing a combo move!
- Yay! Yay!
What're you trying to pull with a weak act like that?!
I know what the public wants.
Encore! Encore!
Everyone wants me to dance an encore?
Who let you back on stage?!
You ruined my act!
Yeah! Tear him apart!
We've got a situation up here!
They're really getting fired up!
Is it our turn yet, Suzuna?
Nope, we need an even better moment to come out.
Oh... okay!
You don't usually get this excited.
I guess.
But I'm having fun.
I've never experienced a school festival like this,
I'm having a blast.
You... stupid... mutt...
Move! Ah, forget it!
Why didn't I get any humans?!
I quit!
Next...
Team Kurita's version of "Romeo and Juliet!"
Romeo, Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
M-Mamori!
Now!
Okay!
Huh?
It's stuck.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what you need to be a lineman like Kuriton!
It's all about "combinations!"
There are five men on the line, including the center.
Combination plays are very important!
Work together and destroy the enemy!
Ya-ha!
Why isn't it opening?
We've gotta make our entrance!
Round three is the infamous Deimon Stamp Relay!
You need your first stamp from the school grounds,
the second from the entrance to the shopping district,
the third at the other end of the same district,
and the fourth and final goal is back at the school!
That's it!
Also, I forgot to announce the results from the other rounds.
Neither event counts!
Whoever wins this race wins it all!
- Then this should've been the only event!
Okay, I'm pumped to the max!
Ready, get set...
Each team is off to a quick start!
Who will make it to the first checkpoint?
What was that?
Get away from me!
Where did those two go?
Running all by myself is too much trouble.
I'm only human...
- Ta-da!
- Huh?
The teams are arriving to the first checkpoint!
The third round's already started!
Hurry and catch up to Omo, Sena!
Right.
Time to eat!
What was that?
The race moves towards the third checkpoint!
Kuroki and Togano are neck and neck,
with Monta and Taki right on their tails!
And bringing up the rear is Kurita!
Wait, someone's coming from behind, and fast!
- Sena?
- What?
Move, move, MOVE!
No freaking way!
The first team to the third checkpoint is...
Jumonji! He takes the lead!
Next are Kuroki and Togano.
They get their stamps...and take off!
Then Monta!
Thanks.
Followed by Taki,
and finally Kurita!
Wait up!
Omosadake!
The card!
I'll get you your mango pudding!
Mango pudding... I'll run, too!
I could only keep it up for five seconds...
I'm only human!
Who's made it back first?
It's Jumonji!
The goal is right in front of him!
Get away!
Goal!
He was just being chased by Cerberus...
This time it's the original top three!
Run, Kuroki!
You spoony nerd!
Excuse me?!
You and me!
Bring it!
Monta's been sucked in, too!
Awesome!
Yay!
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
Did you miss me?
Kurita's bearing down, too!
Wait, that's-
Sena!
He's charging at top speed!
What?!
Go, Sena!
Kurita, stop Sena!
It's Kurita vs. Sena!
For the food!
The Devil Bat Ghost!
He got me!
Shoot!
I made it!
- Not happening!
The stamp goes flying!
Max Catch!
Monta makes a super catch!
Nice catch!
Stamp the card, Monta!
The card...
Is everyone cheering for my dance?
There it is!
Huh?
Yes, stamp the card!
No!
Get away!
How can this be?!
Musashi!
No!
It's over!
Go, old man!
He kicked it!
Are you senile?!
I, uh...
Everyone's stupid but me!
The four are chase the flying stamp!
Sena's in the lead...
Who has the stamp?!
Yes, touchdown!
The stamp.
Finished.
Cool.
- Hooray!
Somehow, some way, Team Boring wins!
How can this be...?
I can't believe Team Boring won.
Sorry, Omosadake.
I guess I'll just be happy
they added mango pudding to the menu...
So tired...
This was our one shot without having to face Hiruma...
Didn't like the teams, huh?
I bet you HATED yours.
Well, I...
I had a ton of fun with all of you guys today!
Okay, tomorrow's another day!
Yes...
Together we can make to the Kanto Tournament!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
What's the matter, Sena?
You look beat!
Getting tired from practicing everyday?
Nah, I'm just... Something's got me really worried.
Are you serious?
Maybe running off into the mountains
like Seijuro Shin will make you feel better.
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Invisible Shackle! Ya-ha!
Get away from me!
Is he still at it?
Never knew he had so much stamina.
He's sure, uh... energetic.
Yeah, energetic.