Which one of them is Eyeshield 21?
No!
None of them are him!
Where is Eyeshield 21?
Huh? Who's that?
It's obviously one of our fans!
Hey, shrimp, do you want an autograph?
Don't be shy!
Huh?
I wouldn't take you losers' autographs, even if you begged me to.
- L-Losers?!
And just who do you think you are?
I'm the Seibu Wild Gunmen's ace running back, Riku Kaitani.
- What?!
- From Seibu?!
What's someone from Seibu doing here?!
Are you...
...a SPY?!
Deimon's not good enough to need spying on.
H-Hey, let's calm down, everyone!
Calm down!
Ah, Riku!
You're right!
Rikky!
- Ri-RIKKY?!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't."  You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero.  What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Three Made a Promise!
I wonder how long it's been since all three of us walked home together.
We used to go home like this all the time before Rikky moved.
Yeah.
But is it okay for Deimon's manager and team manager
to hang out with me like this before the semi-finals?
Deimon and Seibu have nothing to do with this!
After all, Rikky's Rikky!
You sure haven't changed any, have you?
What?
No, it's nothing.
By the way, what were you doing at Deimon today?
I'm interested in someone at Deimon.
- WHO?!
Eyeshield 21!
But I guess he wasn't there.
Come to think of it, I wonder why.
Yeah, I wonder.
Oh, yeah...
Riku doesn't know that I'm Eyeshield.
But...
Rikky hasn't changed any, either.
You've always been stubborn and a bit rude.
Back off some!
But you're a hard worker and the perfect role model for Sena.
Yeah!
Meet our new transfer student, Riku Kaitani.
I want everyone to be very nice to him.
- Okay!
- Nice to meet you!
He's cool.
Kaitani, your seat's over there.
Okay.
What's going on over there?
Well, I think I might have stepped on some nasty-smelling frog or something.
Nice to meet you!
Y-Yeah...
Wow! He bullied the bully!
- Move it!
- Ouch!
Shoot!
Amazing! He's really amazing!
So I was really happy when Riku taught me how to run.
But from the looks of it, you never got over being a gopher.
Ouch!
You didn't keep your promise at all!
Oh!
"Oh," my butt!
Y-Yeah, I'm sorry.
Sena, wait up!
Here. Sit still.
Okay, all better.
How long are you going to let Mamo keep babying you, Sena?
I'm guessing you haven't kept your other promise either, have you?
Hm? What promise?
I-It's nothing! Right, Sena?
Y-Yeah, it's nothing.
You're transferring again?!
But...
I...
Keep your head up, Sena!
A man must always look straight forward!
Yeah, that's it!
Hey, you guys!
Bro, that's them!
Looks like you had some fun at my brother's expense.
R-Riku, what should we do?
This pig-frog's nothing but a pushover!
What was that?!
You brat!
Darn it!
You jerk!
That's pathetic.
Argh!
Stop it!
We'll clobber him instead!
Let go of me!
Stop it!
I'll let him go if you shut up and let us beat you up.
So, what'll it be?
Whatcha gonna do?
So you don't care!
Take this, you brat!
Wait!
Riku?!
You should have done that from the start.
W-What should I do?!
Hey, get a load of this!
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
It's Anezaki!
Man, she's such a pain!
Huh? Bro?
I'm leaving!
Wait up, bro!
Mamori!
Are you two okay?
You shouldn't have done that!
We would have been fine even if you hadn't come.
Sena, are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Rikky sure is strong.
You're also very kind.
D-Don't say that!
I'm not really strong!
Nope, you're strong. And you're kind.
After all, you can't become truly strong if you aren't kind.
I'm going to become even stronger!
And then I'll protect both you and Sena!
Thank you.
Don't cry.
Here, take this.
- Huh?
It's a symbol of our friendship.
I made all of them last night.
A pig?!
No, it's a bear.
No! It's a cat!
I know!
I'll take good care of it.
Sena...
I'm going to become even stronger.
And someday I'll come back.
So until then, you've gotta protect Mamo.
Hold your head up, Sena.
I've told you that a man must always be looking ahead, haven't I?
Yeah, I...
I will protect Mamori until you come back!
It's a promise!
Yeah!
Take care!
Riku!
Riku! Take care!
Sena, don't forget how to run like that!
Don't let anyone make you be a gopher ever again!
Okay, Riku!
It's a promise!
I haven't kept even one of the promises I made with Riku...
Hey, hey! Just what are you two talking about?
This doesn't concern you any, Mamo!
Yeah, this is just between Riku and me.
Really! Leaving me out like this!
Fine!
Sena, I'm going to buy batteries and video tapes for tomorrow and go home!
Man, Mamori's really upset.
It's okay.
She'll feel all better tomorrow, I bet.
Stop that, you guys!
What was that?!
You gotta problem with us?
Don't litter your cigarette butts everywhere!
And you're blocking the traffic just sitting there!
What did you say?!
Mamori!
Sena, stay there!
I...
- What the-?
Huh? What happened?
Run for it!
Yeah!
Mamori!
Wait!
Don't tell me... Sena's actually-?!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to change directions when you're at top speed!
The key point is your heels?
When you want to change directions,
be sure to use your heels as breaks to stop
and then dart off again.
It's all in the heels! Ya-ha
Hey!
Well, if it isn't the devil.
Your running back came by our school earlier today.
Riku did?
Just for the record, Riku's fast.
But Eyeshield 21's the greatest.
Well, there's no point gettin' all hasty.
We'll find out who's best this Sunday.
Who's the greatest QB in Tokyo?
Of all the silly questions...
I'm asking for your opinion.
It's Yoichi Hiruma.
Now who's the one kidding around?
Is your little quiz over yet?
Let me give you my opinion.
I think the greatest quarterback in Tokyo is...
Shien.
It's Shien Mushanokoji.
He's the affluent son of a man that won the Olympic pistol competition
three times in a row.
He's Hajime Mushanokoji's only son.
That's you.
So who's just a "Kid?"
My, my...
How did you find that out?
And here I thought Tetsuma was the only one who knew that ridiculous name of mine.
But your reign as "best" is about to end.
Your Quick-and-Fire won't work on us.
My position as the best, huh?
There was a time when I woulda killed for that title.
But to each their own.
Nothing good comes outta overestimating people.
Oh, you may be right.
The main receiver who catches your passes is just a loser.
Isn't his name Tetsuma?
How can you even use such a simple-minded idiot?
Tetsuma is the greatest receiver!
No one thinks of Tetsuma as some loser, stupid!
You're pretty fired up, aren't you?
Quit trying to act so cool,
'cause I can feel the heat!
Man, you're good at manipulating people.
I don't like you, not one bit.
What going on, Riku?
What did you want to talk about?
We'll be enemies on the field the next time I see you and Mamo.
But that doesn't mean anything to us!
Nice reflexes, Sena.
Riku!
I knew it.
Sena, you're really...
...Eyeshield 21.
Yeah, sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
I'm a running back.
I go by "Eyeshield 21."
So you've been polishing that running style I taught you six years ago.
Well, I'm not sure you'd calling it "polishing."
I was being run around as a gopher so much that I just instinctively mastered it.
I see, so you were good and continued gophering everyday...
Yep.
Hey! Ever since way back then?!
What gives?!
I taught you that explosive dash so you could kick their butts!
Well, you see, no one had to fight or do anything scary if I just obeyed them.
But it's different now.
But I'm not doing this to win fights or be a gopher.
I've been training everyday to win football games!
But you're still pretty green.
That was our 92nd duel and my 92nd victory.
My necktie!
He took it then!
If your tie was a football,
I'd be getting a touchdown by now, Sena.
Does Mamo know that you're Eyeshield 21?
I thought I'd tell her after I became strong enough that I'd be able to protect her.
I thought Eyeshield 21 was really fast when I first saw him.
But I never thought it was you.
Riku, I...
I won't lose.
I can't lose to anyone, including you.
No, including Eyeshield 21!
It's a fight between master and pupil.
No, I'm no longer your brother nor your master.
I'm going to be your arch rival.
And I swear on my pride that I will defeat you!
Riku!
Riku...
I can't believe Sena's actually...
Sena, I won't let you win even once!
I wonder...
...if I can defeat Riku...
Sena?
Huh? Y-Yeah!
I'm home.
You're back pretty late again.
You've been getting home late recently, haven't you?
Yeah...
I don't know what you're up to...
...but I'm rooting for you.
Lately you've had a good expression in your eyes.
It's proof that whatever your doing is right for you.
Well, be sure to be confident in yourself!
Tomorrow we're going up against Seibu.
We've worked so hard to make it to the Christmas Bowl...
I can't let us stop here!
Football is the most important thing out there to me right now.
I don't know if I can defeat Riku or not, but...
...I want to win!
Riku, let's fight!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Sena vs. Riku!
The semi-finals are being held at last!
Riku's really great at running!
But so am I!
Who will make the touchdown?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Proof He's the Fastest! Ya-ha!
Finished!
I finished the cushions!
They look just like Sena and Rikky!
Okay-dokey!
Great! They're even comfy to sit on!
It hurts...