Bando Spiders vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Okay, come on.
- Ya-ha!
Bando Spiders 29 - Deimon Devil Bats 15
Bando Spiders 29 - Deimon Devil Bats 21
Deimon hasn't just gained a kicker.
They're finally playing with a full deck.
Yoichi Hiruma's just grown way more powerful.
Listen up, ladies!
We don't want a tie!
Musashi's kick'll be a diversion!
We're going for the two points with a touchdown!
Got that?! We'll pull it off no matter what!
- Yeah!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Man Beloved by God.
Interesting...
You dare think that by removing your eye shield
and defeating me you'll prove
that you are the real Eyeshield 21?
N-No, I was just...
But you realize, Sena...
The title Eyeshield 21 is a title
for the current era's greatest runner.
There's no way I can simply hand that over.
I've got people I'm shouldering for as well.
I'll shoulder you along since I'm a genius selected by God!
I can't stop!
My stupid brother's totally getting blown away.
It's Deimon's chance to try for some extra points!
With Musashi back on the team,
Hiruma's got a whole new bag of tricks that are available to him.
He might use some new devious strategy.
Set, hut!
Crush Musashi!
The kick's a diversion! Hold them back!
- Yeah!
- We won't let you!
Now!
He's here!
Sorry, but I won't let you near Sena!
How can this be?!
Man, he's so stupid!
Akaba's a bit farther behind thanks to Taki buying me some time.
I can do it!
Touchdown! Touchdown!
Bando Spiders 29 - Deimon Devil Bats 21
With the two added points,
Bando Spiders 29 - Deimon Devil Bats 23
Deimon's cut the gap to just six points!
God's supposed to love me,
but I couldn't even lay a finger on him.
How can this be?
W-Why...?
Taki, thank you.
I was able to pull it off thanks to your help.
I think Akaba would have caught me
if you hadn't run in front of him like that.
We did it thanks to you!
Got that right, Sena!
Well! I'll be sure to get him next time,
so just put your mind at ease!
Hey Bando-Shield!
We don't need two geniuses on the same field!
Let's fight to see who's the true genius chosen by God!
T-Taki?
Will Deimon be able keep this pace up and stop Bando's offense?!
I'll show everyone!
I'm a genius and God loves me!
Set!
Offside!
Deimon's idiot, I mean Taki, is totally offside!
He entered the opposing team's turf before the ball was snapped.
This is a foul.
I made a... foul?
How can this be?!
HOW CAN THIS BE?! HOW?!
Deimon was ordered
to move back five yards as a penalty for Natsuhiko Taki's offside.
Now that Deimon's closing in the gap and getting into a good grove,
it's a real shame they got this penalty!
Don't panic.
Don't you panic!
I'm a genius!
I'll definitely be able to stop him if I keep my cool!
Set, hut, hut!
This time!
Taki!
How can this be?
Akaba flattened Taki!
Will Bando score a touchdown?!
Shoot! I've gotta stop him!
Touchdown!
Spiders! Spiders! Spiders!
Bando Spiders 29 - Deimon Devil Bats 23
Bando's gained six points,
Bando Spiders 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 23
giving them a 12 point lead!
B-Bro...
Once again, ONCE AGAIN,
Deimon's Taki has burst past his own line,
aiding Bando in their offense!
I-It's my... fault?
You jerk!
What were you trying to pull?! HUH?!
Why are you bulldozing US?!
Quit getting in our way, you punk!
Let's calm down, everyone!
T-That's right! Taki's just trying...
What are you talking about?
Me? Get in your way?
I-I want everyone to calm down.
After all, I'm the man loved by God...
Hit the bench, Chinfuzz!
Huh?
Didn't you hear me?
I said to hit the bench!
T-Taki has to swap out?
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what's important when making a field goal!
The hint is "accuracy."
Offense will switch to the other team if you goof this up,
so it's important to make the field goal and get the points!
You better not goof up!
Ya-ha!
W-What are you talking about?
I can... I can still fight-!
Taki...
How can this be...?
How can this be?
HOW CAN THIS BE?!
Bro!
Hey!
Go after him.
Okay!
I-I'll go, too!
Taki...
Peewee!
Quit daydreaming and get on over here!
R-Right!
Bando's extra point kick made it!
Bando Spiders 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 23
It's 36-23 and Deimon's falling WAY behind again!
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 23
It'll be hard for Deimon to catch up now.
How can this be?
Why?
I was supposed to become the star beautifully...
God's supposed to love me, so why?
How can this be?
Really! Where on earth did he go?!
Stupid bro!
Suzuna, did you find him?
Yuki!
I wonder where he went.
Let's search some other areas, too.
Yuki, I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
This isn't anything you need to apologize for.
That stupid idiot!
He gets hyped up all by himself!
And he doesn't even realize that he's putting everyone out..
I can't believe he just ran off!
Suzuna, listen to me.
Just now...
...when Taki made that mistake and was sent to warm the bench...
I had a thought...
I thought that...
...if Taki stayed out of the tournament,
I might get my big chance to play.
Huh?
But then I ended up coming here to search for Taki.
I mean, I wouldn't be able to replace Taki right now anyway!
Deimon needs Taki if we're going to win!
Yuki!
They're keeping guard over Sena while doing a Sweep!
Akaba easily threw down Sena!
Curse that jerk, Akaba!
This really stinks!
And that Taki!
We might still stand a chance if he were actually here!
Where the heck did he run off to during the game?!
No!
There's no way Taki'd run away!
He'll come back for sure!
What's Deimon doing?
There's no way that guy can hold down the tight end.
Thanks for saying that about him...
I never knew that everyone needs him!
You're his first real friends...
The first people who've ever needed him...
And for him to throw in the towel like this...
I can't believe it's going to end with him putting everyone out.
S-Suzuna...
He's loved football ever since elementary school
and was so happy that he could do it with everyone.
So why... Why is he giving up on it?!
My brother's so stupid!
She's... right.
I've wanted to play football since elementary school
and finally got to play in my debut game.
And here I am...
How can this be?!
What are you talking about?
Me? Get in your way?
That's right...
It's nothing new today.
Ever since my debut game,
I haven't really...
...helped out all that much.
In other words...
This is all I'm actually good for.
Bro?
Taki!
What are you doing over there,
you stupid bro?!
Let me put this bluntly.
Power, speed, and experience...
You're losing to Akaba in every way possible.
God's not on your side.
You're just a B-rank player!
Yeah, you're right.
Somewhere a part of me that wanted to believe
that I'm a special person somehow.
But God doesn't really love me.
I'm just a man.
I am... just a man!
Bro...
Then, I'll...
I'll prevail against God on my own!
I wanna take it easy on the bench now...
I'm only human...
Mango... pudding...
He passed out.
Sena!
It's a pity,
but some of your teammates' lack of enthusiasm for football
has had an impact on the game.
He means we don't have any lamo dudes
in our team who would run off during the game!
N-No!
Taki...Taki would never run away!
He wouldn't run off!
Exactly!
Sorry I kept you waiting, my teammates!
- Taki!
Monsieur Akaba, you've gone and made me get serious.
You're such a sinful man!
He sounds just like you.
Don't lump us together!
Listen up, Taki.
Don't try to beat Akaba by pushing him down.
You couldn't handle it.
First you've got to accept that.
Yeah...
I've watched a guy who wasn't born
with any special athletic abilities
and lost to just about everyone he went up against.
But despite his physique, he's managed to get lined up
with the top players by mastering a way to fight.
I've stood beside him and watched him for many, many years.
We're up against the Tokyo MVP, Hayato Akaba!
He's a top player who can't be pushed around!
But you see,
you've got your own way of fighting as the underdog.
You've got your own weapon that will enable you to win!
Set!
Hut!
Well, the game's almost over!
Deimon's still lagging behind by 13 points!
What will they do now?!
I have my own weapon for defeating him!
He's here!
Taki!
I'll admit, I may be a lower level player than you.
But I've got...
...my own way of fighting!
He caught him!
But will you end up on Hayato Akaba's
dinner plate, Natsuhiko Taki?!
I won't let you get near Sena!
You're wasting your time.
That's right!
This is my one and only weapon
I have for defeating you!
Good going, Taki!
Instead of pushing back,
he just let Akaba's shove flow past him.
Go, Bro!
What?!
This heavy-pushing hard-rock type man-!
That's right.
That spin of yours
is your only weapon
you can use to defeat Akaba!
Now's your chance, Sena!
Yeah!
Touchdown!
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 23
Bando Spiders 36 - Deimon Devil Bats 29
- Hooray!
Suzuna, I can't believe he stopped Akaba!
Taki's amazing! Truly amazing!
Yep...!
That was cool to the max!
Taki, you were really great!
You bet I was!
This is Natsuhiko Taki's true power!
Okay, ladies!
Keep up the good work and blast on through 'em!
- Ya-ha!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
There's a six point gap and hardly any time left!
No matter how you feel about it,
the game's almost over!
We're going to win and move on to the Christmas Bowl!
Deimon's definitely going!
Run, Sena!
Blow on past those Bando players!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Time-Up of Light and Shadows!
Ya-ha!
See, earlier...
We were a bit... bent outta shape, too.
So we got a bit carried away... kinda...
- My bad! Sorry!
I really am a great person!
Even if God abandons me,
I can create my own destiny
with my own hands!
He hasn't really changed at all.
He really is...
...a total idiot.