Shinryuji Nagas vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha!
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 28
This game is about to reach its climax!
Shinryuji leads Deimon 35-28!
The Devil Bats have one chance
to score a touchdown and tie the game!
There's almost no time left... Only...
...58 seconds exactly!
Riko seems strangely masculine today...
58 seconds...
And 97 yards to go...
I'm not giving up.
We WILL beat Shinryuji!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Timeouts: Zero!
You got it, everyone?
Whoever carries the ball,
get your butt out of bounds before they tackle you!
If we go out of bounds, the clock stops.
Going 97 yards in 58 seconds is a real long shot...
All we can do is stop the clock at the right times.
Set, hut!
The Deimon Devil Bats turn to Eyeshield 21
for their final offensive drive!
Keep running, get out of bounds!
Not happening.
Shinryuji put defenders on the edge?
Move it!
You die IN bounds!
Sena!
- Sena!
He got tackled on the field... Wait!
The clock's still running!
No, no, no! Someone stop the clock!
But we used all our timeouts!
Spike!
Spike... Oh man, hurry!
Get the lead out, you idiots!
- Right!
Set, hut!
Hiruma spikes the ball!
What the heck's Yocchie doing?!
That is technically an incomplete pass,
meaning Deimon temporarily stops the clock.
Right...
When you miss a pass, they pause the clock.
By spiking the ball on purpose,
you sacrifice a down to stop the clock
and give yourself time to regroup.
Every bit the double-edged sword.
With zero timeouts remaining,
this is the only way Deimon will get any time to plan.
We're almost out of time, and my knees...
We just lost our second down...
Yeah, and we've barely gained any ground.
Now we're down to 49 seconds.
Are you knees all right, Sena?
Don't worry about my knees for now.
I'll be fine.
Sena...
Everyone, put all your energy into blocking for Sena!
Sena's always getting us out of tight spots,
now it's our turn to help him!
Kurita..
Yeah! Don't sweat it, Sena!
That's right, Sena!
That's why we're here.
We'll rip their line wide open!
Guys...
That's right, I'm not the only one suffering...
I'm not going to make any excuses!
Listen up.
That first play was just a trial.
I needed to confirm their defensive formation.
For the next one...
Shinryuji's focused all their defense along the sidelines.
Baldini!
You're gonna be on the line!
Yuki...
- On the line?!
Set!
I seriously doubt Hiruma will try to inch his way forward here.
He must have something planned.
Hut, hut, hut...
Hut...
Now!
Yukimitsu runs to the left behind Kurita and the line!
Rule number 7.1.3 in the rulebook:
Except for the seven men on the line of scrimmage,
one single person referred to as the "man in motion"
is allowed to move before the snap.
That's right!
Most of our men are set up along the sidelines to defend Eyeshield's run...
Meaning if Yukimitsu runs up the middle,
no one will be there to block him!
Hut, hut...
Hut!
By adding Yuki into the mix...
We've got better numbers for going up the middle!
The Devil Bats have focused on Shinryuji's weak center defense!
They're using the weakest guy on the team for a power battle?!
Don't stop, rip them apart!
Open a path for Sena!
Amazing...
There's so few of them, but they're standing so firm!
But I need to give Sena a push, no matter how little!
Sneak... through...
Power through...
...that wall!
Sena!
He's through!
Deimon, 8-yard gain! First down!
All right!
Sena!
The clock will stop while the chains are moved.
There are now 45 seconds remaining,
with 87 yards to the goal!
They're trying to keep advancing bit by bit,
stopping the clock without any timeouts...
He thinks he can keep this up all the way to the goal?
45 seconds left...
Set, hut!
This time Yukimitsu is in motion towards the opposite side!
Stinkin' scum...
Hut!
Crap...
Yukimitsu...
Okay, go towards Yuki!
Deimon, 5-yard gain!
All right!
Nice, Yuki!
Good job!
What is WRONG with you, get in position!
The clock's ticking!
Spike!
Another spike stops the clock at 38 seconds!
There's still 82 yards to the goal...
Well, Sena? Are your legs still okay?
Sena...
Yeah... with the clock stops, I'm managing...
That's why we're spiking every other play.
Get your butts back in position the second each play ends!
Let's go!
Hut!
We will, we will, we WILL...
- WIN!
It's tight... but I can get through!
Deimon, 6-yard gain!
Spike!
73 yards left...
Set, hut!
Deimon, pass incomplete!
The clock stops again, 27 seconds to go!
We're not even halfway there...
I think we're all right.
If we just keep it up, we'll win.
Yeah, they won't make it at this pace.
But I've known that sneaky piece of garbage since middle school.
He'll fight to the end, even when he has no chance of winning.
That's who he is.
No matter how many times he makes a little gain
and follows it with a spike, they-
Something wrong, Agon?
Nah, it doesn't matter if I'm the only one who noticed.
You scum just go get out there and be good little decoys.
- Eyeshield 21!
This is too much effort... I'm only human...
Eyeshield 21...
First down Deimon!
Yes!
But the clock...
A mere 23 seconds remain!
But Deimon still has 68 yards to go!
Shinryuji wants this to end,
they're defending deep in the backfield.
They can keep moving in small increments. However...
The end zone's... so far.
Shoot, we're out of time.
And Sena's almost done...
Man, at this rate...!
W-What was that-?
Set, hut!
Just leave it to me!
Deimon, 8-yard gain!
Yay, big bro!
Hurry and set back up!
Hurry!
Spike! We gotta stop the clock!
What're you staring at, Butt-Monkey?!
We can't waste one second!
Get in position, you idiot!
Right, sorry!
What's wrong with you, Mon-Mon?!
15 seconds...
What's he doing?
You're always delaying the game!
No way...
When did they move Yukimitsu up to the front seven?
He's in motion!
Raimon wasn't rushing to get in position!
Even Ikkyu shouldn't be able
to overcome this much of a head start!
Get in position, Butt-Monkey!
I can't start the play till you're set up!
Don't listen to Hiruma!
They play's already started!
The ball's gone!
Everyone, move! Hurry!
You dirty rats!
This play was never going to be a spike!
Ya-ha!
It's a long bomb!
12 seconds to go!
One touchdown ties it for the Deimon Devil Bats!
Shinryuji has been caught completely off-guard,
and the fateful pass is cutting through the air!
If he catches this pass, it's a guaranteed touchdown!
That's why Hiruma had us move up little by little!
Sena Kobayakawa was nothing more than a setup for this play!
All right!
Max Catch!
I don't think so!
I'M number one in the air!
He touched it!
No way... from all the way back there?!
Ikkyu has knocked the ball off course!
Is this the end of the line?
How?
I knocked it off course...
I know exactly how good you are, Ikkyu.
Even if everyone else in the stadium thought it was impossible,
I EXPECTED you to get a finger on it!
You...
...rat!
Monta has somehow managed to catch the pass!
He's headed for the end zone!
He caught it!
Monta saw through Ikkyu!
Run!
Head straight...
...for the touchdown!
The last line of defense stands in front of Monta!
Shoot, someone's back here-
Sena!
That ball's our lifeline, you're not taking it!
I don't care if it hurts!
- Sena!
Sena sacrifices himself with a lightspeed block!
Shinryuji's final defender is eliminated!
We did it!
Monta is all alone as he flies towards Shinryuji's goal!
- All right!
Yes!
This is it!
When...
When did he notice?
He was all that way from the opposite side...
Even HE couldn't change course that fast.
He knew.
No...
NO!
I pretended not to notice anything...
then I started moving on my own,
while my clueless teammates unknowingly acted as decoys.
Die.
Monta!
If he goes down there it's over!
I couldn't care less about the ball.
But if you're tackled on the field, the clock runs out.
At the last, crucial moment, Agon's perception...
...beat Hiruma's trickery.
It's not over, Max Catch!
The time for catching's over, chump!
Monta is down 20 yards from the goal!
Everyone, on the field, now!
Line up and stop the clock!
Spike!
Man, Monta ran so far!
They're too far to line up again...
That's why I waited till he was all the way out here.
Please... I don't wanna lose.
Not here... Not now...
No... please... we all swore...
But in two seconds... it's all...
It's all gonna end!
With a final score of 35-28, Deimon vs. Shinryuji is over...
Time is up!
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
Time's up?
Deimon lost?!
It's... over?
Is the game really over?!
Really really over?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Huddle with no Answers!
Ya-ha!
You came close, Deimon.
But in the end, there were no miracles.
Eyeshield...
Mamo, is it really over? Is it?
Is it? Is it? C'mon, Mamo!
Everyone...