Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Oh!
- Ya-ha!
Ojo White Knights 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 13
The score's still Ojo 20, Deimon 13.
Deimon let an incredible chance slip them by.
That's really gonna hurt.
The playbook... of death...
H-Hey, let's see it already!
R-Right...
Th-That's-?!
W-Well...
What's with that funny face, Sena?
Well, we have to act natural or Ojo will notice.
I get it! Max poker face.
Look natural!
Death mask!
Smile naturally!
Everyone's acting creepy.
Act normal... Use p-poker faces.
- Loosen up already.
Listen carefully, you Ojo punks.
What's up?
Even though it's Ojo's ball, you're in serious danger with goal line right behind you.
One little push, and we'll score a safety.
Yeah, although we may have stolen the ball, this could work out in favor for either team.
So, what are you getting at?
Deimon's super aggressive. There's no way we'll let such a sweet situation slide by.
He's blurting...
...it all...
...out!
Did you come to scare us with your psychological warfare?
That sounded great!
I'm proud of that one!
So, what's going on?
He wasn't listening at all...
Don't sweat the small stuff!
No matter what happens, 'victory' is written with four characters.
'Victory'
is 4 characters long?
It's four characters?
It is if you use Hiragana instead of Kanji.
Well, we're about to enter the fourth quarter and Ojo's on offense!
Whoever scores next will play a big role in determining the outcome of the game.
It's too dangerous for us to play against Deimon right in front of our goal line.
We need to play it safe and run until we get out of the danger zone.
- Yeah...
That's what Hiruma's trying to get us to do.
Takami turned...
...into Dark Takami.
It'd be great if that scared 'em into running,
but they're no wimps.
Right now,
Yoichi Hiruma is trying to persuade us from using the play that would hurt Deimon the most.
Right. The unstoppable short pass with it's hundred percent completion rate.
The Sagittarius!
Bluntly put, there's no way we can stop the Sagittarius.
So now it's time to sink or swim.
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Demon's Twin Wings!
Set!
Deimon's probably going to make a surprise attack,
but there's nothing unusual about their formation.
Hut!
Wha-?
Both Sena and Monta are marking Sakuraba?!
But if Sena does that, there'll be a huge area left wide open!
If they get through with the Sagittarius...
...they'd score a touchdown.
With my height, I can handle both of them at once!
Sakuraba's weapon is the third dimension.
Ground speed means nothing to him.
Let's go, Sakuraba! We'll use the Sagittarius!
Sena blitzed Takami?!
Sena charged forward so that it looked like two players were marking me.
But he was planning on sacking Takami, our launching pad!
It was a feint when he stopped right in front of Sakuraba.
If this fails, there's no one to cover for us from the back.
Either we crush him or they get through.
We're betting everything on this!
Crap!
Is that what you thought I'd say?
Sh-Shin?!
That jerk!
Wasn't he headed towards Sakuraba so they could pull off another Sagittarius?
Victory...
...is ours!
Takami, with Eyeshield gone, there's no one protecting the goal line!
I can get us another touchdown!
Great! Do it!
Darn it! They're getting through.
No!
Shoot! Shoot!
Is that what you thought I'd say?
I-It can't be!
Monta?!
Neither Sena nor Monta were going to mark Sakuraba.
They were both going to blitz Takami from the beginning!
Sena wasn't getting blocked by Shin.
He was protecting Monta from the ever-invincible Shin!
He was blocking Shin!
They went for Takami's blind spot while he was preparing to throw his Everest Pass.
Oh no!
Is that what you thought I'd say?
He's starting to throw the ball!
He's so tall!
Monta!
Mon-Mon!
I'm too short!
I can't stop him!
Shoot! Shoot!
Is that what you thought I'd say?
Go, Monta!
I took a step forward to throw the pass.
He's going for Takami's super long legs!
Max Catch!
Monta!
Ojo White Knights crossed the line! It's a safety!
You did it, Monta!
We got us a safety!
Your determination was amazing!
How many points do we get for a safety?
Like a 100 million!
You get two points for a safety.
It's 20 to 15, with Deimon five points behind.
Ojo White Knights 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 15
And now we get to go on offense!
If we can score a touchdown, we'll be in the lead, monsieur!
Why's he know everything when it comes to football?
He's supposed to be stupid.
He really is stupid.
I wonder what it's like in his head.
This has gotten simpler. Just score a touchdown!
At last!
At last...
...we'll turn the tide!
Guys, let's show them how powerful Deimon's offense is!
You bet! Let's go, Sena!
Yeah. Although it's really risky, I won't be able to defeat Shin if I don't use my Devil Stun Gun, so...
Yeah, use your Devil Stun Gun like crazy, Sena.
That's your only way to defeat Shin.
It's okay if you goof up and drop a ball or two,
because we'll be there to catch them!
- Yeah!
Guys...
So basically you're telling me to go and let Shin skewer me, right?
You got it!
"Because we'll be there to catch them!"
"Guys..."
You're absolutely nuts!
Yocchie's having a blast.
Yeah, it is crazy,
but you won't stop them, will you?
Nope, I won't.
Okay, let's do this!
- Yeah!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we'll be talking about the line starting the play.
The key point to defeating your opponent is to start your play immediately.
It's a dual between giant linemen! Ya-ha...
Deimon regained offense after forcing Ojo into a safety!
Eyeshield 21's using his Devil Stun Gun like mad!
They got first down!
There's only a five-point gap.
There's still no telling who will be victorious.
The chance of you losing the ball may go up ten fold,
but if you multiply my and Sena's doubled offensive power together,
we're 22 times more powerful!
How'd you figure that?
That's as bad as Taki.
Interesting. I accept that challenge!
All three of them are blitzing?!
Hiruma couldn't throw the ball! He failed to pass it!
They're taking big risks, too.
Their defense is so destructive!
The battle's fiercely raging in the final quarter!
Will the winners be Ojo with their impenetrable defense?!
Or will it be the super-offensive Deimon?!
Deimon's trump card is offense.
If we can't stop Ojo's offense, then they've gotta out-score them.
Ojo's trump card is defense.
We WILL stop Deimon's ultimate offense!
If we keep them from scoring any points, we win.
If they score 99 points, then we'll score a hundred!
This is a crazy seesaw game!
Who will the goddess of fortune smile upon?!
The score hasn't changed and we're down to the final three minutes!
There's only two and a half minutes!
We need five points. A kick won't do!
Score a touchdown even if it kills you!
N-Not good. I'm runnin' outta stamina...
Yuki!
Stretcher! Get a stretcher!
Yukimitsu only has enough stamina to play in half a game.
The fatigue for playing since the first half caught up to him.
This stinks...
This is our last chance...
I hate this.
The ground was muddy throughout the first half of the game.
That probably doubled, or even tripled the toll on them.
They could pass out at any time now!
The game's going again!
I can't lose!
Give it your all!
We didn't do that horrible mask training for nothing!
It was simple but worked!
Building up stamina pays off when playing on a muddy field like this.
No one can compete with the Ojo White Knights when it comes to stamina.
We'll never lose in a contest of strength!
Everyone here completed training on Mt. Fuji!
We're almost to the goal line!
But that "almost..."
...is hard and heavy.
They stopped! Neither side's caving in!
No, one of us is just about spent.
This is bad!
He was running his little heart out while Sena was taking it easy.
He's passed his limit.
Deimon's offense is only working because Peewee's explosive runs
and your Devil Backfire keeps 'em guessing.
H-Hiruma...?
They'll slaughter us if they find out which one we're gonna use.
So don't let them figure out that you can't catch anymore.
Okay.
It's amazing how Sakuraba's filled to the max with energy.
This stinks!
I feel so stupid!
Monta...
What's the point if I give out now?
This is all because I went overboard in competing with Sakuraba.
I'm so stupid!
You're not stupid.
We would have lost a long time ago if you hadn't done all those passes earlier.
I couldn't even move to fight against Shin...
So if you can't move now, then I'll get by Shin with my running!
Come as many times as you like, Eyeshield 21.
I'll run for you too, Monta!
Devil Light Hurricane!
Change my grip...
...and use my Devil Stun Gun!
Moving the ball like that's too risky!
He used his arm as a shield!
He's getting through!
No, I won't let him!
Seijuro Shin broke through the Devil Stun Gun's shield!
I can't believe... I didn't get by Shin!
Great!
No! If he steals the ball-!
Monta!
I... I...!
I've wanted to become a catching super hero,
and have chased after Honjo for the past ten years.
I... wasn't any good at baseball,
but I never forgot the catching spirit that Honjo taught me.
And I've done my best in football-!
In football!
You can't have the ball!
Out of bounds. It's Deimon's ball!
Monta!
That was the last bit...
...of stamina I had left.
I-I wish Honjo...
Monta!
...could have seen me...
H-Honjo?
Am I dreaming or somethin'?
There's no way Honjo would be at a place like this!
W-Wow, Honjo's hands are huge...
I saw everything you did,
baseball boy.
H-Honjo? For real?
Really? You're really him?
Are you Honjo in the flesh?
Yeah.
W-Why are you here?
Ten years ago you were in the bleachers during my final game, weren't you?
You're the boy I gave my glove to, right?
I-I am!
You remembered! You do remember me, Honjo...
No! I can't cry during a game!
You didn't do things half-way.
Even if your battlefield has changed, you've always followed the Way of Catching.
I-I have!
The game's not over until the whistle blows.
Don't give up until it's over!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Monta was about to keel over, but he's as good as new since his idol, Honjo, showed up!
I can't look lame in front of him!
I'll catch victory!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Form of Desperation!
Ya-ha!
It's the former pro baseball player, Masaru Honjo.
Isn't he Mon-Mon's idol?
But why's a former baseball player hanging out with the Kanto Football Association's chairman?
He's the Kansai Football Association's chairman.
Monta!
Sena!
Sorry 'bout that, but I'm all better.
I can't give up with Honjo watching!
Monta...
There's just three yards to the goal line.
It's our last chance to take the lead.
Our last chance...
Let's fly together with the Devil Bat Dive!
Sena...