So you're saying that Kengo Mizumachi's
dislocated shoulder was an accident?
Right.
Very well.
But from here on,
keep a close eye on Shinryuji, especially that Agon Kongo.
Yes, sir.
Agon Kongo... he's just too dangerous.
Let's see, in the next death game we're fighting...
...the Kyoshin Poseidons?!
But isn't Mizumachi
still in the hospital after getting his shoulder dislocated
in that scrimmage with Shinryuji?
Then we're gonna have some sorta handicap...
But even without Mizumachi,
their super tall defense players are amazing!
Sure are!
But that doesn't change the fact
that we have to fight 'em and win!
Good luck, everyone!
Oh, baby! I'll work max hard!
We're fighting against them before our Kanto game with Shinryuji.
Naturally, this'll be a death game!
So you better not lose, kiddies!
- Right!
He's right!
We have to work hard and win
in order to make it to the Christmas Bowl!
That's why we're holding these death games!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Overcome Your "Fear."
We'll win... and defeat all our foes!
Hey, Sena,
why are you staring off into space instead of practicing?
Huh? Well, you see...
Don't tell me you were thinking you'd have a tough time
fighting against Kyoshin since Mizumachi got hurt.
They'll kick our butts if we're not careful.
Knowing Hiruma,
he'll come up with some sorta insane handicap for us.
Like, he might tell you to play by yourself.
No way!
He'd never do that!
How'd you score any points?
Exactly.
But you know,
I'm kinda worried about Mizumachi, too.
Wanna go pay him a visit?
Yeah!
Hey, I wanna go, too!
Y-You were listening?!
Oh, so Mizumachi's staying at this hospital.
It feels like everyone goes here.
Yeah.
I bet even our bubbly Mizumachi
must be feeling down after getting hurt like that.
Then we'll have to cheer him up!
Sure will!
Uh, here's the room!
Hey, we dropped by to pay you a visit!
Huh?
Mizumachi, quiet up!
Splash!
I'm not gonna lose!
C'mon! Enough already!
Sweet! I win again!
Man! All righty then! Let's do it again!
The outcome'll still be the same!
Mizumachi!
And Torakichi!
What's this? You came to see me?
Talk about good timing. Please stop them!
What are you doing?
Can't you tell, stupid? We're racing!
Stupid?!
Racing with a wheelchair and a stretcher?
We're a perfect match
since my leg's injured and his shoulder was dislocated!
So that's the story.
Now for our 21st game!
Okay! Ready, go!
Splash!
Stop it, guys! Hey!
Are they really being hospitalized?
They seem to be feeling better than we do.
Yeah...
Ya-hoo!
I said enough!
We'll get in trouble if you're too noisy!
H-He's right. At this rate...
...she'll stop by!
Yeah, she sure will...
- S-She's here!
Whoops!
Keep quiet in the hospital.
You're bugging everyone.
Kakei, why're you so mad, you grump?
We're not being too loud!
Yeah, don't stop our game!
Good grief. So you two were talking about Kakei.
No, no, and no!
Wrong person big time!
She doesn't look like that.
Her face is way scarier!
You wouldn't be referring to when I look at you like this,
now would you?
It's her!
When'd she get here?!
She's really scary!
Mizumachi, how many times must I warn you?
If you don't quiet down, I'll CURSE you!
- I'm sorry!
Man, I'm tired of sleeping around,
so what should we do next?
Mizumachi, you'll never get better if you don't sit still.
Whatever! I'm already all better!
See? Splash!
Hey!
M-Mizumachi!
Mizumachi?!
Are you okay?!
Just kidding! Did I get ya?
That joke wasn't very funny.
That's going too far!
Sorry, sorry.
And now I've gotta poo!
I-I'm gonna poop my pants! Too late!
Good grief...
Sorry, guys.
I can't believe Mizumachi acted like that
after you came to see him.
Nah, no worries.
I'm just happy to see he's feeling better.
But he won't be able to play in the death game, will he?
Yeah, we'll play without him.
But let me make this perfectly clear.
I don't think Deimon can defeat Shinryuji as you are right now.
We couldn't even score one point against them.
Agon Kongo... that man's a monster.
He can tear through anyone like they're paper.
Even Mizumachi didn't stand a chance against him.
Shouldn't he be back by now?
T-That's Mizumachi's ball!
Which means...
...he heard what Kakei said just now.
Oh, no! I bet he's going to do go something stupid!
Mizumachi, don't be rash! Don't be rash!
I can't believe he ran off!
We have to go find him.
We'll help you look for him!
Yeah!
Yeah, I'll help, too!
Mizumachi! Mizumachi!
O-Over there!
Oh, Kobanzame, that's...
Mizumachi!
...an operation room.
Is that him this time?!
Oh, that's the...
Mizumachi!
...nurses' changing room.
I wonder where Mizumachi ran off to...
Found him!
We're goin' to the top!
Mizumachi's... crying.
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
I swear I didn't see anything, so um, you see...
You caught me looking lame!
S-Sorry...
Don't apologize.
Oh, uh, yeah... Sorry.
I just said not to apologize!
No, I wasn't apologizing about what I had just apologized about!
Mizumachi!
So it still hurts...?
You bet it does!
That jerk dislocated my arm!
It's not going to heal up over night, you know!
S-Sorry...Oops!
Boy, are you ever an airhead or what?!
So um, what you were doing just a minute ago?
Is it because you're frustrated over losing?
That's part of it, but...
Agon Kongo isn't your average guy.
Splash!
He's totally different from everyone else I've gone up against.
For the first time ever, I was really scared.
I'm... scared, Sena.
But man, I'm not sure if our luck's good or bad
having to face the Shinryuji Nagas off the bat.
It looks like our fate's still tied to them.
Yeah...
There's no way we can afford to lose this one!
Yeah!
We've gotta defeat EVERYONE,
so quit statin' the obvious.
Our past ties got nothing to do with this.
The strong always defeat the weak.
It's that simple.
I thought you'd say that.
We WILL defeat Shinryuji!
I'm scared... really scared.
Mizumachi...
Oh, I see.
Back then... I had this icky feeling
like someone was crushing my stomach...
That was fear!
I'm scared, too.
I think he, Agon Kongo, is scary.
But... I love... football!
So I may get scared, and I mean scared, but I still wanna play!
Oh, so you're scared of him, too.
Then how 'bout us two scaredy-cats go at it?
Huh?
Mizumachi, what're you doing?
Well, I'm...
C'mon, bring it on!
Huh? No way!
I can't do that! Your shoulder's-
I don't care! Splash!
Mizumachi!
Splash!
Don't! That's dangerous!
I don't want to be afraid of football forever.
And you don't want to fight that freak
when you're still afraid of him, right?!
Yeah, but...
Then let's go all out and fight!
Maybe it'll help us grow some!
Mizumachi...
Sena, you run and I'll stop you!
Pretty simple, right?
That's how I want to think of the game, and I need your help!
I want to change, too.
There's no "maybe I can change."
I WILL change!
There's no way I can beat him if I don't overcome my fear!
Yeah! That's more like it!
C'mon!
Okay.
Splash!
Mizumachi!
I-I'm sorry! I...
No sweat, I can handle it!
But you beat me and it feels great!
Sena, come take a look.
Wow, it's amazing!
Ain't it?
I always have so much fun
and just love that feeling I get after playing my hardest.
Thank you, Sena.
Now I think I'll be able to look forward to next year's season,
instead of be afraid of it.
Yep!
And just you wait and see!
Next year we're not losing!
Right! I won't lose, either!
Mizumachi!
Kobanzame! Kakei!
You stupid jerk!
Come talk to us if you're ever upset over something.
Don't dwell on it all on your own!
We're friends, aren't we?!
Kobanzame...
Oh, relax! I'm just fine!
- Mizumachi!
- Ouch! That hurts!
I was so worried!
Kobanzame, that hurts...
I mustn't forget how hard all of our past opponents have fought.
And during the Kanto Tournament,
I'll remember why they tried so hard to win and I WILL win!
Kakei!
Huh?
I want to defeat Shinryuji!
I must defeat them!
I see.
Then we'll hit you with everything we've got in this upcoming game.
Yeah, thanks so much!
No prob.
I hope you get better soon!
Agon, what were you doing?! You skipped practice again!
Don't get your panties in a wad!
I'll be there for the first game in the Kanto Tournament,
so lighten up.
That's not what teamwork's about, you know.
Deimon's being called the dark horse for the Kanto Tournament
and they've got the great ace Eyeshield 21 on their team.
I'm really looking forward to their game with Shinryuji!
Lookie here, Shinryuji!
You may have won a bunch of tournaments in a row,
but that's ending now!
Hey, Dread-head, just you wait!
Eyeshield's gonna blow you away!
I'm going to... kill them!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Hey, hey, hey!
The other team's at a disadvantage in the next death game!
Hey, this is so cool!
Those two are gonna help us out!
WHAT?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Invincible Double-Blocker!
Ya-ha!
Splash!
Mizumachi, stop it!
We'll get in trouble again!
Where'd you go? Mizumachi?!
Mizumachi! Mizumachi!
Oh, over there!
That scared me!
You over there,
I'll curse you if you don't quiet down.
She's way scarier than skeletons AND Agon!