- Drown!
- Ya-ha!
The results will always be the same, you fake.
That running of yours won't work on me!
I want to get through...
No, I WILL get through!
You're mine! You're finished!
C'mon!
YES! Touchdown time!
We're going to the semi-finals!
The semi-finals-!
I won't let you!
No way!
D-Did we get a touchdown?
How's the time?!
Stop the clock!
Time out!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
Attack and Defense for 30 Centimeters!
SWEET!
He was stopped!
Kyoshin's Mizumachi just barely managed
to stop Eyeshield 21 at their goal line!
We... We did it!
No way...
I can't believe he stopped Eyeshield...
That spin he used to get by Kakei
slowed him down by a fatal 0.1 seconds.
That was supposed to be the winning touchdown...
There's just 50 centimeters left, no, just 30 centimeters!
My, what a surprise!
It's really amazing that he could stop Eyeshield
with just 30 centimeters to spare.
Mizumachi's desire to win is terrifying!
The score's 23-18!
The Poseidon's have a five point lead!
Poseidons! Poseidons!
And the Devil Bats have called a time out!
There's only two seconds left to the game!
He got through my Moby Dick Anchor!
He got through, without a doubt.
He's no pushover by any means.
Hey, Kakei, why so blue?!
Mizumachi...
Don't you think you're overrating yourself a bit?
I mean, come on,
it's not like the Poseidons are all going to lose
just because he got through your ultimate attack.
We're trying to become national champions!
For the sake of Kobanzame and all the other upperclassmen,
we can't let the season end here!
So we're going to put everything we've got into crushing them!
Yep! Now let's go!
Mizumachi...
He's right.
We made a promise back then...
Didn't we swear...
...that we'd make it to the top?
We're gonna win that game tomorrow!
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Mizumachi.
I'm all better now!
Two SECONDS?!
That was close.
The game almost ended like that!
Just two seconds left...
What should we do?
It was intentional.
I intentionally called the time out
with just two seconds left.
This is our last chance to attack
and the goal's 30 centimeters away.
We'll push our way to a touchdown.
And then the game will end.
But how?
Hiruma, do you have some sorta secret plan?!
Back off!
Anyway, we just have to push for 30 centimeters!
Just a measly 30 centimeters, huh?
Normally that's a distance you could easily cover in two seconds.
But going by Eyeshield's physique,
a battle of strength is going to be tough...
Saying I've got to push through 30 centimeters is easy enough, but...
It's okay!
Let's show them that shorties have their own way of fighting!
Monta...
Komusubi!
You're right.
We've managed to make it this far already!
We shorties have always combined our power together
to make up for our lack in height!
That'll work now, too!
That's it!
If I can't get over the difference in our height,
I'll fly over them!
By fly over them, you mean...
Do you get what you're saying?
Kyoshin's line is...
...filled with the tallest players in Japan!
I-I guess it won't work after all...
Well, it's not like I WANT to try something scary like that, but...
Those Kyoshin jerks will probably be expecting it, but...
But fly anyway, Peewee!
Use the Devil Bat Dive!
The Devil Bat Dive?
You don't have to fly OVER them!
Just turn into a rocket and shoot on through!
You can do it!
You can do it, 'cause we'll be helping you!
You just jump with all your might!
Okay! I'll fly!
Let's see, they'll do that! You know, the...
Deimon will definitely give the ball to Eyeshield 21
and have him fly towards the center.
Right! Exactly! That's my Kakei!
But since this is Deimon we're up against,
they know that we've already figured that out.
Huh? Th-Then isn't that...
They know we know and are gonna do it anyway?!
They're funny!
Then let's have an all-star team
made up of Kyoshin's powerful and tall types on the field!
Yeah! Do that, do that!
I was just about to say that!
But then you won't need us third year students, huh?
All of the super tall players joined the same time Kakei did.
Kobanzame, you just sit and wait for us!
Mizumachi...
In the end, we've done nothing but count on you guys!
We were absolutely useless to the very end!
Me and the other guys...
...have never thought of you as useless.
You never gave up despite how hard our training was!
And I wouldn't have been able to complete my Moby Dick Anchor
if it weren't for you, Kobanzame.
I can't believe what our Captain's saying!
Please get a hold of yourself, Kobanzame!
I'm okay! I was just joking. Joking!
We'll definitely stop them!
We'll bring back a ticket to the semi-finals for you!
Y-Yeah!
Time's up!
Listen up, we've got two seconds!
We MUST stop them!
Yeah!
Poseidons!
Go, splash, go!
Listen up, we're gonna annoy them like mad!
I'm calling out "hut" nine times for kicks,
so go on the tenth one.
I want everyone to get in place then!
Peewee's rocket and our line
are going to work together as one!
Yeah!
RIP THEIR HEADS OFF! YA-HA!
- YA-HA!
The time out's already up!
Both teams are ready!
The unquestionably,
absolute final showdown is held over 30 centimeters!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to make a short pass!
The main point is your wrists?
When you want to throw the ball to someone nearby,
make sure to throw with your wrists!
Throw hard with your wrists! Ya-ha!
Just 30 centimeters to go...
Guys, this is a test of will rather than power!
We're going to work together as one to break through!
A short man's weapon is his agility.
He's bound to use that weapon against us!
Kumabukuro,
these 30 centimeters truly are their last chance, aren't they?
It all depends on if they can get through
Kyoshin's iron wall-like line in one play.
We're dealing with the unpredictable Deimon Devil Bats,
so they could still pull it off!
These two seconds will determine everything.
Set! Hut!
Hut!
Deep inside... I've always been afraid.
You're all so strong...
...that I was afraid you were laughing at us.
So I was always trying to help out in other ways...
I just realized what a small person I am...
GO, POSEIDONS!
Hut!
I won't call you lil' anymore!
You've really surprised me.
I can't believe you've pushed us so hard!
But it ends now!
Hut!
C'mon! Give me all you've got!
The Poseidons will work as a team to crush you!
Hut!
Let's do this!
Watch us closely!
Yay!
We'll definitely, definitely, definitely...
...not lose!
Sena...
You aren't a fake.
Show them Sena Kobayakawa's Eyeshield!
You're right.
It doesn't matter if the real one's huge or that I'm a fake.
Hut!
I don't care who Eyeshield 21 is!
I'm me!
And who cares if I'm a fake or a shrimp!
I'll fight my own way!
HUT!
We're gonna WIN!
Go, Devil Bat Dive!
So he's doing it!
Eyeshield 21 JUMPED!
YA-HA!
- I won't let you!
They're tall!
It's no use! They'll crush him!
We're not done yet!
Let's show them the strength of us shorties!
Devil Bat Dive, Rocket #2!
What?!
GO!
I did it! I flew over them!
The zealous Mizumachi stopped Eyeshield 21!
But there's... just no way!
We win!
Wha?!
Komu...su...bi!
Touchdown!
Game over!
They got a touchdown at the very end!
The Deimon Devil Bats took the lead in the last two seconds!
We won?!
YA-HA!
- Ya-ha!
Ya-ha!
Gen, your not working!
The game's already over, right?
But we're not finished here!
Sorry.
What's with that Rocket #2?
What the heck?
That was a three-part rocket!
Yeah, see you next year.
But Kobanzame and the others...
...their last game just ended!
I'm terribly sorry, Kobanzame.
The ticket to the semi-finals...
It's okay.
You guys joined my last year here...
The training was way too hard.
It was the hardest time of my life,
but also the funnest!
Don't cry, Mizumachi!
You were truly great. Thank you.
Kobanzame...
Well, the game's not over yet!
Let's stand proud as we say goodbye to everyone!
At least at the very end,
let me sound like I'm your senior.
Okay, Captain!
Offer your respect!
- Thank you very much!
You were awesome, Poseidons!
Good going, Deimon!
Kakei...
This victory is yours.
You determined who won and who lost.
T-Thank you...
But you know, I didn't do it on my own.
You see, everyone helped.
The Deimon Shorties, huh?
As a player who has come so far
through taking advantage of his height...
I never even imagined that a player
could take advantage of being short.
You truly are the antithesis of the Eyeshield 21 that I knew.
Let's fight again next year, Eyeshield 21!
What did you say?
It doesn't matter if you're the real or a fake.
All that truly matters is whether or not you're a good player.
Kakei!
So if you want to call yourself that,
then you truly are another Eyeshield 21!
Yeah!
With a score of 24-23,
Deimon Devil Bats 24 - Kyoshin Poseidons 23
the Deimon Devil Bats are going to the semi-finals!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Glad to see you're going to record
the quarter-finals between the Gunmen and the Fishers!
Sometimes I'd like to do my job as a team manager, too.
But then someone steals Mamori's purse!
It's show time, Sena!
Huh? Who's that? He's even faster than Sena!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Appearance of a Lightspeed Man!? Ya-ha!
- We did it!
- Hurray!
Yay!
We did it!
Good going!
Eyeshield 21, huh? But I'm No.1!