Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Oh!
- Ya-ha!
Takami, this will be a touchdown! We can finish Deimon!
One step!
I'm just one step behind!
If I'm gonna catch up, I've gotta rush straight at him without any hesitation!
I can tell from the ball's position, I won't make that one step!
Then...!
Monta!
He's so high! No... it's just speed!
If I jump now, with his speed... I'll crash right into him!
NO ONE out-catches me!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The 9999th Catch.
Sakuraba's in trouble here!
If he jumps now he'll end up in a high-speed collision with Monta!
Sakuraba!
I swore I'd become a REAL ace!
Oh my! He takes to the skies without a moment's hesitation!
Man, here he comes!
This is why they call him the best receiver in Tokyo!
He's got it! The gods of catching choose Sakuraba!
Yes!
Yay! Sakuraba wins!
Of course. His back was to the ball, he couldn't see anything.
No... even if I can't see it...
if I reach out... my arms!
Monta!
I'm not finished yet!
W-Wha-?
Monta just knocked the ball right out of Sakuraba's hands!
Get it!
Go!
We're not gonna make it!
A-An interception... It's Deimon's Ball!
Monta spoils a touchdown pass to Sakuraba!
Yeah!
He did it, he stopped Sakuraba!
I don't believe it...
He just raised his arms behind his head, the odds of him hitting the ball...
Th-That was just luck, pure luck!
Sakuraba's technique was so much better!
Was Raimon's play just a coincidence? Or...
No, that was definitely on purpose?
You came too, Ikkyu?
Yup, I figured things would pick up now that the rain's stopped.
I'm glad I did.
To receivers like me, This is turning into a must-see game.
The way he moved... that wasn't luck.
Monta knew where the ball was.
And the pressure...
No, I can bring the pressure, too!
I'm just as dedicated!
- High five!
Nice one, Monta!
Max pass cut, baby!
Yo, Butt-Monkey.
Hmm?
How'd you see the ball without seeing it?
He saw it?
He saw a ball coming at the back of his head?
He can see?
Nah, I just...
I kept glancing at it up until that last second.
Then I just kinda knew where it'd go from the speed, the wind...
So uhh, yeah.
That's enough to make a catch?
No way.
That's impossible.
Huh... Does it really sound that crazy?
It's ten years of experience of chasing baseballs.
All that practice made you grow eyes in the back of your head.
You predicted Four-Eyes' pass with about 80% accuracy even though you're not used to his style.
Meaning you should be able to get MY passes 100% right.
You don't think...
On the next long pass play...
You're telling me to make an OVERHEAD catch?
Huh? Not feeling too confident, eh, Butt-Monkey?
Not even close...
I'm pumped up to the max!
If I can really make a catch like that...
That'd be my ultimate move!
Butt-Monkey...
How many of my passes do you think you've caught since you joined the team?
Huh? Uh, I dunno... I haven't been counting...
Exactly 9999.
9999...
This can only be destiny.
On the next play, you'll make your 10,000th catch as you perfect your new move...
The Devil Backfire!
Devil Backfire...
Deimon's finally back on offense!
The unique combo of Monta and Hiruma teamed up to get them this chance!
This will be good.
Monta...
Hmm?
It'll be fine. Relax, okay?
I've just never tried anything like this, I'm kinda nervous.
No, you've done it all.
From the day you started playing baseball to when you joined the football team,
you've done nothing but keep your eye on the ball.
You can do it, Monta, I know you can.
I've done it all before, huh...
I guess you're right.
Thank you, Sena.
I'll make my 10,000th catch a big one!
Are you guys really at exactly 9999 passes?
Of course not.
I knew it.
We passed 10,000 a LONG time ago.
Deimon is starting from just in front of their own goal line!
Monta...
His eyes... What's he planning?
Whatever it is, I'll stop him!
No one out-catches me...
This time I'll prove it!
What is this?!
Hiruma takes a cue from the Everest Pass and throws it in a long, high arc!
That's a big one!
Are you getting desperate, Hiruma?
Raimon can't catch it at that trajectory.
Shoot!
But...
I can get this one!
All right!
What the...?
I can see it... I can see the ball!
I can tell where it's flying without turning around!
I've caught so many of Hiruma's spartan passes I lost count.
All I have to do is charge right at Sakuraba with my catch power at max!
Go, Monta!
He's still facing me?!
This is my...
...Devil Backfire!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we're talking about preventing fumbles!
Practice dropping and grabbing the ball to increase your grip strength and defend against fumbles.
Grip the ball with your fingertips! Ya-ha!
He's still facing me?!
This is my...
...Devil Backfire!
MAX CATCH!
D-Deimon...
Gets a first down!
You're spinning again, Sanada...
Yes!
He did it!
He actually caught it!
Awesome, monkey-man!
Yay, Mon-Mon!
Way to go Monta, that was amazing!
Now, what on earth was that catch?!
He caught the ball with his back to it!
Umm... what on earth indeed...
This just in!
Let's see...
"Hee hee hee...
A demonic catch made with your back to the ball while charging at your opponent at top speed..."
"The Devil Backfire!"
- Monta!
- You're so cool, Monta!
- You da man, Monta!
Thank you, thank you!
That was Taro Raimon's ultimate move, the Devil Backfire!
Don't forget the name!
Man... Monta's uber-elite today.
Ikkyu...
There are so many possible angles your arms can point,
but a no-look catch behind the head is the most uber-hard catch you can make!
And he did it while he crashed into SAKURABA...
That freak!
Tetsuma...
I timed my jump perfectly...
...and he still beat me...
Monta...
I... have to...
Peewee.
Hold on for five more minutes.
In the meantime, we use Butt-Monkey exclusively!
Monta...
Okay! Leave it to me!
I'll pile the pressure on Ojo with my new technique.
You just rest up for the next five minutes, Sena.
Set, hut!
First down Deimon!
Four...
...more minutes!
First down!
Three...
...more minutes!
- Push 'em back! Beat 'em down!
Two...
...more minutes!
First down!
Almost there, Sena!
Right, Monta!
Something's lit a fire under Monta, he's literally leading Deimon down the field!
It's been ten minutes since the second half started, but Demon's made it to midfield!
Listen up, boys.
On the next play we've gotta blow Ojo's wall to kingdom come!
- Yeah!
Sena hasn't run once, Deimon's been saving him since the half started...
But to what end?
Deimon's passed their way this far,
will they draw their legendary blade this time
and run it with Eyeshield 21?!
His eyes are full of energy again!
Hut!
- Make a passing wall!
Raimon, I thought as much.
We've got a new plan to neutralize your passing game.
Shin came up the middle?!
A blitz?!
All right!
Not this time!
By switching the bigger Otawara with Shin, we can execute a zone blitz!
I'm not dropping this pass no matter what!
Devil Backfire!
Yes!
Yes! The Devil Backfire strikes again!
It's not over, that position-
I'll just squash ya!
Sena!
Five seconds...
Four, three, two, one...
...zero!
Wh- Sena?!
Look at him go!
My legs... they're so light!
That's it!
This is what Hiruma meant when he said "Ten minutes into the half!"
Fly, Peewee!
Now!
What?!
Nice, Monta!
It's a combo play from Sena and Monta!
Monta used his short stature to run right through Otawara's legs!
Yes! I'm gonna run this all the way for a max touchdown!
But it's not over! Ojo's rampart is closing in on Monta!
Monta!
You can't escape, Eyeshield!
He's accelerating even faster!
Of course!
On a slick, muddy field, Shin's power gives him an advantage.
But now that the ground's dried out, Sena's running technique is back!
His running's so sharp it's absurd.
The light speed running back has returned!
Let's go, together!
Yeah!
- Stop them!
With my catching,
and my running,
- there's nothing we can't overcome!
Touchdown!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
All right, with my Devil Backfire and Sena's running, we can totally win this!
Wait now Ojo's got a combo play?
Another elite-class showdown!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Two Aces!
Ya-ha!
Sena and Monta score a touchdown!
We did it, Monta...
I knew we could, Sena. I knew you'd come to help!
There's nothing more touching than seeing guys show how strong their friendship is.
Sena! Monta! You did it! You did it!
I guess that's a... strong friendship, too...
Boys are hopeless.