Squash that pipsqueak!
Touchdown!
A barrage of Devil Bat Ghosts!
No one even comes close!
Whoa, killer moves.
Hey, Kakei, check the fake Eyeshield.
Whatever.
A fake is a fake.
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 42
Game over! Deimon crushes the competition!
And advances into the Best Eight!
This's only the first time I've seen Deimon,
but they don't feel like anything special.
Hey, Kakei, you think we can just chill on the bench for that game,
like in the first round?
Don't be lazy.
There's no more reason to try and keep ourselves a secret.
We need to blast forward, full steam ahead.
Oh yeah... But to be honest...
These guys can't stand up to us.
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
A Physique-al Barrier!
We're in the Best-freakin'-Eight!
Next's the third round... against the Poseidons!
I'm kinda nervous.
It's all good. We'll blast right through 'em!
Hey, it's Deimon!
Watch out?!
"Watch out?" They're not monsters.
But they were here watching our game...
I guess you came by to spy on us, huh?
Spy?
What's so funny?
We could spend the whole game on the bench like in the first round and still beat you, brah.
What?!
We're gonna win, brah.
You've got too many shorties, and our height totally gives us the advantage.
Oh yeah, one last thing.
You got like, a super-midget on your line, right?
What was his name... Omusubi or something?
Omusubi... No! Komusubi!
Oh, he's here!
I didn't even see you.
Being so short's really dangerous.
You should stay off the team.
Hey, why'd you say that?!
Keep your nose outta our team's business!
I'm warning you, if you're on the field, I'll match myself up with you.
That means I'm gonna stomp you into the ground with my height, dude.
Think about it, you playing the same position as me?
Later.
Hey!
Eyeshield's said this before...
Komusubi, me, all of us - we'll beat the Poseidons!
And prove that even short people can be the best!
Interesting.
We won't run.
We won't lose!
You seem pretty tired.
Yeah, I couldn't stop thinking about what Mizumachi said, it kept me up all night.
The way he was so blunt about it really got me down.
But hey,
we've all stuck it out for this long,
and we're not gonna grow that much before the game.
We've just gotta fight like our lives depend on it!
Monta...
Man, Sena, you were awesome yesterday!
We'll beat the Poseidons!
And prove that even short people can be the best!
Awesome!
They won't know what hit 'em!
What's wrong, Komusubi?
Do you have a stomachache or something?
Look, if your heart's not in it, take a hike!
Ju-Jumonji!
We barely have any time before the Poseidons game and you're just moping!
Come on, don't fight!
U-Umm...
Take it easy, Jumonji.
Clam it!
Either you're motivated to practice or you're dead weight!
Komusubi!
What's wrong with him?
Guess he really doesn't wanna practice.
I wonder what's wrong...
Sena, Monta, do you know?
Well...
Yesterday...
Being so short's really dangerous.
You should stay off the team.
That's what he said.
He just lost my respect.
If he's so depressed about being short,
he never should've played football in the first place.
Have we always been out there with such a coward?
Pretty sad.
Hey, come on!
You guys don't need to take it that far!
Guys!
- PLEASE stop fighting!
- Too heavy!
Komusubi...
So Komusubi never came back to practice yesterday, huh?
We're in big trouble!
What the heck happened?
Komusubi... Komusubi...
...ran away from home!
- Ran away?!
Yes, he left this note at my house!
Suddenly
- "Suddenly?"
- ...What?
"Dear friends, I am forever in your debt."
"Please forgive me for suddenly vanishing."
That's not what it says!
It must be Stronglish...
Ya-ha!
Normal letter - Stronglish
"Stronglish" is the language Komusubi speaks,
a soulful vernacular only other powerful men can comprehend!
Ya-ha.
"The team is better off without me."
"This useless hanger-on won't ever bother you again!"
KOMUSUBI!
This is all that jerk Mizumachi's fault.
You don't think Komusubi's really gonna quit football?!
We'd better check the clubhouse!
Right!
He's not at any of his classmates' homes.
Where'd you wander off to, Fatty Jr.?
He's not answering his phone, either...
Being so short's really dangerous.
You should stay off the team.
I'll go look around the area.
- Me too!
- I'll go!
I'll accompany you, of course!
Guys...
Is that clown-nosed kid brain dead?
The Poseidons are such strong opponents...
What's he thinking?
Aren't you worried at all?!
Let's go home.
- Yeah.
Let those heartless bums go.
We should all split up.
We finally hit our stride as a team...
Now we're falling apart.
Komusubi, where are you?
This tree was planted when my great-great-grandfather was born.
Everyone in the Komusubi family tracks how big they get on this tree!
Look how tall you're getting!
Remember, you're my son.
You're guaranteed to grow up big and strong!
Hey, wait for me!
Same...
Think about it, you playing the same position as me?
Being so short's really dangerous.
- We may be short...
But I can catch.
I'm the fastest man alive.
What can you do, Komusubi?
You really are useless.
- Yep.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to play offense!
The hint is "run and pass!"
You can run straight ahead or try to gain a lot of ground with a pass.
Choosing the right way is important.
Everyone get that? Ya-ha!
Umm... I'm looking for this boy, he sort of looks like a rice ball...
Anything?
Has anyone seen this man?
Anyone with information gets my autograph as a reward!
No one can see the picture!
...Carry the one, and we get a radius of about 300 meters...
- Okay, Kurita, try here.
- Right!
KO-MU-SU-BI!
I guess he's not here.
I'm sorry!
See you tomorrow, Ishimaru.
Monta... what're you...
I'm looking from up high.
That way you get a better view.
Anyway, he's not around here.
Bye!
He's like a wild animal...
I've run all over the place... Time to try somewhere else.
Komusubi can still do plenty even if he's not tall!
Eat, eat!
You're my boy, you'll be a giant in no time!
Dwarf
We've got a few leads...
I'll spend the next few days searching if I have to.
You gather everyone and get back to practicing.
Okay.
Coach Doburoku?
Oh, wait, I'll call you back!
Mrs. Komusubi!
Oh, hello, Kobayakawa!
Have you seen Daikichi?
We're looking for him too...
I see... He was acting strangely yesterday,
and he ran out of the house this morning.
What're you saying, Daikichi?
You swore to follow your master no matter what!
When a man dedicates himself to something, he follows through to the end!
I don't know what happened, but eat up.
Eat up and build your strength.
Here, eat your rice.
If you don't eat breakfast, you'll stunt your growth.
What's gotten into you, Daikichi?
I told you never to raise your hands to your mother
after she worked so hard to cook for us!
I-I understand what you're trying to say,
but you're getting your lecture jumbled up...
Daikichi!
I see...
Do you think something happened at school?
I promise we'll find him.
Is there anywhere special he might have gone?
That's right!
I'm in the way.
Komusubi!
Watch out!
You watch out!
You're really something.
I tackled you as hard as I could,
but you push completely different from the other backs.
You and the others really make an incredible wall.
Komusubi, you're okay!
You're not hurt, are you?
We've been looking everywhere!
Komusubi!
- Komusubi!
Komusubi...
Come back, Komusubi!
We aren't the Devil Bats unless you're out there with us.
Komusubi...
Hey, the three of them didn't bike to school today...
They must've gone back for them
so they could cover more ground.
Jumonji!
N-No, don't!
What's your freaking problem?!
In the way!
- I quit!
- You moron!
- Who do you think you are?!
- You fat little lump!
You wanna quit?!
What, you think we're gonna LET you?!
We ALL make the Devil Bat Line!
We block TOGETHER!
How are we supposed to stop the Poseidons without you?!
Komusubi!
Just leave 'em alone, that went perfectly.
T-Training!
He's revived!
Komusubi.
Thank God... Komusubi's happy again.
Whew...
Every cloud has a silver lining.
He's okay now.
Mmhmm.
- Ow...
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Set, hut, dosskoi!
Wait, why are we doing sumo?
Shh! It's a secret training program for the Poseidons game!
Good timing, because there's a sumo tournament going on!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Toss him out! The Honorable Komusubi! Ya-ha!
Komusubi...I will find you.
Huh? Where's Coach Doburoku?
Off being an idiot.