Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Oh!
Ya-ha!
Throughout this entire tournament, Ojo with its ultimate defense,
hasn't allowed anyone to score a touchdown against them.
But... no longer!
The invincible castle walls were toppled by
Sena and Monta's double touchdown!
Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
There's just eight minutes left,
Ojo White Knights 13 - Deimon Devil Bats 13
and Deimon's finally catching up.
Devil Bats! Devil Bats! Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
With our combo, we'll win to the max!
Too cool!
Not bad!
- Boo-yah!
- You punks!
- You rule! You kicked butt!
Sakuraba!
Their pressure... blew me away.
- Stop them!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Two Aces!
Set, hut, hut!
I'll mark Sakuraba to the max!
Go, Sakuraba!
I can't lose!
It's their Everest Pass!
It's a powerful attack!
Monta intercepted the ball!
Ojo's pass failed!
It's like Monta has eyes in the back of his head.
Nice!
Monta!
- Good goin', Butt-monkey!
Darn it!
Sakuraba...
They're seeing right through our passes.
We need to step back and come up with a new play.
It's okay!
Throw me another pass.
I can't lose to Monta!
I've gotta prove that I'm better than him.
But, Sakuraba...
It'll work out.
Please throw another Everest Pass!
I swear I'll catch it this time!
Throw me... another pass!
Fine. I'll pass you the ball.
There's no need to worry.
Shin?
He's not the type of guy to give up yet.
It looks like Sakuraba's getting pretty nervous.
I hope he doesn't lose sight of what's important.
Shut up, Onihei!
Sakuraba will be just fine!
You better not be right about him for once!
Torakichi...
Sakuraba's just GOTTA win!
Sakuraba, what's wrong with you?
Set, hut!
Let's go, Sakuraba!
It's ANOTHER Everest Pass!
It's HUGE!
Has Takami's record of perfect passes finally been broken?
No, it hasn't!
This is a killer pass showing that he believes in Sakuraba.
That's nuts! That pass is just way too far!
I've caught so many of Takami's passes that I've lost count.
I know... that I can catch it!
Wha-?!
What?! Sakuraba!
Th-That's-
Devil Backfire!
Amazing! Sakuraba used Devil Backfire!
Sakuraba!
I'll definitely...
Uh-oh, he fumbled! The catch failed!
Darn it! Why? Why couldn't I-?!
Ojo's pass is no good!
Sakuraba!
A stretcher! Get a stretcher out here!
W-What a disaster!
Will Sakuraba be all right, after suffering from that terrible fall?
You're really tall.
Hey, you'd make a great receiver!
Please join the football team!
We might make it to nationals with you on the team!
Please be our ace!
Ace? Me, an ace?
Oh, and how about you join the football team, too?
What do you think you're doing?!
How many times do I have to tell you to stretch your arms out?!
I stink...
He's incredible!
Isn't that Seijuro Shin?
He's Ojo's young new ace.
That's right! I wanted to be Ojo's ace...
Everyone's cheering for the great ace, Sakuraba!
Ojo's ace, Sakuraba, is entering the field!
No, I'm not...
I... Shin...
Go, Sakuraba!
Max Catch!
I knew it. I'm no...
- Sakuraba...
Will Sakuraba be okay?
It looks like he hit his head. I'm worried about him.
Sakuraba...
Get up, Sakuraba...
You can't lose.
H-Hey, Torakichi!
Please get up, Sakuraba!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we'll be talking about kicking!
Watch the ball carefully until you're completely done kicking.
Imagine that you made a good kick beforehand! Ya-ha!
Please get up, Sakuraba!
Please don't lose!
Sakuraba!
Sakuraba?!
Don't do this! Get up already, Sakuraba!
My body... feels heavy.
This is just like how things used to be.
That's...
Ojo Ace, Sakuraba
Sakuraba!
Torakichi?
Sakuraba, get up!
You're no loser, right?!
You've gone through painful training, remember?!
You've grown stronger, haven't you?!
So what's keepin' ya?!
If you don't stand up soon, I'll stand up before you, you coward!
Are you cool with that? Wouldn't losing to an elementary schooler be lame?
H-Hey, Sena.
Y-Yeah!
He's standing!
Torakichi!
Whatcha think?
Standing is easy!
Now it's your turn to stand up!
T-Torakichi...
Sakuraba...
Torakichi!
Whoa there.
Don't lose to an elementary school kid, Sakuraba.
I was playing by myself...
I got hot-headed and ignored everyone else.
I was wrong.
I'm not fighting out here by myself.
So-!
Sena, Monta...
I may not even come close to you two as far as talent's concerned,
but... I'll never allow my spirit to break like that ever again.
Sakuraba...
I made a promise with Torakichi.
I swore that we wouldn't stop here.
We'll keep on going!
Everyone in the Ojo White Knights is going to the Christmas Bowl!
Shin, Takami...
We're going to use THAT technique.
No, please let me use it!
But, Sakuraba, we still haven't perfected that move yet.
Sakuraba might be able to handle it now.
Shin, that'll send you both out into the densest part of enemy territory.
I know.
It's both physically and mentally straining. Are you sure?
I'll be fine because I won't be alone.
We will make it work.
Fine, I'll trust you two.
Great!
Set, hut!
Sakuraba, Shin, show them just how strong you two really are!
Right. With our tag-play-!
Let's join the football team together, Shin!
Someday we'll be called the two aces of Ojo!
Wouldn't it be sweet if that happened?
Monta has Sakuraba completely marked!
I won't lose thanks to my Devil Backfire!
Th-That's-?!
It's a short pass to Sakuraba?!
I see, with that short distance...
...Monta will be unable to determine where the ball's going.
They've abandoned their super long cannons and are gaining yardage the safe way.
Sorry, but Sakuraba's play isn't anything as simple as that.
Darn it!
We've gotta get him when he lands, Sena!
Yeah, we'll sandwich him in!
It's Shin?!
Amazing!
Sakuraba, our Pegasus soaring through the sky, has teamed up with the ultimate knight, Shin!
That's it! They're like a giant bow and arrow piercing through the sky!
It's the Sagittarius!
G-Go... Sakuraba!
The Ojo White Knights nab their first down!
Good goin', Sakuraba...
Torakichi...
He's pulled himself together...
Sagittarius...
With Shin in the lead and Sakuraba behind him,
this is a super-powerful technique that allows them to fly across the field!
At first glance, this is a simple enough play,
but since it's just the two of them racing through enemy territory,
it must be very physically draining for them.
Can you do it again?
You bet!
We've finally perfected it.
Yeah. It's a move that required both of us.
Let's blow right through them.
Yeah!
We should be able to get through the sidelines, Shin!
Yeah, together we can handle it!
Sakuraba and Shin are using their Sagittarius to get first down after first down!
I can't stop their Sagittarius!
Darn it! And here we were finally able to fight against their long passes with my Devil Backfire!
Set, hut!
Wow! It's another super short pass to Sakuraba!
Ikkyu, could you have cut off that pass?
No, it would have been physically impossible.
I would try to tackle him when he hits the ground,
but with him there...
Shin blocked them!
The Sagittarius is invincible!
Now they've got to face the defense in front of the goal line!
Stop him, kiddies!
Not good!
Don't let them...
- ...get a touchdown!
- Crush them!
Get through!
Such determination! I've never seen Sakuraba like this before.
Touchdown!
Sakuraba's back and better than ever!
Takami worked hard to polish Sakuraba, and now both Sakuraba and Shin are true aces!
Sakuraba...
That's right... That's my Sakuraba!
Ojo White Knights 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 13
Ojo has pulled in the lead once more!
And here we worked so hard to catch up with them...
It's a cruel seesaw game!
As soon as they catch up, they fall behind yet again!
Deimon's behind by seven points!
Hey now! Weren't we going to karaoke?
What are we doing HERE?
Deimon's powerless before Ojo's Sagittarius!
I can feel the heavy air of trepidation coming from Deimon.
How will they deal with this?
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Shin and Sakuraba are using the Sagittarius!
And here we'd finally caught up!
We're running outta time!
I've gotta stop Shin somehow!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Turn on the Devil Stun Gun!
Ya-ha!
Sena, Monta, did you see our combo-play?
G-Goodness me! Shin isn't the type to put his arm around others!
Will he return the gesture?!
Riko, is that really important right now?
- He used his Trident Tackle!