Don't brake...
And take off!
Then kick it again!
Quit jumping on your bed!
What are you doing, sleepwalking?
Good gracious...
Wha?
Oh yeah, the new term starts today.
There's nothing like real Japanese rice!
Ryokan, where's my rice-
You say you followed your master all the way to the end?!
That's my boy!
I can't believe you understand him.
Then came the final 500 kilometers!
You can only learn what a man's really made of when he's been pushed to his limits!
I would've quit on the second day.
How was your month in America?
Y-Yes, that was one tough study abroad program...
I'd love to know what exactly you were studying
during your time there.
Uh... English!
A-And a an intense, comprehensive review...
Oh, I need to get going.
Isn't it a bit early?
Yes, well... I need to do some advance prep work.
The new term starts today,
and soon we have our first team meeting, where he'll pick the starters!
I survived the entire death march.
I might actually make the first string!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The New Starting Lineup?!
I'm the principal.
I hope you'll all have a safe, uneventful term.
My affairs-
Er, indiscretions are in the past, so those who are in the know,
please cut me some slack, I'm so sorry!
The fall tournament starts next week, huh?
Mamori!
Your loyal loaner players...
...will be training with you every day!
G-Good!
Leave the playboy basketballers to me, I'll crucify 'em.
Hey!
Coach Doburoku!
I got a job with the school!
Make sure you funnel his entire salary to the football team's budget.
Yes, sir.
What the-
What's up?
It's been a while.
How was the training camp?
Jimmy!
Jimmy?
No, no, no, Simard!
I mean, Ishimaru!
Oh ho! American Football Monthly has blurbs on all the teams in the tournament!
What's it say about Deimon?
Let's see here...
"Riding a wave of momentum, their capable offense nearly beat the Aliens,
but they're too inconsistent to have any real shot at victory?!"
Glaring at the magazine won't help.
To be fair, the only regulation match we actually won was against Koigahama.
Ojo's not in our block.
Sweet, that means we get to smash them in the finals after we beat everyone else!
Welcome!
You see that?
Why'd you close the door?!
Uh, well...
That's gratitude for ya,
I come all the way here to cheer for you-
Y-You surprised us.
Ahh, I see!
You're blushing!
You shy boy, you really dig the look, huh?
Just so you know, Suzuna...
Real men only focus on the fight!
They never let sweet-sounding cheers take away from their focus!
Though I appreciate your support.
C'mon, come out!
Suzuna, I-
I'm a manager, and this outfit doesn't suit me-
You look fine!
W-Wait a sec-
Taa-daa, take a look!
Suzuna!
You were saying?
So? You see where I'm coming from?
Mamori...
Well, Suzuna forced me into this-
I'm Monta...
So I'm the captain of the cheerleading squad now.
Even though I'm not a Deimon student,
my brother's going to be part of the Devil Bats!
Really? Congrats!
But when did he-
The team selection isn't until tomorrow.
I see everyone's here.
What's going on, bro?
They said the announcement's not-
What're you talking about, my sister?
My success is 150% guaranteed,
so I let you know a bit ahead of time!
Say that AFTER you pass the test!
If you fail now, I'll have put myself in this ridiculous situation for nothing!
I'll kill you if you don't make the cut!
That hurt, my sister...
Time to start practice, losers!
Today will be your final test.
Sir!
Yuki's really pumped.
Smash 'em! Take 'em out!
Sena and Monta are both light on their feet.
Five points for them.
Set, hut!
Go, go, Devil! Go, go, Bats!
Let's go, let's go, YEAH!
Our playbook... or play cards.
Memorize every last one of them by the time the tournament starts!
Can we really learn all these crazy plays?
I'll have it done in five minutes!
Max concentration!
Natsuhiko Taki, stupid, but a good influence on the team. 10 points.
There, I've got them all memorized!
Unbelievable!
Okay, what do we do if the opponent's lined up with two tight ends and one back?
We focus on stopping the run with a 6-2 defense.
He's right!
Whoa!
Nicely done, Manabu Yukimitsu.
10 points.
Time to run the 40!
Nothing less.
Next, Monta!
Okay!
Max goal!
Monta, 5.1 seconds!
Now, Yukimitsu!
Yes!
His best was 6.1 seconds.
This'll be tough.
The average high schooler runs it in 5.5.
This is my final test.
I'll play in the fall tournament with everyone!
5.6 seconds!
Wow... I shaved off half a second!
Way to go, Yuki!
Excellent!
Yukimitsu's speed gets him 20 points.
All right, time to call it a day.
Whoa, already?
Great job, guys!
What's wrong, guys?
It's like... I'm not even tired.
Yeah.
What's up with that?
Are you kidding me?
What'd you think the point of the death march was?
We're stronger!
Hey, where's Sena?
You really did well, Yuki!
You memorized the entire playbook and knocked half a second off your time on the 40!
I still have a long way to go.
There's a lot more hard work to be done for the fall tournament.
I'll catch like a madman!
We're gonna win the championship!
Yeah, we can do it!
Together, we can face anyone!
Okay... When the opponent lines up this way, we use this formation...
I haven't played in any games,
but staying on the team to the end is my own personal battle.
That was back then...
Now I really think I have a shot at playing in the tournament!
With everyone else!
Manabu, I brought you some tea and crumpets. Hmm?
Manabu?
Oh, I'm just-
What's that?
A vocabulary book.
I need to take a shower now!
I WILL go to the tournament with everyone else!
Football Clinic!
What is the Christmas Bowl?
The championship game between the eastern and western conference champs!
It's a wild game that happens right around Christmastime! Ya-ha!
Okay, time to announce the first string for the fall tournament.
I hope everyone makes it.
Yup.
I'm sure Taki will be fine.
After all, he can catch, block and everything!
Guys...
True enough.
You doofus, it's still too early to celebrate!
If the Devil Bats take him,
he'll really be able to play football!
Everyone I call will be playing offense AND defense.
First is the quarterback: Me!
I'm the kicker, too.
Next are the front five, the line.
Kurita, Komusubi, Jumonji, Kuroki, and Togano.
Yay!
H-Happy!
The two running backs are Eyeshield 21 and Tetsuo Ishimaru.
Tag: Track Team
I like how I'm considered an actual member.
Just shaddap and do as you're told!
Okay, okay, it's fine!
Suzuna?
I dunno why,
but I noticed you aren't telling Mamo that you're Eyeshield 21.
Your secret's safe with me.
Thanks.
Tight End:
Taki-kun's position.
Natsuhiko Taki.
Yay!
Congratulations!
When did she set that up?
Congratulations, Taki!
Here's your uniform!
Now you can finally play football, bro!
Was there ever any doubt, my sister?
Yeah, yeah.
Let's just put this here.
A customized figure.
It's like his long-lost little brother.
Last but not least, our two wide receivers!
Finally...
This is only position I ever had a chance at.
Relax...
I practiced all those pass routes, increased my speed and stamina...
He'll pick me!
Taro Raimon!
Yes!
And also...
It's gotta be Yuki.
Yup!
This is my one shot at a high school tournament!
I'll get to stand out on the field!
I'll get to play alongside the team!
This time...
THIS time!
And also...
...the basketball loaners, Satake and Yamaoka, who'll we'll rotate.
- No!
- What?!
That's it.
Doburoku's got your positions for defense.
Wait!
Why...
Why didn't you pick Yukimitsu?
He worked so hard!
He lasted the entire death march-
Don't waste your breath when you already know, Manajerk!
You can't spend 17 years sitting at your desk,
and expect four months of training to make you better than a regular basketball player.
Well, but...
He couldn't beat their times on the 40,
and his bench press is nothing special.
Satake and Yamaoka are better suited for every single task.
That's all there is to it.
Hiruma...
Can I ask you something?
Isn't there anything more important to you than winning?
No. Nothing.
When you lose, you're finished.
Baldini knows that as well as anyone.
Yuki...
I was so close... I guess.
I like to think so, anyway.
It's like I was told all those years ago.
"People have an aptitude for certain things and lack it for others."
"No amount of exercise will change that."
Keep studying.
These are the most important years of your life.
I guess the lesson here is I'm just not cut out for sports.
Huh?
Yuki...
Oh well, I can still support them from the bench!
I'll use my analytical abilities to help out wherever it can make a difference...
Shoot...
But still...
I wanted to play with everyone, just once.
It'll have to remain a dream.
I want to rerun it from where I collapsed.
I never had a chance... I'm so dumb.
Why?! Why didn't I start last year?!
Maybe I wouldn't have made it anyway,
but at least I wouldn't have any regrets now!
Why?!
Yuki...
Leave him alone.
If we go talk to him now, we'll just make him feel worse.
How can you say that?!
I know how he feels!
Right...
Monta didn't get picked for the baseball team...
And it's not over yet.
There's no telling how many days Deimon will be part of the fall tournament.
If he can improve before it's over...
We play Amino High in the first round!
If we beat them, we'll get to keep playing, right, Monta?
You got it!
The tournament won't end if we keep winning, Sena!
Until EVERY Deimon Devil Bat stands on the field together...
...we won't lose!
Sena, Monta, thank you.
I won't lose either.
Not until I'm on the field, next to you!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Say what?
Eyeshield's a total hottie on par with the hottest Hollywood hunk?!
Hey, Yocchie said, "the bigger the rumor, the better!"
And now Eyeshield's got TV cameras trying to snap a shot?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Road to the Christmas Bowl! Ya-ha.
Hey, Manajerk, check this out.
Th-That's-
Oh, NO!
Our own Manajerk in the middle of cheerleading practice!
Wha- Bu-
It's going straight into my threat book.
You are EVIL!
Ya-ha!