They've decided on our opponent for the fourth death game.
Yeah, we just got a letter addressing that.
So, who'll we be pitted against?
It's a team competing in the Kanto Tournament,
the Taiyo Sphinx.
The Taiyo Sphinx?
Going by Banba's appearance during the lottery,
it looks like they've really been training hard.
Whatever.
We've already gone through a lot
to prepare for our game against Shinryuji.
Yeah!
This'll be easy!
With everyone on the team, you might be right.
But I bet we're gonna get some sorta handicap, right?
Your handicap...
...is nothing!
R-Really?
We're fighting against a team
participating in the Kanto Tournament.
We don't need a handicap!
Then we...
...can win!
Great!
Let's show them just how strong we've become!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
One Lineman Short!
So I was wonderin',
why'd the Taiyo Sphinx decide to scrimmage with us?
I bet they want to find out just how strong we've become!
Yeah, after all,
we're way stronger and more experienced
than we were when we fought them last time.
Yeah!
But Banba and his team's been training really hard.
It'll be okay!
Don't worry!
We've really grown strong these past six months.
We'll easily smash the Taiyo Sphinx's line!
You sound rather confident.
Huh?
Harao!
Kasamatsu!
Banba!
It's everyone from the Taiyo Sphinx!
You guys spyin' on us?!
Don't be stupid!
We just ran into you!
You Chick-a-dee Brothers aren't worth the effort.
What was that?!
We'll put you face-up!
Allow me to give you a warning.
Overconfidence can cost you the game.
Let's just see...
...if we're being overconfident!
How foolish.
What was that?!
Wha-?!
- Jumonji!
Hey, you okay?
How dare he, the jerk?!
For three years...
We've given this our all these past three years.
Don't get cocky just because you've been working on it
for a measly six months!
Well then, gentlemen,
see you at the game.
We'll finish you off then!
J-Jumonji!
Okay?
Don't let that bother you any!
You were going up against a giant.
Shut it.
H-Hey, Jumonji?
Jumonji...
Huh?
How'd you get that bruise?
Did you get in another fight?
No, I didn't.
I got it at football practice.
Why don't you quit playing with a silly little ball
and start studying some?
Leave me alone!
Oh, come on, hot-cakes!
Come play with us!
Let's karaoke!
No way!
Hey, you! Go get lost!
Why should we?!
You got a problem with us, punk?!
I suggest you scram before you get hurt!
I don't feel like messing around with you!
What was that?!
Let go!
Let go of me, you jerk!
What's going on over there?!
Crap!
Freeze!
Deimon Police Station
Why the heck did you go after me?!
I was just trying to help that lady!
I didn't see any lady there!
And why won't you tell me your name and address?
T-That's because-
Oh, I get it.
It's because you were up to mischief, isn't it?
If I'm not careful...
I'll be expelled from the tournament.
It's showtime!
It's the Deimon Devil Bats fourth death game!
This time they'll be up against a fellow competitor in the Kanto Tournament.
It's the team with most powerful line in Kanto, the Taiyo Sphinx!
These two teams squared off once before,
but ended the game in a draw.
Which means we should be in for one doozy of a show!
Jumonji, you jerk!
Where are you?!
Where?
It's no good. He's not picking up.
Is he still upset over yesterday?
Guess it really upset him.
Our game with Deimon last summer...
Without a doubt,
it exposed the great Taiyo Sphinx's weaknesses for what they were.
Everyone not in the line was weak and fragile.
But at that time,
our team's main weakness was our lack of burning desire to win.
A certain man showed that to us.
As such, we are unqualified to enter the Kanto Tournament
if we cannot defeat Deimon!
I have a proclamation to make!
If we lose this game,
I swear that we shall forfeit from the Kanto Tournament!
For real?!
No way!
Looks like they're serious.
This might be bad.
It's just about time for the game to start...
This stinks!
We've given this our all these past three years.
Don't get cocky just because you've been working on it
for a measly six months!
He's right...
I guess it really doesn't even matter...
...if I show up or not.
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
The Taiyo Sphinx have declared that they'll forfeit the tournament
if they lose to Deimon!
Which means that one of these two teams
won't be participating in the Kanto Tournament anymore.
Why? Why'd they do that?
It shows how seriously they're taking this.
No one can afford to lose.
Taiyo Sphinx vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Ra!
- Ya-ha!
Set...
...hut hut!
- Go for it, Sena!
That's strange.
Usually Sena's able to just breeze right through.
They might be moving faster than he anticipated.
Yeah!
They've trained hard to be that fast and overpowering!
W-What the-?!
Are these guys monsters?!
Strong!
Those injuries weren't just for show!
Hiruma's down!
Deimon's line fell like flies!
What gives, you stupid linemen?!
Hold them back!
Everyone from Taiyo was impressive last summer,
but they're way stronger now!
This stinks!
There's no way we can cover Jumonji's turf, too!
We'll just do what we can!
Jumonji, come quick!
Deimon managed to fend off Taiyo's offense!
Now will the Deimon Devil Bats strike back?!
But it appears that Deimon's lineman Jumonji is missing!
I wonder if the Ha-Ha Brothers
will be able to fight to their fullest with him gone.
It'll be hard for us to attack without a strong line.
'Monji, where'd you run off to?
Set, hut, hut!
Peewee, get past Taiyo's defense!
Don't be fooled! His hands are empty!
Crush Hiruma, Kasamatsu!
I've improved since last summer, Hiruma!
Prepare yourself!
Okay! Got it!
So close!
But they stopped Deimon's offense!
I really can see a difference in the Taiyo Sphinx's gameplay from last spring.
What do you mean?
Until then they were a power house
that only focused on their line.
But they've really worked on their back players.
Are you saying we're in serious trouble then, Musashan?
Yeah and since Jumonji's not here, our line's a mess.
What's keeping that jerk Jumonji anyway?!
Hurry and get over here, you punk!
What gives?!
Jumonji no run!
He not like that!
We already knew that...
...without you having to tell us!
B-But he's already really late-
Jumonji...
Come on out.
We found the girl you were talking about.
If you'd just told us the truth,
we coulda let you out sooner.
I'm so sorry. I was just so scared...
No biggie.
You didn't do anything bad.
Dad...
Sorry for all the trouble he caused.
Deimon's in trouble!
They failed to get their first down!
Nothing would change even if I was there
since I can't even budge Banba.
Goodness gracious.
Were you trying to act like a hero?
Your selfish behavior affects absolutely everyone around you.
Did that ever occur to you?
What on earth are you trying to do?
He's right.
I only lost to Banba once,
so why am I letting it eat at me?
I don't care how many times I lose!
I'll never give up!
I've gotta face him head on!
Hey, where are you going?
The Taiyo Sphinx got a touchdown!
Taiyo Sphinx 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
With the extra point, their score's up to seven!
This'll make things tough for Deimon!
Right.
It'll be really hard for Deimon
to break past Taiyo's invincible line
and score a touchdown in the time remaining.
I... I... am such a stupid jerk!
What will you do now, Deimon?!
You'll lose your right to play in the Kanto Tournament
if you lose here!
We can't lose... We won't lose, right Mamo?
I-I sure hope not,
but we can't expect much more out of this make-shift line.
Not lose!
Yeah, we can't lose...
...before he shows up!
Right!
For Jumonji's sake... we can't give up!
It's useless.
It doesn't matter if you add another player or two.
The outcome'll be the same.
Exactly!
We're not gonna lose just because that trash dared to show up!
Oh, really?
What?!
Then let's give it another shot, this time with that "trash" here!
I... I...!
Jumonji?
Where the heck were you?!
K-Komusubi...!
Stupid jerk!
Can't go Christmas Bowl...
...without you!
Sorry.
C'mon, let's go, ladies!
It's time to get this show rolling!
Set, hut, hut!
Struggling is futile!
You were never a match for us to begin with!
Shut up!
If we... lose here...
If we give up now...
We'll lose our reason to hang out!
I won't let anyone throw me around!
W-What's this?! He's not budging?!
We don't...
...let anyone...
...throw around!
Amazing!
Everyone's pushing back now
even though they were getting knocked down earlier!
Yay! Crush them!
I can make it!
Touchdown!
Game over!
Deimon managed to finish the game with a tie!
Thank goodness.
Since it's a tie, neither team has to forfeit the tournament.
Riko, your hair...
Most impressive.
Huh?
I'm amazed you were able to force me back like that.
But you're really great, too.
Oh?
Because that's the farthest I could push you back.
Make it to the semifinals in the Kanto Tournament.
That's when the real game begins.
Yeah!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
The death games are almost over!
Our last opponent will be the newly revived NASA Aliens!
Great! I'll get to fight against Panther again!
Remember that you're betting your seat at the tournament on this!
You'd better win this one!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Last Death Game!
Ya-ha!
Thanks for the other day.
You're...
Um, take this as a sign of my gratitude!
Please accept it!
No, I was just...
- Jumonji!
So she's why you were late!
Is it true?!
Go die under a rock, you traitor!
You're wrong!
Nah, there's no misunderstanding.
They're just super jealous.
Yep.