G-G-G-G-Guys!
For today's game against Deimon...
Don't sweat it, Kobanzame.
R-Right!
With you two on the line, there's no need to worry about Deimon!
Exactly.
Together... Just like we promised...
The winner of the men's 500 meter freestyle
is Kengo Mizumachi.
In middle school, Mizumachi's incredible athletic prowess
and abnormal drive to succeed
left him cut off from his classmates.
We'll win until we're the top team in Japan!
Our school'll take the country by storm!
We just gotta train our butts off-
It's 10 o'clock at night!
You're nuts.
But you said it yourself, brah.
"Together we'll win nationals!"
Look... That's not gonna happen.
You... lied?
I met Mizumachi in the spring of eighth grade.
Gangway, comin' through!
Whoa, the football team?
It's already June and you dudes are still recruiting?
When you put it that way, it sounds kinda sad, huh?
It doesn't matter what month it is.
We'll continue the process without embarrassment if it helps us win.
It's a small price to pay.
I don't play football for the fun of it.
I play to win.
Whoa, for real?
How far do you think you can go?
The national championship.
Yeah, brah, just 1000 more!
Man, the real thing is tough...
Let's call it a night-
One more!
Winner!
We might just do it.
With him on our team, we could get to the Christmas Bowl!
We WILL make it to the finals.
Me, Kakei, all of us!
Our target...
...is the national championship!
Poseidons!
GO! SPLASH! GO!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Devils vs. The Sea Gods.
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Sink the Poseidons! Come on, everybody!
They've got wings now!
How do they flap them?
That's top secret.
Today's the day, Komusubi!
Deimon's shorty squad is gonna let loose
and show the world what we're made of!
- It's shorty time!
Poseidons, Poseidons!
- Poseidons!
- He's so weird!
Poseidons!
He's got some good moves.
Wow...
Mizumachi greets Deimon with a very flashy performance!
Holy smokes!
How'd you even do that?
What's up, little Deimon dudes?
You catch how tall I am?
We're gonna use our height to blow you guys outta the water.
What, you? I told them to kick you off.
I was trying to help you out.
Fight!
And Deimon's shortest player Komusubi responds with an equally impressive act!
I believe he'd consider that more training.
Yeah! Don't back down!
Otawara, are you rooting for the little guys?
That reminds me, you think Coach Doburoku is still off searching for Komusubi?
He could be anywhere by now...
Hey, everyone...
Th-That voice!
Coach Doburoku!
I did it, I brought Komusubi back home!
Umm, he's right here...
He's safe and grunting louder than ever!
- He's totally snapped!
I found him...
It's going to take him some time to recover...
He's probably just drunk.
Huh?
Kyoshin's side is doing the wave!
Well, Poseidon is the god of the sea, after all...
Poseidons, Poseidons!
They're gigantic!
Hmm... Hiroshi Onishi, 2m 4cm tall.
Hiroshi Ohira, 2m 5cm tall!
T-Two meters?!
They're the tallest high school players in the nation!
Hello! I'm Master Kakei's top pupil!
Excuse me? Master Kakei's top pupil is ME.
Fakeshield 21.
Today I'll show you why you have no right to use his name.
And I'll prove to you,
what someone as short as me can do.
The devils vs. the sea gods...
Time to find out who's stronger, eh?
Height doesn't automatically win games.
The better football team will always triumph!
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
Ya-ha!
- Drown!
- Ya-ha!
Two fierce competitors for the championship, it's Deimon vs. Kyoshin!
With a spot in the Final Four on the line, these teams are finally about to clash!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
- Poseidons!
- Devil Bats!
Poseidons!
Devil Bats!
- Poseidons!
- Devil Bats!
Let's get this party started, Komusu-baby.
Komusubi...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to carry the ball!
The hint is "elbow?"
Make sure to keep the end of the ball tight against your elbow and against your side.
Keep your elbow at a right angle! Ya-ha!
You did it, Komusubi!
Komusubi knocks Mizumachi aside!
Komusubi!
I can get through.
Komusubi creates an opening and Eyeshield 21 blazes through!
- Yay!
Yes!
- High five!
You moved so fast!
Instant flying dash to the max!
You were careless.
Clearly,
Komusubi's low center of gravity
gives him a powerful advantage during the initial dash.
This game just got interesting.
Can Deimon turn this into a first down?
Look, it's that swimming stance!
For such a chatterbox, Mizumachi just got really quiet...
Don't let him get to you, Komusubi!
Keep using your moves and beat him again!
Right!
Use what you learned from sumo!
Set!
Hut!
They were even!
No, Mizumachi was a little faster!
Hate to make all your hard work go to waste,
but no one reacts faster to a starter pistol than swimmers!
Komusubi!
Look out! It's Mizumachi's super move!
The Swim!
Ha-whoosh!
Mizumachi breaks through Komusubi's block and swims straight into Eyeshield 21!
Mizumachi! Mizumachi!
That height... and that incredible reaction time!
It's practically impossible...
As a defensive lineman, Mizumachi can only move in reaction to the offense.
There's no way he could start moving first.
Deimon fails to advance!
They fail to get a first down!
The Kyoshin Poseidons now switch to offense.
We've gotta sack them and get the ball back!
As long as we put up a solid defense, we'll be fine!
Set, hut!
Look out, they're gonna come through Komusubi's spot!
Stop them!
Don't you dare forget about us!
Yeah!
Folks! We've just seen Kyoshin's two-meter twins, Hiroshi Ohira and Hiroshi Onishi!
They're so much taller!
Shinen breaks through!
44 yard gain, first down!
Yes!
Incredible! The Poseidons are poised to get a touchdown!
That was a huge play!
They're hosed if Komusubi can't do his job.
If the line keeps crumbling like that, it won't even be a contest.
Eyeshield and the chimp kid aren't big or strong enough to stop those two.
O-Otawara's analysis is completely correct!
This is a first!
Deimon will fall today.
Onihei!
Hey, you're Onihei, the guy who got completely owned by Mizumachi
way back in the first round, right?
- Torakichi...
Kyoshin Poseidons - Deimon Devil Bats
Until someone finds a way to negate Mizumachi, the Poseidons are unstoppable.
I'm 167 centimeters tall, and even I couldn't do anything.
With those three as short as they are, Deimon is helpless.
You still have time to swap out.
A short wall is no wall at all.
Hiruma!
Get your heads in the game, you stupid pipsqueaks!
If you care so much about height,
why did you even start playing in the first place?!
Even short guys...
...have their own...
...way to compete!
-We won't run!
- We won't run!
Now you're acting like a man, Daikichi!
It's Komusubi's parents!
How does the Komusubi family fight?
With speed? With height?
No, you fool!
Show them the brute strength only a moving company man can develop!
B-Brute strength...
A-Arms...
Yeah! We'll figure out a way to beat Onishi and Ohira.
So focus all you strength on beating Mizumachi.
Even though we're short, if we all work together...
We can even beat those giant freaks of nature!
Let's do this!
- Deimon shorties! Yeah!
Set...
Remember, Monta! Turn your opponent's strength against him!
Right!
Just a few more yards to the end zone!
Will the Kyoshin Poseidons score first?
At this distance...
There's no doubt that the Poseidons will try to push straight ahead.
I'll still swim right past you even if you figured out our play.
You get me, Komusu-baby?
We score first, brah.
He crawled underneath him!
The Rip!
He's back!
Pushing the opponent up with the arm and slipping underneath!
If a big beanpole's strongest move is the Swim, then a short man's best move is the Rip!
Komusubi figured it out on his own!
Mizumachi will win.
They called me a master of finesse.
Don't you think I tried something as simple as the Rip?
He's using the point of his elbow to block the Rip!
All you midgets think alike!
Komusubi!
W-Win!
He's going to try and overpower him from down there?!
With Mizumachi pressing down from above with all his weight...
It's down to power now!
Don't lose to him!
- He did it!
Turn your opponent's strength...
...against him!
He fumbles!
Max Catch!
J-Just moments away from a touchdown...
The Deimon shorties steal the ball back!
- Hooray!
Hooray!
The three of you are the best!
Hooray, hooray!
I couldn't give you a wonderfully huge physique like mine,
but your mother gave you a wonderfully small physique instead!
Right, Daikichi?
Power... He didn't use technique to win at all...
In the end, he beat Mizumachi with the single most basic tenet of football.
There are some things you don't get till you see them first hand...
I get it now.
I was a real bonehead to take you lightly just because you're short.
Don't get confident.
I'm going to rip off the mask and expose you as the fraud you are.
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Way to go, shorties!
You're on track for a first down!
It's no good, the Poseidon line is too tall!
They're like a tidal wave!
Then fly over them like me, like a true Devil Bat!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Secret MVP! Ya-ha!
Pig Bros!
It looks like he understood.
I guess they're the "Pig Bros." now?