We're all very excited about playing the Japanese team.
What are we looking forward to the most?
Why sushi, tempura and miso soup. I also hope to climb Mt. Fuji.
Who do I think will win?
I'm a former NFL player.
You can tell these Devil Bats that if by some miraculous fluke we lose, I'll perform "dogeza" for them.
He's making fools of us!
He'd better watch the dogeza talk, or we WILL have him down on his knees.
That guy's a garbage coach.
He's using Panther as a ball boy.
Panther?
Shoot, it's too high!
Sweet! He's a rocket!
Hey, Panther! Watt's got the data on the Japanese team, the Devil Bats.
Wanna see?
I'm good. I don't get to go to Japan, anyway.
Plus, they're not Seijuro Shin's team, right?
He steps so lightly!
His whole body's like a whip.
Panther, the man with zero gravity legs.
So light...
So sharp...
I've never seen anyone...
...run like that.
I want to compete with him... on the field.
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Weightless Man!
Our "Alien Autopsy" plan is all about the blitz.
Blitz?
It's a very aggressive defense style.
The Alien's strongest weapon is their long bomb.
To stop it, we need everyone to abandon their usual positions and rush the quarterback!
That's a blitz.
So it's basically us tackling him before he passes?
All of us? But then...
Doesn't that leave the backfield wide open?
We should leave a few behind just in case, right?
It's all or nothing!
Kill or be killed!
Starting today everyone's doing tackling practice!
Alien Autopsy to the max!
I want to face Panther... no matter what!
The plane is now beginning its final descent into Narita Airport.
Panther, I can't believe you paid your own way even though Coach Apollo
didn't put you on the away roster.
How'd you get the money?
I did that "dogeza" thing you showed me, Watt.
Dogeza?
Oh, this. It's a traditional Japanese pose,
used to express deep, sincere appreciation, or plead someone for a favor.
Wow.
I read that anyone will hear you out if you do this.
Oh?
Got something on your mind, Panther?
Uh, well- Can I have some more oatmeal?
You should go.
Grandma...
But you earned this.
You want to go to Japan, don't you?
Thanks, Grandma!
There's a guy over there I just have to face.
I wanna play his team!
I promise I'll pay you back someday.
When I become a pro, I'll save every penny and you'll live like a queen!
Yeah, yeah, just get down!
Take my black panther headband.
You've always wanted it, right?
It's yours.
Thank you...
Thank you, Grandma!
Grandma... I'll give it my best shot!
Flight AKU021 from Houston will arrive on schedule.
I'm sure you already know I won't use you in the game.
Now get my luggage, ball boy!
Yes sir.
I can't believe the Aliens are playing so soon after landing, and against a college team!
There's nothing to freak out about.
American or not, they're high schoolers, just like us.
But they're so big!
You're sure they're in high school?
Panther...
Hey, Panther, get your head out of the clouds!
Now drop the bags already.
Welcome, Coach Apollo, welcome!
Mister Editor-in-Chief.
Have you prepared everything we agreed upon?
Yes, of course.
Nothing but the highest class of goods, I trust.
Absolutely, sir.
Well, let's see how Japan's best stacks up.
Everyone, eat your fill before the game!
And you can polish the footballs and get the equipment ready.
Something wrong?
N-No... Yes, sir!
What are they thinking?
They're acting like a bunch of tourists.
Why is he by himself?
Looks like Apollo still doesn't plan to have Panther play.
Here, now's your chance.
Homer?
But-
If you don't eat, you'll be too starved to run in the game.
Thanks, Homer, Watt.
Hillary, you've ruined my suit and my shoes!
Someone, towel, now!
This is infuriating!
Panther! Who said you could eat?!
You've got it wrong, coach.
The two of us gave it to-
Shut up!
Answer me, Panther.
Look at me, using this rag.
Take my black panther headband.
You've always wanted it, right?
It's yours.
Now you've got your teammates punching you?
You're a lost cause.
You okay?
You hitting him's exactly what he wants!
He'd kick you off the team, maybe even have you expelled.
You wanna play, right?
And then go pro?
So your grandmother can live free and easy?
I'm sorry, Homer. You're right...Thank you.
NO!
Hillary is gone!
Everyone search for her, now!
We don't see her anywhere.
No excuses, move it!
You WILL find her!
Coach?
What do you want? And why aren't you looking for Hillary?!
Umm... If I find her, will you put me in the game?
What?
Please.
Just get going, and don't come back until you find her.
Is that clear?
Yes!
I swear I'll find you...
Ow...
Where'd you come from?
Sorry.
I'm Sena Kobayakawa, one of the Devil Bats.
Sena?
You're trying to look for that cat, right? I'll help you look.
I don't need your help.
This is my job.
If I find her, I'll get to play in the game!
I want to face you on the field.
You play football, too?
Yes.
Then you know Seijuro Shin, right?
Of course.
The only Japanese players I respect are Seijuro Shin and Eyeshield 21!
And I came to Japan to take on Eyeshield!
Really? Oh, look!
Hillary!
No way...
Sena, are you Eyeshield 21?
Today's "international goodwill" game, the NASA Aliens vs. the Zokugaku Frilled Lizards is about to begin.
Football Clinic!
What's the difference between a "return touchdown" and a regular touchdown?
When the receiving team takes a kicked ball and runs it all the way back for a touchdown.
It's one of the most exciting plays in football! Ya-ha!
Here we go.
I can't wait to see this.
How will a Japanese college team fare against a top American high school team?
I bet they get blown out.
That's what I'm thinking.
Whoa, seriously?!
Where did Sena run off to?
Set, hut!
Three, two, one, zero.
What the heck was that?!
The Shuttle Pass.
No one can stop our long passes.
Behold our world-renowned Space Shuttle Pass!
It's still going!
This is mission control.
Landing site is confirmed to be 5.2 yards ahead!
Touchdown!
Amazing...
They went all the way from midfield in one shot...
That's why we've gotta flatten him before he throws.
You really think we can do it?
If we can't, we'll never win.
I can catch up.
You're really good, Sena.
You too, Panther.
Argh...
Panther, there's a shortcut!
Ow-
Three, two, one, zero!
They're the real deal.
That's nothing compared to what it'd be like with Panther.
They'd be even stronger?
We're gonna face the ultimate team, and win!
Can we really beat them?
The game's been scheduled and we WILL win!
Where could Sena be?
Well, we lost her.
There goes my chance to play in a real game...
But why wouldn't he use you, when you've got such incredible speed?
It's my own fault.
That one time...
Go, Panther!
Grandma...
What are you doing, Panther?! Run out of bounds, like I told you!
Let's go, Panther! You can do it!
No! Get out of bounds, now!
I wanted to show off for my grandma, and I ignored the coach's orders.
Why didn't you listen to me?
I'm never using you again.
Your so-called "Zero-G" legs are worthless.
If you don't care about teamwork, stay off the field!
I haven't been in one game since that day.
So that's it...
I did this to myself. But I refuse to quit.
I'll earn another chance to play, become a starter again, and won't stop till I'm in the NFL!
For myself, and Grandma...
But even after she strained so much to put me on the plane...
And I came all the way to Japan to face you...
When I saw a video of your running,
I thought, "I HAVE to play against him."
Come on!
You just said you refuse to quit, right?
Sena...
Dragon Freight
Zoku U?
We're looking for a truck that made a delivery there.
That ain't much to go on...
We really need to find it!
Please... Please, sir!
Ahh, the cat?
Over here.
It's gone...
That's weird... Maybe it ran away?
I doubt it'd have gone too far.
Hillary?
Here, Hillary!
Here, girl!
That's enough.
When I go home, I'll tell Grandma,
"I made a great new friend over in Japan."
I'm glad I made the trip, even if I don't get to play.
It was worth it to meet you.
Panther...
What the heck are you doing?!
This is dogeza, right?
Japanese people do this to show they're really grateful, right?
Dogeza?
What's so funny?
I mean it!
Yo, Panther!
Homer, Watt, guys!
Mamori?
There!
Wait!
Stop!
Yeah, we got her!
That should be enough to get you on the field.
Rock on, Panther!
Thanks, everyone...
Thank you, Sena!
And thank you, Devil Bats!
Cheers!
But how'd you know we were here?
Somehow Hiruma just...
Where does he get his intel from?
Thanks a million.
Next time, we'll meet on the gridiron.
It will be my honor!
What're you doing?
This is what "dogeza" really means.
You lower your head, and say "please" or whatever's appropriate.
THAT'S dogeza?
It will be my honor.
It will be my honor!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
The Japan-US game is underway!
It's here... but Panther's still benched!
But the Shuttle Pass and Muscle Barrier are already so powerful!
Stop being a chicken! Show some spine!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Blitz! Japan vs. USA! Ya-ha!
My name is Hiruma, I represent the Deimon Devil Bats.
I've brought a small gift for you as a token of goodwill, Coach Apollo.
I look forward to our game three days from now, sir.
What a quaint culture.
I'm scared of the Devil Bats!
We're gonna lose!
Save me!
Ya-ha.