Set! Hut, hut!
Touchdown!
Taki, you're great!
Yeah!
He's amazing!
We've finally got a full offense.
Taki block!
The tight end is supposed to be able receive or block during battle.
Both of them require you to be really fast.
That position's perfect for Taki!
Please don't praise him like that.
He's stupid, so it'll go to his head.
I'm a genius!
Darn it! It ticks me off when he poses like that!
We're gonna have a practice game with the Zokugaku Chameleons next Wednesday!
We're doing this practice game to prepare for our match against the Yuhi Guts.
So don't get lazy!
I-It's Habashira's...
It's finally time for my debut game!
As if!
You've got the wrong idea!
I can't possibly let you play!
Huh?
You're still not a student at Deimon.
He still hasn't entered Deimon?!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
Ah ha ha! My Debut!
My debut game leaves me behind again!
How can this be?!
It can't be helped.
You haven't even taken the entrance exam yet.
Don't worry, chin-fuzz!
The mid-semester entrance exam's this Tuesday.
In other words, if you pass the exam
you can play in Wednesday's game against Zokugaku.
So it IS my debut!
Say that AFTER you pass the exam.
No worries, my sister!
I'm a genius so there's a 150% chance of me passing!
Manajerk, Baldini, Team Manajerk, make sure he passes the test!
We gotta make sure he plays in the practice game against Zokugaku no matter what!
O-Okay!
Hiruma, you know there's a better way to ask for a favor!
C'mon, everyone! Don't worry!
There's no way I could fail.
Guys, I'm leaving my brother in your hands.
What's wrong? Why so tense?
My brother's an idiot, ya know?
I'm worried about whether he'll pass the entrance exam or not.
But Taki's full of confidence. I'm sure it'll be okay!
No, no!
His confidence has never been a good indicator!
Really?
In elementary school, boys who can play sports well are like heroes.
Because of that...
and how he hates to lose, he went crazy over sports.
Taki's great, but he's stupid.
He's cool, but he's an idiot.
This's it!
It's a sport with a ball and fighting,
so it's perfect for someone like me who can do both!
My sister, I'm going to enter the NFL and play football!
Yeah, right.
But neither his elementary school or middle school had a football team.
And then he tried to get into a high school that had a team, but...
He failed the exams 'cause he's stupid.
So he fled Japan and suddenly went to America.
I see why you're worried...
That's my brother for you,
but he really is passionate about football.
So I want him to pass Deimon's entrance exam no matter what!
Suzuna!
Okay! Let's do it, Sena!
Yeah!
Let's try our best!
Thank you, guys...
What's wrong, everyone?
You all look so serious!
It's like you got zeros on your tests or something!
T-That hurt, my sister!
Be serious and work hard!
I-Isn't it a bit tight?
First let's do math.
What level are you at right now, Taki?
Can you do simultaneous equations?
Leave it to me!
I breezed up to six times six!
Six times six?
Y-You mean...
Like nine times nine?
Yes, nine times nine!
It's eighteen!
Nine times nine is eighty-one!
So close! I got it right if you write it backwards!
I see. So we're starting from multiplication...
This'll be tough.
W-Well, let's work on the English alphabet!
What's this?
"L!"
That's a "J."
And this is his strong point?
Next: Who's the author of the novel "I am a Cat?"
Tama is a common name for cats.
Tama!
It's Soseki Natsume.
Next: Who was the first President of America?
Ieyasu Tokugawa!
George Washington!
So close!
Let's skip the details and keep moving on!
Enough already!
Why are you so angry, my sister?
Everyone...
Everyone's working so hard for you,
but what's the point if you're not going to take it seriously?!
I'm always super serious!
Also, getting so worked up is bad for your skin!
Forget you!
Suzuna!
Yukimitsu, let's keep going.
Y-Yeah.
Taki, can you read this?
That's easy! It's "American Football!"
H-He's right!
What just happened?!
Maybe...
Maybe...?
Stupid...
He's so stupid!
Sena!
I don't think Taki...
...meant any harm.
I don't care about him anymore!
You can just leave him be, if you want.
Come on!
I'm serious!
But if Taki doesn't pass the test
he'll lose his chance to play football, let alone our practice game.
It can't be helped.
You reap what you sow, ya know.
But Taki likes football so much...
...that he even went out to America.
He's a friend who completed the death march with us.
I want Taki to pass!
Well, I'm heading on back now.
Amazing, Taki! You're doing it!
Keep it up, Taki!
This is awesome! He got three in a row right!
Here's the next one!
Touchdown 6 Field Goal 3
You get six points from a touchdown and three from the field goal.
You've scored points 40 times and have 201 points.
How many touchdowns did you get?
Isn't it obvious I got it 27 times?
It's right!
It's RIGHT!
Sena, maybe, just maybe...!
Maybe what?
He understands everything in relationship to football!
I told you, didn't I? I'm a genius!
Let's keep this pace up!
Right!
Alrighty then! Let's work on it all night to the max!
Boo-yah!
There's five subjects in the mid-semester entrance exam, totaling 500 points.
Please remember it takes 200 points to pass.
Excuse me, are you listening?
Please wait a sec! We've still got ten minutes!
Fine...
So then...
if you put Kurita in the center, what's the angle between him and Kuroki?
I passed the test 150%!
Right... Wrong... Wrong!
I guess this subject was tough for Taki.
Right... Right...
Wrong... Right...
He's starting to improve.
Right... Right... Right...
Wow, he got 203 points! You're safe, Taki!
But... for some odd reason I feel like I'm the one who was saved...
Big time...
Student ID: Natsuhiko Taki 1st Year Classroom 2
Deimon High School 1-2-3 Deimon, Amata City, Tokyo
Student # 1287522691
At last! At last I'm a high schooler!
I'm a genius!
Guys, thanks for your help!
I kinda feel like he's making fun of us when he's thanking us.
Suzuna's not here...
Football Clinic!
What's a "blitz?"
It's when a linebacker or defensive back tackles someone during defense.
You're giving up on your defense when you do this! Ya-ha!
You'll get burned if you think we're the same Zokugaku we were last spring!
We weren't goofing off all summer long!
Um... Thank you very much...
for driving me back from Nagano.
No need for thanks!
I came here to crush you today!
So be ready!
It's his Fire-cracker Kick!
Deimon's only offense is Eyeshield's running and the #80 monkey's passing.
Surround #80 with four people!
I'll be sure to kill Eyeshield myself!
Yeah!
Zokugaku doesn't know that we've got a tight end now.
We know all about your offense!
Touchdown!
Zokugaku Chameleons 0 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
What?!
Taki!
Taki really loves football.
Habashira, it wasn't Eyeshield or the monkey!
The tight end?!
Who should we mark?
Eyeshield, the monkey or the tight end?
Set! Hut, hut!
Eyeshield's running!
Amazing!
Habashira has greatly powered up since the last time we played against each other.
He doesn't have the ball!
Where's the tight end?!
Touchdown!
Zokugaku Chameleons 0 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
So they've got a tight end now...
We can't let Taki beat us!
- Let's stop him, Sena!
- Yeah!
Don't underestimate me!
Touchdown!
Zokugaku Chameleons 6 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
Sweet!
Great! Let's keep pushing forward!
Yeah!
Maybe I'll let Eyeshield go this time...
Or maybe the butt-monkey...
or perhaps chin-fuzz, after all...
Who should I choose?
Fine, let's target all three players!
All three?! That's crazy!
It's the Chameleon way to change your strategies to match our opponent!
Stop them even if it kills you!
Okay...
Taki block!
Suzuna, why don't you stop hiding over there and come on out?
No, well I'm not worried about my brother.
It's just, well, I wanna see if Deimon will win or not!
Bro!
Y-You did it! You're great, bro!
It looks like Taki's having a great time.
He's gathered up the ball...
And everyone trusts him...
He may be stupid,
but my brother's cool!
I'll stop you!
Go, bro!
Touchdown!
You did it, bro!
Set! Hut, hut!
You can do it, bro!
My sister, I'm a big star!
You idiot! Keep your eyes on the field!
I swear... He's such an idiot.
Suzuna!
Taki's doing a great job!
Up till now we've only had two offense cards.
Now that we've got Taki,
we have three cards so we can use more attack patterns to confuse the enemy with.
Game over! Deimon wins!
Zokugaku Chameleons 28 - Deimon Devil Bats 30
So you found a tight end, huh?
He's our new weapon.
Looks like you had a good summer.
Same with you.
If we can both keep winning,
eventually Zokugaku and Deimon will play each other.
I'll pay you back for today when that time comes.
I really am a super genius!
Come on!
Sena, thank you.
He may be stupid,
but my brother was cool!
Yeah!
The Devil Bats are the best!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
What're we doing here?
Hiruma ordered us to come to the tournament's stadium.
But Shin and Ojo are practicing together with an adult team!
We can't just stand back and watch them!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Ghost is Off Limits?! Ya-ha!
Guys, we're training as soon as we get back!
Yeah!
Make sure not to have another lame game like today!
Got that?!
Yeah...