Scorpions!
Ya-ha!
It's the big Deimon-Dokubari game,
with a spot in the "Best Eight" on the line!
But amazingly, Hiruma's gone missing!
Talk about a big problem!
Get the tight end!
Touchdown!
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
They can read us like a book...
- Yeah!
Football's all about up here.
Argh, I can't take this!
I'm gonna clobber that shrimp!
I've had enough, too!
Freeze!
Move it!
I'm not moving!
Listen, Hiruma WILL show up.
And until he does, we need to do our jobs!
Right...
If Hiruma's not here, we need to make up for his absence!
If Hiruma were here, he'd say,
"Wake up, their line's not that tough!"
So if we hit them with a full frontal attack, we can open a path
and Eyeshield can run it through!
Okay, everyone?
Yeah!
Right!
We got this!
Okay, let's go! One, two...
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
Can they really win without Hiruma?
Will the Devil Bats survive?!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Missing Leader!
The Dokubari Scorpions are up 14-0!
Ah... Takekura.
Keep fighting, everyone!
Okay!
The Deimon Devil Bats are without their captain, Hiruma.
They just can't set the pace!
How will the rest of the first quarter go?
Set, hut hut!
I totally knew you'd run it!
It doesn't matter if they know...
I'll make up for Hiruma!
Get Eyeshield!
- Forget it!
Now!
After him!
Touchdown!
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
- Hooray!
- Yay!
A touchdown!
- Eyeshield 21 scores a touchdown!
- Please calm down.
- Yeah!
These guys have nothing!
Great job!
They just landed a lucky punch.
If we can predict his movements,
it doesn't matter how fast Eyeshield 21 is.
We'll close in on you.
You can't escape the scorpion's stinger...
Deimon barely stops Dokubari!
The score is 14-6!
Hiruma...
Okay, we still have time.
Let's keep calm!
That quarterback has no confidence in his passing ability,
but he's still keeping calm, so they're gonna run it.
And it will clearly be Eyeshield!
Set, hut hut!
Eyeshield!
Eyeshield is crushed!
Too heavy...
They've got us completely figured out.
It's like they're predicting everything we do!
I told you, football's a psychological war, fought up here.
It doesn't matter how hard you meatheads try.
Ojo and Seibu don't stand a chance, either!
...Body language?
Yes.
There's no way you could predict
your opponents that well just from what you observe at their games.
Kanagushi's observing Deimon's telltale habits and body language very closely.
That's doubly bad for Deimon without Hiruma.
That should stop them from trying any more runs.
They've got no backup quarterbacks.
I don't care if you draw a few penalties,
focus on demolishing that plain-looking quarterback.
We'll get him off the field,
and there'll be no stopping us.
One minute left in the first quarter, and Deimon's back on offense!
Set, hut hut!
Go!
Roughing the passer!
Ishimaru!
They're targeting him!
- Ishimaru!
- They...
- ...did that on purpose!
That tears it!
Calm down! They'll eject you!
Tackling the passer after he's thrown a pass is a blatant penalty.
Dokubari is forced back 15 yards.
But there's no time left!
The first quarter is over!
We can't pass... and no one can think of better plays... This stinks.
Yeah...
Guys...
I'm sorry... I'm doing terrible.
Oh, no!
It's not your fault, Ishimaru...
Man, how're we supposed to beat them?
If we're gonna lose anyway...
...we should lay the smackdown on 'em first!
Hang on to this.
Our game plan for Dokubari.
You'll need it after the first quarter.
Don't open it before then!
Oh yeah!
Hiruma gave this to me!
Huh? It's from Hiruma?
What's it say?
The score after the first quarter will be 14-6 Dokubari.
Deimon's only points will be an Eyeshield 21 touchdown right before the quarter ends.
They'll feel pressured and start targeting the quarterback.
Th-This-
It's dead on.
Did he really know how things would play out?
With Hiruma, anything's possible.
N-No way...
Did he vanish on purpose?
YA-HA!
Sorry I'm late.
- Hiruma!
Hiruma, you're finally here!
Hiruma!
Yay, Yocchie's here!
Thank goodness...
The prima donna takes the stage.
Yay, Hiruma! You're safe!
"Safe?" What's that supposed to mean?
H...H-H-H-H-H-How?!
Sure you didn't misread something?
We always believed you'd make it here, Hiruma.
Yup!
Well, losers? Did you learn something today?
You can't win football games if you lose your cool.
The only part that you can let run wild is right here.
Keep your hearts hot and your heads cool.
That's real football!
I see... Hiruma wanted to teach us...
Nice work.
Hey pigtails.
You're okay at mind games,
but what say we make this an IQ match?
B-Bring it! I'll show you!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What do the numbers on the field mean?
It has to do with "10 yards!"
You can stay on offense if you advance 10 yards in four plays.
You repeat that until you reach the goal.
Got it? Ya-ha!
Hey, hey, Hiruma!
What kinda plays are we gonna run?
First we wear this.
Our secret weapon against Dokubari's offense.
Lipstick?
The second quarter begins!
Can Deimon mount a comeback?
U-Umm...
What the heck's up with the makeup?
U-Uh... Well anyways, they look motivated again.
Look closely at their fingers when they line up.
If they're gonna run the ball,
they'll be aiming to rush at top speed,
and they'll focus more weight on their fingertips.
That'll increase the blood flow and make the fingertips redden slightly.
Set, hut, hut!
Deimon's obviously going for a run!
Crush Eyeshield!
They rushed in!
Did they see through a run?
What the- A pass to the monkey?!
Yeah, go!
It worked!
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
Deimon's within two!
Wha... But it was so obvious... All their fingers were so pink...
It worked.
So that's what the lipstick's for...
Sneaky...
You won't get through again!
We'll put our receivers all over the place
so they can't figure out our routes!
Watch their receivers' eyes.
When they look all over the place,
just remember where they looked first.
That's where they'll go.
The first?
Not the last?
When you've got pass routes memorized,
you don't need to look around.
When they look all over the place,
they're trying to take attention away from where they looked first.
If Hiruma's right...
He'll go that way...
Set, hut, hut!
There!
Charge, Eyeshield 21!
Deimon runs an interception in for a touchdown!
And the tide turns!
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 18
Deimon roars back with consecutive touchdowns!
With Hiruma back in the mix, they've taken control of the game.
This is the real Deimon!
How did you know?!
How, indeed?
Now it's our turn.
We'll get them this time!
Figure out who he's passing to!
Whichever receiver he chooses will start acting a little more excited.
That guy's REALLY excited.
He's getting the ball...
It's the tight end!
Whaat?! The monkey again?!
Max Catch!
Touchdown! Deimon scores again!
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 24
That's impossible!
That weirdo's excited posing was just an act?!
You got duped just because we have a natural dunce on the team.
This is hysterical!
They got the worst possible opponents.
You'd have to be insane to take on Hiruma in a psychological battle.
Set!
The enemies' right feet are 5 centimeters further back than normal.
They're getting ready to charge.
It'll be a run!
Right!
Hut, hut!
Oof!
They stopped them again!
Deimon, Deimon, Deimon, Deimon!
Dokubari got this far by reading their opponents' moves,
but they never considered what would happen
if someone turned the tables on them!
Half-baked strategies like that
only work on weak teams that can't hide their quirks.
Enough with the mind-reading!
Dokubari will win the mental battle, period.
Deimon doesn't have a big team.
We'll batter 'em till they run out of energy!
Deimon leads 24-14 as we enter the final quarter!
Oh, you're not going to watch the end?
No... I'll be back later.
Squash that pipsqueak!
Call me whatever you want...
The Deimon Devil Bats
won't lose to a dirty, underhanded team like Dokubari!
Touchdown!
What?! Multiple Devil Bat Ghosts?!
Th-That...
Eyeshield 21... He's evolved again?!
Whoa, killer moves.
Hey, Kakei, check the fake Eyeshield.
Whatever.
A fake is a fake.
Dokubari Scorpions 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 42
Game over! Deimon crushes the competition!
- We did it!
- Yeah!
Hey, Mamo, look!
Right! Now...
...we're in the Best Eight!
Only eight teams left.
Feels like we're really getting there.
Yeah!
This's only the first time I've seen Deimon,
but they don't feel like anything special.
Hey, Kakei, you think we can just chill on the bench for that game,
like in the first round?
Don't be lazy.
There's no more reason to try and keep ourselves a secret.
We need to blast forward, full steam ahead.
Oh yeah... But to be honest...
These guys can't stand up to us.
This is impossible...
A dream... This must be a dream!
That's why you're here!
In real life those two caught you!
It all went according to plan, just like they said on the phone!
There's no way you escaped!
So you admit everything, then.
Those two caught you! It all went according to plan, just like they said on the phone!
You're my slave now!
No, anything but that!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Yay, we're in the Best Eight!
But don't celebrate yet.
Oh no, Komusubi ran away from home!
I'll go look!
At such an important time!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Physique-al Barrier! Ya-ha!
Plan or no plan, how could he disappear before a game?
Hiruma had us all so worried...
He takes everything on himself...
Mamori, you should try and support him more...
As a girlfriend...
Right.
I'll support him as a MANAGER.
W-What? That's what I s-
Say it again! This sounds juicy! Yay, yay!