I should take the handoff like this.
Ahh, perfect!
Hey, dude! Toss that ball over here, would ya?
The ball, the ball!
U-uhh...
I-It slipped!
Th-Thank you...
The BASEBALL!
Do you not see my uniform?!
Pick up the ball on the ground behind you!
S-Sorry about that...
And that's school equipment, isn't it?
You trying to steal it?
No, you see, I just want to get used to carrying the ball,
so I borrowed it to practice-
Forgive me!
Excellent.
That's beautiful!
MAX DEDICATION!
Practicing during school, that's max dedication!
You rock, dude!
N-Nah, it's no big deal...
Yeah, I can see how carrying a rugby ball would be tough if you didn't practice.
Umm, it's an American football...
Look, one-handed!
W-Whoa! And right in the center!
It's a little easier if you hold it on the laces.
Hey! What're you doing, ball boy?! Get the lead out!
Uh-oh!
See ya, rugby dude!
It's football...
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Catching Master!
He caught it so easily...
I definitely need to get used to the ball.
Maybe I should buy my own?
Mamori?
Hi, Sena!
What's with the posters?
Our secret weapon.
You done yet?
Sheesh...
Eyeshield 21
2 Touchdowns on Ojo
The Hero of Notre Dame comes to play for Deimon!
Join me on the field!
Now accepting members!
No way!
We need more real members who practice with us every day.
As it stands now, we won't stand a chance in the fall tournament.
The first thing we need is someone who can catch.
We'll be in big trouble without a receiver to catch your passes.
Catch?
Someone as tall as possible.
Height gives receivers an advantage.
All right, everyone slap these posters up all over school!
Don't we need permission?
Just stick 'em up, you have MY permission.
Oh geez- I got us permission!
I wonder if posters will be enough to get people...
But they're better than nothing.
Guess I should at least ask him.
That's right, until the probability is at 0%, it's too soon to quit!
Strikeout!
I'm still in it! Still got defense!
He can't tag up!
I got it!
Why's he going to left-
Max catch!
Wow!
Run!
Throw it home!
He can't hit OR throw.
He catches well, though.
Deimon plays complete baseball.
We need players who can run, hit, and catch.
Ow ow ow! I'm sorry!
Hey, rugby dude!
You came out to see me, huh?
The football team?
Y-Yes!
Forget it.
I mean, it'd be really lame.
Huh?!
Oh, don't get me wrong, I didn't mean football itself is lame.
I'd never insult someone else's sport.
I meant that it'd be lame of ME if I didn't stay focused on baseball.
I've dedicated my life to catching.
My catching's gonna make me a hero someday.
Be a hero through catching?
You ever heard of the Shuuei Bears' #80, the catching master Masaru Honjo?!
This's one of Honjo's ACTUAL gloves!
He makes the most unreal catches!
Honjo, you're the greatest!
Yikes, the stitch... Okay...
There!
Ever since that day, I've practiced catching like my life depended on it.
So I can be a catching hero, too!
I don't stray from my path. That's just how I live.
Sorry, football dude!
He knows exactly what he wants to accomplish... Good for him.
Just watch... My max effort will get me on the team!
Most of the highlights from football games involve catching!
Say what?!
The heck? If that was me I would've caught it easily...
The girls love him...
No, no! I've gotta-
Unfortunately, due to an accidental collision with Deimon's ace player Eyeshield 21,
Sakuraba had to leave the field.
Eyeshield 21?
I'm so sorry...
Eyeshield 21 has released the following statement:
"Did you catch my Homicide Tackle?"
"Accident schmaccident, I did it on purpose."
"I don't show mercy to people who mess with my run."
"If you don't wanna die, stay outta the way! Ya-ha!"
Is that what Eyeshield's really like?
It was you, Hiruma...
Yup. You get in the enemy's head, you win.
You gotta become their worst nightmare!
Don't worry, no one would take that seriously.
Wow, Eyeshield's a jerk!
Well, who cares about him.
This glove's gonna make me...
...into a catching hero!
Max dedication!
Football clinic!
What position is Hiruma?
The quarterback!
The core of the offense, he chooses the plays, throws the ball, and leads the charge! Ya-Ha!
Did you see that last night?
The football team, you mean?
Who the heck is that Eyeshield 21 guy?!
He's really scary.
He said it was on purpose!
Yeah, that was pretty sweet.
I couldn't believe he went that far!
He's like an evil hero or something.
Everyone's forming these terrible impressions...
Yo, football dude!
Football?!
There's someone from the football team?
G-Good morning...
I saw the game on TV last night!
That Eyeshield 21's a real butthead!
Acting all tough because he injured someone... He should be disciplined!
B-But without him, we'd never have advanced past the first round...
Ooh, yeah, yeah!
The Koigahama game was your first win, huh?
Let's celebrate!
Your first win, and my making first string!
You made first string?!
Err, I dunno yet.
They're posting the team after school! See ya!
I can't see!
Huh...? He's not here yet?
Is this the announcement?
How'd he do?
I never got his name...
Excuse me!
There was a freshman with spiny hair like this who was really good at catching.
You mean him?
Kaminari Montaro?
Third string?
Third string's basically backup for the backup.
They're more like really dedicated fans than actual team members.
Our baseball team had a lot of applicants.
I feel for them, but I can't let everyone make the team.
M-Monta!
You weren't at the club room, I've been looking everywhere-
Oh, my bad, I forgot all about it!
Third string... I really blew it!
Hey, uhh...
I knew making first string right away was too much to hope for...
But man, third string...
Third string doesn't even make the bench, let alone real games.
I won't get to be a catching hero...
Guess my dream's gotta stay a dream...
I never had a shot at being a hero, did I?
Are you... giving up?
I... I really thought you did great!
Risking your body to make those catches, wanting to be a hero, refusing to compromise...
Striving for one goal ever since you were a kid! That's really impressive!
I never really had any goals, myself.
You...
That's why... why you can't give up that easily.
If you keep trying, eventually you'll make second...
No, you'll make first string!
First strong? Me?
I'm sure you can do it, Monta!
Y-Yeah!
If I just keep practicing, they'll want me on the main team someday!
Yeah!
Honjo, I'm sorry for being such a whiner!
I'll try even harder from today on!
It's all yours!
MAX dedication!
Left!
I got it!
You...
Here.
What do you think you're-
Well, I thought I'd be a good third-stringer and pick up the ball for you...
You still don't get it.
Oh, I promise to stay out of the way.
Plus I'm technically a member,
I figure if I work hard then eventually I'll make second string- I mean, first string!
No, it means you're done.
Guys who "make" third string are really being told to quit.
Y-You mean-
The team doesn't want you.
You're cut!
I-I'll be the ball boy, I'll do anything!
Please, I'm begging you!
You're stubborn... Just beat it!
What's up?
You're messing up our practice!
Take a hike!
Get lost!
Back to work, everyone!
M-Monta...
Smother everyone who's tall with tons of posters!
I hope we find a receiver.
Sena, what's wrong?
Is someone pushing you around?
Here it comes.
What?!
Hiruma.
Does a receiver HAVE to be tall?
No, not really...
Is it a problem in football if you're only good at one thing?
No, dingus, it's the opposite.
We WANT people who're only good at one thing.
Everyone's a specialist in football.
Like he's a power guy, and you're...
Even the professional leagues are like that.
S-Sena!
He didn't take any posters...
Hey! Wait up!
Leave me alone!
Stay away from me!
Here.
I'm finished.
They won't even let me be the ball boy...
I'll never play pro baseball!
My catching isn't enough to make me a hero!
Uh, well...
Does it have to be baseball?
We need someone who's good at catching on our team.
How about-
I've dedicated my life to this!
You expect me to just switch to football because I can't hack it at baseball?!
B-But it'd still be catching-
Just go away!
It's over!
I had to wake up from my dream sometime!
All over...
Why?
Why does it have to end?
Why are you just resigning yourself?
There's no reason to give up on everything just because you couldn't play baseball!
Baseball's not the only sport where catching can make you a hero!
You can be a receiving hero, playing football!
I... We...
We need you!
Shut up...
I said leave me alone!
Monta!
Ya-ha! Think fast, monkey boy!
What the heck?!
Eh, too bad, without the drive, you couldn't handle it.
H-He's outstanding! Are you sure?!
Monta.
Shut UP!
He ran off with the ball...
Get ready for another night of Honjo!
Another fine play out at the warning track!
Guys who "make" third string are really being told to quit.
The team doesn't want you.
You're cut!
Great game, Honjo!
I'd say the Bears' win today was thanks solely to your arm, wouldn't you agree?
Oh, of course not.
I'm only the player I am because I have the support of my teammates, because we need each other!
I... We...
We need you!
Masaru Honjo, Shuuei Bears' #80, the catching master...
He and his teammates need each other...
Honjo, forgive me!
I couldn't make it as a baseball player!
But now, for the first time in my life,
there's someone who says his team really wants me to join!
People who say they actually need me!
I'll try to be a catching master for them!
Wait a minute!
Why does Sena have to play receiver at practice?
Because we don't have enough people.
He'll be a receiver or a lineman or whatever I tell him to be.
No way!
Ready! Set, hut, hut!
Too high!
This is how you catch!
Monta!
#80, just like Honjo!
I'm in!
Another teammate!
Really?
Ya-ha!
I'm gonna be a catching hero!
All right, time for a special dish, Cerberus!
Ouch to the max!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
Sena's going to see Sakuraba after injuring him in the last game?!
Apologizing to the max!
I'll go with him, it'll be fine!
If you go it'll just make things more complicated!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Hero's Qualifications! Ya-ha!
I'll patch up your torn pants!
Is something wrong? Hmm?
Mamori... She's considerate to the max!
Hurry up, now.
Come on, Monta.
Umm, my name isn't actually Monta-
What's that, Monta?
Taro Raimon...
Whatever.