ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Fighting to Win!
Even Eyeshield couldn't outrun him...
What's going to happen now?
He's too much.
How can he be so...
And the lead changes hands!
Sakuraba!
I-It's still just a one point lead!
This game just got a lot tougher.
Our chances of winning depended entirely on if that Peewee can beat Shin or not.
Keep at it! It's only one point!
Set, hut!
Turnover!
There.
Takami is superior, as always.
He's already got a grasp on Eyeshield's speed...
He won't throw another pass that Eyeshield can cut off.
Superior my butt.
He doesn't have to throw any risky long passes, that's it.
All he needs to do is string together short passes and runs.
They'll advance and eat up the clock at the same time.
Touchdown!
It's the 2nd quarter, do your best everyone!
A 22 point lead...
Seven minutes left in the 2nd quarter.
The pass to Eyeshield's complete!
Go, Eyeshield!
It hurts...
Against Shin, Eyeshield's...
Like a scrap of paper.
Halftime! The score is Ojo 35, Deimon 6!
It's finally over...
No more...
It hurts too much!
If I hadn't been wearing pads, he might've broken my bones!
Ow!
No more.
I'm just gonna get tackled again anyway.
I don't like hurting.
If you had given it the first time I asked, you wouldn't have gotten hurt!
Too bad Mamori's not here to save you again.
If you tattle on us, I'll really beat you up!
I don't wanna get hurt!
Mamori was right... I'm not cut out for this!
Everyone... I'm sorry!
The Knights have a huge lead after the first half, thanks to Sakuraba's athletic prowess!
Let's see... I caught one pass, missed one, and let one get cut off...
You lazy slackers!
Were you asleep out there?
Letting yourselves be blocked by novices...!
And our first possession... Sakuraba!
I don't ever want to see you bobble the ball like that again!
He remembered...
What's this thing?!
Err... Excuse me... That's a sticker from his sponsor...
Don't insult the equipment with this garbage!
No, no, no, no, no... You see-
This kind of carelessness is what leads to injuries!
How do you expect to beat our opponents when you can't even protect yourself?!
M-Mr. President?
Slip this one on before you go back out there.
I can't-
Sakuraba...
If Jari Productions loses its contract with American Burger, we'll be out 30 million yen.
Will you be able to cover that loss?
Do you understand? Football is the game, and this is your job.
A game?!
That's my last sticker. Do NOT lose it.
I'm very busy and had to leave. Eyeshield 21.
Oh, welcome back.
You sure went a long way to get those tapes, huh?
Huh? Where's Eyeshield?
I just passed by him, he kinda seemed like he might possibly have been leaving.
Huh? HUH?
Well, I can understand.
Eyeshield has been taking Shin on this whole time,
while we've been completely useless,
even though we're supposed to be blocking for him.
He must be mad at us for getting in the way all the time.
Probably thinks, "I can't play with these people."
Maybe he's abandoned us...
N-No, that's not it!
Err, rather... I don't think it is.
I mean, we've all been trying our hardest.
It's not just me.
Everyone's putting their bodies on the line out there.
A 29 point difference at the half...
I guess the tournament's over for us, huh?
We've still got a shot.
About a 0.1% one, but...
0.1%...
It's enough. Until our chances are at 0%, it's too soon to give up.
Compared to last year's 99-0 game, we're definitely a lot better.
And we have Eyeshield this year, too.
Even though they're beating us, I'm still ready to play.
You said it.
Now last year, I would've been ready to give up.
But if Eyeshield's not playing the second half...
That manga...
Mamori bought it for me...
In the end, I lied and said I lost it.
Enough.
I have to stop running from pain.
I won't give up until it's all over.
No matter how badly it hurts.
It's almost time for the second half to begin.
I'm sure we're all excited to see Sakuraba play again!
You're late!
You didn't leave?
Sorry, the bathroom was really crowded!
That's it? You had us scared there!
We thought you went home!
Yeah, there's still 30 minutes left.
My chances of getting by Shin aren't zero yet.
Went to buy batteries.
Again?!
Football Clinic!
What is a "huddle?"
A meeting where the players plan their next move!
You've only 25 seconds to huddle up, so hurry up and pick a play! Ya-ha!
All right, group around Eyeshield 21.
Then it's up to your legs to score us some touchdowns.
No matter how hard we get hit, we all have to shield Eyeshield!
No matter how Deimon moves, Shin will crush them.
Set, hut, hut!
I'll give it everything I've got.
It's useless.
Wh-?!
The Spear Tackle again!
Man, he felt that!
Are you okay, Sena-?
He didn't break your back, did he?
I've figured one thing out.
Even if he's too far to tackle, Shin stretches his arm out at the last second,
and it feels like he's thrusting a spear at you.
Normally you'd be able to get through, but Shin has the strength to stop runners one-handed.
I need to get all the way out of his reach...
This is tough...
I won't give up... Just a little further.
Touchdown!
Two minutes left in the 3rd quarter, and it's 49-6!
Nothing less from Sakuraba's team!
This is bad.
At this rate, we've gotta score before the last 4:50 of the 4th quarter.
Still no good...
Just a little more...
Spin.
If you can't dodge to the side, spin past him.
Spin?
Yup.
R-Right!
If I can't dodge to the side...
So close!
He almost made it!
So close... Just a little further...
Eyeshield has been playing both offense and defense... With so much anaerobic exercise...
...his muscles must be on fire from lactic acid buildup.
Anaerobic? Lactic acid? That means he's wiped out, right?
Yes. And yet...
Little by little...
He's getting faster!
Eyeshield 21 earned his reputation as the "Lightspeed Running Back" at Notre Dame.
Let me make one thing clear here.
He's faster than you.
Save your breath.
We don't let taunts get to us.
Kurita's stronger than you.
WHAT?!
I'll smash him!
Hey, Peewee.
You're not gonna be able to block their passes anymore.
Hit the bench while we're on D so you can focus on offense!
Okay.
Umm, Eyeshield?
Why don't you take off that helmet and towel off?
And you need to stay hydrated!
I-I'm fine.
Oh, don't say that-
No! I'm fine.
D-During games, I prefer to stay focused on the field.
Oh... Just call if you need me, then.
Just a little more...
Hut!
Target: Sakuraba.
The line's fallen!
Changing target!
Touchdown!
Shoot... I couldn't break away, again...
Argh!
It's okay, we still scored.
50 points down... Even six touchdowns won't be enough.
4:45 left to go... Game's over.
Oh, we're on offense again!
All right!
You guys can do whatever you want from here on. I'm outta here.
We still had a billionth of a chance up until a second ago.
But now it's zero.
They're just gonna run the clock down for the rest of the game.
We've gotta do our best all the way to the end!
So people will praise you for sticking it out?
So we can pat ourselves on the back for trying, even though we lost?
No, but... there's still meaning in trying, you know...
I play to win.
Putting forth effort when there's no chance of winning is pointless.
Hiruma!
Isn't the captain supposed to stay in the game until the end, even if there's no hope left?
Who's gonna play quarterback, then?
But without Hiruma...
After all that effort to recruit extra members...
I'm not giving up.
A little more... Just a little more...
What'd I just say?
Fighting until the end-
I can get past him.
Umm, I mean... I might possibly... be able to get past Shin.
A little longer... Just a little longer...
You wanna beat Shin?
Oh, nothing like that, I just thought with a little more time, I might have a chance...
Quit babbling like an idiot!
Do you wanna beat him or not?!
I-I do!
I'm so close...
That's why... I don't want to quit yet!
Okay. Huddle up!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
YAY! The game against the Ojo White Knights reaches its climax!
Sena bets everything on one last play!
It's not over. I still have time!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Never Quit!
YA-HA!
Where the heck did Sena go to get batteries?
Geez...