Set!
W-W-Wait a second!
There's no way on earth this will actually work!
Ow...
No more...
Come on, Sena! I'm working hard too!
Together we're practically a clone of Mizumachi!
Let's go, Komusubi!
Hut!
I told you this wouldn't work.
I guess we're missing something...
I really thought I was on to something.
C'mon, c'mon!
I have to get to sumo practice or they'll get mad...
Clam it! We got you juice, didn't we?
I didn't think you'd put me through anything like this!
You know, when the lines collide,
if you're even a bit slower than the other guy you get nailed.
Even if you're tall...
Actually, you'd think tall people would be thrown off balance easily.
It's all about the charge.
Charge!
That's right! If you attack before he gets going...
His height, speed, and special moves won't mean squat!
He'll go flying!
Charging...
I hate this, but the juice is so yummy...
Sumo!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
Toss him out! The Honorable Komusubi!
You want me to teach you sumo techniques?
Please.
No.
Why not?!
Because it's too much trouble.
I don't wanna do anything I don't have to.
I'm only human, after all.
Pretty please?
No way. It's too much trouble.
We'll treat you to some mango pudding.
M-Mango pudding?
My groin's gonna rip!
Endure it.
Persevere.
Perseverance, endurance!
Man, this is tougher than it looks, huh Sena?
My thighs feel like they've been ripped apart.
Next is pole striking, give it a try.
Perseverance, endurance!
Or is it time to go get my pudding?
Just let us rest for another minute.
Yeah.
Keep your arms close to your sides and strike higher!
Komusubi's doing great.
Hope he's not seriously considering switching to sumo.
He really wants to beat Mizumachi.
True, true.
Perseverance, endurance!
Okay, this looks like a good spot for a break!
I'm in!
What's up, guys?
Otawara?
You guys quit football and join the sumo team or something?
Oh no, we're on a secret training regimen for the Poseidons game.
Huh? Secret training?
All right, I'll take you guys on!
Let's go, all three of you, right now!
Whatsamatter, scared?
You ready?
Take your stance...
Komusubi...
Begin!
Push, push! Try to take me down!
Are you okay?
Maybe the initial charge isn't the key after all...
Oh, so that's why you started studying sumo?
Yes...
I wouldn't say you guys have the wrong idea.
But you tossed Komusubi aside like he was nothing.
You have it good, Otawara. You're tall AND built.
And strong.
Size and power aren't always enough to be a good defender.
The most important thing is heart.
If the front line loses its spirit, so will the rest of the team.
Hunh...
Even though I never actually get to carry the ball,
I'm part of a team, and I want everyone on it to play their best.
Kurita said the same thing once.
Boy, you're a lot more insightful than you look Otawara, I'm surprised.
Surprised? Whatta ya mean, surprised?
Oh, uh, my bad.
You wanna know a secret?
No matter how big your opponent is, you'll never lose
if you can figure out how to turn his own strength against him.
Turn your opponent's strength against him?
How do you actually do that?
You'll have to figure that out yourselves.
'Cause I gotta fart!
See ya!
How do you use your opponent's strength against him?
I got it!
- What?
That!
"That?"
What?
Yo!
Huh? Where's Komusubi?
I don't think he's coming to practice today.
Why not?
It's almost time for the quarter finals.
Is he sick or something?
Oh, no...
He's doing secret training.
What kind of secret training?
I have no idea.
What's with this mountain of dumbbells?
Komusubi, he...
Komusubi?
Where is he?
What are you doing down there?
Isn't that gonna make him even shorter?
What's he doing?
He's trying to learn how to turn someone's strength against them.
I think.
Need a favor!
No, that's too much trouble.
I don't wanna do anything I don't have to.
I'm only human, after all.
Please, Komusubi really wants to see if his training paid off!
You sure you won't wrestle him?
We'll treat you to mango pudding again.
M-Mango pudding?
Then he should try his hand at the real thing.
They just happen to be holding an event this weekend.
"Deimon Shopping Arcade Sumo Tournament?"
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to throw the ball!
The trick is in the arm motion!
You need to move your arm as straight as possible when throwing a pass.
Everyone get that? Ya-ha!
Dosskoi!
Hooray, hooray, Deimon shorties!
Shorties...
I guess we're entering, too...
Might as well see what we can do, right?
As backs, we need to react quickly before we smash into someone!
The Deimon Shopping Arcade Sumo Tournament is officially underway!
There's no excuse not to be excited as these magnificent specimens
show off their strength and let their powerful hips run wild!
Our winner today will receive 10,000 yen's worth of leftov...
Err, high grade fireworks!
Ooh, those look awesome! Go get 'em, guys!
I can see how that was a leftover...
I kinda wanna set it off, though...
Here are the brackets...
Whoa, who got this crazy seed?!
Last year's champ.
To win the tournament,
you'll have to go through our reigning seven-time champ!
From Ojo High School...
Ojo?
Makoto Otawara!
Otawara?!
You guys came, too?
Is it really a good idea to be sumo wrestling
the day before your quarter-final game?
You're in the same boat as us!
Come to get even with me for tossing you around, huh?
If you want a piece of me, you'll have to make it to the final round!
I already feel like I'm being crushed...
It's even worse than when he's on the field, huh?
Let's get the first round underway!
First, from Deimon High School, Sena Kobayakawa!
And his classmate, Montaro Kaminari?
It's Taro Raimon!
Okay, Sena, time to let loose!
Who should I cheer for?
Good luck, guys!
In position...
Take your stance...
Begin!
Dosskoi!
He vanished?
Not bad-
Awesome!
Amazing!
He's always been great at side-stepping.
That's the match!
Huh?
I stepped out...
Oh, Sena...
Your legs really don't work for a lot of sports, huh?
Good thing you picked football.
Take your stance... Begin!
Way to go, Komusubi!
Great charge!
I wouldn't have had to come out here
if they hadn't tempted me with mango pudding...
Going home's so much trouble... I'm only human.
Hey, kid!
You've got the physique of a sumo wrestler, do you wrestle?
Huh? Oh, yeah...
You've gotta change into your mawashi right away or they'll disqualify you!
Wait, no...
Why do these things happen to me... What a pain.
It's clobberin' time.
Omosadake...
What a rough opponent...
I don't wanna wrestle someone this good... I'm only human.
Take your stance... Begin!
- Omosadake!
H-He's so strong...
I'd say he's a genetic freak.
It doesn't seem like there's any way to counter that much bulk.
I wonder if Omosadake's okay.
You don't have time to worry about him, you know?
You're Otawara's next opponent.
Depressing to the max...
- Good luck!
Go for it, Monta!
Take your stance...
Begin!
I've only got one option!
Max charge!
Wait, I changed my mind-!
- Monta!
Ow...
Take your stance... Begin!
Hooray, hooray, Komusubi!
Komusubi advances to the finals!
The long road is finally over, and the tournament's final match is here!
Komusubi, at a mere 150 centimeters, has overcome his height handicap,
but can he tear down the impenetrable wall that IS Otawara?!
Man, he's so much bigger!
Is he gonna survive?
How can Komusubi...
Let's see the results of your training!
We wanna see your new move, Komusubi!
Pretend Otawara is Mizumachi and send him flying!
Komusubuddy!
You can do it!
Take your stance...
I can tell you're fired up.
You really gonna try and beat me?
I dunno what kinda practice you've been doing,
but it's not gonna be enough to move me an inch!
Begin!
Whoa, not so fast! I want those fireworks!
Oh no, he's gonna use his power to push him from above!
Run for it, Komusubi!
Oh my!
The tiny 150 centimeters Komusubi has lifted the invincible Otawara over his head!
That pose...
That's what he's been practicing this whole time?!
- Go!
- Get him!
Use your opponent's strength...
...against...
...him!
He's thrown him!
What the-?!
- Yes! He won!
Oh, but the invincible wall stands solid!
A splendid recovery by Otawara!
Not bad at all!
I'm impressed that you made such good use of my advice so fast!
But I'm not giving up those awesome fireworks!
That's the match!
We already have our winner.
Well, this is unexpected.
The winner is decided by... nudity!
You did it!
That ruled!
Congratulations.
You're really cool, Komusubuddy!
Komusubi's living proof...
Even if you're short, or small,
you can face anyone on even ground if you just work hard enough!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
What? Sena fell for the Poseidon's taunts and is going one-on-one with Kakei?
Kakei's gonna show him why he's only a fake Eyeshield!
He'd better not run, either!
Interesting!
Let's see some guts, pipsqueaks!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Man Who Remembers #21! Ya-ha!
I got full of myself and said, "I swear to bring him back..."
I can't return empty-handed...
Komusubi... where are you? Where?
Komusubi!
I can't believe you're out here!
We were so worried!
Komusubi... where are you...?