Eyeshield 21
- Ya-ha!
- Oh!
It's all thanks to the terrifying Ballista, to the terrifying strength of Seijuro Shin!
I'll tell you in advance this time, too.
We're firing the Ballista to the right.
They're using the Ballista...
...on the right?
Another advance warning!
Cool!
Takami's got an evil side!
Look, he shifted his glasses like a movie villain!
Did Takami turn to the dark side like Yocchie?
Maybe...
Maybe this is all part of a bigger, grander plan.
W-What's the plan, Hiruma?
We can't defend against this.
Don't wet your pants just yet!
No matter how fast someone throws a pitch,
if you know its trajectory,
you can knock it right back at the pitcher.
I guess if you know its course...
Theoretically...
But he's mad strong.
We've just gotta believe.
In ourselves, and each other.
In the end, that's really what football's all about.
And that's what got us this far, didn't it?
Believe in ourselves...
...and each other.
That's right! We need to trust our individual strengths!
No point in thinking too hard.
Yeah, we just gotta do it!
Yeah!
Don't forget that God's blessed us with my presence, too!
Yay! Everyone's motivated again.
Yeah!
Musashi always knows what to say in situations like this.
The truth is, his little announcement is meaningless.
We don't actually know if they'll come straight at us or not.
Now, why would that stinkin' Four-Eyes take the time to explain the Ballista in detail?
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Impregnable Fortress.
Takami.
Why are you telling them our plays?
Because I might be lying.
Hiruma's not stupid enough to take me at face value.
Either way, they have no counter-play.
You're not Shin, I know you don't play things straight.
But you sure are confident when it comes to the Ballista, aren't you?
Will Ojo run the Ballista to the right as promised?
That's what they want us to think, they might run to the left!
Or THAT could be the trick, and they ARE going right! Or-
Or THAT could be the REAL trick and they're going left after all!
What a complex strategy!
Riko, you've transformed again.
I'm too excited, I can't go back!
Riko...
Set, hut...
Are they gonna go right?
Or maybe...
Gotta stop them... either side, I have to stop them!
Hut!
Shin does as Takami said!
He's off to the right!
I, the easygoing prodigy, will stop him!
How can this be...?
What's it gonna be,
Four-Eyes?
When are you gonna move?
Hiruma...
You and I are a lot alike.
No matter how hard we work, we'll never come anywhere close to supermen like Shin.
You're not getting through!
So to cover for our lack of athletic ability, we use every dirty trick in the book!
Takami runs the ball to the left himself!
It's a QB scramble!
What?
That slowpoke Takami's running the ball?
Well, I saw that one coming.
You did?
Shoot, Shin and Nekoyama tricked us!
He's all alone over there!
Stop him!
What?
That line's set up to block our view of a pass!
It's a trap!
Sakuraba?!
Sakuraba's running down the left side!
Fly, Sakuraba!
There goes the Everest Pass!
Here it comes!
No one else could reach a ball that high...
Ojo could never pull it off without Sakuraba.
He explained their play... Shin charged through the right side...
The real plan was the Everest Pass!
Get him, Mon-Mon!
But Sakuraba's 40-yard dash time is 4.86 seconds.
Monta's is 5.0!
You mean there's no chance he'll catch up?
Even a 0.14 second difference makes a huge difference out there!
Man...
I can't catch him!
Being shorter than him is one thing...
...but now I'm slower, too?!
Keep running, Monta!
Flatten Sakuraba!
Sakuraba!
Fight on, Sakuraba!
Whoo! You're the number one receiver, Sakuraba!
Go, Sakuraba!
No, no! Crap!
Don't give up!
It's not over till it's over!
He's right! Watching Honjo taught me...
...never to give up no matter who you're up against!
What?!
He's catching up!
Yay! Go, Mon-Mon!
Monta!
I'm not gonna make it!
Sakuraba's in perfect position!
Yes, this is it!
Ya-ha!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How many different kinds of face masks are there?
Each position is different, huh?
Each player can choose from different face masks depending on his position.
There are over 50 different types!
Pick the right one for YOU! Ya-ha!
Ya-ha!
It's a demon!
Hiruma?!
How'd Hiruma get there?!
I figured your play out.
It's Hiruma!
He's right on top of Sakuraba, preventing him from jumping!
Beautiful!
Hiruma predicted exactly where Takami's Everest Pass was headed!
And now Monta's coming from behind, with Hiruma on the other side!
Sakuraba is surrounded!
In Sakuraba, Mr. Takami finally found a performer
who could help him use his height, and created the Everest Pass...
That was the melody he wanted to play this time.
An emotional performance that would leave his opponents in tears.
And of course, Yoichi Hiruma caught on and saw through it.
Your ego's getting the better of you, Four-Eyes!
Winning's all that matters, it doesn't matter HOW you do it!
You're right, I got soft. I guess I don't think as clearly as you.
What-?!
The ball!
It's going...
...out of bounds!
I'm impressed, Hiruma.
I didn't think anyone would figure out it was an Everest Pass.
But the airspace out of bounds...
What?!
...is Sakuraba's fortress, a place even you can't penetrate!
Catch it, Sakuraba!
Catch it and show Raimon how far above him you really are!
Wha-?!
Wha-?! No way, you can't catch a pass out of bounds!
He's already past the sideline!
When he lands they'll call the pass incomplete!
Gotta touch the field!
If I can touch one toe...
I WILL make it!
Yes! Do it, Sakuraba!
Touchdown!
The Everest Pass is complete, and the Ojo White Knights score an incredible touchdown!
All right! Sakuraba's the best receiver in the whole world!
Sakuraba!
Unbelievable...
He was so far out...
How can this be?!
Yoichi Hiruma saw through everything,
yet Takami and Sakuraba's faith in each other proved superior.
How did he catch that?
He's tall as heck...
His legs are long...
And compared to M-
I know, I know.
You don't have to say it, I know I don't stack up.
Monta...
Ojo White Knights 6 - Deimon Devil Bats 3
It's 6-3!
With Ojo's touchdown, the Ojo White Knights take the lead back from the Deimon Devil Bats!
Shin rules the ground, and Sakuraba rules the air.
No Ojo team in history has ever been blessed...
...with a pair like them.
Now you've seen the new Ojo offense.
Sure, putting Shin on both sides of the field increases the pressure,
but I'll take him over that untouchable Everest Pass you and Sakuraba have going on.
The Everest Pass is what makes the Ballista so devastating.
The combination, the ability to switch between them at will,
THAT is why our offense is now complete.
Sakuraba is 186 centimeters tall...
...and Monta is 155 centimeters.
Monta - Sakuraba
And Saku's faster, too...
Dude... What do we do?
Sakuraba's height's a problem.
No one on Deimon even comes close.
Height, vertical leap...
How do I beat him?
How?!
Sena...
It's all good.
But I'm...
You're awesome.
I thought he got away from you, but you really closed the gap at the last second!
Sure, you're not as tall or fast as him,
but you stuck it out to the end, like you always do.
Sena...
I know Shin's just as fast as me,
but I'll keep fighting with my own weapons, just like you.
Yeah! Let's get 'em, Sena!
They've gotten pretty reliable, too.
Let's get this extra point, too!
Excellent, Takami.
Stay focused until your job is finished,
and keep widening the point gap!
Ojo lines up for the extra point.
They're sure to kick it for the guaranteed point.
Ojo may have fallen behind early, but can they take the lead
and turn it into another blowout victory over Deimon?
They don't have anyone like Musashi, they might not make the kick!
Here comes the kick!
Hiruma and Musashi aren't the only veterans...
I'm here, too!
Kurita!
M-Master!
What the-?!
He jumped?!
He tipped it!
Kurita!
The kick is no good!
The mammoth, 145 kilogram Kurita, flew through the air!
Even long-dormant volcanoes can erupt!
And that... that was...
An Eruption Jump!
Master! So cool!
Kurita got us!
K-Kurita actually jumped...
Unbelievable...
He jumped almost 30 centimeters!
Almost as high as the Poseidon's High Wave!
Heck, that might've been even higher!
He's just as tall as Otawara at 195 centimeters,
and with that 30 centimeters jump he towered over the line!
You average kicker could never break through!
He's not just fat, he's BIG and fat!
Wow, you gotta respect Kuriton's size, huh?
There's more to it...
He was able to jump that 30 centimeters because...
He's been doing squats, day in and day out.
The first time he barely squeaked out 20,
his legs gave out and he bawled like a baby.
Kurita's legs and hips
were very weak compared to his upper body.
That's why I made him do squats.
These days he can bang out 2000 without missing a beat.
Whoa... all that training and effort for one 30 centimeters jump...
It wasn't just that...
It came from the effort those three have put into making the Devil Bats a real team.
Their friendship made the wall a little bit taller.
Deimon's kicking power outclasses ours.
Gen Takekura will guarantee Deimon a full seven points with every touchdown.
Then we won't let them score a single one.
We'll stay in the lead until the final whistle blows,
and counter Yoichi Hiruma's tricks by not giving them a chance to rest.
For my part, I will take out...
...Eyeshield 21!
The enemy's about to advance.
Both teams are poised to strike.
This incredible showdown, Deimon vs. Ojo,
currently stands at 6-3 Ojo!
As the rain starts pouring down,
the Deimon Devil Bats begin their counter attack!
Set,
hut hut!
Ojo's blitzing!
In a risky defense, Ojo abandons the backfield!
Shin rushes in to tackle Hiruma before he can pass!
Shin's blitzing!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Just when Kurita finally stopped them...
Now that Shin has your speed, he's become an invincible monster!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Superman!
Ya-ha!
Man, Kurita's Eruption Jump was something else.
I always thought he was just a big fat guy.
Yeah, until he blocked a kick.
I have an idea, a way to stop Sakuraba!
You serious, Sena? What is it?
Okay!
We have Kurita cover Sakuraba!
That could work!
Nice idea!
Nice, Sena!
We've got our anti-Sakuraba plan!
That's impossible.
His stubby legs would never catch him.
It's so easy to tell who on our team is smart and who's an idiot, huh?
So many idiots...