- Fire!
- Ya-ha!
The Seibu Wild Gunmen break through Deimon's openings
and add another seven points!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Seibu Wild Gunmen 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Will those seven points determine the winner?
A 15 point lead...
Deimon can stay in this if they keep their spirits up,
but that's much easier said than done.
Deimon vs. Seibu...
The receivers...
The line...
The running backs...
Even the quarterbacks...
Seibu outclasses Deimon in every aspect.
I expect seeing Hiruma outsmarted hurt much more than the touchdown.
What do we do, Hiruma?
At this rate...
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Musashi is Right Here.
What's our next move?
What do we try now, Hiruma?
Hiruma?
Hey, don't you have anything to tell us?
I guess even Hiruma's gotta admit...
...there's nothing we can do, huh?
Having seen such a clever play fail,
Deimon's only remaining alternative is a straight,
head-to-head game.
But...
Is he giving up?
Hiruma...
But we all promised...
We're in high school now, but it's still just the three of us...
No problem.
Even if it's only before games,
we'll use Cerberus to force people to play on our team.
Sorry I'm late!
What's up with those clothes, Musashi?
Well, I rushed over here,
so I didn't have time to change outta my work clothes.
My dad's getting too old for carpentry.
I give him a hand at his job sites sometimes.
The tournament's just around the corner.
Relax.
I'll do my job.
We made a promise back in middle school.
The three of us are going to the Christmas Bowl.
The THREE of us promised...
This is the first round of the spring tournament!
The Deimon Devil Bats can come back if they make this field goal!
Musashi! It's only 45 yards!
That's not impossible.
You could make it from 55.
Gen!
Tamahachi?
Your father just collapsed!
He passed out while he was working and fell off a beam!
You gotta hurry!
Right, I'm coming-
I'm sorry...
I have to make this kick first...
What're you saying, Gen?
Your dad might be dying.
He could go any minute.
But I'm the only one... who can kick...
Get going, you old fart!
Your concentration's all messed up now, you'll never make it.
You'd just mess this up.
I'm sorry!
Musashi...
Hey, Hiruma, he'll be back soon, right?
Musashi never came back...
We still can't make it without you!
Please, please come back, Musashi!
Kurita...
Gen, if you're going to visit your dad,
I'll come with you.
It's okay, Tamahachi.
You need your afternoon break.
Tama honey, you forgot your lunch.
Here!
Geez, you didn't have to come all the way out here.
What if you'd fallen down or something?
But I made it just for you!
Please, give us a break!
Our owner's suffering a medical problem,
which is why construction has been delayed.
We just need a small extension on this month's bill.
If he's out of commission,
then Tamahachi and the other employees will lose their jobs...
The only thing I can do is try to take my dad's place in the company.
Huh?! You're dropping out?!
M-Musashi...
Takekura Construction's got nothing to worry about.
The principal will provide all the assistance you need.
You think my dad and the others would take dirty money?
If I take over,
my stupid dad won't be so stressed and he'll get better.
That's all there is to it.
You're sure...
...there's no other way?
No other way.
There's just one second
left in the half.
We're out of time.
If they don't score at least once more this half,
Deimon can't win.
They need to close the gap in one second...
The only chance of that is a field goal.
Agreed, but Deimon doesn't have a kicker.
We're still so far from the end zone...
Wait.
You aren't planning to kick it yourself, are you?
You have a better idea?
45 yards...
That's way too far.
Musashi...
Why...
Why can't Musashi be here?
That kick tee...
Don't touch it.
That's Musashi's.
Musashi's...
Hiruma...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to catch a short pass!
The hint is "distance."
Shake off your opponent,
put some distance between yourselves and catch the ball.
Get the lead out!
Ya-ha!
This will be the Deimon Devil Bats' final play this half!
If they make this kick,
they'll keep their chances for a second-half comeback alive.
This kick could spell victory or defeat for Deimon.
But from that far away,
Hiruma's inaccurate power kicks won't even come close to the goalposts.
The probability he'll miss is 99%.
Hiruma...
Musashi!
That's right!
Musashi hasn't gone anywhere.
Musashi is right here!
So high!
And it's actually going straight for the uprights!
Go!
Go in!
No good!
Deimon can't score!
And that's the half.
Hiruma...
Everyone, don't let it get you down!
We've still got the second half!
Yeah, yeah, cheer up!
Hiruma...
Yocchie...
No way...
Yocchie's crying...?
Hiruma, Musashi is still with us.
He's fighting alongside us!
I'm sorry, Hiruma!
I was the one who started giving up.
But I...WE need to make up for Musashi until he comes back!
We're still in this!
Come on, Hiruma!
He's right, Hiruma!
Hiruma!
A laptop?!
Hiruma you weren't crying?!
Eyeshield!
What the heck happened in the first half?!
Don't let a worthless hack like him take the ball!
I-I'm so sorry!
And you, Fatty!
Stop whining like a baby!
O-Okay!
Eyeshield and Fatty
are the keys to our plan for the second half.
If we go with this plan,
we'll put 'em through the wringer.
Now, can you guarantee he won't get the ball from you again?
What do you think is the difference between us?
It's pride.
"I won't let anyone defeat me."
Only those with that level of pride...
...can sacrifice themselves to protect the ball.
It's all for the ball!
Yes!
The play's name is...
"Blast!"
Deimon will start the second half on offense.
Down an overwhelming 15 points,
what amazing secret play will they pull out next?
They'll keep pushing!
Shoot 'em down!
15 points isn't enough to call this a game.
I mean, that one over there hasn't given up even for a second.
I assume, anyway.
Sends a chill up my spine.
Set...
Hut!
We can't go to the Christmas Bowl with Musashi if we lose!
A straight charge up the middle?
Kurita's a one-man phalanx forcing open a path for Eyeshield!
Deimon, four yard gain!
Huh? Just four yards?
That's not very Deimonesque.
Where's the one big play?
Deimon advances five yards!
Kurita charges up the middle again!
How're they gonna make a big gain with such short runs?
Are they just gonna creep forward?
How come they're happy with such a slow pace?
Perfect.
I'm ready for more!
Check out Kurita's aura?
Master!
It's just steam...
Looks like something lit a fire under Kurita.
A freight train couldn't stop him now.
Hey, are we just gonna let him hog the spotlight the whole time?
Of course we're not.
We can't let this continue any longer.
I'll show you, Ushijima.
Dual Horn!
It's gonna be a little different from the straight blocking Doburoku taught us.
But if you think about it, if he wants...
...to go head to head with three veteran street fighters...
...he's going all kinds of down.
You nerf herders.
Go ahead and try, nothing's gonna change!
Set, hut!
Eat this! Dual Horn!
What?!
We don't let anyone throw us around!
We're gonna pay you back-
-a million times over!
- Go!
Deimon, four yard gain!
Deimon, six yard gain!
First down Deimon!
Deimon, 16 yard gain!
Deimon's kicking butt!
Seibu can't stop their brute force rush!
Did Hiruma's missed kick get them motivated again?
Results aren't always everything.
Sometimes the act of trying is enough to show people the light.
Awesome...
With Kurita smashing through the walls...
Yard by yard, inch by inch...
We're getting closer and closer to the goal!
Someone stop Kurita!
Yeah, I admit it's pretty nuts.
The Blast isn't really what you'd call a "plan."
Fatty's just using his bulk and power
to break your wall down!
Go!
BLAST!
Yay! Kuriton's blowing them up!
Wow!
Deimon's slow and steady Blast plan has beaten back the Seibu Wild Gunmen
and taken the Devil Bats centimeters from the goal!
All right, line-girls, we're not even a ball length from the goal.
Take them out!
Match his power! Push him back!
Don't let them one step forward!
I'll show you my pride!
Fly!
What? He jumped?!
I won't...
...let anyone defeat me!
The Devil Bat Dive!
Eyeshield takes flight!
Touchdown, Deimon!
We did it!
This time... he protected the ball instead of himself.
Deimon closes the gap to nine points!
Remember!
We need two more touchdowns to turn this around!
Fight like your lives depend on it!
Got it?!
- Yeah!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Yay! The Devil Bats are fighting back!
Oh? Seibu's arguing about something.
Riku's being benched? Why?
I dunno, but this is your big chance!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Demonic Counterattack! Ya-ha!
Dad?!
Oh, Gen.
I was just saying a little prayer for your father.
I-I see...
If he doesn't recover, I'll curse him!