Ya-ha!
Eyeshield 21
Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Ya-ha!
- Oh!
Max-
Catch!
Raimon makes catch after catch!
Super catches coming from any and all directions!
Rock on!
Ace receiver!
Nice catch!
Taro Raimon...
Even without any real knowledge of our defense,
he's catching all those passes...
What are you kids doing? Double the defense on #80!
Don't leave Raimon alone!
Takami, put me in on defense, too!
No.
Takami!
You're going to be our key to victory in the second half, Sakuraba.
But-
I understand how you feel, but I can't afford to waste your stamina.
Thank you all to the max!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Knight who Controls the Skies.
Okay, ladies.
We've gotta strike while Ojo's defense is still softened up!
- Right!
What's this? Deimon is playing Yukimitsu early!
Yuki...
We're all counting on you!
Right!
Yukimitsu lacks stamina... for Deimon to be using him at this stage...
They're being forced to use their best weapons, perhaps?
They're adding another receiver.
Why would they use Yukimitsu now?
What're you planning, Hiruma?
Why, this formation is...
The shotgun - everyone except the linemen are positioned as receivers!
This is the Seibu Wild Gunmen's trademark play!
Shotgun shmotgun, we'll just squash 'em all!
There's no mimicry going on here!
No one can imitate HIRUMA'S shotguns!
YA-HA!
Very true...
If they're using the shotgun...
It doesn't matter. We'll put a defender on all their receivers.
Ojo's ramparts will hold back the enemy.
We're gonna stick with the Butt-Monkey.
Ojo will have a defender on every one of you.
That's why we go with Butt-Monkey. The rest of you are decoys!
I'm so pumped I'm shaking.
I'll catch whatever you throw at me!
Then let's not give 'em any more time to think!
Set hut!
Charge, losers!
Okay!
Max pass routes!
All their receivers are off, but who knows who Hiruma will target!
We can do this!
But Deimon's shotgun blast doesn't even faze the Ojo White Knights!
Every receiver has a defender on their tail!
Nothing less from Ojo's defense!
We're all covered... but... just keep going, Monta!
You won't get past me, Eyeshield.
Only Iguchi's on Raimon...
One-on-one...?
He's a decoy!
You took too long!
That's the Devil Laser Bullet!
A long pass to Monta right up the sideline!
This was Hiruma's plan?
But with the timing, Iguchi's height will shut Raimon down.
Iguchi moves to intercept!
Snatching the ball out of midair is one of the biggest plays you can make!
- Good!
- He's got it!
No, he doesn't!
He's no Ikkyu! You can get it, Butt-Monkey!
What the-?
Monta!
What the heck...
How can he have such a strong grip when the ball's been in the rain this whole time?!
Max Catch!
Deimon's pass is complete!
- Monta!
Monta!
You rock, Mon-Mon!
Go, Deimon!
You jump like a real monkey!
Yay, monkey-boy!
The Deimon Devil Bats are now 40 yards from the goal!
Deimon's powerful offense is overcoming Ojo's defense!
That was incredible, Monta!
I knew you'd make the catch!
It wasn't quite as good as I could have done it, though!
You're embarrassing me, guys!
In that situation, against Iguchi, the odds were 6-4 in your favor, Butt-Monkey.
Not a sure thing, but good odds nonetheless.
But we needed to take the shot before they send HIM out.
"Him...?"
Sakuraba...
Sakuraba...  I can't call myself number one until I beat you, too.
Get out here...  I want to settle this!
I...  I...
Hooray, hooray, Ojo!
Hooray, hooray, Sakuraba!
You're number one, Sakuraba!
Torakichi...
Please, Coach. Put me in!
Sakuraba...
Raimon's going to run circles around us!
I have to stop him!
I...
I made a promise, to Torakichi, and myself!
To become the ace... everyone says I am!
But Sakuraba...
They always put 100% of their effort into risky plays without any hesitation.
That is the core of Deimon's offense.
Shin...?
If Ojo avoids any risk, but only uses 99% of its power, they'll break us eventually.
Sakuraba, we need you playing full time.
You're the only one who can stop Taro Raimon.
Shin...
Every training session, every drop of sweat... it's all been for today.
I know I can do it!
Even if I'm playing offense AND defense, I won't run out of energy, not anymore!
Sakuraba.
Sir.
Get out there!
Shut him down.
I will!
Looks like Tokyo's "best receiver" is finally stepping out.
Sakuraba...
Sakuraba's playing on both sides of the ball...
Now that he's out here, the real catching showdown begins.
You know what that means, Butt-Monkey.
You'd better win.
Yes, sir!
Monta...
Sakuraba...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What's the name of the Japanese national high school football championship?
It's the big game that Sena and everyone are aiming for!
The annual national high school football championship game is the "Christmas Bowl!"
Pay attention, all you budding football players! Ya-ha!
S-Sakuraba's heading onto the field!
They're pulling out all the stops!
It's as if they're playing in the championship game instead of the semi-finals...
Although... to win today, both teams will need their full power!
I'm surprised you're letting Sakuraba play defense too, Coach.
At some point, he became worthy of that confidence.
His desire, his motivation...
I'm comfortable banking on him.
Sakuraba's taken another step forward, then.
Yes.
Today... whoever loses the nerve to take risks first will lose.
So we play this game like it's our last!
Yes, sir!
Monta Kong.
The Mole-y Buddha Ikkyu.
Tetsumachine.
And Ace Sakuraba.
They're the four kings of Kanto wide receivers.
Who're you calling Monta Kong?!
You're transforming, Monta.
But among those four, obviously the best one is...
Sakuraba!
Ace Sakuraba's finally playing!
Ojo's gonna win for sure now!
Sakuraba vs. Monta
Will the Deimon Devil Bats be the first to score a touchdown this season against Ojo?
Set, hut!
Max Dash!
He's fast!
Raimon's running at full speed!
They're going for another long bomb!
It doesn't matter what kind of pass it is.
These boys ALWAYS run at full speed!
No need to try to conserve energy!
With that mask off I feel like a million yen!
Oh ho, Monta reverses direction!
He flies right past Sakuraba!
Not this time!
I'm open!
But Sakuraba reappears right in front of Monta!
I... can't see anything!
It's no good!
They've got the others completely covered.
Squash Hiruma!
Deimon's pass fails!
Shoot!
He's huge!
The more I look at him, the taller he seems...
Was Sakuraba always that much taller than Monta?
He looks a lot taller than he did back in the spring.
He's got a new attitude.
Attitude?
The way he carries himself, the way he feels about himself.
He doesn't approach football the same way the old Sakuraba did.
Deimon's 1st down ends with no gain.
Sakuraba...
When you and Tetsuma were chosen as the best receivers in Tokyo...
I... I was really jealous.
No one out-catches me.
If you're the best receiver in Tokyo,
then I'll become the best in the world!
That's my goal, too.
Sakuraba! Get him next time too!
- Go, Monta!
Set, hut!
What?!
Shoot... I'll break away from you, Sakuraba!
The Max Catch always wins!
You're not getting away!
Deimon's second pass is incomplete!
No gain on 2nd down, either!
What do we do, Hiruma?
Hiruma...
It's all right.
They saw through that second pass.
Crap!
No matter what I do, I can't get away from him.
Huddle up, Butt-Monkey.
Deimon hasn't advanced after two downs.
If they can't move forward on 3rd down, a 1st down might be out of the question.
Set... hut hut!
Baldini, once you start moving, that'll be the signal.
They won't move... they've already settled on their defensive formation.
Ojo's stopping the long pass to the Butt-Monkey with Sakuraba.
And with Shin out there, they've got the 4-short 3-deep LB covered.
They've got Peewee AND Butt-Monkey locked down.
I couldn't really follow all the stuff he said...
But if Hiruma says he's got them figured out...
I'm sure of it.
This is the formation I saw from the chopper.
Hut!
I see exactly where their defense zones intersect!
That route...
Catch it, Butt-Monkey!
There's Hiruma's Laser Bullet!
Monta!
Right to the intersection point!
Sakuraba!
I'm the best...
...in the world!
He underestimated Sakuraba.
Hiruma...
Sakuraba has LATERAL reach, too.
I won't let you get it!
Deimon's pass fails!
Way to go Sakuraba!
Even with Hiruma's dead-on prediction, Deimon is left with no other options!
A third pass fails! THIS is Ojo's invincible rampart!
Suddenly they're completely dominating Deimon!
I knew Sakuraba wasn't just some pretty boy anymore... but...
Nice block, Sakuraba!
You see that, Deimon? That's what Ace Sakuraba can do!
Torakichi...
Sakuraba's keeping his promise...
Me too... me too...
Someday...
I'll be able to make plays like that, too!
Man... we had that laid out perfectly...
I can't believe he made it from over there... Argh!
But...
The game's not over yet!
I know, Monta.
It's only just begun.
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
These last few plays haven't even moved us a single yard!
We're 40 yards from the end zone, now what do we do?!
My turn, huh?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Kingdom's Ballista!
Ya-ha!
He looks bigger because of his new attitude...
Suzuna... I know what you're thinking, but it's not happening...
That goes for you all, too.