I hate to admit it, but that was perfect, kid.
Complete to the max!
Yay, there's nothing to fear from the Mammoth Attack!
Thank you, Mr. Johnson.
You did a great job.
Sir!
Way to go, Sena.
Huh? Panther, Homer...
Where're you going?
Off to look for the Shuttles...
For the rest of our teammates.
All of them?
Yup.
I'm sure they feel the same
about football as we do.
Then let me help!
Can we come with you?
Good idea!
I cleared my Death Climb just like Sena.
I'm in!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Brothers of the Texas Ranch.
So this is the Northern Light Blizzards'
"Russian Roulette" formation?
They rotate their defenders
and keep blocking over and over.
Even Panther got tackled when they caught him with this.
Which means Sena would get pulverized.
So we need to get between Sena and the Roulette,
and block for Sena all the way to the goal.
Easier said than done, though.
Yup. There's the problem.
Whoa, you have an idea?!
What's the plan?
I dunno.
Dude...
Nothing?!
Why don't YOU guys think of something?!
You're the brains of the outfit!
This isn't the time for infighting.
- Shaddap!
- Stay outta this!
Hey, there's one of the other teams...
The Savanna Survivors?
They're huge.
Heh heh...
What're you gonna do?
Chill out, I'm just saying hi.
Hey! Looking forward to playing you guys.
Where do you think you're going?
What is it?
I said...
I'm looking forward to playing your team, jerk!
Oh, the Asia team!
The Asia team... Who were they...?
Umm... Rashoumon? No...
The Showtune Rats?
Deimon!
- The Deimon Devil Bats!
Right, right, Deimon, Deimon!
The first game...
When was it again?
Two days, I think...?
You...
"...think?"
Do you guys...
Sorry about that.
We're all just so preoccupied with the Northern Light Blizzards,
we completely forgot about you guys.
I get the feeling...
...that you guys...
...aren't even giving us a chance.
To be honest,
that's correct.
- You wanna go right now?!
Watch out!
Wow! What a miracle!
African power!
What's with those guys...
Yikes...
They're our next opponents...?
Wow, the Savanna Survivors sound incredible.
They might be way beyond the Russian Roulette's level.
Yeah...
But we gotta beat them first
or we won't even get the chance.
Man... What do we do?
A-Anyway, take a look at this tape I borrowed.
A video of the Shuttles-Blizzards game...
The Russian Roulette formation?
Yes.
I think if we can counter it,
we'll have an easy time against the Survivors.
Us... have an easy time... against them?
Yes!
Flawless.
Yes, it may be executed perfectly.
But that's only with one person defending.
If three people came in to block at the same time...
The same time?
And if those three
surprise the Blizzards with their power,
the formation should collapse!
Surprise them with power?
Yes.
If you three hit them simultaneously
using your best attributes,
your block will send shock waves through their formation!
Our best attacks?
Togano has power,
Jumonji has technique,
and Kuroki has speed.
If you three can hit them with all that at once,
you'll add an incredible triple-team block to your arsenal!
- A triple-team block?
A super block that nothing,
including the Russian Roulette,
will be able to stop!
- Even the Survivors?
Of course.
Yeah! Let's do it!
We'll wow 'em all with our awesome new block!
What do I do, what do I do?
Give me my orders, boss!
Leave it to me.
I've already got the perfect method
to power you three up.
What the...?
Umm...
He's creeping me out...
What...
...the heck...
...are we doing?!
That's a rodeo bull.
You three are to band together and tackle that bull.
- Tackle it?!
N-N-N-No way!
That huge bull?!
We can't do that!
Yes you can.
If you time your power,
technique and speed
to all work perfectly in sync,
you'll succeed!
Actually,
if you can't beat a bull as small as this,
the Russian Roulette formation
and the Savanna Survivors will destroy you!
I-I guess so...
O-Okay...
Let's give it a shot.
L-Let's go...
- O-Okay!
Set, hut hut!
What're you two so afraid of?
You came in later than us!
Were you even pushing?
Say what?!
Nothing will come of arguing with each other.
Your new block will be nothing more than a fantasy!
Once more!
- Right.
Come on...
I said you needed more power!
Yeah, well you're too slow...
Both of you need better technique!
- Say what?!
You got a problem?
I'm serious, you need to speed up or we'll never get anywhere!
Put more power into it or we're toast!
Can you two at least TRY to move the right way?
Clam it!
Let's go!
You clowns!
Calm down!
You need to make your individual skills compliment each others-
- There's no way we can
- take down a freaking bull!
I quit.
This is ridiculous,
three guys hitting at the exact same time.
Nothing's gonna happen no matter how many times we try.
B-But then-
Sorry.
I'm done here.
Yeah.
Me too.
Me three.
W-Wait a minute!
The Russian Roulette!
Your new...
...triple team block...
What...
What now...?
Chest!
It has been an honor.
Yo, Watt.
What're you doing?
Hey, guys!
This is what the Japanese call "Flower Arrangement."
He's wrong again...
You look more at home with that.
Yeah...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what's important in a wide receiver like Mon-Mon!
The key is "avoidance?"
A wide receiver needs to speedily dodge his defenders
so he can catch the pass.
Don't get caught!
Ya-ha!
Crap!
Boring.
Our own play...
Kuroki?
You guys?
- What're you two doing here?!
All right, this side of the line belongs to me, so stay out!
Fine, but if you cross mine, I'll beat your bones!
Shut up, you idiots, I was here first!
Wreck the Russian Roulette!
Smash the Survivors!
Send 'em packing!
Why?
Um, are you all...
What?
...practicing football?
What do you want?
What team?
The Deimon Devil Bats...
The ones in the Cream Puff Cup?
Yeah...
Why?
We just started playing, too!
Teach us how to play!
We read in the paper...
...that you guys...
...are linemen from the famous school
that's playing as the Asian representative!
Oh yeah?
Famous, eh?
We did come in third in the Tokyo Tournament...
- Teach us stuff!
So to block,
you gotta go for your opponents armpits and lift him up!
'Kay!
Keep you eye on the ball, and...
Focus on your target...
Okay!
These kids...
...are all...
...complete messes.
Push up on the armpits with your palms!
That's it, John! Just like that.
Eye on the ball, Tom!
Okay!
I got it!
Now you've got it!
Eyes on the target...
Right!
Way to go, Sally!
Where did Jumonji and the others go...?
Playing with children of all things...
I give up...
Let's see what you can do!
- Right!
- Set, hut, hut!
No good, try it again.
You've got it all wrong.
Settle down.
Too soon...
Way too soon.
Why the heck aren't you moving like you're 'sposed to?
YOU messed up, you went to my spot!
You were both going the wrong way to begin with!
Shut up, blockhead!
Doofus!
- You dope!
- Hey, break it up!
Easy, easy, easy!
No infighting!
You gotta stay calm and watch your teammates.
And you need to take into account
your OWN strengths and weaknesses, too.
Think about your teammates and figure out
if they'll be able to catch a pass, or make a run!
In other words...
...you gotta, uh...
You gotta trust...
...in your teammates...
In your whole team.
Okay, got it!
Let's go!
Okay! Set, hut!
Yay!
We should...
...give it another shot.
You said it.
Man...
He knows how to push back.
Yeah, but unless we take him down,
we're doomed.
- Yeah, yeah, we know.
Let's go!
- Right!
I promised to take care of the bull
if they let the brothers practice with it,
but they've lost all motivation.
Now what...?
You guys came back?!
Yeah.
We don't let anyone...
...throw us around!
The key is...
...to trust in...
...your teammates!
- YA-HA!
Wow, their triple team block worked!
They cleared their Death Climb!
The Ha-Ha Brothers have done it!
- We're not even related!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
The Triple Ha-Ha Strike is complete!
Just in time for the Survivors game!
We're not gonna stop now!
We just gotta beat them and it's on to the Blizzards!
That's the spirit!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Shout of Friendship! Ya-ha!
And that's all the Shuttles!
Good work, Panny!
Thanks, guys.
The only person left is Coach Apollo.
Yup. We'll take care of rebuilding the Shuttles,
you guys take care of the Blizzards for us!
Oh yeah, with Mon-Mon's catching
and Sena's runs, we got it!
You can leave it to us, to the max!
We'll blow the Blizzards away!
Right, Sena?
Y-Yeah...
Yes... we'll win!