Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Wolves' Battlefield!
Banba was really...
It's horrible.
He's really a monster.
Rikiya... Gao...
Taiyo!
Curse them!
How lame!
That loser Banba got beaten down so quick!
Instant death!
He's an embarrassment to the school!
He's from the soccer team.
It's Satoshi Mura!
Mura, you shouldn't laugh at him here...
But it's so funny!
Who?!
He heard...
Who was laughing at Banba?
Get down here.
Gao...
If you don't show yourself, that's just fine.
Everyone in the stands...
...all get...
....their little spines...
...broken to pieces.
No!
Suzuna!
Hiruma?
O-Oh no! This is horrible!
The monster, I mean, demon Gao is breaking into the bleachers!
We didn't do it!
Who the heck was laughing?!
This looks bad, Mura! Real bad!
Let go, stupid!
Why's that monster care so much anyway?
His team just fought against Banba!
I don't get it!
Th-Th-Th-This looks bad!
This is really bad!
I did it.
I said that.
Riku?
Rikky?!
What's keeping you?
Weren't you going to crush me?
I can dodge him!
He can't be all that fast with that ridiculous muscle in the way.
Riku!
With my speed...
...and my Rodeo Drive...
...I can dodge him!
It wasn't you.
You're not a coward.
I can tell that much.
I bet...
you wanted to test my strength since Marco's kept any information about me from leaking out.
I'll fight you in the semi-finals,
along with the Seibu Wild Gunmen.
What are you doing, stupid?! Huh?!
Hey, just kidding!
Boy, our joke sure shocked everyone!
My, good job ending it without anyone getting hurt.
And now we know a little something.
That giant isn't a power mongrel.
He was pretty cool, up until the end.
It isn't that he can't control his amazing strength,
he just doesn't want to.
That type's the most dangerous.
Everyone's gonna be okay.
Boy, I'm tired.
Hey, Riko...
Thank goodness everything turned out okay.
We're up against either Seibu or Misaki next...
Who'll win if everything goes smoothly?
Seibu, I imagine.
Marco, I'm a little excited about fighting Seibu in the semifinals.
Rikky!
Riku!
Are you okay, Riku? Riku!
Guys...
You really shocked me back there.
Oh, Rikky! Don't do something dangerous like that again!
Oh, yeah...
Geez, she's still treating me like a kid...
Sena, are your legs better yet?
Yep.
They're still a little sore,
but I can run again.
Great...
Riku, your game's tomorrow, isn't it?
No worries there.
There's no way we'll lose to the Misaki Wolves.
I've even improved my Rodeo Drive.
You always act so tough, Riku...
You're my only true rival.
Let's find out who's the real number one in the finals!
Yeah!
Hey, Sena!
Let's race over to the train station!
Okay!
I'll run to the max, too!
Whoo! It must be great to be a boy!
Good luck, everyone!
I can't see either of them anymore...
Wow, they're fast.
I can't keep up with those two.
Aren't you...
...from Misaki Wolves?
I'm their ace running back, Taiga Kamiya!
Was that overkill for a first hello?
Am I too much?
His legs are super long...
You're way too fast!
Just a second ago I heard you say that the Misaki Wolves are pushovers.
Isn't that a tad harsh?
I was just stating a fact.
Riku...
Who're you again?
Just kidding! You angry?
I know who you are!
You're Rodeo Drive-using Riku Kaitani.
Riku...
Well, see ya around.
Eyeshield 21, I'm looking forward to finding out which of us has the better legs.
Hey, you've gotta get through us first!
Do you think you'll actually win?
Don't make me laugh!
But didn't you lose to Eyeshield?
What?!
If Eyeshield and I are fighting over who's number one,
that puts you at number three.
You jerk!
Riku!
Eyeshield 21 is the title for the fastest runner, right?
There's no way that's right.
Well, I'm just...
H-Hey! He's already been given that title
by Bando's Akaba, a former Eyeshield!
Exactly.
So when I beat you, that eyeshield's mine.
I love collecting stuff like that.
I collect spikes and stuff from my defeated foes.
Later!
That eyeshield of yours...
...is gonna be mine!
What an egotistical jerk.
Riku, don't let what he said bother you any.
Yeah...
Riku...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Do you know how many yards long the football field is?
Does everyone know the answer?
The football field's 120 yards long.
That's 110 meters.
Conquer the field!
Ya-ha!
It's a clear, calm day, making it the perfect conditions for today's game
with Quick-Draw the Kid leading the Seibu Wild Gunmen!
I don't really lead them...
Versus the Misaki Wolves, lead by the long-legged Kamiya.
I'm not just leading them.
We're like the Kamiya Wolves!
Am I too much?
I'll kill that quick-draw gunmen team with my long legs.
Hey!
You just keep yapping.
I'll be glad to teach you how to shut that mouth!
Good luck with that, Mr. Number Three.
He's REALLY confident.
Mamo, what's Kamiya's best time for the 40-yard dash?
Let's see... 40 yards in 4.6 seconds!
Wow, he's fast!
But ya know,
despite all his bragging, he doesn't stand a chance against Sena or Riku.
Yeah...
Watch carefully, Sena.
I'm going to teach this jerk his place during this game!
Good luck, Riku!
Well then, let's get started.
Kid, let's crush them right off.
That way he'll never brag again.
You're on fire, Riku!
Go at them full blast!
Today's strategy is... to go all-out and attack!
He's always like that,
but since nothing good ever happens when we're doing too good,
let's keep from getting too hot or too cold.
Okay! Let's go!
We're pioneers on the open field!
Wild and tough!
Never let your prey escape!
Bare your fangs!
Misaki Wolves!
Misaki Wolves vs. Seibu Wild Gunmen
Zoom!
So then, Riko, what we should expect from this game?
Okay!
As you know, Seibu is a wildly offensive team.
In comparison,
the Misaki Wolves have formed a strong offense and defense
based around Kamiya's long legs.
Since both teams have their own unique style,
it'll be a matter of who keeps their cool and who-who-who...
Riko, you're doing it...
Anyway, this isn't a game to be missed!
The Misaki Wolves start on offense!
The game will start with Seibu's kickoff!
And a marvelous kick sends the ball to the back corner!
He can't reach it in time...
Kamiya's going after it, but it's gonna be a stretch for him!
He was nothing but talk.
It's mine now!
Kamiya breezed across the field and caught the ball!
What?!
- Stop him!
He got faster!
And he's still accelerating!
But Kaitani and his team are standing in his way!
Stop him!
Wolf Fang!
Touchdown!
Taiga Kamiya has performed a kickoff return touchdown!
He broke through them without slowing down at all.
He's making the same pose Mon-Mon does!
Jerk! He stole it from me!
This is my instant death technique, Wolf Fang!
Am I too cool or what?
Wolf Fang's just like a wolf's fang!
He was just like a wolf jumping after his prey.
This is it!
That's the Misaki Wolves unique style!
Let me tell you something interesting.
4.6 seconds is my record for running laps.
I'm way faster once I've locked in on my prey.
Just you wait, Eyeshield!
I'll finish things up here soon enough!
I know that there's a type of player that grows more powerful during the actual game...
So he's best in-game, right?
Misaki Wolves are going into offense with a seven point lead!
Kamiya!
How dare you focus on Sena when you're fighting me!
Set, hut!
Kamiya's running for it!
No you don't!
Kaitani's going after Kamiya!
What?! That was an act?!
They're passing it to Kamiya?!
Wolf Fang!
Amazing!
The long pass to Kamiya was a success!
He's both a running back and a receiver!
He even stole my catching!
Kamiya's making a run for it!
He's running!
He's breezing past all of Seibu's defense!
No, he's breaking through!
At this rate, he'll score another touchdown.
Kamiya keeps on running straight to the goal line!
Uh-oh, it's Kaitani!
He's chasing after him full-throttle!
- Go, Riku!
But even Riku can't...
He took too long to start running.
Even with his fast legs, there's no Kaitani will make it in time.
Darn it!
If only I'd started running sooner!
But-!
Wow! Kaitani's catching up!
I WILL stop you!
Wolf Fang!
Kamiya suddenly accelerated and widened their gap!
He's like a wolf racing across the open plains!
Touchdown!
The Misaki Wolves ace player, Taiga Kamiya, has scored another touchdown!
The jerk!
He stole another one of my poses!
So he wasn't just talk.
Seibu's got to keep their guard up.
It's the Kanto Tournament, so both teams are great.
The team that fails to meet their full potential is the one that will lose.
Right...
After all, even Shinryuji lost...
Misaki Wolves 14 - Seibu Wild Gunmen 0
The Misaki Wolves are strengthening their lead!
I'm doing awesome today!
We've just about nabbed victory!
That was a fluke.
Going by your expression, I bet you're jealous of me.
You're-!
You're no where near as great as Sena and me.
Now who's acting tough?
What are you doing?!
Go more all-out!
Goodness, we're stuck fighting another formidable opponent.
I swear, they just don't want to give us an easy victory.
Kid...
The ball!
Please give me the ball!
I swear I'll crush that jerk so bad!
Oh Riku, you're falling back into your old bad habit.
You'll get burned if you get too heated up.
This game's gonna tougher than I thought.
Riku...
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
Hey, hey! What's going on, Seibu?!
You might actually lose!
There's no way that Seibu and Riku are gonna lose!
Calm down, Riku!
Keep your cool, Riku!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Rodeo Drive Stampede!
Ya-ha!
What are you writing, Toga?
- Oh, n-nothing.
- C'mon, quit hiding it!
Let us see!
- This is wicked good!
Unlike a certain someone...
What a difference.
Sh-She stinks...