- Space
- Mammoth
Mammoth Attack!
The NASA Shuttles crash and burn!
A third-rate team like yours has no business on the field.
Now keep your end of the bargain, and dissolve your team!
Fine...
As we agreed, the Shuttles...
...are hereby disbanded.
Man...
Are the NASA Shuttles finished?
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
A New Trial.
It's all my fault...
all of it.
Please, Coach! Don't do this!
Coach...
Watt...
Talk the coach out of this.
Sorry, Panther...
There's nothing we can do.
But-
Panther...
What can you do for them?
Coach Doburoku?
Why do you think we came
all the way to Texas in the first place?
Because...
...we need more experience
if we're going to win the Kanto Tournament.
Then you obviously don't have any time
to fret about other teams.
If you lose your focus,
we'll end up just like the Shuttles!
I can't believe the Shuttles got destroyed like that...
And they're really breaking up the team...
That's how the world works,
there's always someone better.
- The Blizzards are the real deal.
Players are nothing more than parts of a machine.
Anyways...
We can't let 'em keep getting away with this, can we?
No way!
The way he calls players "parts" really ticked me off!
Yeah!
Let's beat them down, chew them up and spit them out!
Guys...
So we're all on the same page?
- Let's do it!
Well said, boys.
There's only one way for us to beat the Blizzards.
I call it...
...the "Death Climb!"
Death... Climb?
This time, you've all got individual assignments.
Peewee.
Y-Yes?
You're gonna neutralize Ivan's Mammoth Tackle.
Right!
Butt-Monkey, you've gotta intercept Nikolai's Soyuz Pass.
Yessir!
Baldini and the Ha-Ha Bros,
you counter their Russian Roulette formation.
- Right!
Team Fatty will work on blocking.
Roger!
Let's work extra hard!
Everyone needs to buckle down,
pass their assignment with flying colors,
and come back here before the Savanna Survivors game.
That's the Death Climb!
Umm... I understand why we're working individually,
but what exactly are we supposed to DO?
What you need to do...
...is figure it out on your own!
We get it!
- See you later!
Wait up, I wanna come!
Good luck, guys...
They know what's up...
Players aren't parts.
They have to decide for themselves what matters most.
Sure, "Death Climb" sounds cool,
but what should we do for training?
Man...
Stupid Hiruma...
Throw us a bone, man.
Perhaps...
coming up with individual training methods
is part of the Death Climb,
in which case we've already started.
What do you mean, Yuki?
Well, thinking about lots of different possibilities and devising a plan
during a game requires sense and intellect,
so I was thinking that coming up
with training methods might in itself be training.
Hrm, instinct and intellect, huh?
There are lots of different plays in football,
so you need a good head on your shoulders to improvise
and develop new ones on the spot.
Good idea, Yuki!
Way to pay attention!
Yay, Yuki!
Which means...
...that we're...
...your team.
- See to that whole
- "devising a plan" thing, would ya?
Uhh, well like I said,
the important part is to figure it yourself-
Thanks.
Thanks, sucker.
Easy for him to say...
What the heck are you looking for, Monta?
Well, something's bound to inspire me sooner or-
Ow ow ow...
What do we do with 'em?
Just toss him in the trash!
Are they fighting?
Looks like it...
Let's just go, we don't wanna get involved.
C'mon, whatcha gonna do?
I-It's Homer!
Why you...!
Uh-oh!
Rock on, Sena!
Dude, that was awesome to the max!
- Who're you?!
Uh-oh.
What do we do?
This is the police!
What do you punks think you're doing?
Oh man!
Cheese it!
You okay, Sena?
Panther!
So the "police-"
Yup, it was me.
Hey, Homer, you all right?
Mind your own business.
What's your problem?!
We just saved you from a beating!
Who asked you for help?
But your shoulder's already injured,
and if you'd gotten in a fight there's no telling how much worse-
Maybe it would've been for the best.
I mean,
I'm not gonna play football anymore.
Don't say that!
Please, Homer, keep playing with us!
Let's rebuild the Shuttles!
Don't make me repeat myself.
I'm never playing football again.
But you love football.
Don't go around picking fights just because you're mad.
You think you know how I feel?!
Tossed around like a rag doll,
called a third-rate player,
I've never been more humiliated!
The Shuttles are gone because of me!
I don't even know how to throw a pass anymore!
Do you realize how disgusted I am with myself?!
I'm sorry...
Just forget about me.
Homer...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us about Yocchie's position, quarterback!
It's all about your "brain?"
A quarterback needs to be able to analyze
the other team and come up with ways to gain an advantage.
Use your brain! Ya-ha!
Have the other Shuttles really given up on the team?
I thought they'd want to get together
and try to start over from scratch...
But Homer was the heart of the Shuttles,
without him we wouldn't be able to function as a team.
But, he's lost all motivation to play...
He's really gone downhill if he's picking fights with thugs.
His pride's been destroyed.
The Blizzards are really tough.
We didn't even stand a chance.
No way!
Your runs were incredible!
You're way faster than when we played-
Even still...
In the end, it wasn't enough.
Not you too, Panther!
You're not gonna quit too?!
Homer even did dogeza to get the coach to put me in...
I only had a place on that team because of him.
I basically owe my football career to Homer.
They're the only people I could ever play with...
...but the team's in shambles.
Playing doesn't mean anything
if it's not with them!
Panther's gonna quit too...
What's all this, now?
Why's everyone acting so glum?
Grandma?
Oh, the Japanese boy!
Good timing. Come with me, children.
Grandma, what're we-
Yo, Japanese boys.
I owe you guys one!
- Big Bear?!
Whoa, he's huge.
Big Bear?
Wait, then today-
Our District 35 team's going
head-to-head against District 36!
I may be in your debt, but a game's a game.
District 36's going home a winner today!
Get over yourself.
With Panther AND the Japanese boys, we've got this in the bag!
Man, they never change.
Y-Yeah...
And she's already volunteered you to be on the team.
But... I...
Come on, Panther!
Let's run together.
Let's play some football!
What's the hold up, Panther?
Go get ready!
District 36 vs. District 35
You think Panther'll be okay?
The Deimon mascots are here to cheer, too!
Here it comes!
Sena?
Whoa...
He's so fast...
Yay, Sena! Go!
Atta boy, Japanese boy!
Shoot! I'll stop you in your tracks!
Touchdown!
Woo-hoo, the Devil Bat Ghost!
His speed's even more impressive up close...
A kickoff return touchdown!
He sure showed them!
Sena, how do you keep evolving?
I... I want...
I want to run with you, Sena!
Yeah. Let's run it in, together!
Set, hut!
They're on the same team,
why the heck are they racing?!
What incredible speed...
Keep going, guys!
Get another touchdown!
Gotta get the Japanese boy!
Crush him!
Ahh, nuts, now Panther's got it!
Bedtime, kid!
Touchdown!
Yeah, the Zero-G run!
Panther's such an awesome runner...
Yeah! Yay, yay!
Those two...
Keep going! Rack up those points!
Don't let them score again!
Game over! District 35 wins!
Yeah, District 35!
We won!
Yahoo!
Panther, how can you think about quitting when you're running's so-
I meant it.
I meant what I said, until I got to run with you.
After watching you, I knew there was no way I could ever quit.
I wanna keep running.
I can't help it, I just love football!
Panther...
Homer won't quit so easily, either.
He... all of them will come back to the sport.
Good, you finally get it.
It's like your oatmeal.
Your body never forgets how good something it loves feels.
And anyone can see how much you boys love football.
That's right.
Homer will remember the feeling, too.
Yeah!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Panther's motivated again, now it's on to Homer-
Ack, what're you doing in a pro wrestling ring, Sena?!
I have to if I'm gonna get Homer back and beat the Mammoth Attack!
No one will be laughing if you get hurt!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Fighting Spirit! The Death Climb! Ya-ha!
Now eat up, Japanese boys!
I made enough oatmeal for everyone!
Ooh, it looks great!
Num!
Eww...
I knew it...