See you later.
Thanks, Sena.
I promise I'll get the team back together,
you guys worry about completing the Death Climb.
Yeah, I'm sure Coach Apollo and Homer
will come to their senses.
Come over any time you need a snack.
I'll have plenty of piping hot oatmeal ready for you!
Y-Yeah, oatmeal!
We'll be good on oatmeal for about a century!
C'mon, ease off!
I still owe you a lot more.
This time I'M gonna beat YOU down!
P-Please, don't...
You're really going too far, Homer.
If you've got too much extra energy,
I've got just the thing for you.
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Fighting Spirit! The Death Climb!
Why do you keep looking up at the sky?
Maybe there's some kinda hint for the Death Climb up there...
I doubt it.
Gotta come up with a way to intercept that Soyuz Pass...
Not again...
That's it!
Eureka to the max!
Basketball?
Max Catch!
What're you doing?
Planning for the Soyuz Pass!
I'll get it from the side!
Who's the monkey?
Maybe he wants to play?
Could be fun.
Let's see whatcha got!
Max Catch!
Feints are ineffective to the max!
Nuts!
Ouch...
C'mon, Monta!
Bring it on!
Shoot, I couldn't even catch one pass...
You okay?
It's hard to tell which way the ball's gonna bounce, huh...?
I got destroyed... never even got a finger on the ball.
But I figure if I can learn to catch a basketball,
I could intercept the Soyuz Pass.
Yeah, you may be on to something.
Right?
Tomorrow I'll get-
You're sure you're okay?
My legs are shot.
You need to take a break.
Agreed.
Remember, I'm not liable in the event of any injuries or broken bones.
You DID sign the waiver.
Come back when you get stronger.
What...? Huh?
Scary dude...
This is...
A pro wrestling gym?
That last guy must've tried to challenge them.
The Mammoth Attack!
If I can get them to train me...
I might be able to beat him.
Whoa man, fighting pro wrestlers?
You'll get creamed.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Fight. Fight.
Yikes!
These guys are even scarier up close.
Homer!
I can't believe you guys followed me all the way here...
Did Panther put you up to this?
Oh, no, he didn't...
Anyway, what're you doing here, Homer?
What do you think?
I'm gonna be a pro wrestler.
What's so weird about that?
Lots of ex-football players become wrestlers.
That old fogy's one of 'em.
I'm not old!
The name's Johnson, and I'm still plenty young.
You're the one-
You used to play football?
Yup, on the same team as Homer's older brother.
I've known this runt here since he was a kid.
But what about football?
Football? Forget that mess.
I never wanna touch a football again.
But a player of your caliber...
My "caliber?"
You saw the game.
I don't have any "caliber" after such a pathetic showing.
Get real!
How can you say that?
Panther's out there trying to get the team back together all by himself!
Don't you have any love for football?
Even if I do, without talent, I'd have to stop playing eventually.
That game opened my eyes.
When you all learn the same lesson
you'll quit talking about "love of the game."
We've still gotta go to the Christmas Bowl!
Then answer this.
How are you gonna beat the Blizzards?
How...?
Can you stop Ivan's Mammoth Attack?
Do you have a plan?
Well...
There you go.
Your dreams of the Christmas Bowl are a joke.
Wake up and smell the coffee.
But we MEAN it.
We intend to play in the Christmas Bowl!
All right.
Then show me how serious you are.
What do you mean?
Get in the ring and let a wrestler tackle you.
Hold on, what's that got to do with anything?
Look, Ivan's Mammoth Attack is at...
No, it might even be above their level.
If you can't face them, you can't face him.
Of course, you might not be able
to play your beloved football after this.
I thought you were serious.
You were gonna beat the Blizzards?
Then show me.
That was kind of mean, don't you think?
Telling a spindly kid like that to get in the ring.
I just taught him not to talk big without the nerve to back it up.
You don't have to force yourself into pro wrestling.
I'm not forcing anything.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to play wide receiver like Mon-Mon!
The key is "catching!"
A receiver has to catch the pass, no matter what.
Keep your eye on the ball!
Ya-ha!
What's this?
A waiver.
Waiver?
We're not responsible for what happens in the ring.
If you get hurt, you can't sue us or take legal action.
It's getting late, so come back tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning?
If you really do want to get in the ring,
sign that form and bring it here tomorrow.
Sena, don't tell me
you're seriously gonna get in the ring?!
Well, it WOULD be pointless if I got injured and couldn't play!
Obviously!
Football and wrestling are two different worlds!
You're forbidden!
Right...
Homer was just being a jerk.
Let Panther take care of him.
I'm bushed, let's get to bed.
The subject is closed!
Yeah!
You get to bed too, Suzuna.
I thought you were serious.
You were gonna beat the Blizzards?
Then show me.
There you go.
Your dreams of the Christmas Bowl are a joke.
I did it, Mamori...
Death Climb... no problemo...
The Death Climb...
Yes, the Death Climb...
We're supposed to be preparing for the Christmas Bowl.
This isn't about proving our desire.
This is about training!
Morning!
Already...?
Huh? Where'd Sena go?
Ack!
The waiver's gone!
Oh no! Did Sena...?!
Hurry!
Sena?
You're really gonna do it?
Yes.
Don't be dumb.
A squirt like you's just gonna get hurt in there.
Homer!
Panther...
Are you nuts, Sena?
Don't do it!
Please, don't let Homer get to you, this is insane!
No, I'm not trying to prove anything to him.
This is MY Death Climb.
I'm doing it for me!
Sena...
Use your elbows, your elbows!
Mr. Johnson.
I signed your waiver.
A football uniform...?
Should be enough of an advantage.
Johnson, don't-
You're sure?
Yes. Please!
Shouldn't we be stopping this?
He's made his decision as a man,
I can't interfere now.
Men...
Here I come!
Okay!
What?!
The Devil Bat Ghost!
I see... so he's not just some pipsqueak.
So I don't need to hold back, then?
No, sir.
He's fast!
Whoa!
What happened?
A weak dodge like that won't work in a game!
He's right,
dodging like that'll just get me tackled anyway.
I need to get through untouched!
Get ready!
Once more!
- Sena!
You alive, Sena?!
Don't die on us!
I'm fine...
I feel like I'm getting somewhere...
Just stop, that's enough!
You're serious, I get it.
You're gonna get hurt!
Do you hear me, Sena?!
C'mon Johnson, that's enough.
You'll kill him...
You too, stop already!
Keep going!
Sena...
This is my Death Climb.
I have to defeat the Mammoth Attack!
You're really serious...
I want to get stronger and go to the Christmas Bowl.
You love football too, Homer, you should understand!
I know you don't want to quit!
Keep going!
I certainly can't stop after hearing all that.
When the opponent takes his last step,
his knee will always turn inward!
Gotcha!
That's the feeling!
He did it!
Yay!
Check it out, Panther.
The old me's up there...
The way you were up till now.
Panther, I wanna get better.
Better than I've ever been.
Yup.
SENA!
You awake?
Y-Yeah...
Thank goodness...
Whoa, easy!
Thanks, Homer.
You helped me find the hint I needed
to beat the Mammoth Attack.
Geez, man...
Well, thank you, too.
Homer...?
I'll be watching the results of your Death Climb from the stands.
And I'll be waiting for the Shuttles' return.
Leave it to us! We'll be back soon!
Right!
Male bonding is so cute...
Hey, Homer, you quitting pro wrestling?
This shrimp's going all out,
I can't just sit on my hands.
Ah ha, so you still wanted to play football after all, eh?
Guess so.
Mr. Johnson,
can I keep coming back here to practice until the game?
Whoa there-
I still have room to improve!
Geez, Homer's going back to football
and I gotta train a little kid.
Unbelievable.
Yeah... we're gonna wreck the Blizzards!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Boy, this is scary!
Monta and I found our hints!
Huh? What's up with Yuki and the bros?
Well, while we were practicing their new block, they all split up!
Sibling rivalry at a time like this?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Brothers of the Texas Ranch! Ya-ha!
Hey, pass it!
Huh?
Him...
The monkey from the other day.
Focus on the ball...
I'm back!
Hey, pass!
Right!
Max Catch!
Who'd leave a banana peel out here...