Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Oh!
- Ya-ha!
Th-That's-!
Was that a short pass to Sakuraba?!
We've gotta get him when he lands, Sena!
Yeah, we'll sandwich him in!
Amazing!
Sakuraba, our Pegasus soaring through the sky, has teamed up with the ultimate knight, Shin!
That's it! They're like a giant bow and arrow piercing through the sky!
It's the Sagittarius!
Touchdown!
It's a cruel seesaw game!
As soon as they catch up, they fall behind yet again!
Deimon's behind by seven points!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Turn on the Devil Stun Gun!
It's a fierce battle between Deimon and Ojo.
It's a cruel seesaw game where as soon as they catch up, they fall behind yet again!
Ojo White Knights 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 13
Deimon's behind by seven points!
They just aren't closing in.
But they aren't falling terribly behind, either.
Whether on defense or offense, neither side can let their guard down.
Even Agon came.
So even Agon's curious about this game's outcome.
We've gotta score some points!
We can't let them pull any further ahead.
But ya know...
...we're outta ideas.
What should we do?
In that case-!
In that case...
...let me look for a weakness in their defense and run an option route!
But, Yuki...
- Will you be okay?
Ojo's defense is really strong.
I know I can do it!
Please let me try!
Yukimitsu...
If that's what you want, then I'll open up a path for you.
Kurita!
Right! We don't let anyone throw us around!
We're gonna kill Ojo! C'mon!
We'll murderlize 'em!
That's right! Murderlize 'em!
Mamo, what's "murderlize 'em" mean...?
Hiruma, is that okay?
Set!
Well, is Deimon going to use their overpowering pass,
the Devil Backfire that they showed us earlier?
Or will they have Eyeshield 21 run?
Hut, hut, hut!
Hey, Kurita! Facing you head-on's a blast!
But I'm gonna stop you!
I won't let you stop me!
I've gotta slip through!
I've gotta let him slip through!
There!
What?! It's Yukimitsu!
Mark Yukimitsu!
I've gotta catch it!
Heads up, Baldini!
I'm surrounded.
No way! My option route was perfect...
They reacted so quickly.
This isn't going to work!
Don't give up, Yuki!
He's right!
I can't give up now!
I must... MUST catch that ball!
Deimon's pass was successful! First down!
- Yay!
I did it!
Yay! Nice going, Yuki!
Impressive! Deimon's come so far before using a middle pass.
They nailed Ojo in their blind spot!
This is Yukimitsu's specialty, which we first saw in the Shinryuji game.
It's an option route where he quickly determines the pass route.
Yuki, nice play!
I heard your voice, Sena.
Thank you.
Ah, oh, it's nothing...
You did it! You did it, Yukimitsu!
Great! Now it's time for a full-throttle counter-attack!
You bet!
Let's go full-throttle!
Yeah, full-throttle!
Sounds painful...
Okay, ladies, we're gonna hit them with all we've got now!
Next play goes to the butt-monkey!
Got it!
Yukimitsu may have broken through in that last play, but Deimon's offense hasn't really changed.
They'll probably try to throw a long pass to Raimon next.
Don't let them trick you.
- Okay!
Sakuraba...
You've got enough strength in you now for this to work.
So long as you and I can combine forces, we have a way to defeat the Devil Backfire.
Well, Deimon miraculously managed to get their first down!
I hope they keep up the pace!
Set, hut, hut!
All righty!
Devil Backfire Max Long Pass!
Monta!
Hey! Mon-Mon just told them our strategy!
Sakuraba bumped me?!
This bump will slow Monta down for one second!
Curse that Sakuraba!
He used his strength to throw Monta off balance.
No, that's not all he was doing.
They slowed down the passing process....
...so that they could destroy the launchpad!
Whew! Sena's going in with a light speed block!
I won't let you!
I'll protect Hiruma!
Good. I knew you'd come running.
That's why it was vital for Sakuraba to buy that one second for me!
I'm going to skewer you along with Hiruma!
There it is! The Trident Tackle!
I've gotta protect Hiruma! I must!
But... can I stop the unstoppable Shin?
Can I protect him?
You a masochistic or somethin'?
Why are you waiting for him to whack you?
Agon!
Huh, come to think of it, when we were fighting against Shinryuji...
...my bump didn't work on Agon.
I wonder why.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we'll be talking about improving your catching technique!
When catching a pass, try to catch with your hands so that you can quickly move on with the play.
You better not drop the ball after your friend passes it to you! Ya-ha!
He blocked Shin's tackle!
There's his Trident Tackle!
He skewered both of them!
He used his other hand...!
Deimon failed to pass the ball!
They haven't moved a single step forward!
B-But for a second it looked like he'd stopped the tackle.
What happened...?
Sena, are your arms okay?
My arms?
- Oww!
- Knew it!
That's a no-go!
But it worked for a second!
Cool! You stopped the Trident Tackle!
Now do it a thousand more times!
No, a thousand more times is impossible.
You did good, Peewee.
Hiruma?
You're the first person to ever stop Shin's tackle, even for a moment.
Well, I thought I had to stop him for everyone's sake, so...
Besides, when I saw Agon in the audience,
my body just moved on its own...
Even I would get sent flying if I tried to block Shin's spear head-on.
The only way to stop it is to whack the spear with your arms from the side.
I wonder if he realized what he was doing.
So that little twerp's turning fierce now.
That's it. If I go at his arms from an angle... I'm sure...
Not bad. That'll be your new ultimate technique.
You use your arms to fend off his.
It's the Devil Stun Gun!
The Devil Stun Gun?
Incredible! Eyeshield 21 used his new technique to defend against Shin!
It's called the Devil Stun Gun!
His impact will be several times stronger when combined with his light speed running.
This truly is a demoniacally powerful move against Ojo.
Devil Stun Gun, huh?
Do you know why Hiruma names all of your techniques?
Well, so they can scare the enemy and help us win... or something?
That's not completely off, but that's not the main reason.
It makes it clear that you're only supposed to use it when you absolutely have to.
Since you're using one hand to block, you're only holding the ball with one hand.
Your offensive power may double, but the risk of you losing the ball increases ten-fold.
So your ultimate move comes with a risk.
Be picky when to use it.
Okay!
All righty! I can't lose, either!
Sena managed to push aside Shin!
Now to do things my way!
Your way?
Time for monkey tricks?
Set, hut, hut!
Hey, let's get everyone pumped up!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Catch this long pass!
Monta, use the Devil Backfire!
There he goes again!
Sakuraba's using his long arms for another bump!
That won't work! Determination to the max!
- That's not even a monkey trick!
B-Back off!
He recovered too quickly!
I didn't stop him for long enough!
Not bad. It's 100 million times better than monkey tricks.
We won't let you...
...get to Hiruma!
Hiruma, pass!
Go, Deimon! It's your big chance to throw a long pass!
How quaint.
But you really shouldn't underestimate Ojo's ultimate defense!
They're surrounded!
There's no way he can throw a pass now!
Shin's taken advantage of this to break past Kurita and Kuroki!
Great! Now crush him!
It can't be!
That's right. Since this is our only chance to throw a long pass...
...we'll run instead!
Oh my! Hiruma doesn't have the ball!
Get Eyeshield! Come back!
Yay, Yocchie!
Hiruma!
He's as sickeningly clever as ever.
He used his own body to hide that he was passing the ball to Eyeshield.
He had that twerp start running once Shin's focus was completely on him himself.
Ojo's amazing! Everyone's regrouped so quickly.
I've gotta use that technique.
Okay!
Get a good grip on the ball!
Eyeshield slipped through!
He dodged three people at once!
He's passing by all of Ojo's defense!
You can't pass!
But his last hurdle is the giant, Otawara!
It all depends on him!
It's no good!
Don't give up!
Amazing!
Yukimitsu blocked just now as if he knew exactly how their defense was going to move!
That won't work!
Now, Sena!
Yuki!
Sena, go!
He got through! He's finally broken past all of Ojo's defense!
He's zooming! THIS is Eyeshield 21!
Here comes Shin!
That jerk! Wasn't he going after Hiruma?!
He got there so quickly!
Think about it for a sec, Fatty.
He can't catch up.
It's a race between two light speed runners!
Who will be victorious?!
They're both running as fast as humanly possible.
They're in the light speed world of 40 yards in 4.2 seconds.
But it's no use.
The gap will never change since they're going the same speed.
Wow! Go, Sena!
Sena!
Can Eyeshield 21 score a touchdown?!
It's impossible?
Perhaps it's logically impossible, but...
Logically he shouldn't be able to catch up.
But I know Shin...
Shin'll definitely stop the light speed Eyeshield 21.
He's coming!
Shin's coming!
He jumped!
That's foolish. There's no way he'll catch him.
Yay!
He dodged him!
Now for the touchdown!
I've told you before, Eyeshield 21...
The ones going to the Christmas Bowl...
...will be Ojo!
He's using just one finger?!
I'm almost there.
I'm almost to the goal line!
If I hold the ball out in front of me...!
Sakuraba! He believed that Shin would stop him and ran on ahead.
Sena!
Monta?
You're not getting through!
I warned you that Shin and I would attack with a tag play.
Darn it! Even though I'm blocking him, Sakuraba's arms and legs are too long!
No one can beat me and my long reach!
It's Ojo's ball!
Deimon didn't score a touchdown!
Ojo White Knights 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 13
The score is unchanged with Ojo 20, Deimon 13!
Deimon let the chance of a lifetime slip by...
They didn't let it slip by.
If Shin wasn't there...
If they didn't have that monster on their side, that wouldn't have happened.
He truly is the greatest linebacker in history!
Is Deimon finished now?!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
I can't believe he stopped Sena with one finger! Shin's unbelievable!
We're just a foot away! No, just 10 centimeters!
Break through Ojo's walls!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Demon's Twin Wings!
Ya-ha!
Guys...
Which play card will we go with next?
You decide!
The white card is a safe play that sticks to the books.
The black card will turn the tables instantly if it works, but if we fail, we're doomed.
It's the card of death.
You knew they'd choose that one before you even finished, didn't you?
Serves 'em right.
We'll either sink or swim with this playbook of death.
We'll sink or swim... with this playbook of death...