Seeing is believing, folks. The Deimon Devil Bats have beaten the Amino Cyborgs
and advanced to the second round.
Despite the fact that they lack a dedicated kicker, the Devil Bats
made up for their shortcomings with an overwhelming pass and run game!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Legendary 60-Yard Magnum!
No way, dude.
They're just a little out of range.
That's the game!
Wow!
The Bando Spiders win, 7-6!
Smart, as always.
The Bando Spiders' kicker is Kotaro Sasaki.
His extra point success ratio is 100%.
100%?!
But extra point kicks are just one point, right?
In a tight game like that,
one point can make a big difference.
The difference between victory and defeat, to be precise.
Wish we had a kicker like him.
I'll say.
Where's Musashi, again?
Oops!
Sorry, pops.
What? Gimme that!
What's up?
This old dude here...
...doesn't wanna give me my helmet.
People who don't care for their equipment never make it to the top.
What's your freakin' problem?
Hey, gramps!
You want a piece?
Let's go!
Easy, Kuroki-kun!
We finally have the whole practice field to ourselves today,
let's just get practice started.
Better learn to watch your mouth, pops.
I'm sorry about all that.
You've got some speedy legs there.
If you train your torso and head to move less while you run, you'll get even faster.
What's this?
You know, that thing's been in this empty locker ever since we built this room.
That's a place kick tee, isn't it?
Kick tee?
Something to hold the ball on for a kick.
You balance straight up on the tee. There are two basic types.
Umm... That kick tee is...
Is to be left where it is.
Don't mess with it.
Why?
It belongs to Musashi.
Musashi?
That's the legendary kicker who formed the Devil Bats with Hiruma in middle school.
We'll need it when Musashi comes back to the team...
Oh, so he is coming back?
Well, um...
Forget about him and get back to practicing your own positions!
Well, day one's over - four teams down.
And 32 left.
I gotta say, the Devil Bats really improved.
I'd say they stand to make a respectable showing.
If they could just get the "60-yard Magnum" Musashi back,
they'd have a shot at winning it all!
Oh please, 60 yards?
That's nothing more than a fairy tale.
There aren't even any official records.
Still, there's no questioning Musashi's kicking ability is almost otherworldly.
Man, 60 yards? That's pretty sick.
I mean, the Japanese high school record for longest kick is only 58.
Hey, let's find Musashi and convince him to rejoin the team!
Yeah, good call!
We've got my catching, your running...
our team with a kicker would be like an elephant with a bazooka!
We'd quadruple our chances of making it to the Christmas Bowl!
Wait, how do we find him?
Man, did you see how hard he nailed the ball?
He's gotta be the top high school kicker in the nation.
Yeah, some people are already calling him a kicking legend.
I heard he quit the last team he was on because he and someone else got in a fight,
but it must've been tough for them to let a guy like that get away!
Who're you talking about?
What team is he on now?
Satoshi Muro, he's on the soccer team.
Satoshi Muro?
Mu-sa-shi.
Yes! Yes!
Mura, you rule!
I'm kinda nervous.
C'mon, we're gonna persuade Musashi to the max!
THAT'S Musashi?
He doesn't look too smart.
Who're you?
You don't recognize me?
Oh, you're the kicker from yesterday's game!
The guy with the 100% success rate!
Kotaro Sasaki of the Bando Spiders.
Ahh, I get it. You came to scout our team!
Scout? I don't waste my time on un-smart activities.
Then what're you doing here?
I've heard all the rumors about the 60-yard Magnum.
How he, Deimon's Musashi, can kick a 60 yard field goal.
Great, just great!
Satoshi Muro, I challenge you to a kicking competition!
Never again will anyone call you the #1 kicker!
Huh? A kicking competition?
Eureka!
A penalty kick shootout, you against us!
Against the SOCCER TEAM?!
If we win, we'll make him come back.
But we don't stand a chance!
Sure we do!
If I play goalie, we'll win for sure!
Remember, I'm the catching master!
Oh yeah...
They're freshmen from the football team.
The football team?
You got some fluke victory in the first round,
and now you're challenging ME to a kicking competition?
Get over yourselves!
Fluke?!
Hey, hold on...
Oh yeah!
Ah, I see. Good call.
One condition!
If we win, our team takes all your scheduled practice field time.
Okay, you're on!
And if we win, you have to come back to the football team.
I think they've got the wrong guy.
Come BACK to the football team?
What're you babbling about?
Ah, whatever.
It's not like we're gonna LOSE!
We'll get twice as much time on the practice field!
Then it's settled!
Let's do this!
Hello, you need FIVE players for a shootout!
You're short a couple.
Whatever, they won't even score one goal.
We'll just grab whoever we can.
Whoever...?
I got this, just follow me.
O-Okay!
Hey, we need two people for a penalty kick shootout!
Everyone went for a run.
What should we do?
We need two people, or...
Or we'll end up having to forfeit...
Excuse me!
Would you mind giving us a hand with something?
Oh yeah, that guy's always here working on something...
He seems to know a lot about athletics.
If you train your torso and head to move less while you run, you'll get even faster.
Really?
Yeah, pretty please?
Okay, let's get the shootout started!
Soccer Team
Football Team
This team is NOT smart.
Football Clinic!
When do you kick the ball?
You can kick the ball into the goal for three points instead of a touchdown.
And you can get one point for kicking it in AFTER a touchdown! Ya-ha!
We got this!
We can't lose if I stop all their shots!
You goof, you're not even paying attention!
You cheater!
Yes!
Wha?!
Not paying attention?
That was smart!
Wow! That was cool!
I bet I could've made it as a goalie, too!
Lemme show you some REAL smartness.
Smart my butt.
Go put your skirt back on, ya fruit.
Amazing, he got it right in the corner!
How'd you like that, Satoshi Muro?
Ah, whatever.
Mutton-chops there was the only one to worry about, the rest are garbage!
Garbage?
Sweet, another super catch!
He blocked two in a row...
It ain't over yet!
Now, would you kick the ball for us?
Look, he's eating!
He's eating it!
A dog can't kick a soccer ba-
Crap!
Yes!
He even kicked it with his hind legs!
You ready to get serious?
Bring it!
I gotta do something about that monkey of a goalie.
That's right, monkey-boy there is the football team's star receiver!
I see.
Then how about THIS?!
No problem!
I-It turned?!
You've never had to worry about catching a curving kick.
Not like catching a nice gentle pass from a teammate, is it?
Eat that!
Okay, Sena, it's up to you! Seal the deal!
Easy for you to say...
I can't... see where he's going!
What side is he gonna kick from?!
Awesome!
What a waste of effort.
Another curve.
What happened to the super catches?
He's too used to reacting to objects moving straight at him.
In fact, he might be worse at catching curves than an amateur.
He wasn't trained to be a goalie.
He's finished.
He can't control his kicks, either...
Curve combo!
How'd we end up a point behind?!
We're doomed!
I can't believe we NEED the old dude to score the last point!
It's down to that no-name carpenter.
This game's in the bag.
We'll get to use the field twice as much!
Hey, sir, just so we know, have you ever played soccer?
Never.
Uhh, Sena, I thought you said he knew what he was doing?
But...
That stance...
That was 45 yards!
You're incredible, Musashi!
Your code name's "The 60-yard Magnum!"
I can't make a 60 yard kick, you doofus!
It's a great bluff.
In football, you win by getting in the enemy's head.
Hey, mister, don't blame us if you throw out your back trying to kick, okay?
How'd... this.. happen...
The #1 kicker...
Muro!
You okay?
Get him to the nurse!
Holy...
Who is he?
Mister, what's your name?
Gen Takekura.
Musashi's easier to remember.
Th-That guy's-
Musashi?!
Musashi...
That's an old nickname.
Not many people call me that anymore,
not since I dropped out of high school.
Wait a sec.
If you're Musashi, then you'd only be a second year high school student...
You're only 17?!
Yup.
Hey, Musashi!
This tee's exactly 60 yards from the goalpost!
So far!
You can really kick it through from all the way out here?!
You're the 60-yard Magnum, right?
Then you should-
It's a lie.
A LIE?!
You guys should know full well,
you've hung out with that big-mouthed jerk long enough.
Big-mouthed jerk...
Hiruma...?
I don't care if the 60 yard story's a lie or not!
Let's rumble, Musashi!
We'll see once and for all who the best kicker is!
I quit playing football.
I don't feel like kicking that ball anymore.
You're #1. Congrats.
Coward!
I've lost all respect for you!
Musashi!
Please, hear us out!
Why did you leave the Devil Bats, Musashi?
I abandoned Kurita and Hiruma.
Playing on a weak team is no fun.
The Devil Bats are better now.
We completed an entire death march
and we've got a full roster of reliable players!
Please.
Come back to the Devil Bats!
We need a kicker!
With a good kicker, we'd be the best team out there!
You call THAT a better team?
Give me a break.
If you want me back, ask again after you've REALLY improved.
Please, wait!
You swore with Hiruma and Kurita
that you'd all go to the Christmas Bowl, right?
So if the Devil Bats get better, you'll rejoin?
Will you promise?
We'll keep practicing and getting stronger.
And... And when we do,
please come back to the team!
I'll think about it.
Real men don't go back on their word!
When we get better, you'd better come back!
Keep watching us, Musashi!
We'll get stronger...
...faster...
...better!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
What? Taki's not even a Deimon student yet?!
Have no fear! There's a 150% chance I'll pass the mid-year entrance exam!
If you don't pass, you can't play football for Deimon!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Ah ha ha! My Debut! Ya-ha!
You picked up some good freshmen.
We're still waiting for you.