Stompity stompity stompity stompity...
Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Oh!
- Ya-ha!
We'll win! We'll beat Ojo!
Ballista!
W-Wait, that's-
They went into the Ballista formation right after the kickoff!
Here comes Shin!
And Otawara and Ikari!
Watch out!
- Shut 'em down!
I won't budge, Kurita!
Neither will I!
- Open a path!
- I'm not backing down!
I won't back down!
Stop 'em!
Tackle Shin AND the returner!
We can't...
...do anything!
The invincible Shin, the lead blocker, heads the charge!
Starting from deep in their own territory, they're almost to Deimon's side of the field!
Can Ojo break free?
Eyeshield's coming in from the side!
There he is!
Tackle Eyeshield!
I won't let them escape!
Sena!
Yes, he got him!
What a fight!
Eyeshield avoids Watanabe and makes the tackle on Nekoyama!
He's showing us real heart!
Good job, Sena!
You're back!
Took you long enough, Sena!
You okay?
Yeah... Nice running.
- Sena!
Max revival!
You're amazing!
You had us worried!
Ya jerk!
And now you're acting like a big shot!
Guess you're all right now, huh, Sena?
Sena! Sena! Sena!
The crowd's on their feet, cheering for a revived Sena!
- Thank you, thank you, excuse me...
- There's the pointless bowing!
Well, THIS hasn't changed.
Shin was right.
Yes.
Eyeshield's far from finished... We can't get lazy even for a second.
I know.
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Battlefield, After the Rain.
Ojo White Knights 13 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Ojo, up seven points begins their drive.
And once again they're set up for the Ballista!
I've only got one shot at beating Shin...
Say what?
Use power? On SHIN?
Knock him aside?
Shin's strong, he can bench press 140 kilograms...
But Sena can only bench 40 kilograms...
A 100 kilograms difference...
B-B-But you need more than arm strength to push someone!
You need weight, too!
Sure, Shin's really muscular, but he's slim. He can't weigh that much right?
He's 71 kilograms...
Sena's 48 kilograms...
A 23 kilogram difference...
The strength I'm talking about isn't what you'd use in a fight.
When I say charge up your power,
I mean that when Shin speeds up right before he goes to hit you with the Trident Tackle,
you've gotta speed up even more!
Understand?
Yes!
Set, hut!
Shin's running as Nekoyama's lead blocker!
- We won't lose!
Go, Peewee!
Right!
Here comes Eyeshield!
Good! That's what I expect from my rival!
I'm not like Riku or Shin...
I don't have any technique for making quick speed bursts...
I can only...
Charge up my legs... Not yet...
Build up... build up... and unleash it!
What?! His acceleration-!
He can't be trying to fight Shin with power!
Is he nuts?!
He can't win!
I'll win!
I'll beat Shin with strength!
I'll hit him everything I've learned,
everything that got me here!
He's-
He's going to hit him at his top speed, the 40 in 4.2 seconds!
A light speed bump!
Sena!
He sent him flying!
Hiruma!
Yocchie got him!
- Yeah!
- Go, Eyeshield!
Hiruma...
That's good enough, Peewee.
Right!
Hiruma made the tackle, but the Ojo White Knights still get the first down!
No problem!
Nope! Shin has it all under control!
What a spectacular offense. Ojo is no longer just an "impregnable fortress."
This team has evolved into an unstoppable scoring machine, they're an "invincible army" as well!
Good blocking, Shin.
Shin...?
Shin's always so calm... I can't believe how worked up he's getting.
He's the type whose true abilities only come out against strong opponents.
He AND Eyeshield 21.
What an interesting pair they make...
They constantly bring out the best in each other... Where will it stop?
The bump didn't work on Shin either.
What am I supposed to do?
Building up for that sudden acceleration...
It worked really well, but it took a toll on my legs!
But right now...
Shin...
S-Sena, what's your plan now?
The bump didn't work...
Then next time, I'll...
- Then next time, you'll...?
You said it twice.
Admit it, you don't have a plan.
No, but- Anyways!
Anyways, he's gotta try.
We'll hit him hard, too.
With the Delinquent Deathblow, with whatever it takes.
We'll stop Seijuro Shin, the "perfect player," even if it's only for one second!
Everyone's acting like big shots... I'd better join in.
You haven't had that look on your face since the Bando game!
I'll use the cat-clap trick and flip Shinjuro Sei on his head!
This isn't sumo!
- His name's not Shinjuro Sei!
- Whatev!
My stupid brother...
But they're in a good mood... Mentally, they're still in this.
At any rate, we've gotta use all our strength to stop Shin!
25 yards to go for Ojo!
A touchdown here would give them a 14 point lead and make this a two-touchdown game!
To Deimon, a lead that big could very well be insurmountable!
Set,
hut!
Here comes Shin!
Okay, charge up my legs...
Huh?
My legs... won't move!
Sena!
It's a pass this time!
It's complete!
Shoot, his legs alone might be longer than one of my strides!
First down Ojo!
Sena!
Timeout!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we're talking about playing catch by yourself!
Throw the ball straight up and catch it, trying to make the spin as perfect as possible.
You can practice passing AND receiving all on your own! Ya-ha!
I... can barely even flex the muscles...
Looks like you really overworked them
doing multiple Devil Bat Ghosts out on that muddy field.
Not surprising, not surprising at all.
Your legs have been taking a pounding.
You won't be able to do that charged-up acceleration for a while.
I'm fine, I can still play!
Don't, you'll hurt-
Please, let me play!
Sena...
Hiruma!
Duh. I can't bench you.
However...
...you can't run.
Say what?
You're serious?
I can't run...?
Just stay in your stance.
Don't make any big moves, just let your legs recover.
But then-
The rest of us will pick up the slack.
Musashi...
I may not be as fast as you,
but I've gotten pretty built from all those years of construction work.
The most important thing you can do for the team now
is to steal Shin's focus while you rest your legs.
I told you, ten minutes into the second half.
Eight minutes from now, that's when you'll be able to run for real.
I hope Sena'll be okay...
Y-Yeah...
I thought Eyeshield's legs had reached their limit... He can still run?
Set, hut!
This is a huge surprise - Musashi is blitzing!
You aren't going anywhere!
Musashi overpowers Ojo's linemen and sends them flying!
Takami is forced to get rid of the ball!
You can always depend on Musashan when the going gets tough!
Musashi can bench 100 kilograms, he's second only to Kurita!
I'd say you pressed more than that just now, you old fogy.
I wonder.
All I'll say is EVERYONE from Deimon's improved over these past few months.
One minor success changes nothing.
We'll finish Deimon on the next play, with Ojo's Ballista...
...and Shin!
You really think it'll be that easy, Four-Eyes?
Ojo White Knights 13 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Musashi's reckless blitz prevented any gain on that play.
But Ojo's not finished yet!
Deimon is forced to line up a mere 15 yards from their own goal.
We have no guaranteed way to stop Shin.
What do I do...?
Even if I can't run, I'll stop Shin.
I'll use the what I've gained from all my training and hit Shin head-on!
Stop Shin, w-with the Rip!
- I'll blow Shin up with a hip explosion!
I'll get Shin with the Natsuhiko Gentle Spin!
I'm charging right at Shin!
Shin's getting smashed into the ground!
I'll crush you, Shin!
I can't run, I can't move, but I'll get Shin with spirit!
Th-They're way too obvious...
Everyone's obsessed with the idea of charging straight at Shin.
It's so obvious!
These freaking morons...
Timeou-
Are you taking a timeout or not?
Sometimes, the things that make the least sense make the MOST sense.
This's one of those times.
Nothing's gonna stop the fire in their eyes.
Set, hut!
Shin's the lead blocker again!
- Destroy Shin!
- Not happening!
Here it comes, Takami and Sakuraba's Everest Pass!
Takami read Deimon's defense correctly!
Why didn't Hiruma change the play?
He's not one to make such a nonsensical decision.
What?!
That Butt-Monkey can only see Sakuraba.
Monta!
Sena reminded me of something, Sakuraba!
I can't win if I try to compete with you on height!
I've gotta hit you with everything I've learned up until today!
Bump!
Yeah! Dodge that bump!
That's our Ace Sakuraba!
Watch out!
Sakuraba's off, with Monta in hot pursuit!
Takami, this will be a touchdown! We can finish Deimon!
Why do I have such a bad feeling about this?
Don't tell me, Raimon's...
No... there's no way...
Don't waver. The Everest Pass will work!
The Everest Pass, with its untouchable height!
And there goes the Everest Pass!
One step!
I'm just one step behind!
If I'm gonna catch up, I've gotta rush straight at him without any hesitation!
I can tell from the ball's position, I won't make that one step!
Then...!
Monta!
He's nuts!
This kid, he put all his energy into his legs instead of turning around to block the ball!
His back's to the ball... he's trying an overhead catch?!
He's so high! No... it's just speed!
If I jump now, with his speed... I'll crash right into him!
NO ONE out-catches me!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
What the heck kind of catch did Monta just make?
Even if I'm not looking,
I've caught so many of Hiruma's passes I always know exactly where they are!
Rock on, Monta!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The 9999th Catch!
Ya-ha!
No one beats Monta when it comes to catching,
but Deimon's players are tops in other areas, too!
A kicker no one can out-kick.
A trio no one can out-motivate.
A pair no one can out-eat.
A pair no one can out-signal.
And guy no one can out-pointless bow.
- He's got no competition.
A man no one can out-spin!
A whole team no one can out-stupid.