Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Oh!
- Ya-ha!
That's it! If I can't slow him down...
Touchdown? Did he make it not?!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Final Moment!
If Shin got the ball even a little over the goal line,
Ojo will score a touchdown and win!
But if Deimon successfully stopped him, then they'll win!
Now, who did the goddess of victory smile down upon?!
T-Touchdown!
The Ojo White Knights have flipped the score!
Ojo White Knights 27 - Deimon Devil Bats 22
White Knights! White Knights!
We lost?
- Darn it!
Not yet.
Huh?
It's not over yet.
There's one second left on the game clock!
One second?
It's still too early to give up.
There's still... one second left!
- One second?
It's not over yet?
Hey, Dobie, what'll happen since there's still one second?
Ojo will get to kickoff one last time since they just scored.
But since there's only one second left, the time buzzer will go off right away.
But they'll let the last play...
...run its full course.
So we've gotta catch their kickoff and score a touchdown?
There isn't a one-in-thousand chance of that happening against Ojo!
It's like trying to fit a camel through the eye of a needle.
But still...
But we've still got a chance!
Yeah!
So the game god made a miracle and gave us one second.
No, the miracle-maker here...
...was him.
He really pulled through.
Yuki...
I had it calculated out.
It was supposed to end at exactly zero seconds so Deimon wouldn't get the chance to try something.
During that last play, Manabu Yukimitsu realized that he couldn't stop me,
and before time could run out...
...he sped me through the goal line.
He's a... formidable foe.
Manabu Yukimitsu, I will not forget your name.
It was a logical play born from desperation.
How lame! A loser's desperation is the most disgusting thing out there.
Yuki...
That's all I can do for you.
It wasn't much.
The rest is up to you, Sena...
Ojo White Knights 27 - Deimon Devil Bats 22
I have to get all the way over there in a single play.
There's one second left...
It truly is our last play.
I will score!
Sorry for everything.
I abandoned the team when you needed me.
I wasn't there to help you fight.
Musashi...
That's why...
...I won't let it all end here!
Same here! We're going to the Christmas Bowl together!
Yeah.
Look! That goofy Aha-ha idiot looks so serious.
That shows how serious he's taking this.
Yep.
Hey, Sena.
I never dreamed I'd be out here playing football with you when we first met.
If we hadn't met you...
...we woulda ended up as whiny losers.
Let's go to the Christmas Bowl together!
Everyone's so pumped up, even though they must be exhausted.
But I think that you're probably the most tired.
Despite how fierce this battle's been,
you've stayed in the lead, directing everyone, Hiruma.
Thanks, Suzu...na...
Suzuna?
Don't say it.
I already know.
Since I'm the cheerleading captain, I know I shouldn't be trembling.
During the game with Seibu in the Tokyo Tournament, everything depended on the kickoff...
And in the end, we lost.
That was just too much...
Sena, Mon-Mon, Yocchie, Kuriton and Musashan and everyone...
I'm sorry all I can do is cheer for you!
I'm so sorry, Sena.
All I can do is cheer for you.
Sena, you've just gotta... You must...
It's okay. I'll go win this, Suzuna.
Sena?
Yeah!
Okay, ladies!
Is everyone ready?
Sena, you've gotta catch the ball after they kick it and run.
You've got one chance to get past the perfect player, Shin.
Believe in yourself, Sena!
Must! Win!
Hey, let's do this, Peewe-
No, Eyeshield 21.
Okay!
So it all comes down to this.
Right.
Deimon's offense versus Ojo's defense.
We're back to our roots for the final battle.
Kurita, if we win, I'll finally have gotten back at you for beating me in the Spring Tournament.
But ya know, if I could have,
I would have preferred to get pay back with Deimon in a game at the Christmas Bowl.
Yeah!
But regardless,
the ones finished here are...
- ...you jerks.
- ...you guys.
I finally realized this during the course of this game.
When a football player's standing on the field,
he doesn't say "we might win."
Shin...
Riku...
Agon...
Me...
You've gotta be confident and thrust your chest out as you say,
"I will win!"
"I'm the greatest!"
So I'm going to put this on and face Shin in one last battle.
It signifies that I'm the greatest runner of my generation.
I'm Eyeshield 21!
I'll defeat Shin!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Please tell us, Arima!
You'll be great if you have a strong body and a keen mind along with a strong desire to win.
Everyone, have fun with football! Ya-ha!
It's down to the fateful final second!
Here's the last kickoff!
After they kick the ball and the play ends,
we'll finally see who will be victorious!
Ojo White Knights 27 - Deimon Devil Bats 22
Ojo's five points in the lead.
Now for the fateful kick!
The kicker's...
...Otawara!
They put everything on power rather than technique or distance.
This was unexpected!
Otawara made a super powerful kick!
It went low!
It's going everywhere!
Dang it!
Someone...
...catch it!
No! It's too far away!
Dang, what max-power! That ball's flying around everywhere!
Four-Eyes kept it a secret that Otawara would kick!
This is the choice I made to send Deimon to Hell.
The only one who can catch that crazy ball...
...is just...
...me!
Right. Very good.
I can't!
With my legs,
there's no way I can get past Ojo's ultimate defense and score a touchdown.
Then how about passing?
He can't! He's got no aim!
Think! Think of something!
Turn those gears in my head!
Think! I have 0.2 seconds to think!
Time's up!
We're finished!
No!
After this play, it's game over.
If I don't carry the ball to the goal line, we won't be able to win.
What should I do? Let Monta run the ball?
Don't give up!
If there's even a 0.1% chance of us winning...!
Don't let him pass!
Tackle Raimon. Forget about everyone else!
Darn it!
Don't stop, Monta!
I know! I KNOW!
But... th-there's no way I can get through!
There's not even a 0.1% chance anymore.
0%!
My legs are heavy... Shoot!
Sena, you've been getting past all these incredible players?!
Our only hope's to pass the ball to Eyeshield,
but that monkey's too burnt out to make a pass even if he could aim.
The odds are...zero percent.
He could go for a handoff, but Eyeshield's too far away.
I could yell, "Hey, Peewee! Get over there and take the ball!"
Then he'd run from the other side of the field in 0.1 seconds,
and grab the ball.
He'd never make it in time.
The odds are... 0%.
Crap!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
What should-?
Sena!
What?!
I'm sure Hiruma's thinking up something.
I'm not all that smart and don't know all that much,
but Monta can't move.
Monta's in a pinch!
So I've gotta go get that ball no matter how far away he is!
Sena, I know you can do it!
That runt!
That little peewee moved on his own without me telling him to first.
Yeah, but they're already surrounded.
Deimon's in a bind!
Kurita!
I'm surrounded!
It's over.
Not yet!
If Eyeshield's on his way, then...
Gather up!
I want Eyeshield, Monta, Taki and me, all four of us!
What?!
Don't let him deceive you.
Just focus on Raimon, who has the ball!
What?! Where's the ball?!
What's this? What type of gameplay is this?
I don't know! It's a new strategy!
Where's the ball?
I don't have time to explain, so you'll have to figure it out intuitively.
In one second I'm going to give one of us the ball.
Okay, I got it, Hiruma.
The other three will all be decoys, right?
We'll pretend all four of us have the ball and take different routes to the goal line.
We'll meet up again after we score a touchdown!
Good luck, everyone!
They wouldn't try that on this muddy turf!
It's a trick play where they scatter like hornets from a nest.
It's the Killer Hornets!
Who?! Who's got the ball?!
Logically thinking, Eyeshield should have it.
But is that just to trick us?
Hiruma!
Take advantage of their moment of doubt!
The expected works because we pit it with the unexpected!
Now! Now's my only chance!
Ojo's defense'll be confused for 0.1 seconds!
I only have a brief chance at this!
It's Eyeshield!
Go!
Sena!
Break down Ojo's walls!
Yay!
Sena!
Stop Eyeshield!
Go, Eyeshield 21!
Stop him! STOP HIM!
Whee, it's light speed at 4.2 seconds!
No one can stop him now!
But there's still the last boss.
There's another 4.2 second light speed monster here!
Shin!
Come, Eyeshield 21!
It all ends in this final moment.
Faster... Faster!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
- Please!
Sena!
- Sena!
Go, Eyeshield 21!
Yeah! Use all of your remaining strength now!
It's the last episode of Eyeshield 21:
Everyone, Let's Play Football! Ya-Ha!
Sena, from now on speed'll be your weapon.
Right, Riku!
Let's go!
Wait!
Riku!
Excuse... me.
What's wrong, Sena?
Nothing. I just saw another elementary schooler about our age run by.
He was really fast.
Huh? 100 yen? I dropped it?
Wait, did you follow my car? That's incredible!