- Ya-ha!
- Fire!
He truly is the SHOTGUN Kid!
My eyes couldn't even keep up with his pass!
His passing speed is 0.1 seconds!
He's definitely one of the super advanced high school players!
He's fast!
J-Just now...
...the motion Kid made when he threw the ball...
I couldn't see it...
Hey, bushy-brows!
A handshake?
It's Deimon's playbook for today.
I based all of our plays off of your Quickdraw taking 0.2 seconds.
Now I've got to come up with all new plays!
You always make a big deal over everything
to get into our heads and joggle us up.
Those cards, your weapons and even that scary hairdo are all part of the plan.
I'm finally figuring out these mind games of yours.
Not bad.
Kid won't be forgetting how Hiruma
tackled him from his blind spot.
He'll have to pay close attention to everyone for the rest of the game now.
The underdog has always had to rely on crazy strategies.
It's important to set up as many as they can.
All right then!
Let's use our killer anti-shotgun play!
Yeah!
'Course we'll use it!
We even wore handcuffs to prepare for this moment!
Let's topple them!
It's bumping time!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't."  You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero.  What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Field of Despair!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 7 - Deimon Devi Bats 6
It's seven to six with Seibu in the lead by one point!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Will they be able to get any more points?!
They're down to 32 yards
and Seibu's Shotgun offense is still being executed!
We've trained hard for this!
We'll finish them off!
Great! Let's go!
Set, hut!
We did it!
What?!
Amazing!
Seibu's receivers have been defeated!
Impressive. Now I can't throw the ball.
The Deimon Devil Bats have done a marvelous job
preventing Kid from making any passes!
The Bump Strategy was a big success!
Everyone's wonderful!
Kid, they're going to use bumps.
Should we set up a counter strategy?
Nah, we don't really need to.
Bumping doesn't work on him, does it?
It's The Human Locomotive, Tetsuma!
He's finally entered the field!
Now for the real fight, Butt-monkey.
You're the only one who can stop him.
Got it!
Go cut lose, Tetsuma!
Tetsuma!
Er, since you're older I guess I should say Mr. Tetsuma!
I remember back when the two of us
were playing together in the beach football tournament.
We made such a team that we became legendary.
Where'd he become legendary?
In his head.
But now we're on different teams.
Today I'm going to defeat you
and prove to the world that I'm Tokyo's greatest receiver!
Um, Mr. Tetsuma...?
Oh, hey, shouldn't you say something, too?
I will complete my task.
Anything you do is futile.
Your defense means nothing to me.
I will catch the ball where ever it is thrown.
That is all.
Man, his eyes are so... cold!
There are three key showdowns in this game:
the battle of receivers with Raimon and Tetsuma,
the battle of running backs with Eyeshield and Kaitani...
And the battle of quarterbacks with Hiruma and Kid, right?
Set, hut!
Tetsuma, slant!
The receivers' showdown is up first.
Eat this! Heart Bump!
It isn't working.
Touchdown!
Seibu's Tetsuma got an overwhelming victory in the battle of receivers!
We can't stop him...
So that's Tetsuma's power!
He's too strong.
Our training was all worthless!
Monta...
He's amazingly powerful.
There's no fighting him!
The extra point conversion's kick was a success!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 14 - Deimon Devi Bats 6
It's now 14-6! Seibu's in the lead big time!
We're not done yet.
The fight's just beginning!
He's huge!
I'll show you just how strong Seibu is with these two horns of mine!
What's he yapping about?
If he's just a big blockhead...
...we'll simply crush him!
Set, hut!
Seibu's Ushijima is rushing after Hiruma in order to intercept the pass!
I won't let you! C'mon!
Eat this!
Twin Horns!
What was that?!
It looks like the pro wrestling move, western lariat!
He's not done yet!
Jumonji, next he'll-
You're pretty clever, aren't you?
Because my left arm is my other horn!
- Darn it! Stop him!
Ready for more?!
Twin Horns!
He even flattened Hiruma!
Deimon's pass is incomplete!
Their line being broken so easily has gotta hurt.
That's not fair!
Isn't it against the rules?
It's like he fused two of Komusubi's Rips
from our game against Kyoshin together.
So it's their own fault if he knocks them down.
Football is just that type of sport.
No way...
Besides, Suzie...
This isn't some sissy game.
It's a deadly world of fists and fighting.
Ushijima! Ushijima!
Argh!
I can't stop him!
Guys...
Sena!
This is Seibu, Sena.
We attack even if it means we'll get hurt.
We attack even on defense!
How interesting.
The more I see, the more I think our policies are alike.
But they're not the only ones who are super offensive.
If they get 99 points, we'll get 100 points and win!
Set, hut!
Wow! Eyeshield 21 is running around to the sidelines!
Riku!
Sena!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to catch a long pass!
The key point is your head?
When you want to catch a long pass,
make sure to only move your head so you don't decelerate.
Don't let your eyes leave the ball!
Ya-ha!
- Eyeshield!
Go, Peewee!
Stop him, Riku!
Sena, you've improved a lot since we were classmates.
But I don't want to admit it!
I can't admit that your speed's a match for my own!
I'm just a little faster.
Really?
Great! Then I can get through!
He's using the Devil Bat Ghost?!
But, Sena, you still can't defeat me!
Take this! Rodeo Drive!
He stole the ball!
It's Seibu's ball!
Good going!
Riku!
He's pretty good.
He stole the ball on top of tackling him!
He has good control over his speed
both when he's on offense and when he tackles!
He's the terrifying rookie ace, Riku Kaitani!
Why?
I know that I'm faster than him!
So how did he get right in front of me?
I've fought and defeated you 94 times now.
That's pretty lame, Sena!
What do you think the difference between us is
when our speed's about the same?
What's different... between us?
It's pride.
Pride?
Sena, just now you instinctively tried to protect yourself from my tackle.
"I won't let anyone defeat me."
Only those with that level of pride...
...can sacrifice themselves to protect the ball.
It's all for the ball!
What was I thinking?
I can't believe I gave him a hint!
Right now, Sena and I are rivals!
Our pride?
Only those with that level of pride...
...can sacrifice themselves to protect the ball.
Seibu's easily winning all of the position-based showdowns.
All that's left is...
Kid versus Hiruma,
the showdown between quarterbacks!
Peewee,
we're blitzing them again!
But the blitz won't work!
Shut up! We're blitzing anyway!
O-Okay!
Set, hut!
GO!
They're blitzing again!
Hiruma, you idiot!
Don't you understand that a blitz won't work on the Kid?!
The zone Hiruma was protecting is wide open!
Kid's taking the opening and shooting his Quick-and-Fire!
I warned you!
You should fall to the back and go heavy on the defense!
Quit attacking them!
They're using the BLITZ again!
Give it up!
Push forward like nuts!
Why's he doing this?
The more they blitz the fewer people there are in the back.
Kid's pass rate is going to hit 100% soon!
Hiruma, let's give it up...
No, just go after them even more!
Go crush that darned bushy-brows!
Go blitz 'em, kiddies!
They're blitzing yet AGAIN!
What's gotten into Hiruma?
It looks like he's completely lost his cool.
Is it because Kid's Quickdraw was faster than expected,
which threw off Hiruma's plans?
So the strategist has fallen victim to his own strategies?
His computer-like intelligence can't handle it
when something unexpected happens.
He's so fragile.
Darn that Hiruma!
What's gotten into him?
Just like Hiruma predicted before the game,
Kid's Quickdraw has sped up by one and a half times!
Someone from the bench is sending out some sorta signal.
It looks like she's telling him a game play.
Set!
Hut!
Hey!
Kid, time to face me!
Now Kuroki's blitzing forward!
But now the position Kuroki was supposed to be protecting is left wide open!
Someone...
...cover for him!
That's nuts!
We can't keep Tetsuma in line
AND protect someone else's area!
Get those extra points!
Kid, throw a touchdown pass!
If this pass gets through,
Seibu will have two touchdowns in a row!
I get it!
He's mine!
How'd front lineman Kurita get back there?!
Kurita's supposed to be painfully slow!
How'd he sneak back there?!
Hiruma... He's nuts!
What's going on?
It's a modern football play called the "Zone Blitz."
When Kuroki ran forward,
Kurita left his spot in the front of the line
and snuck to the back.
All of a sudden a huge wall appears
where there wasn't supposed to be anyone!
The first blitz failing,
then pressing Kid to make his Quickdraws
and even acting like he'd lost his cool...
It was all done to set up this trap.
By riling him up and adding on the pressure,
he forced Kid to speed up his Quickdraw.
Meaning that Kid was throwing his passes too quickly?
- He did it!
- Yay!
Yocchie, your plan worked!
We did it, Kurita!
Catch that pass!
I'll definitely catch it!
We've practiced for this... Huh?
I don't see the ball anywhere!
What's going on?
Where's the ball?
Kurita, it's not in the air!
Darn that Kid!
Look down!
Oh, my!
Just when we thought Kid had thrown a pass,
he does a feint and runs through the opening
created by Kurita going to the back!
Unbelievable!
He saw through Hiruma's scheme right at the last minute!
Uh-oh!
Hiruma's chasing after him!
Yoichi Hiruma...
...was never gifted with an athlete's body.
He's made it this far thanks to his fierce training and sharp wits.
Hiruma was the only one who noticed Kid start to run.
But he was still too slow.
Kid has won the battle of wits.
Touchdown!
No... way...
Hiruma...
Won by a hair!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
This is bad!
The Wild Gunmen are attacking like mad and Hiruma's given up!
If only Musashi were here now!
Quit your whining!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Musashi is Right Here! Ya-ha!
I can't believe it!
So Hiruma's strategies won't work on him.
But I bet Yocchie is just letting it look like they won
and actually has some other plan up his sleeve.
It's not over yet, right?!
Mamo,
how many strategies did Hiruma come up with?
All together, there were 17.
But now, I don't think any...
None of them will work...
...so long as the Kid's here.
It's my first time seeing Hiruma look like this.