Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Ya-ha!
- Oh!
I'm the best...
...in the world!
I won't let you get it!
Deimon's pass fails!
Awesome!
Way to go Sakuraba!
Sakuraba!
Even with Hiruma's dead-on prediction, Deimon is left with no other options!
A third pass fails! THIS is Ojo's invincible rampart!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Kingdom's Ballista.
You see that, Deimon?
Sakuraba's height makes him like a huge castle wall!
You're compressing me, Otawara...
Quit gawking, you midgets!
Right...
Sorry...
We're still on offense.
That's right... we've still got a chance.
40 yards between Deimon and the end zone.
Deimon has thrown three incomplete passes in a row.
We're still so far away...
Deimon's in a tough spot... They've tried the same play three times with no result.
If it happens again, Ojo goes on offense and takes away all of Deimon's momentum.
I don't like how this's going...
What do I do...?
Guess I'm up.
We can score first with a field goal.
Musashi?
You old fogy, you think you can really land one from all the way back here?
You're the one who named me the "60-yard Magnum."
That's right, we still have a chance at three points if Musashi kicks it in!
Then get out there and show 'em your best stuff.
For real?
A kick?
Oh ho, could this be...?
They're kicking?
Guess they're settling for a field goal...
Apparently.
That's no fun.
It seems Deimon will go for a field goal despite the distance!
Can they come away with three points?
Even the so-called "60-yard Magnum," Musashi,
doesn't have much of a chance at this distance with all the rain.
Seriously? We're way far away from the goal.
Can he really sink it from back here?
It'll end up being about 57 yards from the kick tee to the goalposts.
Realistically, the odds are absolutely terrible.
You guys gained all this ground against Ojo's iron defense... I can't let it all go to waste.
I'll make this.
Listen, everyone.
Considering the distance and the weather,
they don't have much chance of making this to begin with,
but don't take any chances.
They're not doing this out of desperation.
Shin?
That man WILL make this play successful.
What?
What are you talking about, Shin?
Don't you remember our scrimmage against Deimon last April?
We won 99-0, but we only saw him kick once.
He even deflected Musashi's kick...
How? How?!
The strength... The angle...
It would have gone in if I hadn't touched it.
With his power and speed, this rain won't change a thing.
If we don't block the kick somehow, it WILL go in.
So we'll smash 'em before he even kicks the ball!
He won't have time to get his foot near it!
That's right! Put the screws to them!
Musashan, kick it to the moon!
Please, Musashi...
This is the best we can do... It's all on you!
It's just like the last time.
No, it's completely different.
This time we've got THEM.
They will stop Ojo!
Musashi...
So you're saying this one'll go in no problem, eh, grandpa?
You bet.
He's calculating it...
Considering the distance, the rain, the wind...
Don't worry, Musashi!
We'll block every last one of 'em so you can kick it right up there-
Monta!
Uhh, well I mean, how should I say this...
I think we should leave the three of them alone for a minute is all...
Our job is to give them space to focus on the kick.
Right... we won't let Ojo near them!
Set, hut, hut...
Come on already!
Hut, hut...
Shoot, it's Shin!
We can't stop him!
Gotta slow Shin down...
Those eyes...
I'm right in his face...
...but he has no fear!
Go in!
Make it!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Japan's biggest football championship is the WHAT Bowl?
Your hint is "rice!"
The college and semi-pro champions face each other
in the annual "Rice Bowl" for the title of best Japanese team!
Never stop charging until you win the championship! Ya-ha!
It's... good.
It's good!
The Deimon Devil Bats score first and lead 3-0!
Musashi has just landed an incredible field goal from an astounding 57 yards!
And for the first time in the Kanto Tournament, Ojo has been scored upon!
He did it!
That kick was awesome!
- THAT kick was awesome!
Your kicks are always so rough, old man.
Sometimes I can't even bear to watch, they're so ugly.
It went in, what do you care?
Ojo White Knights 0 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Ojo White Knights 0 - Deimon Devil Bats 3
Yay! Deimon scored first!
This is amazing, we haven't scored first in forever!
We can do this!
No... THIS is where it starts getting tough.
I'll say he's the 60-yard Magnum...
Musashi...
You see that through all your chains, loser?
When it comes to kicks, no one beats that old codger!
That old relic can't do anything!
Don't badmouth the old guy!
He's no ordinary old grandpa!
He's just some old fart!
Old...
Settle down, Ikari.
It was still just a field goal, only three points.
Ojo's defense still hasn't permitted a single touchdown.
That's right!
We just need our new and improved offense to score a touchdown on them!
Musashi kicks off and the game resumes!
Deimon finally tackles Ojo's returner.
Ojo will start their offense from their own 45 yard line!
Let's go.
We'll introduce Deimon to the strongest offense in Ojo's long history.
Gonna play your best card right away, huh?
If you were in my shoes, you'd use everything you had to try and end it early,
wouldn't you?
Here comes the attack that destroyed Ojo's golden generation.
The new Ojo offense...
Ojo's offense has taken the field, and among them...
...is Seijuro Shin!
For the first time ever, Japan's best high school linebacker is playing offense!
And with the addition of Shin, Ojo has been able to completely revamp its offensive strategy!
The strongest offensive formation in Ojo history...
Shin, and his Trident Tackle... will be running.
Here it comes...
The Ballista!
We won't use any tricks or feints like Hiruma.
THIS is Ojo's new offensive formation.
The line and I are like a bow...
...but we aren't knocked with some run-of-the-mill arrow.
We have a massive spear named Seijuro Shin.
This... THIS is the Ballista.
And I'll tell you upfront, Deimon.
Ojo's first play is will be a charge right up the middle.
This is unheard of...
Is Takami attempting to steal Hiruma's reputation as a master of psychological warfare?!
Is he...?
No way...
Telling us would make defending the play so much easier...
Here they come.
Set!
Wait, what is this?!
Shin has started running in the opposite direction!
- Hut...
- What the...?!
What's going on here?!
He's coming!
Hut!
They're seriously doing a charge up the middle, like he said?!
He's coming, it wasn't a bluff!
They're really running it up the middle!
But how...?
Even Shin can't pull off a charge up the middle when we all know about it!
Don't sell us short-
What destructive power!
Seijuro Shin will not be stopped!
Even Jumonji is tossed aside!
That first run he did was to give himself room to build momentum
so he could bash through the line at top speed!
Stop him, Fatty!
Can Deimon's final stronghold, Kurita, snap the giant spear's flight?!
Kurita can do it!
Kurita!
Musashi made his kick!
Now I have to make this block!
- Stop him!
He did it!
Way to go, Kurita!
The heaviest lineman in Kanto, Ryokan Kurita puts his 145 kilogram bulk to good use!
In a close quarter standoff, he's invincible!
WHAT?!
No WAY!
He lifted that huge titan Kurita right off his feet!
This isn't a technique like my Spider Poison, or a natural gift like Agon's reflexes.
This is pure speed and power.
Unbeatable strength born from relentless training.
Oh no!
The Ojo White Knights get a first down on a huge gain!
Thanks to the terrifying Ballista, to the terrifying strength of Seijuro Shin!
So simple... He's the strongest...
Nothing can stop a prodigy who puts forth effort.
Shin... he's a true monster on the field.
This formation where Shin moves backwards first is exactly like an arrow being drawn back.
The enemy is drawn forward, and the arrow is fired right into their ranks.
The very essence of a ballista...
I-I... I don't understand...
Even Kurita couldn't stop Shin...
Man! These guys-
Even if we know what they're gonna do, we can't stop 'em!
Exactly.
Regardless of whether or not you see it coming, the Ballista is unstoppable.
I'll tell you in advance this time, too.
We're firing the Ballista to the right.
Stinkin' Four-Eyes...
What now, Hiruma?
Ojo's Ballista is incredible...
But if we don't stop it... if we don't stop Shin...
...we can't win.
What do we do...?!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Whoa! Shin's speed and power are outta this world!
This is the Ballista... Shin at his most serious!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Impregnable Fortress!
Ya-ha!
You see how sick the Ballista is, losers?!
Say what? You wanna go right now?!
Bring it on!
Dude...in some ways, this is the ultimate showdown.
The dog won!
Cerberus, get out here and stop the Ballista, too!