That's the end for Eyeshield.
I'm scared...
I'm so scared!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Terror of the Chameleon!
Time to change strategies!
Thank goodness! Now I won't get tackled anymore.
Listen up, Butt-Monkey!
'Kay!
Got it?!
We crushed their trump card, Eyeshield!
This'll be so easy now!
Set, hut!
Take that!
He passed it over to #80, just like I predicted.
Squash him, guys!
Shoot!
Eyeshield, pass! Huh?
Sena's... so far off...
Peewee...!
Oh, no! What happened to Sena?
He's so scared that his legs turned to mush.
Sena...
Monta...
Monta!
That hurts!
Just kidding! Don't worry about it!
I'm counting on you next time!
Keep it up!
Don't make that face!
There's nothing to worry about as long as we keep an eye on that monkey #80.
Set, hut, hut!
You can do it, Devil Bats!
Nice catch, Monta!
Max Catch!
Mamori, please watch me!
This is my Super Catch!
Eyeshield, pass! Huh? He's not here?!
Are you okay, Monta?
Never mind, don't worry 'bout it.
Quit worrying to the max!
I see!
So the strategy is to have Monta do the catching and Eyeshield do the running.
But why isn't Eyeshield running like normal?
I wonder what's wrong?
Let's change our strategy!
We managed to squeak by a 10 yard gain,
but they were able to completely figure out our strategy.
At this rate they'll kill Monta!
Shut up!
Hiruma!
We'll try running again.
But-!
Didn't you hear me tell you to shut your trap, Fatty?
But...
Now that they're ticked off they're going to lean on Eyeshield even more!
It's just as I planned.
I have to go, but my leg's won't move!
I'm scared... I'm so scared that I can't run!
Set, hut, hut!
Sena!
Monta, you can do it!
Aren't the Devil Bats using the exact same strategy over and over?
At this rate, #80 will get smashed!
Raimon!
You can do it, Monta!
Don't lose!
Squash them!
Don't worry about it, okay?
I wonder what's wrong with Eyeshield?
Hiruma, are we going to keep doing this?
Monta's just about reached his limit!
Hiruma...
Monta, I'm sorry! It's all my fault.
That monkey #80 has reached his limit.
We'll put him outta his misery in the next play.
Yeah!
Set, hut, hut!
Great! Now that monkey boy's finished.
Monta!
You can do it, Monta!
Raimon!
Monta, you shouldn't over do it.
I can still go on! It'll be a breeze!
Pumped-up to the max!
The Devil Bats have changed so much since Monta joined,
but at this rate none of that will actually matter!
But...
I'm scared.
I'm hopelessly scared.
I'm scared! I'm so scared!
Sena!
I'm sorry, Monta. It's all my fault.
Never mind! Don't worry 'bout it!
I believe in you.
You have your legs, and your legs are the BEST!
Okay! Let's do it aga... Whoops... To the max!
Even though Monta's been beaten up so badly, he's still trying hard, while I....
I've gotta change!
This time I HAVE to change myself!
Okay! Let's go!
We've crushed both Eyeshield and that monkey #80.
It'll be a one-sided fight from here on.
Gotta change... No, I WILL change!
Set, hut, hut!
MAX Catch!
Fool! Struggling is meaningless now!
Sena!
He doesn't have the ball!
Go, Eyeshield 21!
I'm gonna change!
Trample him!
Great! It's our first down!
You did it, Monta, Eyeshield!
Nice run!
And your catch was great!
Sena, I've always believed in you.
Monta!
Yay! We did it!
It's not like we're done yet.
But he's really happy!
No more going easy on 'em!
We'll crush them our way!
Set, hut, hut!
How horrible! That's against the rules!
But I'm not even holding the ball!
Shut up!
They're everywhere!
So they've finally shown their true colors.
Are you okay, Sena?
Huh?
I'm fine.
It's because of your special neck training!
Yeah!
But I don't think that's everything.
I can't really describe it, but it feels like there's a power gap.
Power gap?
I've fought with people way more impressive than them before.
Well, that's it.
What do you mean?
He means-
Is everyone okay?!
There's no way we can continue the game!
What should we do?
I'll hear none of that!
We'll just send out three replacements.
You've got three other replacements?
It must be tough for a small team, huh?
Violence is a type of strategy, ya know!
There's no way we'll lose! No way!
But our team doesn't have any back-up players...
Hurry up! It's show time, you three Ha-Ha Brothers!
Otherwise, I've got that picture.
Okay, fine!
But let us tell you one thing! We're not brothers!
Some new guys came out.
We'll crush them!
What a pain!
Beats having those pictures thrown around everywhere.
You jerk!
Wanna fight? HUH?!
Don't underestimate us!
Go for it!
I'll beat it into your body that Rui Habashira is the strongest!
Football Clinic!
What's Monta's position?
He's a wide receiver!
It's the position where you run into enemy territory and catch the pass!
The position's given to players who are good at catching! Ya-ha!
I won't lose!
You can do it!
Go!
I won't lose!
What?!
He did it!
Go!
Go, Eyeshield!
He did it!
Awesome! That's beyond the speed a normal human can run!
So that's Eyeshield!
Awesome!
Go, Devil Bats!
I did it!
We did it!
Nice Run!
We've won.
That's a 16 yard gain!
Stop him!
A 9 yard gain!
Stupid idiots! Everyone, stop Eyeshield!
But then someone else will be able to get through elsewhere.
Amazing! It's 34-21!
It's our first time taking the lead like this!
We are definitely getting stronger!
Quit stating the obvious, Fatty!
Set, hut, hut!
Max Catch!
Of course Eyeshield's great, but Monta's really amazing, too!
It's amazing how much the team can change in football when you pull off a good pass.
Football's great!
I think it's obvious, but we're not letting them score another point!
Crush those three losers before they throw another lame pass.
How are you feeling, Three Brothers?
We're not brothers!
I bet you're tired. You can take a little break.
Hey, Eyeshield 21, come here!
Set, hut, hut!
It's Eyeshield 21!
Keep a close eye on him!
He doesn't have it!
I won't let them trick me!
They'll pass to the monkey!
Smash him before he throws the ball!
Your area's full of nothin'...
...but holes!
Holes? Then we'll open up a hole here.
Shoot!
It's a screen pass!
The block's 2-to-1!
YA-HA!
A screen pass is kinda like this,
where you intentionally let the opponent slip through right here.
Once the opponents have spread out, you block them 2-to-1.
In the meantime, you pass the ball to the side and then dash through the hole in the wall!
Huh? My screen time's over? Hey, hey! No fair, senorita!
He's here!
It's a game between the aces!
A game between aces?
They're no challenge for us!
I won't let you through, no matter what!
I'm not scared...
This is nothing compared to Shin!
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
Shin? He's trash!
No, his speed wasn't like this.
I could only get by him once, but my goal is to be like Shin!
We've got to change even more!
Both the Devil Bats and I do!
It's all so we can fight against Shin again at the fall tournament!
So we can't let ourselves get held back!
It doesn't matter how long his arms are!
He lacks the speed!
He's on a different level. They're totally different!
They're worlds apart!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
WHAT?!
We won!
Great!
He's not done yet.
Eyeshield 21 can still get even faster!
Yep!
Victory for the Devil Bats!
Great job, Eyeshield!
Thanks for your support! Max thanks!
Hey, we did it!
Yeah, thank you. Monta, it's all thanks to you!
What are you talking about? You'll make me blush!
But...
But?
We've still got a long ways to go when compared to Shin.
We've got to keep our goals highs!
After all, there's a whole bunch more great people out there!
Why're you trying to act all cool-like?
No, it's not like I was trying to...
Shut up! Let's enjoy the happiness we earned today!
You're probably right, but...
There's no "buts" or "strikes" to it! I'll leave Eyeshield behind!
Don't do that!
Isn't it great? The Devil Bats have gotten stronger!
It's the first time we've had a game that was really like football.
Don't cry over something like this!
I'm going to set my goals even higher!
Hey, guys, what did we promise the losers would have to do again?
Master Hiruma!
You're going to be my slaves for a while!
So that's how he gets his slaves...
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
Why? Why is it?
I heard that there's a flood of people wanting to join the football team!
That's right! And so now we've got to give them tryouts, but...
We're holding it at TOKYO TOWER?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Scorching HELL TOWER! Ya-ha!
Hey, hey! There's another crazy poster up!
Football's so cool!
Man, I can't see!
Maybe I should join.
Don't. I hear it really hurts.
Hey, there's something written about us up there!
I'd be okay!
It says you'll be a chick magnet!
Might be nice.
What's it say?
Let's see, let's see!
"Looking for Possible New Recruits!"
"Hey guys, listen up!"
"Play football if you wanna be a lady killer!"
"Play football if you wanna get better at fighting!"
"Play football if you wanna get rich!"
"Just shut up and follow me!"
That sounds just like Hiruma.
"From, Eyeshield 21."
I'm falling! I'm falling!