Suck on this!
Nice one.
Looks like football's paying off.
Football?!
Don't say that word, it makes me wanna puke!
I've got mail.
Ya-ha! Where might the Ha-Ha Brothers be wasting their time today?
Get your butts to the clubhouse.
You wouldn't want those pictures uncensored and released to the public, right?
Curse that Hiruma...
What's all this?
Everyone watch closely...
The new clubhouse is open for business! Ya-ha!
There's... a whole new building!
Ya-ha!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
A Slacker's Pride
C-Cool!
It's all sparkly!
We've all got our own lockers!
There's my name...
Let's be good neighbors to each other, Komusubi!
That tears it...
Listen up, people!
I've got something to say to all of you!
My name is Taro Raimon!
Stop making fun of me by calling me that stupid nickname "Monta-"
I got it from Joe Montana.
The greatest superstar in NFL history.
He's the closest thing there is to a football god.
His arm was the force behind countless comeback victories... They called it "Montana Magic."
That's so cool!
Monta Magic!
So cool!
Everyone, please, call me "Monta" from now on!
Why do we have to share a locker?
We keep telling them we're not brothers...
What?
You little-!
Enough, just ignore him.
We're not gonna be here much longer, anyway.
It's party time!
We're celebrating the opening of our new clubhouse!
We sure earned it! We played hard against Zokugaku!
And we've certainly put in a great deal of practice.
I hope we "loaners" are useful to the team, too.
Of course you are!
The Devil Bats wouldn't even be able to play if it weren't for you all.
Oh, well, when you put it like that, Mamori...
I guess I'll have a bite!
Those three...
Whew, I'm stuffed!
I couldn't eat another bite.
I may have had too much...
Manajerk.
American Football Monthly?
Read the page I bookmarked.
Oh, sure...
"The Aliens, from America's X High School are coming to Japan!"
"They seek a Japanese high school football team to face them on the gridiron!"
X High is one of America's premier football schools, they must be one of the best!
Hey, they want to play right in the middle of the Kanto tournament!
None of the teams still in the tournament could play.
So the only available teams are the weaker ones?
No team would be reckless enough to challenge them, right?
I sent in our application two days ago.
S-So reckless!
What's wrong?
It's from American Football Monthly!
"Thank you for your application. The winning team, chosen via random lottery, was the Taiyo Sphinx."
Oh boo, we didn't get picked.
Actually, I kinda feel disappointed AND relieved.
That was too quick for it to have been a random lottery.
Hey, Fatty. We're going to American Football Monthly's office tomorrow.
Huh?!
Man, it's too hot, I don't have the energy.
Do they even want to be here?
They always get like that as soon as Hiruma leaves.
Okay, so, the line!
When we run the ball, our job is to open up a path in front of us.
When we pass, our job is to stay back and protect the quarterback.
So basically, if the line isn't solid, we can't do anything.
It used to be I was alone and we couldn't do anything anyway.
But now we've got five whole people!
If we all train hard, we'll be a really strong line when fall comes around!
That's right, the only two guys who're a problem are both gone.
This is our chance to look for the negatives.
Nice idea!
Let's do it.
The Taiyo Sphinx were chosen to face the Aliens through an impartial random lottery.
But we got this text yesterday, Mr. Editor-in-Chief.
What's that? "The winning team that will face X High,
chosen via random lottery, was the incomparable Deimon Devil Bats."
"Congratulations, ya-ha. Editor-in-Chief of American Football Monthly?!"
I sent no such thing!
Then who DID send it, hm?
Hiruma, don't tell me you snuck into he- OUCH!
But the team we contacted was-
Uhh, chief?
It definitely came from us.
It's in the log.
What?!
What is going on here!
We hand-picked Taiyo before the article was even published!
Before the article was even published, you say?
I thought as much.
This "impartial lottery" never even happened.
Chief?
Harao!
We're here to discuss the Aliens game.
Th-That's Taiyo Sphinx's Banba!
Taiyo Sphinx, Mamoru Banba. Squat high school record holder.
Taiyo Sphinx, Kiminari Harao. Position: Quarterback
Taiyo Sphinx, Niinobu Kasamatsu. Position: Lineman
Err, actually...
Actually, the Aliens will be facing us, the Deimon Devil Bats.
So you're all free to go home.
Excuse me?
Who do you think you are?
Th-The thing is, somehow the Deimon Devil Bats ended up getting a message saying they won, so...
So just ignore it, eh?!
You chose us to be their opponents from the start!
Deimon's playing this one.
Hop a train back home and get back to your tanning beds.
H-Hiruma...
Deimon's a garbage team, you don't stand a chance, eh?!
You'd shame Japan.
You're saying you're better than us?
Clearly!
You think you can best us?
Let's find out.
A game to see who represents Japan!
Nope, nothing.
Where did he put those stupid things?
P-Practice!
You stinkin'-!
Don't mess with us!
Practice!
Stupid midget!
Kuroki, gimme a hand!
Now! Smash him, Jumonji!
Argh, he's some kinda freak!
Football Clinic!
What does "NFL" stand for?
National Football League!
It's America's top professional league!
Their power and speed are the greatest in the world! Ya-ha!
You've been mocking us long enough.
It takes all three of you... to beat me.
What?!
Komusubi's taking a long time.
Think we should check on him?
What're you waiting for?!
Do it!
Hey, what's wrong?
Jumonji?
Where're you going?
Hey, wait up!
What're you doing?
You going somewhere?
I'm going home.
What're you talking about?
Have you lost it?
What about the pictures?!
Who cares?!
Wha-? "Who cares?"
Umm, where are you-
We quit.
We've had enough.
Why should we train? We never cared about any of this.
Go ahead and tell Hiruma, we don't care.
If you change your minds, will you come back?
We'll be waiting... Especially Kurita, he...
It couldn't be helped... I mean, they just left outta nowhere.
I told you, remember? They never had any motivation in the first place.
I wonder...
I mean, in the Zokugaku game,
they all looked like they were really enjoying themselves!
Yeah, that's a good point...
Football is fun.
I think if they just kept playing, they'd understand the appeal, too.
Maybe...
I mean, I've only just come to realize how great of a sport it is.
Sena!
My fault.
Komusubi, are you okay?
The battle to represent Japan is on!
The battle to represent Japan?
Our opponents are the Taiyo Sphinx.
So the Sphinx have this incredible line.
I don't know if we can beat them...
Stop wetting your pants, Fatty!
We just have to use our line effectively!
That's right!
We finally have a full five people to play the line!
That reminds me, where are those boneheaded brothers?
Well, you see-
Uhh, they didn't come to practice today.
Come on, Sena, they're not gonna come to practice tomorrow, either.
Let's at least try to convince them.
Are you sure about this, Sena?
Don't worry, Mamori.
This is one of my duties as team manager.
Sena...
There they are!
Come back to the team!
You?
Komusubi?
Get real! We quit. Q-U-I-T.
P-Please!
What a pest! Let GO!
Komusubi, careful!
Are you sure you won't rethink this?
Oh, first Fatty Jr. and now the manager?
We're playing the Taiyo Sphinx to determine who'll represent Japan.
The Devil Bats need a strong line.
Come back and play football with us!
So you want us back on the team because YOU need us?
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean it like that. I just thought you might have come to like it...
Us? Liking football?
That's a good one, man.
But during the Zokugaku game, you looked like you were having a blast!
Come on.
Dorks.
Don't ever come near us again!
Here's your ord- EEK!
That editor had no idea what he was doing.
You bet.
Now we're stuck in a game we shouldn't have even had to play, eh?
We're only playing Deimon. It will be an easy win.
Good point!
Come on in!
They're huge!
Must be sumo wrestlers.
They're like Kurita-sized.
Congressman Habashira has a very close relationship with my father's company.
Habashira?
His son's team played Deimon a few days ago.
According to him, numbers 51, 52 and 53 on Deimon's line are all complete trash.
Let's hope they haven't quit yet, eh?
It doesn't matter. We win with our own ability.
Sorry to interrupt, but I happen to be #51.
Who're you overcooked turkeys calling trash?
Can we see you outside for a sec?
We don't need the bat.
We'll bust them up with bare hands.
Banba, you've got one minute to deal with them.
One minute's much too long.
I'll give it another try tomorrow.
Hey, that's-
Ten seconds on the dot.
Lousy...!
You three're just a bunch of small fries, eh?
You call yourselves a line?
Keep trying. I'll show you what a real blocker is.
Blocker...
Okay, when you're pushing back a blocker,
you have to put your palms under their armpit, squeeze, and-
Remember this, you filthy trash...
This is the power of the Sphinx.
For a moment, he seemed to get stronger.
Let us depart.
You trash stay there in your dumpster, eh?
A-Are you guys okay?!
Beat it!
B-But you're all-
Shut up!
We just got bullied, huh?
Pipe down.
How'd it go, Sena?
I see...
I thought we finally had a full set of linemen...
I'm sorry...
Stop wasting your breath pining for guys who aren't coming back!
Time to train! Run!
How do we win on the line?
You really came back!
We don't let anyone throw us around!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Oh, "We don't let anyone throw us around," huh?
Glad your heads are in the game, but our opponents are unstoppable!
Even Kurita's been knocked on his back by the Sphinx's Pyramid Line!
This is a chance to show them what you're made of!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Lower-class Laughs at its Challengers! Ya-ha!
How do you win on the line?
Yeah. Tell us what to do.
All right, I'll teach you.
What's with the rope?
We're all tied together?
Cerberus!
You and your brothers need more stamina!
It's great to finally have the brothers motivated, isn't it?
We told you, we're not even related!