Survivors vs. Devil Bats
- Let's go!
First...
Speed!
Now me!
Power!
And finally,
Technique!
- You're going down!
What?
Repeated Devil Bat Ghosts!
Touchdown!
Game over!
The championship game is today!
The competitors are...
Representing the Asian region,
the demons amongst demons,
the devil kings themselves,
the Deimon Devil Bats!
And representing Europe and Russia,
the pulsating Aurora Borealis,
The Northern Light Blizzards!
The cup's as good as ours.
As I always say,
talent is everything in this game!
You rag-tag kids are about to learn what talent is, like it or not.
You're forgetting something, Afro-Man.
Talent can take you so far.
Hard work can take you ANYWHERE.
And they're about to prove it.
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Silver Snow's Secret Weapon.
Four schools nominated to represent their corner of the world
in this amazing football event.
The first ever international Cream Puff Cup championship!
The Deimon Devil Bats vs.
the Northern Light Blizzards!
The match is mere moments away!
It doesn't get any more exciting!
Go, go, Devil Bats!
Put them away!
Sena, go get 'em!
Coach...
Coach!
You decided to come watch!
Hey, it's Apollo.
Did you set this up?
Who, me?
Please, help us reform the Shuttles!
We still want to play football!
All of us, with you, coach!
We're not quitters.
No matter how high the mountain is, we'll keep climbing!
Exactly!
We're all in it for the long haul!
What do you say?
It doesn't matter what you say,
a losing team is still a losing team!
The Devil Bats...
Watch how the Devil Bats play.
You think your friends down there can show me anything?
What can THEY do?
Please, wait.
It's true that individually,
none of us really stack up against the Blizzards.
But we... we're NOT on our own.
We've got each other to rely on.
Our team managed to win against stronger opponents
because we stick together!
We fight as one!
And I'll play, for myself, for my teammates!
And for Panther, Homer, and Watt!
We'll prove it in this game!
We're not just parts in a machine!
Guts and effort always win!
Justice will prevail!
So don't just turn your back!
You lousy brats.
Don't you dare talk down to me.
Fine.
I'll watch this game.
No matter how badly you embarrass yourselves.
Don't hold back.
Crush them until there's nothing left!
In the name of the great northern expanses,
our offense will barrel through like a relentless blizzard!
Our defense will stand firm as the frozen tundra!
We are the Northern Light Blizzards!
- Shining like an eternal aurora!
Listen up,
we can't lose a single game
if we're going to the Christmas Bowl!
Roger that!
We aren't gonna lose to those freaks!
If we do, I'll quit reading manga forever!
We won't!
We got this!
Now I'm pumped!
Yes, we have to win it for Panther
and the rest of the Shuttles, too!
And...
To bring us another step closer to Shin, Riku,
And all the other incredible people waiting for us!
We WILL win this game!
Rip their heads off!
- Ya-ha!
Blizzards vs. Devil Bats
Ya-ha!
What a kick!
Like the harsh northern wind!
It goes on and on like an endless blizzard!
I will...
Blast off!
He's fast!
- Go!
Stuff that runt!
He whizzes past the Blizzard defenders one after another!
Win!
Look, the lightspeed dash!
Touchdown!
- Yes!
- Somehow, some way,
Eyeshield scores a touchdown on the kickoff return!
Way to go, Sena!
The extra point is good,
and the Devil Bats jump ahead with a 7-0 lead!
Eyeshield 21's running technique is beyond reproach!
Can anyone out there stop his lightspeed legs?
Bah.
A little handicap will make things more interesting.
Now, can the herd of mammoths from the silvery snow lands
mount a comeback?
Here it comes, Butt-Monkey!
There it is!
Nikolai's Soyuz Pass!
Deimon's victory depends on their ability to stop this play!
Time to show off my new special move from basketball practice!
Watch carefully!
Aah, but he's pursued by simian-I mean, Serge Montanikov!
Maybe they're long lost brothers...
The gorilla and the chimpanzee-
Or perhaps the yeti and the macaque, face off!
It doesn't matter if I'm shorter, I won't lose!
Monta!
I refuse to lose!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what's important in a wide receiver like Mon-Mon!
The key is "midair?"
A wide receiver needs to keep his eye
on the ball at all times and control
the fight for the ball in midair.
Don't mess up and catch the air instead!
Ya-ha.
It doesn't matter if I'm shorter, I won't lose!
I refuse to lose!
Taro Raimon intercepts the Soyuz Pass
for the Deimon Devil Bats!
Monta!
- All right!
What are they doing?!
Those meatheads are gonna get it!
The Devil Bats are on offense once again.
They're starting about 50 yards from the goal.
Set!
Hut!
Here comes Eyeshield 21!
Don't let him get going again!
Smash him with the Russian Roulette!
- Time for the new move!
First comes speed.
Then power.
And finally, technique!
- Rip his head off!
Can he run it in for a touchdown?!
Get him! Now!
Mammoth Attack!
Wait, Eyeshield doesn't have the ball!
Hiruma's signature fake handoff strikes again!
What?!
Deimon's true aim was a field goal by Musashi!
Amazing!
Musashi sinks a 50-yarder!
Wow.
Ya-ha!
The Deimon Devil Bats add three!
- Sheesh...
- Your kicks are as brutal as ever.
We're too far back.
What do you care? It went in.
Deimon's defense opens the second quarter in a big way!
They've completely shut down the Blizzards' offense!
A third interception!
With 30 seconds left in the half,
the Blizzards have yet to even get a first down,
and Deimon is on offense AGAIN!
These guys are nothing, what is wrong with you idiots?!
You're handing them the championship
on a silver platter!
We can do this.
Yo, Peewee.
Our next move is a full frontal assault.
You're gonna humiliate Mr. Mammoth.
Right.
Sena's got it!
Here comes Ivan's Mammoth Attack!
Don't think about dodging.
Watch the opponent's knees,
and make the first move!
Squash him, Ivan!
Blow past the mammoth!
Touchdown!
The Deimon Devil Bats neutralize the Mammoth Attack,
and go into halftime with a 17-0 lead!
- Yeah!
All right, 17 points.
If Sena keeps scoring we've got this in the bag.
Yup, the cup's ours!
We can do it!
We can go all the way!
Can they really...?
You haven't won yet...
Time to swap out a few parts!
It looks like the Blizzards
have changed their lineup for the second half!
Who is this new player?
Hmm...
I don't have much data on the Blizzards...
Let's see...
Here he is!
Ivan's twin brother, Owain Ivanov!
They're twins?
They don't look a thing alike...
Must be fraternal twins.
Twins?
Where, where, where?
- Just forget about it...
Time to show off our secret weapon.
Guess he put in a new part.
What're you trying to pull, Morgan?
What's his deal?
Dunno...
My shoulder's been aching ever since Ivan nailed me...
I've got a bad feeling about this...
The break hasn't dampened Deimon's spirit.
They're steadily moving deeper into Blizzards territory!
It doesn't matter who they send out.
Right. We've got this!
Yay!
Don't stop now!
Yay! Yay!
Set, hut!
Eyeshield 21 is running again!
Will they manage to stop Sena this time?
Same timing as before...
Same timing...
Wait a sec...
Watch it, Sena!
What?!
Screw Attack!
Sena!
Stretcher!
We need a stretcher!
Sena...
Sena... it'll be all right!
Come on, Sena, can't you hear me?
Answer me!
Sena...
Wake up, Sena!
He's got a concussion...
he won't come to for a while.
B-But...
Without Sena...
What'd you think of Owain's Screw Attack?
Do you have a replacement part?
What a pinch...
Deimon doesn't have anyone to replace Eyeshield 21!
Hiruma... Hiruma!
Looks like this is the end of the line.
What will you do without Eyeshield, Devil Bats?
This...
This is terrible!
With their lightspeed runner Sena Kobayakawa
benched with a concussion, what will they do?
What can the Devil Bats do?!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
With Sena out of commission,
how will the game end?!
We'll have to hang on until Sena
can return to the game!
We have to win this one!
That's the spirit!
There's no time for naps, Sena!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Break through the Blizzard! Ya-ha!
The Devil Bats are hosed
if they can't use Eyeshield...
There's only one option...
An ancient Japanese medicinal charm!
Be HEALED!
Wake up, Sena!
No! Hang in there, Sena!
So... this is traditional Japanese magic, eh?
You can't be serious?!
Sena!