ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Let's Play Football!
What?! The football team?
That's Hiruma's club...
Well, Kurita is REALLY nice!
Let's shoot for the Christmas Bowl, together!
But Hiruma's the worst kind of person there is.
I warned you not to associate with him.
And football is...
It's just way too dangerous!
Sena, you're the most feeble,
sapless,
frail,
weakest person out there!
You didn't have to say all that...
I'm on the disciplinary committee,
so if they make you do anything dangerous, you come straight to me.
Oh, I'll be fine.
Besides, I'm the manager, not a player.
Manager?
I won't actually be playing football,
just handling the team's affairs.
You think you can handle it?
Yep. Team manager!
Ya-ha!
Morning practice!
I keep telling you, I'm supposed to be the manager!
Whoa, you're here extra early!
Good morning!
This is the first time we've had three teammates since the club started.
I was so excited I couldn't stay asleep!
In fact, I was so pumped up I started practicing at 2 A.M.
We got a real doofus here, huh?
You lunkhead, you broke it in half!
S-Sorry.
He's scary strong.
Ah well, we'll make the principal buy another one.
But he's even scarier.
All right, do we need anything else from him?
N-No, I don't...
They've got a lot of stuff...
A ladder?
Oh, that's for "ladder drills."
You stand inside and practice stepping like this to learn the basic movements.
You step inside the gaps, like this?
Right, right.
Good job!
Uh oh, now it looks like I came here to practice!
'Kay, let's see what you're made of.
No!
You're still the newbie here.
Hold on,
my neck's still sore.
I'll run the 40 and call it a day.
The 40-yard dash.
It's been a while.
Okay, I'm timing you!
Let's see the payoff from this morning's training!
I'm not going to get much faster from just one day!
Umm, how fast does one usually run the 40-yard dash?
Your average Joe can do it in 5 seconds.
5 seconds is the line that separates regular people from sprinters.
4.8 seconds is considered elite for a high schooler.
Oh...
By the way,
the country's fastest high schooler is the Ojo White Knights' Seijuro Shin, at 4.4 seconds.
But that dude's a monster.
Here I go!
Move it!
Ready...
What's his time?
Ryokan Kurita runs the 40-yard dash in 6.5 seconds.
You freakin'-
Your man-pig legs are getting SLOWER!
What happened?! Morning training my butt!
I couldn't help it, I'm all tired out!
Watch this!
Quick!
Ya...
Ha!
Yoichi Hiruma, 5.1 seconds!
Awesome!
Ya-ha!
A new personal best! I rule!
And last but not least...
N-No, I'm just the manager, so I-
You what? Simply want to run so bad it hurts?
Great.
That's the enthusiasm I'd expect from a new member.
With his legs, he should break the 5 second barrier easy.
I-Is Sena really that fast?
If he was, I'd think he'd have been famous in middle school...
Well... Just watch, you'll see.
Ready...
Sena Kobayakawa, 5 seconds exactly!
That's amazing, Sena!
Really?
Sena Kobayakawa...
Ranked number one in his year for the sidestep drill during middle school physical fitness tests.
Where did you find that-
Being a gopher built up your legs.
Their explosive power.
That's how you got that rocket start...
But then you slow down right away, which'll keep you from setting a record.
Essentially, you just need to maintain that speed.
Cerberus!
Ya-ha!
See? His REAL speed...
4.2?!
That ain't high school level,
that's a pro player's top speed!
The kid's got legs of gold!
Sena Kobayakawa runs the 40-yard dash in 4.2 seconds!
But with Cerberus chasing him.
You're incredible, Sena!
We have to keep your speed top-secret!
The spring tourney's in the bag.
Oh, that's right.
When does the tournament start, again?
Tomorrow.
TOMORROW?!
SO! We need to find eight more players before the tournament tomorrow.
Eight?
Don't you need at least 11 players for a football team?
We'll HAVE 11 with eight extras.
I'm nine,
10,
11.
Hey-
With your speedy legs, I'd really love to see you play too, Sena.
But, well, even if you're the manager,
if you WANTED to play someday, that'd make me really happy.
Anyways, let's try to find nine people.
Okay.
We each find three! Do whatever you have to.
Hit up those guys in the other sports clubs!
Three people by the end of the day!
Let's go get 'em, Sena!
Three people, huh...
Whoever brings back the least... pays the price.
This isn't going to be easy.
I just started school, so I don't know anyone...
Umm, would you guys like to play football?
Football?! Hiruma! HIRUMA?!
He's already scared everyone off.
What're you lookin' at?
Don't come within five meters of us!
Lousy jerk...
Unbelievable.
Oh, managers do a lot.
They set up our games...
T-That's right! This is my chance to prove I'm manager material!
Members of the basketball team!
How would you like to play in a football game?
We'll provide the equipment, the space, everything!
All we need is YOUR fighting spirit!
Umm, excuse me...
I, uh, was wondering if any of you might be interested in playing football...
Nah, we'll pass.
Not interested.
Oh, I see...
I stink. Why does this always happen...
Hey, do you guys want to play in our football game?
No!
Hey, you're playing for my football team now!
Wha- Again?
Leave us alone, we said we're not playing!
Oh?
Pretty strong refusal for a buncha freshmen...
Satake and Yamaoka, Class 1-2, right?
H-How do you know-
Oh, I know a lot more.
Satake, you wet the bed until sixth grade.
Wha-
And Yamaoka... Oh?
You kiss your favorite model's poster good morning every day?
Man, that's embarrassing!
How do you know-
Attention everyone, I have a big announcement!
We'll play! We'll play!
Let us join the football team, please!
That's two... Nice.
Well, they're big.
Oh, do you want to join the sumo club?
Atta boy! Let's get you practicing right away!
But the football-
This isn't happening...
Okay, hit me with everything you've got!
I'm telling you, I'm not here for sumo-
If you're just going to talk, I'll come at you!
What're you doing down there, Sena?
I'm never gonna get anyone to join the club...
Football clinic!
How many meters is 40 yards?
About 36 meters.
They use 40 yards to measure all kinds of aspects of a player's ability!
Ya-ha!
The judo club said no, too...
P-Please, just hear me out!
We're not going anywhere near Hiruma!
Please, just-
I've asked almost every club...
The track team!
With their speed, they'd be perfect for football!
A football game?
Yeah, sure. Count me in.
Really?!
I know how it is.
Hiruma's recruiting the new students, right?
Yes!
So, if I play with them, we'll get some experience exercising together,
and I can try to recruit the ones with promise into the track team.
That's fair, right?
Give and take.
O-Of course!
Yes! I actually managed to find someone!
Oh, when's the game?
Tomorrow! I'll see you there!
T-Tomorrow? I can't tomorrow!
The thing is, I do deliveries part-time for the local newspaper.
If I don't finish them all by tomorrow afternoon, I'm cooked.
In fact, I doubt I'll even come close today...
Sorry.
That's right... Tomorrow is so sudden.
Wow... He got that many by himself?
How did it go, Sena?
I, uh... didn't even get one.
I'm so sorry.
Zero for you, too, huh...
And Hiruma only made it to seven.
I really wanted to enter the tournament.
That's why I want to enter the tournament, no matter what it takes.
It makes me so excited,
working together to reach a common goal, running right over our opponents on the way!
Yahoo!
Let's shoot for the Christmas Bowl, together!
I-I-
I'm going around again!
No such luck...
E-Excuse me!
If you finish your deliveries by the end of today, you can play, right?
Let me help you!
All right, you take that half.
That's a lot of deliveries, you sure?
Yes.
Meet me here when you're done.
Thanks!
Okay. I absolutely have to make all these deliveries today!
Ah, Mamori.
She might say I'm stuck being a gopher again.
But running around for a common goal...
...isn't so bad.
Hey, Sena.
You really did a number on us yesterday.
Don't mess with us.
We couldn't do anything at school with HIM keeping an eye on you, but school's out.
And we're gonna get even with you.
J-J-Just wait a sec-
K-Knock it off...!
You little...!
I can't...
I can't fail now!
Get ready for some pain-
You...
...little!
Only a few left, I can make it!
I will...
...finish the deliveries today!
Well, I'm all done for the day. Of course, I have a bike.
Maybe I pushed him a little too far.
I'll check his half... Wonder how he did.
You scared the heck out of me!
That was really fast.
You delivered them all on your own?
Yes, every last one.
Awesome! You really helped me out.
So now you can play in tomorrow's game, right?
Yep, a promise is a promise.
I'm Tetsuo Ishimaru, second year.
Sena Kobayakawa, first year.
Nice to meet you.
You too!
Incredible! You're incredible, Sena!
That gives us, um...
One, two three...
With me and Hiruma...
10 people...
We're still one short.
So close...
Well, there's still tomorrow morning.
We...
...won't make it.
Uh, um-
I-I'll be the last one-
What a gyp!
How does a store run out of sugarless gum?!
Do your job, you bums...
Oops.
I haven't been keeping up.
Yahoo!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
Yeah! Somehow, some way, it's Sena's debut game!
But can he even play?
Whoa, everyone on the opposing team has a girlfriend!
Mamori will come out to see me! I think...
You THINK? What a goof!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Blaze a Path Down the Field!
Ya-ha!
We did it!
So I'm the only one who did anything?!
You useless bums, give those drinks back!
Kurita, you got the goose egg, prepare to pay the price!
What's "the price?"
Don't worry, just carrying our stuff.
Here!
ALL of it.
Ow.