What?! Where's the ball?!
Killer Hornets!
Go, Eyeshield 21!
Shin!
Come, Eyeshield 21!
Let's put an end to this now!
Faster... Faster!
Go!
It's one-on-one!
Whoever wins this final bout will move on to the finals.
It's Seijuro Shin versus Eyeshield 21!
Yay!
- What?!
Faster! Much faster!
He did it!
Not yet!
Uh-oh! Shin's catching up!
Sena Kobayakawa...
You appeared like a comet, giving me someone to compete with.
You're my ultimate rival!
But now it's time for me to take you down!
He's accelerating!
Sena!
No way!
Darn it, Shin's just a little faster than me!
It's because he isn't carrying the ball.
It's all over if he catches me.
I'll use my arm to make some distance.
He deflected me.
He didn't just deflect him!
He's already caught him!
With just his pinky and ring finger!
What a monster!
He's so strong.
My wrist's... gonna snap!
You can do it!
Don't drop the ball even if it kills you!
He's right! This ball... is our last ball!
Crap!
The game's as good as over.
Not yet!
No, he's off balance!
He recovered!
The fight's not over yet!
He recovered from that?
My body's ready to give out on me.
But I can't collapse yet!
I've got to win... this showdown with Shin!
This will decide everything.
The Trident Tackle versus...
...the Devil Bat Ghost!
He's cutting across from the right.
It'll be a light speed cross step at 40 yards in 4.2 seconds.
What?!
He jumped!
He jumped over me!
He faked doing a Devil Bat Ghost
and did a one-man Devil Bat Dive!
No you don't!
- Sena!
We must...
...WIN!
You're finished, Sena Kobayakawa!
I don't stand a chance against Shin in a contest of power.
But my weapon isn't power; it's speed!
I'll defeat Shin with speed!
Ya-ha!
He accelerated enough to overcome the speed barrier for a second!
40 yards in 4.1 seconds!
It's the world of super-light speed.
I see it!
T-T-T-Touchdown!
We won...
We won!
We... won.
- YA-HA!
- The ferocious battle's over!
The winners of this epically fierce game
are the demonic Deimon Devil Bats!
Ojo White Knights 27 - Deimon Devil Bats 28
Deimon tried to scale Ojo's thick walls several times,
and at long last, they've finally overcome them!
In other words, the-
-the ultimate offense team is the Deimon Devil Bats!
D-Dad?
Kumabukuro, when'd you get here?
I just got back from America.
Man, I'm glad I made it in time.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
I got to... play in this crazy game with everyone...
...and win!
It's no dream!
What are you doing sitting over here so quietly for?
We all worked hard...
...to win!
With anyone missing...
...we couldn't have won!
So let's rejoice together!
Include me, too!
Guys... Yeah!
We won! We WON!
We did it, Musashi!
Ojo! We actually be Ojo!
Guys, everyone's so amazing!
Yeah.
Hiruma, thank you! Thank you so much!
Hiruma...
...job well done.
I guess.
You did it, Sena, but the next time I fight you...
"Don't reward the winners."
Right. The winners get all they need with the pleasure of having won.
Got that right!
But they won't be able to sit on that throne forever.
Got that uber-right.
Just you wait, Sena.
The one who will beat you next time...
- ...is me!
They're just trash!
Agon?
Agon, where are you going?
To the gym.
Right now?
Is he trying to strengthen his grip?
Agon, did you watch the whole game?
Those worthless runts...
N-No way... No way!
Darn it! Darn it! Darn it! DARN IT!
But everyone did their best...
We all tried so hard!
I'm sorry.
I failed you, Torakichi.
Why?! You won! You'd already won, Sakuraba!
This is what happens in a game.
WHY?!
Monta!
Sakuraba...
Would you... please take this to the Christmas Bowl with you?
We fought fair and square, and I still lost.
I want you, as my strongest opponent, to have this.
Please.
No, I can't accept it.
Torakichi, I have to take Honjo's glove with me!
I'm gonna be loaded down to the max!
So don't entrust that to me or Sakuraba.
You should throw yourself into your rehab so you can take it to the Christmas Bowl yourself!
S-Shut up!
Hey!
Torakichi...
Just you wait and see!
I'm going to join the football team as soon as I enter middle school.
I'll become the absolute best receiver EVER!
I'm gonna make you squeal with frustration!
You can do it since you're determined not to lose.
Don't you dare jinx me!
The opposite of everything you say always happens, ya know!
I may have lost today, but I won't lose next time.
The battle for the title as number one catcher isn't over yet.
Yep!
Monta!
Oh, right! Honjo!
Huh? He's gone.
He already left...
Taro Raimon, huh?
Continue to believe in your own path and never waver, baseball boy.
Otawara!
Kurita!
Me, Otawara and all the seniors have to retire now.
Starting now, Ojo's new captain will be you, Shin.
Please take care of Ojo.
I will.
Retiring already?
That was fast.
Someone has to keep their cool until the very end to keep the team together.
In Deimon, that would be you.
It's over. It's... all over!
I forgot during the game,
but I gotta pee!
Gonna leak!
Meeting comes first.
Sena...
Hey, let's go, Mamo!
Suzuna, I think I'll pass.
You should go tell Sena he did great.
I can't! Sena only made it this far because of you!
I'm afraid not, Suzuna.
Sena's been walking on his own this whole time.
He decided on this by himself.
He worked hard on his own.
He overcame everything!
And now he's standing here...
There's nothing more I can do for Sena.
He's really grown up.
I've gotta stop crying.
Remember what I said earlier?
No matter who wins, in the end, everyone will laugh with tears in their eyes.
Mamo...
Congratulations Sena and everyone.
Sena Kobayakawa.
Shin...
Next year a new generation of Ojo players will play against you.
Right.
I will be the challenger then.
W-W-Wait, no, I...
I guess I...
Me too. By then I'll be even stronger than I am now.
Glad to hear it.
This is the first time I've ever seen Shin look like he's actually enjoying football.
Shin isn't conceited.
He is always racing to meet higher standards.
But it's also true that even as a middle schooler, no one could stand up to him as a rival.
Shin grows stronger when he has a goal to aim for.
Right. Those two are going to create a whole new football generation.
It's their time now.
I had a great time, too.
You were my goal that I was always chasing after.
I'm glad I started football.
I'm glad I was introduced to the world of football!
Well, we've finally made it, Hiruma.
We just beat Ojo.
"Just" Ojo, huh?
That's just like you.
We've still got a long way to go. We're not done yet.
I know.
We don't have time to goof off before the Christmas Bowl.
Now we've got to win the Kanto Tournament.
Set, hut!
Welcome to the National Football League!
Here come the super stars!
And introducing the sensational rookie Japanese shooting star,
Eyeshield 21, Sena Kobayakawa!
- Sena!
Set, hut!
Eyeshield! Eyeshield! Eyeshield! Eyeshield!
Touchdown!
Anyone can become a great hero.
Everyone, let's play football!
Everyone, Let's Play Football! Ya-Ha-!
YA-HA!
- YA-HA!