Well, it's a beautiful day today.
And throughout the ages Deimon High has celebrated Field Day!
I still just can't believe it!
It's said that healthy bodies build healthy minds,
We're really doin' it!
Yeah! We're going to the semi-finals!
so I'd like everyone to try their hardest.
But next we're up against Seibu and they've got the Kid and Tetsuma!
But I'd also like you to be careful not to get hurt, okay?
Also...
We've gotta get fired up!
Yeah!
And Seibu's also got Riku...
Oh, one more thing before I forget.
The team that loses has to play in the traditional penalty game.
Please don't get too carried away!
A penalty game?
Ya-ha!
That's right, a penalty game!
H-Hiruma?!
We're gonna CRUSH the Red Team and WIN!
Y-Yuki?!
What the heck?
We'll stomp on the Red Team!
M-Mamori?
It's Deimon's Field Day of Death!
The loser's goin' to hell!
Even Mamori and Yuki have gotten weird!
What's going on?!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't."  You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero.  What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Field Day at Deimon High School!
Shall we go, everyone?
Do whatever it takes to win!
We're winning!
Going by how strangely they're acting...
...this has to be bad.
Looks like one of them's acting the same...
Everyone on the football team's on the Red Team,
except for those three, who are on the White Team.
Which means...
...we're up against Deimon's Brainy Trio.
But still, the team that loses...
...has to play in the hellish penalty game!
I can't even imagine what they'll do to us!
A-Anyway, it won't matter if we don't lose!
We HAVE to win, Sena!
Yeah!
Well, Deimon High's Field Day is about to begin at long last!
Everyone's on fire!
I, Machine Gun Sanada, and Bomberhead Kumabukuro here
will explain and analyze games whenever we're asked to!
What are we even doing here?
That aside, the first game will be tug-of-war!
Get ready!
Good going!
Sweet!
Awesome!
The Red Team had an overwhelming victory
thanks to the football team's ultra-powerful linemen!
Red Team 20 - White Team 0
It really shows that they train hard.
Amazing! That was great, guys!
Boo-yah! We're gonna kick max butt in the next game, too!
Okay, let's keep at it!
The next game is the ball toss!
Get ready! Set!
This is the most crucial of all the games!
Who will win the ball toss?!
However many balls you win by
will be how many points the winning team gets.
It'll be an important game!
Red Team is currently in the lead!
But will they be able to protect their position?!
They're pretty good!
Now they've made me get serious!
The fools!
Set, hut!
Ya-ha!
Is that allowed?
The White Team's amazing!
It's a true free for all!
But is this really allowed?
It's okay! It's totally okay!
So that's that!
They're way in the lead!
A-At this rate, we'll lose!
Max Catch!
I see. So we're gonna dump them in.
Yay, go! Slam dunk!
Monta, are you sure about this?
It's fine!
Max Slam Dunk!
Huh?
Okay! Game over!
The White Team has 102 balls!
And Red has zero.
Red Team 20 - White Team 102
Not good! We're gonna lose!
We've gotta turn the tables somehow.
Who knows what they'll do to us if we lose!
So then,
let's win in the next game, the three-legged costume relay!
We'd win 100 points!
We could turn the tide just like that!
Great! Let's win for sure!
Yeah!
Now for the three-legged costume relay!
Be sure to select your partner from the audience!
The first round just started!
That costume...
I wonder how they're given out...
Supposedly it's randomly chosen through a drawing.
Hey! What gives?!
There's no way that was random.
Yeah, it wasn't random.
No way that was random.
Komusubi, there's a cute bunny!
I wonder who's inside...
I'll kill you if you run in front of me,
you dumb forest friends!
I don't like that bunny!
I know exactly who's in it now!
Wow! The Red Team's just barely in the lead!
The person in the lead is the pretty plain,
but fairly fast invisible man, Ishimaru!
The white team's dog and pig pair
has darted pass the track team's Ishimaru!
That dog and pig are fast!
Who's inside them?!
A dog and pig?!
Why bother with costumes?!
Even though he's part of the track team,
a dog and pig got past him.
Yeah, and here he's on the track team...
On the track team...
But isn't this normally against the rules?
It isn't against the rules, is it?
Is it?
Right...
This isn't even a three-legged race anymore...
Hey, Sena,
have you picked out a partner from the audience yet?
I totally forgot!
But I don't know anyone in the audience...
Then how about me?
Suzuna?
I came to cheer everyone on!
It'd be great!
I'll run with you!
Okay!
The race is entering the final stage!
It's the Red Team's flying monkey Raimon
and his trainer Doburoku from the football team!
Great, we're winning!
Go for it!
Monta! You're almost there!
Hurry!
The Red Team's just about to hand the band to the next anchor!
Sena, Suzuna, I'm counting on you!
Okay, let's go!
What's with that turtle?
It's fast!
Yay, this is fun!
What?! This isn't even a three-legged race anymore!
The turtle man that suddenly appeared is a great sprinter!
H-Haven't we seen that running style somewhere before?
Yes! There's the goal!
Move it, move it! Wanna die?!
Th-The White Team reached the goal and stole the victory!
H-Hiruma...
It's only natural for a bunny to be faster than a turtle.
R-Right...
Ya-ha.
The White Team's WAY in the lead!
Red Team 20 - White Team 202
If the Red Team doesn't get their act together,
it'll be hard for them to win!
But now for the event everyone's been looking forward to!
I've been waiting for this!
It's the folk dance!
Let's forget about fighting and rivalries!
Let's dance!
It's a small breather in the middle of a war.
Mamori's hand will be in mine!
M-Mamori!
Ah, Mamori's hand!
It's so soft and white.
I'll love Mamori forever, no matter how evil she becomes!
M-Mamori?
Uh-oh!
The fun's not over yet!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell me how to get by the enemy!
The key point is spinning?
When you want to get by your opponent,
make sure to spin around once when you're right next to him.
Watch your opponent carefully!
Ya-ha!
It's finally lunch time!
I'm beat.
Good job, guys.
Um, this is a little embarrassing, but...
Here! It's a boxed lunch!
I made it myself.
M-Mamori's homemade lunch!
Monta, Mamori's been kinda strange today.
You should be careful.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
Here, say "Ah!"
- Ah!
- Monta!
It's hot!
It figures.
I thought I was gonna die!
Come on!
Really, they sure have changed over night.
Hey, there!
We have to win the second years' relay race!
Aloha!
The real problem's Hiruma.
Yeah.
Our runner in the afternoon race is...
Ishimaru.
So if HE behaves...
...it'll be an easy victory.
That's good.
It's not good!
Do you think that demon Hiruma...
...will keep quiet and let him reach the goal?
- You're right.
You know him.
I bet he's hiding somewhere along the track
with a bunch of weapons on hand!
But I'm not going to keep quiet and let him get his way!
we'll beat him there and hold him down!
- Hold Hiruma down?!
W-Well, I know it sounds crazy, but...
...it'll be fine if we all go after him!
It'll work out!
- That's nuts...
It's time for the afternoon games to start!
The first game is the relay race for the second year students.
Ishimaru from the Red Team is in the lead!
Between his training for the track team and the football team,
his legs aren't just for show!
Enough already...
A-Anyway, we can't let our guard down!
We're gonna jump him all at once!
- Y-Yeah!
That evil aura...
And I know exactly who's emitting it.
Okay, let's go!
You need something, ladies?
- Nope, not a thing.
Good.
W-What?!
Ya-ha!
What was that?
Red Team 20 - White Team 250
Now then...
The wait is over!
Next up is the main event of the day!
Now for the finals - the mock cavalry battle!
But with such a large gap in the scoreboard,
turning the tide will be difficult.
Huh? Oh, I see!
It's no good!
With a gap like this, it's pointless!
Whoever wins the mock cavalry battle will win 300 points!
So what was the point of the other games then?!
Anyway, we can still beat them if we win this!
Yeah!
Hey, Red Team!
What do you say to a good ol' handshake to playing fair in the finals?
There's something up!
It's clearly a trap.
I won't do it! Nope, no way!
You really don't trust us!
Do you hate shaking hands or something?
M-Mamori, it's not that!
H-Hey, wait, Monta!
Something's not right!
H-Handcuffs?
What gives?!
Before I realized it, they'd already caught me!
They're taking this too far.
Th-The Deimon Brainy Trio is scary...
What should we do?
Monta, Kuroki, Taki and I all got handcuffed.
Now we can't be the horses.
We'll have to be the knights.
Yeah...
Huh?
What's up?
If they really did this just to prevent us from winning,
why didn't they handcuff all of us?
Who cares about that?!
Right now it's kill or be killed.
I'll never forgive Hiruma for this!
We're gonna crush him!
R-Right! Let's just calm down and do our best, okay?
Listen up, ladies!
I want everyone to use the routes I showed you!
I'll kill anyone who messes up the formation!
- Yes, sir!
Wow...
Do you really use battle strategies for a measly game of mock cavalry battle?
At any rate, this is the last game!
We have to win!
- Right!
It's time for the mock cavalry battle to commence!
Ready!
Use the formation "Mock Cavalry Battle-Style Shotgun!"
I-I'm surrounded!
You're mine!
Argh! They're quick!
Under General Hiruma's command,
the White Team has made some good moves!
The Red Team's cavalry is falling one horse after the next!
It's just what I'd expect from Hiruma!
Man, with my hands like this...
...all we can do is run!
This's bad!
Taki, look out!
Oh, no!
I'm a skilled player even with my hands tied up!
I beautifully pushed them away to escape!
Just now...
I feel like I've seen that before...
Don't you go UMPH and push...
Bump!
Even if we've got our hands tied up,
we can push the enemy to make them lose their balance.
Let's use bumps!
I remember bumps...
Yeah, they were used in the game against Taiyo!
Kamaguruma bumped us and threw our balance way outta whack.
Okay! Now it's our turn to throw the White Team's balance way outta whack!
Yeah!
Boo-yah!
You're totally open!
Take that!
You're mine!
BUMP!
He's wobbly!
Now!
- What?!
- Max Catch!
- Sweet!
- Great!
We did it, guys!
The bump is a killer football technique.
Good thinking, Red Team!
The Red Team has just turned the tide!
Look carefully at the enemy's routes!
Think of them as receivers after the ball when they go after our headbands!
Push 'em...
...and crush 'em!
- Bump!
Oh, YEAH! BUMP!
Bump!
That's right.
You don't have to completely knock them down.
Just use a bump to throw off the timing for a pass.
That will put an end to the Quickdraw Kid's ultimate move, Quick-and-Draw.
They need the courage to blow Seibu's receivers away.
I wanted to create a real situation for them where it was "kill or be killed."
Awesome!
The Red Team has taken the lead and won!
The Red Team has won
the Deimon High School Field Day tournament with a score 320-252!
Let's have mango pudding after we finish cleaning up!
Th-Then, you were all acting strangely just to make us get serious?
Yep.
Sorry, everyone.
But boy did you ever enjoy yourself!
Yeah, you really enjoyed it!
You totally enjoyed it.
Mamo, you were cool!
We have one week until we fight Seibu.
So we're doing our regular menu plus working on bumps.
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
It's Eyeshield 21!
Is he helping the track team?!
That for real?
Yeah, there's nothing to worry about if he's on the team.
Run, Plain Ishimaru and Sena!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Spinter's Sena?! Ya-ha!
Max Bump!
Here's my bump!
Yay!
Hey, bump!
I sure am glad Hiruma's on our side again.
Yeah, normally we just take him for granted, ya know?
Yeah, Hiruma may be a little violent,
but he REALLY is the BEST strategist!
- Sure is!
Okay, let's get back to practice!
We need to work hard on our bumps, after all!
Yeah!
We can't lose, even to Seibu!