All-Japan American Football Fall Tournament in Tokyo
A Block  Semi-finals
Seibu Wild Gunmen vs. Deimon Devil Bats
The Semi-finals...
It's the Seibu Wild Gunmen vs. the Deimon Devil Bats.
Hey! You look pretty excited!
Be sure to go easy on us today.
Riku?
Riku!
L-Let's do our best today!
Good luck!
Sena! Rikky?
Mamo, sorry, but...
I'm definitely going to defeat Eyeshield 21.
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't."  You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero.  What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Proof He's the Fastest!
Wild, Wild Gunmen! Wild, Wild Gunmen!
I think everyone already understands this,
but these guys are on a different level from normal high schoolers.
Losing concentration just once could cost us the game.
R-Right!
Hey, Sena, are you worried about that Riku guy?
No, not exactly...
But man, standing on the same field as Seibu like this
reminds me of when we teamed up with Kid
in that beach football tournament.
They were really reliable, great allies back then.
But now they're enemies standing in our way.
Riku...
Sena!
Come on, analyst Kumabukuro!
Tell us what you think the outcome of the game will be!
Come on, don't hold back!
Well, when looking at sheer power, Seibu is vastly superior, but...
Anything could happen in this game.
Which means what?
I wonder what will happen when two very offensive teams
butt heads with each other.
I'm very excited!
It's time for the coin toss!
Deimon's kicking off!
They're starting with Seibu on Offense!
Well, let's stick with the usual game plan.
We'll force our way through!
Yeah! We're pioneers on the field!
Wild and Tough!
Ladies, don't let something like "semi-finals" scare you!
We're going to the TOP!
In order to do that, these little cowboys are gonna...
...get CRUSHED!
YA-HA!
- Ya-ha!
- Fire!
Get 'em, kiddies!
Go!
- You can do it!
- Yay!
One of the key showdowns in this game
is Deimon's Eyeshield 21 with his light speed legs...
...versus Seibu's rookie Kaitani with his Rodeo Drive.
Oh, Riku Kaitani...
...caught the ball!
Riku's coming!
He'll use his Rodeo Drive!
Doesn't matter if we stop him!
Let me show you, Sena!
This is my ultimate running technique, Rodeo Drive!
He vanished!
How can this be?!
W-What?!
Rikky!
He got through... instantly?
Just 60 yards left!
Wait, wait, wait!
Just how far do you plan on letting him go?!
Riku Kaitani's amazing!
He crossed half the field in seconds!
Will he go for the goal?!
It's useless!
- He vanished!
Don't underestimate me!
Amazing!
He just got by Jumonji!
But, I won't lose!
Stop him, Peewee!
I dare you to stop me, Sena!
Riku!
It's the explosive dash, Rodeo Drive!
Kaitani just got a touchdown!
Good going, Riku!
Impressive.
H-He's amazing!
What incredible running!
The kick was a success, too!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Seibu's in the lead by seven points!
A-Amazing!
That's Riku's running style...
Sena!
Now I've challenged and beaten you 93 times!
Sena, do you think closing your eyes will make me stop?!
What an incredible play!
As soon as the game
started Riku Kaitani from the Seibu Wild Gunmen
got a kickoff return touchdown!
What? What?
A kickoff return touchdown?
What's that?
It's when the opponent catches the ball
and runs it to our goal line after we make our kickoff.
It's a very rare, big play.
A-Amazing, Rikky!
OH NO!
What's going on?
He outright vanished!
Calm down, ladies!
He sways his upper body like a rodeo player.
Doing that lets him utilize an incredibly fast change of pace.
Change of pace?
It was originally a running technique used in rugby.
Amazing!
I can't believe he integrated that technique into his own running style.
Riku really is amazing!
Don't be afraid.
We've got a great runner here, too.
He's an idiot that's honed his running style for over ten years
while working as a gopher running through crowds.
Show 'em what you got, Sena!
Let them see you run!
Show it to me, Sena!
Well, everyone's probably still in shock over that sudden touchdown,
but now Seibu's kicking off and Deimon's on Offense!
Everyone, block them!
Make sure to open a route up for Sena!
We practiced shoving like mad!
With so many people blocking...
There's my route!
He's as impressive as ever.
He's using the Devil Bat Ghost!
He's slipping by all of Seibu's defense!
It's completely different from Riku Kaitani's intricate foot work.
Harsh training gave birth to his fierce acceleration and deceleration technique.
No normal defense stands a chance against his running style.
Riku!
S-Stop him, Riku!
I can't shake him!
I can't... catch up!
Go, Peewee!
Riku...
Sena!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to dodge a tackle!
The key point is your hand?
When you want to dodge a tackle,
be sure to knock them down with your hand
once they draw close to you.
Knock the enemy down and RUN! Ya-ha!
Touchdown!
He did it!
As expected!
See that?!
That's how cool Deimon's ace, Eyeshield 21, really is!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
There's yet another kickoff return touchdown!
It's the second one and we're only 40 seconds into the game!
This is the first time I've seen someone counter a kickoff return touchdown
with their own!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
It's seven-to-six and Deimon's catching up!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
That was close.
I would have lost if I went up against him head-on.
Riku!
You are... really great!
I might not be match for you right now,
but I'll try my hardest!
That's the best way I know
to thank you for teaching me how to run.
How long are you going
to keep spouting that childish nonsense?!
There's only winners and losers here.
Crush or be crushed.
That's all there is to it!
It's a crazy game clear from the get-go!
I wonder what will happen next?!
I don't know!
I don't know,
but Deimon's clearly in trouble
if this is going to be a battle for touchdowns since Deimon doesn't have a kicker.
Too bad, Deimon!
They failed to get the extra point from the kick!
It's seven to six with Seibu in the lead!
Well, it's Deimon's turn to kick off!
How will the Seibu Wild Gunmen attack this time?!
They're using him again!
GO! Everyone, crush him!
I dare you to try!
He slipped through again!
Kaitani is AMAZING!
None of you could ever hope to catch me!
Oh no!
Eyeshield's after him!
How fascinating!
It's a battle between the two teams' running aces!
Sena!
Riku!
It's a fight between master and pupil.
No, I'm no longer your brother nor your master.
I'm going to be your arch rival.
And I swear on my pride that I will defeat you!
Same here!
Sena, show me just how strong you've become!
I'm not the same person I used to be!
I'm gonna win and go to the finals!
I challenge you, Sena!
W-What?!
You can't stop me!
What should I do?!
Stop him with your body!
Use the Devil Bat Ghost!
Got it!
What?!
A-Amazing!
W-What's going on here?
Sena!
Riku!
I won't lose!
Me neither!
What?
What's going on?
Whoops! Both players flew outta bounds at the sideline!
The stupid brat!
They're too fired up.
But Seibu's Kaitani
has just 32 yards before he reaches the goal area!
Wild, Wild Gunmen! Wild, Wild Gunmen!
Thank goodness...
We managed to stop him from getting a touchdown, but...
But he made it half way across the field!
You've gotten...
...a bit stronger.
But...
The real fight is just beginning, Sena.
No, Eyeshield 21!
Y-Yeah!
What are those two talking about?
I know!
Maybe Eyeshield's actually...
- Busted?!
...a friend of Rikky's!
- D'oh!
What is it?
- No, it's nothing!
Now for the main character to take the stage!
He's the greatest in Tokyo,
no, as far as offensive power is concerned,
he may be the greatest in history.
He's the lightning fast Quickdraw Shotgun Kid!
We'll just watch him carefully for a while.
After all, it's the first time my team's ever seen your passes up close.
My, how scary!
But I'm not going to start bickerin' with you.
I know I can't beat you in psychological warfare.
Aren't you the cautious one?
Set!
Wow, what a formation they've taken up!
It's Seibu's ultimate move, the Shotgun!
It's like the start of a marathon race.
Everyone's lined up in the front.
Does that mean all of them are receivers?
Hut, hut!
They're all charging at once?!
How're we supposed to stop them?!
If we can't stop all of their receivers,
then we've got no choice but to blitz the quarterback!
Kid's Quick-and-Fire is invisible!
He'll throw the ball before you catch him,
so a blitz won't work!
He went for Kid's blind spot!
- Yay!
- Great!
You don't have enough time to even use your 0.2 second quickdraw!
The pass was a success!
Stop him, Butt-monkey, Chinfuzz!
Deimon managed to stop him!
But Seibu's gotten their first down!
J-Just now...
...the motion Kid made when he threw the ball...
I-I couldn't see it...
Jerk!
You kept that move a secret until the semi-finals, you weasel!
Just worked out that way.
Nothing good comes from being overestimated, ya know?
What should we do?!
The blitz isn't working!
And Kid's shotgun is just getting faster and faster!
And then there's Riku running and then there's Tetsuma!
What should we do?!
Quit squealing like a pig, fatty!
The game's just started.
Y-You're right, Hiruma!
We'll be okay, right?
You bet!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Kid's passes are amazing!
And then there's Tetsuma!
Isn't this gonna be a bit tough?
Aren't you forgetting someone?
You've got me here and I'm a legendary catcher in beach football!
What?! I've never heard of that legend!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Field of Despair! Ya-ha!
What's wrong, Mamo?
I see! I get it!
- Get what?
How Rikky and Eyeshield are related!
It explains Eyeshield's running style.
It's pretty simple when you think about it.
- We're busted!
Eyeshield was...
...Rikky's running coach!
It's hard to tell if Mamo's intuition's great or horrible...