Ya-ha!
Distance to Las Vegas: 1838 km.
DEATH MARCH - DAY 3
Deep post!
Tough to the max!
We're not the only ones suffering.
Down with...
Deimon!
Shinryuji!
Down with...
Deimon!
Shinryuji!
Taiyo Sphinx!
Ra!
The time limit's down to 40 days.
This is for the Christmas Bowl!
I wish I'd given up when I could!
Got that right!
I wonder if anyone would notice if we took it a bit easier?
Hiruma, you want 40 kilometers to be our daily goal?
We just barely managed to make 20.
At this rate, we'll never make it to Las Vegas!
I can't do this!
I wish we'd gone back to Japan!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Quitters?
Super recovery?
What's that?
Your muscles are sore right now, aren't they?
It's because your muscle tissue's been shredded.
But if you rest up and let them heal, they'll be even stronger than they were before.
That's the trick behind "super recovery."
So that's the deal with muscle training.
Training's meaningless unless you rest afterwards so that super recovery can work its magic.
But there's only 40 days left until the fall tournament.
We won't make it to Las Vegas if we rest after every day we train.
Then...
What will we do?
We'll train for two days and nights!
The death march was originally supposed to be a killer program where you worked at night!
If you double the muscle fatigue, you'll double the super recovery.
Two days and nights of training?
Are you nuts?!
We'll be up all night training during summer vacation...
I'm gonna die.
This is tough!
Everyone, be sure to ice down or else you'll swell up.
Feels good!
We're setting off right on schedule!
Ah, that's it!
Hiruma is the only one who seems fine.
He should be exhausted after calling out pass routes
while shooting and carrying that heavy bag AND giving orders.
He's amazing!
We can handle this much if we're gonna buff up! Let's go for it!
What are you doing, Manajerk?
Go tend to the brats.
I'm not leaving. Now hold your leg still.
Hey, what are you doing?!
I said to sit still!
Once I get the hang of kicking it, I should be able to run way quicker.
Then I won't get as tired so easily.
It's still hard for me to believe that little shrimp is Eyeshield.
Seriously.
I was just starting to respect Eyeshield a bit,
but I feel like a total idiot now that I know it's him.
He's only a hero because he's fast.
Everyone has at least one thing they're good at.
What's wrong, Jumonji?
Too tired to talk, huh?
Sorry.
I didn't do it on purpose!
Really, I was...
Aren't you pooped?
Of course I am, but I've got to hurry up and get good at kicking this thing.
How long?
Huh?
How long have you loved football?
Well, it hasn't really been long...
Is it strange?
What?
It's pretty strange that we're actually participating in this killer training, isn't it?
I don't think it's strange...
Well, I think it is.
Especially when you think about how we used to be...
We want to change.
Change?
We want to change, just like you.
No, I haven't really...
I'll admit you're good.
But I won't lose to you.
Jumonji!
Wake up!
What's with this?
Isn't it obvious? We're running away.
We're not gonna endure this torture anymore.
Let's hurry back to Japan.
And enjoy a fun summer vacation!
Hey, wait a second!
What is it?
Are you sure about this?
About what?
Do you really wanna run away with your tails tucked between your legs?
Have you lost it after pushing that truck too much?
Where are you going?
To the potty.
I'll go too.
Sure...
Okay!
Let's go now!
I said to wait a second!
Football Clinic!
What does the defense line do?
They block against the approaching enemy's attack.
Don't lose against the offensive line in a battle of brawns. Ya-ha!
That's why I said to hurry!
What is it?! Gotta problem?!
We're going home already!
We're not gonna do this anymore!
You can't stop us!
Here's a map to the Japanese embassy.
You can go home after you hitch-hike your way there.
In 40 days, the last chance Hiruma and Kurita will ever have at the fall tournament will begin.
They've got no choice but to stick with this torturous death march.
But you first years still have next year.
If you're diligent in your training for a full year, you'll be able to put up a good fight next fall.
You don't have to bet your life as an athlete on this year.
What are you saying?!
Monta!
I want...
I want to help them win at any cost!
They've been hardcore about football ever since junior high.
They stood out like sore thumbs at school, but their love of football was unparalleled.
Like I care.
That's right! That doesn't mean diddly to us!
We're leaving!
What about you, Jumonji?
Fine.
You've changed.
Hey, Kuroki, Toga!
Shut it!
Later!
Hiruma, Kuroki and Togano have...
You still have time to stop them if you hurry!
Hiruma!
Anyone who's not serious about this can leave.
But we've worked so hard to make it this far together!
So far?
The death march has just started.
It's just like Hiruma says.
What about you?
Aren't you gonna leave together with that trash?
Those two are going back to Japan?
And here we all said we'd work hard together...
It's not like I can't understand their desire to leave...
But maybe they'll think about it some more and change their minds.
So only Jumonji stayed behind?
Yeah.
Those three were always together...
Quit yacking about it and go to sleep!
Hey, can we stop now?
Stop what?
We don't have to keep running!
Why didn't you say so sooner, darn it!
We finally escaped that living hell, so why the heck were we still running?
But ya know, we've gotten pretty tough lately.
Your arms! They're bulging!
So are yours!
But Jumonji's arms are the biggest!
Jumonji's always been the best at arm wrestling, hasn't he?
It feels kinda strange with just the two of us.
The three of us were always together...
I wonder if he'll come after us...
Jumonji?
Yeah.
He won't.
He wouldn't come...
Ya-ha!
Time to leave!
I'm still tired.
Huh? Where's Jumonji?
Huh?
His luggage is gone!
He didn't...!
Jumonji! Jumonji!
Jumonji!
I wonder if he went after the other two.
No way!
He didn't.
I bet Jumonji went to go get Kuroki and Togano.
How do you know that?
Because...
We want to change!
Please! Please wait for Jumonji to come back before we set out.
Do you have any proof that he'll come back?
No... I don't.
What should we do, Hiruma?
Hiruma, please!
We're leaving!
But...
Hiruma, we can wait a little while for them!
We don't have time to wait for people who might not even be coming back!
Let's get ready.
I'm staying here!
I know that Jumonji and the others will come back.
Sena?
We'll work hard to catch up with you after they get here.
So go on ahead.
Sena, I understand how you feel, but...
It's okay, Mamori.
We'll definitely catch up, so go on ahead.
Sena...
We'll be waiting for you, so you better catch up to us!
Right!
Okay, fine!
Those who want to wait can wait!
Those who don't, get ready to leave NOW!
We're going!
Since you trust them so much, I'm going to stay and wait, too.
Monta!
We first years gotta stick together!
Thank you, Monta.
I'm sorry!
Komusubi?!
I'm staying!
Komusubi...!
But, Sena, tell me one thing.
How come you believe in them so much?
Wanna know!
Because... Because they made a promise together with us at the airport.
That's right.
Sure is!
It isn't stopping.
Wonder how long it'll keep raining...
I wonder if Jumonji's pushing the truck in this rain...
Probably is.
He's so stupid.
Ganging up together with THEM.
We could have had a blast together if he went back to Japan with us.
Wonder if he'll come...
He won't.
Jumonji!
What gives?!
So you came after all!
Are you going back to Japan with us?
I get it!
You weren't sure if you wanted to or not because you're afraid of airplanes.
Am I right?
I'm sticking with the death march.
I'm sticking with the death march until the end!
You serious?
Are you fine with being called trash forever?!
Anyone who wants to call us that can!
We've already made up our minds to go back to Japan, right, Toga?
It's summer vacation in Japan right now.
We could still have fun together.
What's the point of staying here and pushing some truck like idiots?
Whatever! The two of us are leaving!
But...
He's always been different from us!
What?!
How am I different?!
You read it too, right?
In some football magazine a while back they were praising you,
but acted like we were nothing but trash!
What's with that?
Kurita, Komusubi and Jumonji made some key plays,
but Kuroki and Togano were practically useless.
Did it really say that?
Did you see that?
Even trash can read.
I see.
So we're the trash-combo, then.
Isn't that great?!
Are you for real?
It's the truth, isn't it?
Let's go already, Toga.
Yeah!
What did ya do that for?!
You're trash through-and-through.
Doesn't that bother you any?!
Shut up!
Like it even matters!
YOU'RE not trash, after all.
Trash gets along well with other trash.
I've always thought of you two as my buddies.
So I've never been able to forgive people when they call you two trash!
If you're trash, then so am I!
We'll always be together!
Then come back to Japan with us!
We just can't do this!
We're going to change!
Even HE was able to change!
He...
You mean Sena?
There's no way he can do something that we can't!
You...!
You jerk!
That hurts!
Hey, look.
Up at the sky!
A rainbow...
Three, four, five... Huh?
What are you counting?
I got punched way more by you two!
No, that's not it.
Do American rainbows only have six colors?
Four, five, six, seven, eight. There's eight colors!
No way! Four, five, six...There's just six!
You two are so stupid.
No matter where in the world you go, all rainbows have SEVEN colors.
What's that?!
Wanna fight, huh?!
Wanna give it a try?
The death march...
Guys!
Just so you know, we're not doing it for you.
We're doing it for ourselves!
Jumonji!
Hey!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima blaze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Yay! We made it to San Antonio!
But where'd Sena go?
Did he get lost again?
Any problem can easily be solved by the great Suzuna Taki, who's taking the stage!
Yuck! What the heck are you doing here?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: OH! My sister! Ya-ha!
Hey!
Sena?!
There's six people!
Everyone came back!
Hey!
Guess I don't need this anymore...
Welcome back!
DEATH MARCH - Day 4
Distance to the West Coast: 1784 km