It's pouring rain here as we enter the 20 minute halftime period before the second half begins.
P-Pouring...
It's like we're playing in a giant pool.
We'd better get inside.
What're you doing, Se-
Hang in there for now.
I'll find a way to beat them before halftime's over.
We now turn to Riko for an analysis of the first half.
R-Right, we've seen great plays today.
First is Ojo's new weapon, the Ballista.
They've added the linebacker Seijuro Shin to their offense,
and his power and speed seem invincible!
In addition, Takami and Sakuraba's Everest Pass may demonstrate
just how far they've come offensively even better than the Ballista.
Ojo controlled the pace the whole time.
Deimon's only points came from two Musashi field goals, and even those barely made it.
Deimon has yet to score a touchdown. Do they have a chance to come back?
The key to Deimon's offense, Eyeshield 21, has been completely shut down thus far by Shin.
Indeed. Eyeshield 21, Sena Kobayakawa, holds the key to a Deimon comeback.
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Our Fate lies in Halftime.
All Dobu said was "Once halftime starts, wait right here."
What was he thinking?
- What the heck is that?
The new Devil Bat Mobile!
I wanted to surprise you guys.
This guy has no idea how to manage his money.
He's gonna end up fleeing his debts again...
No time for games.
Welcome to our personal waiting room.
I finished compiling the footage, Hiruma.
Good. Cue up the tackles while I watch this.
Right there.
I'll loop this...
Peewee.
If you wanna space out, ice your knees while you do it.
Oh... right.
Let me and Anezaki handle this.
As for the rest of you, we've got 20 minutes before halftime's over.
If we don't find a way to win before the 3rd quarter starts,
the game's over for us.
We only gave up two field goals in the whole first half.
No touchdowns.
Everything so far has been in line with our predictions.
I haven't seen any mistakes from you.
But our focus isn't on maintaining a seven point lead for the entire second half.
Keep scoring until they're overwhelmed,
and show the whole country why Ojo is the king of football!
Seven points isn't any kind of safety net.
Deimon still has Eyeshield 21.
Haven't you already beaten him...?
Eyeshield 21 is a player who will suddenly evolve in the middle of a game.
A seven point lead can be erased by one touchdown.
We can't rest easy yet.
I agree.
We can't just focus on defense, we need to keep up an aggressive offense as well!
Eyeshield isn't finished yet.
He'll try to make a comeback.
Prepare for Trainer Doburoku's ultimate move, the ladder massage!
When he cuts back to pursue his opponent...
Normally you'd slow down, but he sped up!
The more I watch him, the more perfect he looks.
Huh? You leaving already, Musashi?
If I sit around for 20 minutes my kicking leg will lose its edge.
I'm going to practice until the game starts back up.
Un deux trois, un deux trois.
Will you go out there with me?
You mean like on a date?!
Wha-?! No!
I know, that's just an old Bulgarian joke.
I don't wanna lose my catching edge.
And I can't sit still anymore!
Okay. You can count on me, Monsieur Mon-Mon.
Come on, Komusubi!
Okay!
Let's roll.
- Yeah!
Sena...
Don't be so sad.
Suzuna...
I know how you feel, but cheer up, okay?
I... I'm not good enough, so everyone else...
Shin... he didn't speak a word,
but his eyes said everything.
"Is that it?"
Sena...
I'm...
I'm frustrated... I can't...
No one else cares.
You're up against Shin, after all.
If you just wanna play better that you have so far,
you don't have to suffer alone.
Trust in everyone else.
They're all waiting for you.
Sena...
The game's not over.
Seven points is nothing!
What does Yocchie always say?
"We'll rally in the second half!"
You finally smiled, Sena.
You can't start feeling better till you smile!
Now Yocchie's smiling!
Hiruma?
I got it, Peewee.
You do? You figured it out?
How to beat Shin?
A way to catch him?
You bet I did.
One... we've only got one way.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we're talking about throwing long passes!
To throw a long pass correctly, properly rotating your body is more important than arm strength.
So make sure you train your whole body! Ya-ha!
One... we've only got one way.
You use your arms...
...to send Seijuro Shin flying!
S-Sena... use his arms?
To knock Shin aside?
Th-That's...
...impossible...
Totally...
You have to.
Like I said, it's our only option.
There's no more time, the game's about to resume.
I'll only say this once, so open your ears as wide as they'll go.
This is Shin's top speed.
What's his time on the 40, Manajerk?
About 4.2 seconds.
4.2? The same as Sena?
Human legs can't run any faster than that.
Then... it's not like he can BEAT Sena.
That's WHY he beats him.
Huh? Why?
Shin's superior arm strength plus the 4.2 second speed...
The Trident Tackle's range is ridiculous.
You should know, he's hit you with it enough times.
If the speed is the same, the one with the longer range will win.
A spear has the advantage over a sword - that's basic war strategy.
That's why this is our only option.
Build up your strength,
and charge at Shin's chest.
Cross swords with him.
Destroy Seijuro Shin with arm strength!
The Deimon Devil Bats vs. the Ojo White Knights.
The second half of this incredible semi-final game is about to begin!
Anyone in here who's ever missed or skipped even one practice, raise your hand.
Takami?
Back in 6th grade.
SHIN?
Well, he got lost on Mt. Fuji that one time.
Oh yeah...
I believe the only person here who's never missed even one day...
...is Otawara.
Really?
Yeah, you even show up on our days off...
because you forget we have them off.
Ahh, don't sweat the small stuff!
Exactly.
Otawara is the only one who's never rested. Everyone else's hand went right up.
All that proves is how harsh Ojo's training sessions are.
But all 46 of you have every right to be proud,
because you're still here!
You've followed your dreams, and all 46 of you came together
to make up the best Ojo team in the school's history.
Out of 104 people who tried out,
you are an elite group of 46 who endured hellish training and formed an unshakable bond.
Now get out there and finish off the strongest offensive team in Kanto, the Deimon Devil Bats!
Sena!
Mamori...
I just wanted to tell you something, Sena...
Musashi told me all about how you were forced to play for the Devil Bats back in the spring...
Your code name is Eyeshield 21!
He said Hiruma was so happy, that he'd finally found the teammate he'd been waiting for.
When the newly-formed Devil Bats played Ojo last spring,
I'll find someone you can't even touch,
a running back who moves at the speed of light.
Hiruma's been waiting for you since the day he formed the Deimon Devil Bats.
For a light speed running back... for you, Sena.
You were chosen to destroy Ojo...
...by me.
Thank you, Mamori.
I'll be fine now.
Hey, the rain stopped.
The sun has come out to shine down on me like a giant spotlight.
It's clearing up!
Clearing up!
I'll say.
It's so sunny it almost looks fake.
Gotta love the sunny weather.
We're not just hanging by a thread.
We still got a lucky star on our side.
Aah, that's no star, that's the sun!
- The sun IS a star.
My stupid brother...
Yay, Sena's back!
- Yahoo!
- It's about time, Sena!
Yahoo!
Did you finally snap out of it?
Sena...
By the way, Yocchie...
What'd you mean when you said we had a lucky star or whatever?
Ten minutes into the half.
If we make it ten minutes into the half, the momentum will shift back to Deimon.
Ten minutes...
...into the half?
The dark rain clouds that have hung over the stadium thus far have faded away,
and the sky is now a pure, deep blue!
And now this hard battle will resumes
as the 22 most elite players, the chosen ones, take the field again!
Deimon lines up to kick off!
I feel... I dunno, I feel strange.
Huh?
I was always afraid of fights and confrontations...
I spent my whole childhood running around as a gopher because I couldn't stand up for myself.
But now I'm using my running to take on Shin... and I'm taking the fight TO him.
What the heck are you talking about?
You've been bringing the fight to people this whole time!
You challenged THEM despite being small, you took on all those superhuman players,
and you blew past them! That's what got you here!
He's right...
Bit by bit, little by little I've gotten stronger
thanks to all the other teams I've faced up until now.
To be honest, I have no idea how I'm going to overcome Shin...
But...
Habashira, Panther, Kakei, Mizumachi, Riku, Kid, Akaba, and Agon...
I have to take everything I learned from playing against them...
...and use it to beat Shin!
He needs time to build up his power...
We'll buy him as much as we can...
...and pick up the pieces when it's all over.
So run your heart out.
Run!
Guys...
Eyeshield 21...
I will take you down with everything I've got!
Shin...
Here it comes...
The second half is underway!
Musashi's violent kick rips the now-blue sky in half as it flies across the field!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Go Sena! Knock Shin for a loop... Wait, how are YOU gonna-?!
If we're going to beat Ojo, it's the only chance...
Then build up your courage and charge!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Battlefield, After the Rain!
Ya-ha!
Halftime or not, if I rest too long, I'll get sluggish.
The 40 yard dash in 4.2 seconds.
The limits of human speed...
No one on earth can outrun this speed!
What?! Who could possibly pass me NOW?!
I'm not food, I'm only human!
A dog...