And what about you?!
You all have to leave Japan immediately, remember?!
Yeah, that's right!
You don't need your airplane tickets anymore, right?
D-Don't tell us...
Ya-ha! We're getting special training in America!
This is a stuffed animal.
What are you talking about?
It's a stuffed animal.
Do you mean you want me to take care of him?
I know that animals aren't allowed to ride together with the passengers in the cabinet.
Please calm down, sir!
I-I HATE airplanes!
Hey!
I'm going back!
Anyone who wants to leave can jump off the plane anytime they like.
I'm going home!
I'm leaving, too!
Me, too!
What are you going to do?
I-I... Well...
Spit it out!
Sena!
Use your parachute!
Yeah! Huh? It won't open!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Take Cerberus Back!
It won't open!
Ow, ow, ow!
Are you okay, Sena?
Y-Yeah...
You were thrashing around!
I had a horrible nightmare...
Anyone would have nightmares after suddenly being thrown onto an airplane
and being told that we're going to America.
On top of that, Hiruma put you in charge of Cerberus.
Cerberus?!
Don't worry. He's being good and sleeping right now.
But is it okay for him to take up an entire seat?
There's a bunch of extra seats because the Aliens brought so many players to Japan.
What's going to happen to us now?
What's wrong? You look pale, Jumonji.
My feet aren't on the ground.
Well, duh! We're on an airplane!
Don't tell me...
W-What is it?
Do you have acrophobia?
So what?!
I can't believe a ruffian has acrophobia! How lame!
Bug off!
Jim, look at that.
What? What? What?
We can use that.
How cute! It's a cute little girl!
Not the brat, stupid! The thing she's holding!
It's an ugly, ugly, UGLY stuffed animal!
Be quiet, stupid!
You only have to say that once!
So, what are we going to do? What'll we do? What'll we do?
Didn't you get what I just said?
What? What? What?
I told you to stop repeating yourself!
Okay, okay.
Good. Now go get that stuffed animal!
Michael...
Little missy, could you be a good girl and let go? Huh?
What's with you?!
I feel sick. I'm gonna barf!
Hey, stupid, the bathroom's over there, OVER THERE!
Boss, what're we going to do with this?
Just watch.
I see. You're so smart, Boss!
All set. Now go give it back!
Okay!
Hey, Cerberus, what are you doing over here?
This stinks...
Hey, Manager, you're supposed to be its babysitter, right?
Huh? Michael?
Michael? Michael?
Michael?
Have you seen Michael?
Sure haven't...
Michael, what were you doing over here?!
No,no! You can't leave me without saying something first!
You sure got heavy all of a sudden!
More, please!
Please give me a serving for three!
Okay...
Aren't hungry?
I feel too sick to eat...
Oh, Michael! Did you learn how to talk?
Good boy! You've sure grown up!
Mama, Michael learned how to speak!
Really? Isn't that nice?
Michael, Mama praised you, too!
Here! It's your reward!
Boss, it's weird, weird, WEIRD!
Ouch!
Have you already forgotten?
But that stuffed animal's eating beef jerky.
Huh?
You stupid idiot! There's no way a stuffed animal can eat beef jerky!
But I saw him eat it!
We are about to land at the Houston Airport.
So this is America!
We're there! We're finally, FINALLY going to land!
Despite all of their whining, they're super excited. They're such kids!
Michael, come back!
Michael, here's that beef jerky you like!
Boss, did you see that? Did you?
See what?
The stuffed animal ran.
Ouch!
We hope that everyone enjoys their trip.
We're looking forward to flying together with you again.
Make sure we don't forget anything.
Hiruma, where are we staying tonight?
Nowhere!
We don't have a single cent to spend on a hotel!
We'll have to raise money while we're here!
How are we supposed to do that
when we're in a place we've never been to and know diddly-squat about?!
Dunno. I've got other things to do.
I can't believe he just dumped that on us...
What's wrong, Sena?
I forgot Cerberus!
Hiruma's gonna kill me!
You forgot this!
But this is a stuffed animal.
That's right. It's supposed to be a stuffed animal, isn't it?
Well, no, it's not like this one, you see.
It's more, how to put it...
Right, right! It's ugly and vicious!
Come to think of it, there was a little girl carrying around another one identical to this.
That's it!
Where's Hiruma?
He told us to meet up at the Football Stadium at six.
Then he ran off by himself somewhere.
You said six, right?
I've got to find him before then!
Cerberus!
Football Clinic!
What does the quarterback do?
They're the leaders over the offense and are first to throw the ball.
They need the intelligence to quickly make decisions and come up with strategies. Ya-ha!
Cerberus!
We'll split up and help search for him!
First let's look for the girl.
The teams will be Kurita and Komusubi, Mamori and I, and then...
We'll pass on this one.
Jumonji, doesn't feel good so we're not going to help out.
Then look after our luggage!
This stinks! We came all the way to America just to search for some dumb mutt!
Yep...
Let's see...
Any luck?
But why on earth did Hiruma bring Cerberus to America in the first place?
Back when Hiruma and I were in middle school, Cerberus...
For a stray mutt, you've got a pretty good sparkle in your eyes.
I like you!
From today on, you'll be Cerberus!
Ever since then, Hiruma's looked after Cerberus, and Cerberus seems to obey Hiruma.
That for real?
But Cerberus is also a member of the Devil Bats!
At any rate, let's split up and search for him again!
Right!
I swear! I can't believe everyone's making such a fuss over such an ugly stuffed animal!
W-What's that?!
Hey, what's that?
Ask me all you want, but I'm not sure myself.
I bet that's contraband!
Arrest them!
Hey, that's...
Hiruma!
Hey, Hiruma!
Are you friends with these men?
Nope, never met 'em!
What?!
Hey, Hiruma!
You can't say that!
Later!
You jerk! Monster! Demon!
They got through customs okay, right?
Yeah, now we just have to wait for a chance to steal that stuffed animal from the girl again.
What's in your bag?
It's Michael.
You know stuffed animals can't move!
But he's grown up!
He even talks by growling at me!
Right, right.
I know! You must be hungry!
Wait a sec, Michael!
It's the Houston Burger Special!
T-There's Cerberus!
Michael, just be good and eat that inside the bag, okay?
Hey!
Thief!
After him, Sena!
Yeah!
We've gotta get Cerberus back!
Kurita, Cerberus is in that guy's bag!
We're gonna collide!
Cerberus!
Jerk! What the heck are you doing?!
Wait!
It's so crowded!
He's cornered!
What?!
Boss, that way!
Okay!
Sena, pass him!
Over here!
Max Catch!
Jerk, give back my bag!
Shoot!
Sena, take it!
Monta, don't try to pass him!
I knew it...
Lucky!
They're being as crazy as ever!
Cerberus!
What?!
Touchdown! Ya-ha!
Hi-Hiruma...
A real dog was in the bag! Why? Why? Why?!
Shut up!
Hold up!
You're the ones who were trying to bring in contraband gems, weren't you?
Arrest them!
It's the stuffed animal we hid the goods in!
Good job, Cerberus.
These two are wanted criminals with bounties on their heads.
What a resemblance!
They're identical!
My Michael!
What a strange turn of events, but at least we got Cerberus back!
Now Hiruma isn't going to kill you!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Hey, hey, Sena!
Did you and Monta get lost this time?!
Where is this?! Someone, please tell me!
Looks like something's going on over there!
Isn't that football?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: American Football Downtown! Ya-ha!
This sure is a small hamburger...
But the only reason we're even able to eat is because...
...of the money Cerberus got from that bounty.
Everyone should be grateful towards Cerberus!
Right...
Darn him, that stinkin' Hiruma...
He abandoned us!
We'll remember this!