How many times do I have to tell you?!
If you only use your arms you'll never hold them back!
Use your glutes, your glutes!
Man!
Coach!
Good... Come on!
Yes!
Your legs are getting better, but you still need work.
Once more, please!
Your step-in's no good!
Once more!
Grab the armpits!
M-More...
We can't lose.
We're going to the Kanto Tournament!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Sena Kobayakawa.
How can this be?!
Just run the route, you idiots!
Next we blitz.
Are you okay, Eyeshield?
Rest a little,
you've really been overdoing it today.
It's okay...
I'm fine.
Boys are so stubborn about the silliest things.
Hm?
Oh, no, I'm talking about Sena, not you, Eyeshield.
He forced himself to the Ojo-Seibu game even though he was sick.
He said "Eyeshield and I are the same size and HE always works hard."
Maybe he's just getting too worked up.
No, he's...
He said he wants to do his part as a member of the team...
A member of the team?
That's right! Sena said that to me, too!
All our members are wonderful.
Catch, Butt-Monkey!
I really hope we can make it to the Christmas Bowl.
Me too, Mamori-
Hmm?
I'm sure Sena's proud to be part of the team.
After all,
he joined all on his own.
Aren't you going home, Sena?
Nope, I've still got a few things to do.
Want me to help?
Nah, I can do it.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Yeah...but-
Relax! I'll be fine, you can go home.
O-Okay...
You're in high school now,
you have to make real friends, on your own!
You are Eyeshield 21!
Touchdown!
It's already over...
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
Sena Kobayakawa, #21.
Position: Running back!
You're nothing more than a fake.
How long are you going to hide behind your Eyeshield mask?
You're an American football athlete.
When I'm a good enough player
that Mamori won't have to worry about me.
I'll tell her myself.
I'm not there yet,
but I'll keep running forward.
Tomorrow will decide everything!
I'm Sena Kobayakawa of the Deimon Devil Bats!
I swear I'll fight with everything I have!
Good luck, Sena...
Sena!
Move it! Mamori's already here!
Man, I was so nervous I couldn't get to sleep!
Oh yeah, I might be on TV, so make sure you watch the game!
See ya later!
On TV? Really?
Today's the day.
We have to work hard, as Devil Bats.
We'll make it to the Christmas Bowl.
Oh? You look like a new man today.
It's do or die, only one school will survive!
The battle for third place is about to begin!
Akaba!
Yes?
We'll be introducing the players individually today,
what do you think of "The Wizard of Lead Blocking, Hayato Akaba!"
Not bad...
May I arrange the tune a bit differently?
Introduce me as "Natsuhiko 'Gentle' Taki!"
- "The Doofus" is fine, sir.
"Doofus..."
Dun dun DUN!
We arrive at our seats JUST in time!
That was close, huh Kobanzame?
Yep, it's time Mizumachi!
Who's gonna get the last ticket to the Kanto Tournament,
Deimon or Bando?
Either way, this will be a tough game.
Geez, Kakei, you're always so stiff.
Eyeshield 21...
And here come today's players!
First is the hard rockin' beats
of the team that kicked its way here today, the Bando Spiders!
"The Smart Kicker," with a perfect kick success rate of 100%,
Kotaro Sasaki!
I'm feeling smart today!
Man, that guy loves being the center of attention.
Not unlike a certain someone...
Next is last year's MVP,
"The Wizard of Lead Blocking..."
"The REAL Eyeshield 21," Hayato Akaba!
Cool! Is he for real?
The REAL Eyeshield 21?
Akaba...
Real Eyeshield 21 my butt!
He's cruisin' for a brusin'!
S-Settle down, guys!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What's the most important thing to have
for Eyeshield's position, running back?
The hint is "keep the ball!"
If you drop the ball,
the opponent goes on offense,
so you need to protect the ball with your life!
Don't drop it!
Ya-ha!
And their opponents,
who went from unknowns to contenders overnight,
the Deimon Devil Bats!
First is the unsinkable battleship
with the 160 kg bench press,
Ryokan Kurita!
Kuriton, give them a "hnnraba!"
Next is the monkey who flies through the sky,
risking his life for every catch,
Taro Raimon!
Max Catch!
And the tight end who can run, catch, and do it all,
Hello to my fans from around the world!
"Natsuhiko 'Gentle' Taki...The Doofus!"
How can this be?!
We received two introductions, so I combined them!
That's so cruel...
The only man who could turn dry ice black
with his demonic presence,
the ruler of hell itself, Yoichi Hiruma!
And his protectors,
all monsters in their own right!
The tiny tank that can turn on a dime,
Daikichi Komusubi!
Komusubi's parents are here today to cheer him on!
Next, they don't let anyone throw them around!
The Delinquent Deathblow will explode today!
With balance and technique, Kazuki Jumonji!
With speed and tenacity, Koji Kuroki!
With power and heart, Shozo Togano!
Together, they are "The Three Ha-Ha Brothers!"
- We're not even related!
The secret weapon, Manabu Yukimitsu!
Where could Sena be?
This morning when I said "today's the day" to him,
he looked like he was ready to play himself!
It reminded me of what you said yesterday,
and I thought, he really is like a 12th player.
Mamori...
Hmm?
Sena...
What... are you doing, Sena?
Football's... too dangerous for y-
I'm sorry I could never bring myself to tell you, Mamori...
But I have to go...
...because... I'm...
And finally, the man behind the mysterious mask known as "Eyeshield 21,"
"The Lightspeed Running Back,"
Eyesh- No!
Sena...
...Kobayakawa!
Sena Kobayakawa?!
That unassuming freshman in class 1-2?!
He's the awesome invincible Eyeshield 21?!
Yeah!
I've been waiting to say this forever!
SENA!
SENA! SENA! SENA!
Yes! He finally worked up the nerve!
Man, he's popular!
- Thank you, thank you!
- Aha, pointless bowing!
In this sense, he hasn't grown at all.
Sena...?
Wha-Eyeshield 21's true identity
is their manager, Sena?
Look, Shin, Eyeshield is-
Hmm? Is something different?
His arms and legs look exactly the same to me.
Oh yeah, you remember people by their muscles, not their faces...
You're awesome, Sena!
I-Is this okay?
It is, isn't it Hiruma?!
He doesn't need to hide anymore!
The next time he'll be allowed to call himself Eyeshield
is after he plows through Vampiro over there.
He does that, I have no complaints.
So you realized you had no chance
and threw away your identity on your own?
No.
I don't care who's real and who's fake.
I'm going to play with everything I've got, as myself!
Very well.
Let's hear what kind of beat you can crank out.
Sena... is Eyeshield...
Leave Sena alone!
How come Sena's always gone whenever Eyeshield's around?
I can't believe I didn't notice...
If I'd thought about it for one second I would've figured it out...
I couldn't tell...
Even though Sena's been growing up all this time...
I've been treating him like a child.
The whole time, I've done nothing but hold him back.
I'm so selfish.
So... selfish...
Just leave her alone.
But...
She's not weak...
She'll be right out.
What am I doing?
Sena's been working so hard to become a good football player...
What am I-
Last but not least,
after all that excitement,
is the manager,
Mamori Anezaki!
We have to work hard, as Devil Bats.
That's right...
I...
I have a job to do...
As the Devil Bats' manager!
She manages the team, signals from the bench,
and still has time to wolf down cream puffs!
Hiruma, why'd you give me such a dumb intro?!
Here, everyone!
Double check all your plays before we go out!
Double check to the max!
- Mamori...
- Here.
Good luck, Sena!
Let's show them all what a kick team can do!
A rockin' beat and a ear-splitting shout!
Bando Spiders!
Rock and soul!
There's no point in worrying about what we don't have!
Even without a kicker,
we fight like Deimon Devil Bats.
I don't care how many of us die along the way, just win!
Everyone put your hearts into it!
Let's make sure Musashi hears us!
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
- C'mon!
Prepare yourself for the strongest,
smartest kick team's first strike!
Huh?
This is-
The whole Bando team's suddenly moving to the right!
Move up!
They're going for an onside kick!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Bando's doing an onside kick
at the start of the game?!
Already?!
The fact that they're being so reckless
means they've got faith in their kicker!
Here comes Kotaro!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Ultimate Kick Team! Ya-ha!
Hi! I'll introduce the rest of the team!
First is the drunken trainer, Doburoku Sakaki!
Hey hey!
Come on, people.
And all together, the loaners from other clubs!
Good ol' Ishimaru, Yamaoka, Satake, and Omosadake!
I'm not food!
I'm... only human...