Man, Riku sure was amazing yesterday.
Rodeo Drive Stampede...
That running style's incredible.
But so is mine.
My running can't lose to Riku's and Shin's-!
What's wrong? Why'd you yell?
Oh, yeah, it's nothing.
Sena, your...
...shirt's on backwards.
H-Huh?
Hey, Sena, do you have some time after practice today?
Sure do.
I was thinking of giving you and Rikky some new shoes.
Shoes? For Riku and me?
Yep!
I want to give them to you before you play off against each other.
Mamori!
See you after practice!
I'll go e-mail Rikky about it.
Okay!
Mamori looks so happy.
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Knight with no Blind Spots!
You're not done yet, Sakuraba!
You can go even higher!
Right! Once more!
Okay! Here I go!
Okay!
More! More!
You guys are great!
I'll fight, too!
I won't lose! Let me play-!
Shut up!
Oh, it's Shin!
A-Awesome!
You're always ready for anything!
Not quite. I haven't perfected it yet.
Huh?
Mamo?
Rikky, congratulations making the semi-finals.
I'd like to give you and Sena new shoes as a reward!
Let's meet up after practice by the shopping center's entrance!
Give me a call if you get lost.
Mamo's still treating me like a kid...
I'm gonna be late!
Shin?
Riku sure is late.
Yeah...
I wonder if practice is running late today.
Probably. But he'll be here soon.
Yep!
What was that?
Teach me your Rodeo Drive.
Why do you want to learn my Rodeo Drive?
Receiving Call From Sena
If I can boost my tackle with your Rodeo Drive at the last minute
and hit someone with 120% my normal speed...
I could overcome Sena Kobayakawa's great speed and catch him.
Shin went to see Kaitani?!
Why would he do that?
Takami, if Sena Kobayakawa fought Shin right now, who would win?
Be honest.
Naturally, no one is an overall better player than Shin,
but speed-wise it's fifty-fifty.
Actually, the odds might be against Shin.
No matter how strong your tackle is,
it's useless if you can't touch your enemy.
Shin is trying to develop the ultimate spear
that will allow him to stop his foe
no matter how fierce the battle.
So Shin's wants to learn Riku Kaitani's Rodeo Drive?
Probably.
If you combined Shin's one-armed Spear Tackle...
With Kaitani's super fast Rodeo Drive...
Even a kid could answer that.
The answer's simple.
Shin's powerful arms combined with the Rodeo Drive's speed
would send him flying...
...directly towards the ball!
It looks like the weather's taking a turn for the worse.
Sena, can you get a hold of Rikky?
Sena?
Oh, it's nothing.
He's not picking up.
I've been working on boosting my speed just before the tackle
so that I can defeat Sena Kobayakawa.
It'll be complete once I combine it with the secret behind your Rodeo Drive.
There's no way I could teach that to you!
I'd never do something that would put him at a disadvantage!
Besides, I already lost to you in the Tokyo Tournament!
Why do you want me to teach you-
So I can learn how to run.
You're a better runner than me.
It started raining...
I guess his practice really is running late...
Then it can't be helped.
We'll try again later.
Yeah...
Later, Sena! See you tomorrow.
Yep!
I wonder if something happened to Riku...
Riku!
What happened to you?!
Riku...?
I saw Shin.
Huh? Shin?
I think I might have done something horrible.
Huh?
I might have created a monster!
I'm sorry.
Riku!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Do you know how many quarters a football game's broken into?
Think back on the games!
Football games are broken into four quarters.
After each quarter,
the teams swap to opposite sides of the field.
Did everyone get that? Ya-ha!
White Knights! White Knights! White Knights!
Wow! Just what I'd expect for Ojo!
They've got a bunch of fans!
Monta!
Hey, Sena!
What's going on?
Why all the commotion?
Well you see, the team going up against Ojo hasn't shown up yet.
But it's almost time for the game!
Oh, they're finally here!
Boobs! Boobs!
Hey, sorry! We ran into some engine trouble.
Boss, can we dump it here?
Sure!
Boobs! Boobs!
Whoa, we made it!
Boobs!
Well done.
It was nothing!
It was easy with boss here!
B-B-Boobs?
Hey, aren't those are the dudes that defeated Shinryuji?
We're honored that you came to watch us!
Yeah! But geez, you're frail!
I'm the Sado Strong Golems' captain, Ganjo Iwashige.
I'm his number one disciple, Susumu Kyotai.
Let me tell you something!
It's the Way of the Boobs!
It's our ultimate technique we give to those who've lost after a "well fought game."
Way of the Boobs
You should become my pupils!
N-N-No thanks...
W-We're...
Don't hold back!
The Way of the Boobs is great!
We accept newcomers any time, any day of the week!
Boobs! Boobs!
Way of the Boobs?
What's that?
Man, Sena's really late!
Geez, where are they?
Rikky!
Mamo...
What happened yesterday?
I was so worried!
Well, I was at practice...
Really, you should have called us!
I guess, I was just a bit tired.
Sorry!
By the way, is Sena around?
No, but I think he'll be here soon.
I see.
Man, those guys were weird,
but they might be pretty tough.
Yeah...
Sena!
Mamori!
Riku...
What?! Shin asked-?!
Hey, hey.
Don't tell me you actually taught him how to use your Rodeo Drive's running style!
I did.
W-Why?!
We're stuck fighting against Ojo next!
Teaching that to Shin...!
Riku, that's gonna put you at a disadvantage, too!
Sena, what's your opinion?
Do you wish I hadn't taught it to him?
So I can learn how to run.
You're a better runner than me.
He didn't even hesitate over asking me to teach him so that he could better himself.
I'm angry at my pettiness
and my own stupidity.
I want to see Shin at his full potential.
That's why I'm going to tell him the core secret behind my technique.
Fine, I'll tell you.
Watch my legs very closely.
Rodeo Drive Stampede!
Well? Did you figure it out?
Just before you take a cut while using the Rodeo Drive,
take a goose step.
I'm sure you'll get the hang of it once you try it out in a real game.
Now then, give it a try.
Rodeo Drive Stampede!
I imagine he'll try out his newly perfected Spear Tackle in his game against Sado.
His perfected...
Did you want to fight against Shin before he perfected his technique?
No...
Next is the semi-finals. Since we've gotta win anyway,
I want... I want to fight Shin at his strongest!
Sena, that's what makes you Eyeshield 21.
The game's about to start!
It's the Ojo White Knights vs. the Sado Strong Golems!
Will Ojo, the strongest competitors in this tournament, come out victorious?!
Or will Sado be able to swat them down?!
This'll be a great game!
Entering the field first is the grand king, Ojo!
Yay! It's finally starting!
Yep!
Ojo! Sakuraba! You rock!
Now appearing from the mist is...
...the powerful Tokyo team, the Ojo White Knights!
First up is the brains of Ojo!
He's a player that wields knowledge like a weapon.
It's the level-headed, super tall quarterback, Ichiro Takami!
And next is Takami's Twin Tower,
the idol player turned true American football player!
He's the young white lion, Haruto Sakuraba!
- Sakuraba!
Sakuraba, you can do it!
You're number one!
Ojo's wall makes the way with his giant body and super strength!
It's Captain Makoto Otawara!
Yay!
He's cool!
If he didn't do that...
Now for the man we've been waiting for!
He's got speed, power and technique!
He's got the potential to be the perfect player!
He's the greatest linebacker in history!
Seijuro Shin!
Shin...
Now for the Sado Strong Golems to enter the field!
R-Riko, why're we shaking?!
I-Is there an earthquake?!
I-It's-!
Amazing!
Iwashige and Kyotai are carrying a giant boulder!
This is a display of power unlike any other!
Not bad!
Kyotai and Iwashige are carrying that boulder by themselves?!
Wow! They're strong!
It's time to go, my disciples.
Spread the word of the Way of the Boobs through this game!
Ojo's nothing to be afraid of as long as we defeat Shin!
I'll defeat him!
I'll beat that guy Shin to a bloody pulp!
Uh-oh! Sado just challenged Ojo!
- Boobs!
- Oh!
Strong Golems vs. White Knights
I swear by my pride as a knight that we will win!
We did not come here to fight against our foes!
We came here to defeat them!
- Glory on the kingdom!
I swear by boobie pride in the name of boobs!
We did not come here to fight with boobs!
We came here to become friends with them!
- Way of the Boobs!
W-What's with that?
Ew...
The game will start with Ojo kicking off!
Kyotai caught the ball!
Go, Kyotai!
You're pushovers!
Ojo's defenses...
...got crushed!
That was nothing!
No one can stop Kyotai's run!
This time Ojo's wall, Otawara, is going to intercept him!
Otawara!
You're pathetic!
I'm not interested in anyone but Shin!
Go for it, Kyotai!
Boobie Crush!
Oh no! Otawara was sent flying!
Even Otawara-!
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
You taught Shin the trick behind your Rodeo Drive!
What were you thinking, Riku?!
I may have created a monster!
Will we get to see his perfected Spear Tackle?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Ultimate Spear!
Ya-ha!
Listen my disciples, you must show everyone how great the Way of the Boobs is!
You there, call boob time please.
Huh?
Call boob time.
H-Huh?
I said to call boob time!
What the heck is "boob time?"