Deer! Deer! Deer!
The Deer are completely overwhelming them!
This is shaping up to be a David and Goliath situation!
It's no good... We can't stop 'em...
Nice, I nailed the 40 yard marker!
Check it out!
Knock it off, Mizumachi.
They could eject you for that.
Sorry about that! I didn't mean anything by it!
Don't kick me out, Mr. Umpire!
He's a referee, not an umpire.
Anyways, we're down by 14.
You sure we can do this?
Kakei?
Whoa, you're already changed!
You jumped the gun!
We were doing so good keeping everything a secret for the fall tournament!
This IS the tournament.
There's no point in keeping ourselves a secret if we lose.
True that, true that!
But being a "secret weapon" sounds cooler.
I thought the Kyoshin Poseidons were all average-sized.
It doesn't matter how big his opponents are, Onihei will come out on top!
You're a lot smaller up close, Mr. Senior.
Bigger isn't always better in football.
Why don't we find out,
Mr. Senior?
Set, hut hut!
Learn your place, freshman!
Well, Mr. Senior,
I'll teach you that blood, sweat and tears alone aren't enough to win football games!
No problemo!
That's the game! The Poseidons win!
Kyoshin Poseidons 31 - Hashiratani Deer 14
No way... Onihei lost...
This is a shock...
The Kyoshin Poseidons... They're a new dark horse.
A-Amazing, one of the big championship contenders,
THE Onihei and his Hashiratani Deer have been bumped off!
Losing to these smart-mouthed jerks... at a time like this...
You're too old!
Your era's over.
Tall, wiry guys like me are the wave of the future!
Even your NAME is old.
Why's he have to be such a snot?
They already lost, it doesn't matter what anyone says to them now.
You know, this shows that even technique as refined as Onihei's couldn't bridge the gap.
A gap...
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Courage to Stand Firm.
Did you know about the Poseidons' trump cards?
Just a little.
They never even showed up at regular practices.
Hey, Manajerk.
That tape's invaluable.
Take notes on all the Poseidon and edit the tape so we can see
what ratio of plays they use depending on the down and yards remaining
and also how each individual player moved during those plays.
Offense, defense, extra points, blockers,
kickoffs, onside kicks, returns, tight ends, punts, the works!
Okay.
Sena, you never would've made it as a manager.
Those Poseidon guys are gigantic.
Holding them off's gonna be rough.
I'll be a-okay!
Not as rough as being next to him.
If height's really that big of an advantage...
It means being short's that much more of a handicap.
Oh, Suzuna!
I came for those materials you promised me.
Now, where might Eyeshield 21 be?
Oh, hello!
Um, Eyeshield 21's...
The thing is, he... Oh, he already went-
He's in the john!
- Nice save!
Oh... I guess I'll just wait for him to come back, then!
What do we do?
I'm sorry! I just wanted to get the Bats some publicity...
What's the plan?
You shouldn't have said he was in the bathroom, Mon-Mon!
Don't pin this on me.
And who're you calling Mon-Mon?
Something wrong?
- No, nothing!
This is taking too long... Could you check on him?
I came here to get the dirt on Eyeshield, so I need to talk to him no matter what!
Right...
I'm really sorry,
but you have your uniform, right?
It's not even a game day...
Guess I should go get changed.
Hey, you're...
You're tiny.
Wait, are you Eyeshield 21?
You're so small I didn't even notice you.
Uhh... Hello...
Hello yourself!
Man, talk about a crazy coincidence, huh?
But yeah, you're a real midget, you know.
You're sure you're the real Eyeshield?
Uhh, well, y-
Didn't you study abroad at Notre Dame?
Well, that story's actually-
Kakei spent some time in America during middle school, he said he met you.
A Japanese person who played football at one of Notre Dame's affiliates, Eyeshield 21.
You mean there really WAS an Eyeshield 21 in America?
Hiruma didn't just make that nickname up?
The real... Eyeshield 21?
I never knew you were such a shorty.
Oh yeah!
I wanna fight you, Eyeshield!
Fight?
Hup, two, three...
Catch.
See if you can get past me.
He's gigantic...
Whatsamatter? C'mon already.
Huh?
Wait up?
Are you serious? He ran away.
What's up, Mizumachi?
Guess what, Kakei?
I just ran into Eyeshield.
Eyeshield?
I told myself I'd stop running away...
I...
Football Clinic!
What is an "interception?"
When you catch the opponent's pass and go back on offense.
It's a big play that changes who's on offense and who's on defense! Ya-ha!
Let's all play our hardest in the third round, Devil Bats!
Here here!
Let's eat!
It's not cooked through yet.
That piece belongs to me!
Say what? I don't see your name on it.
Thank you, everyone!
I never expected you to treat me to Korean barbecue to celebrate my debut!
- I'm not good with speeches, but I'll live up-
- They're eating your share, bro.
There's not enough heat over here.
Even Onihei was smothered by their height.
Shin's not as big as them, but even he's much bigger than me.
The real one!
Deimon?
Barbecue after the game...
Even after 30 years, neither of us have any new ideas.
Eh, Shoji?
Doburoku?
Is this the first time they've seen each other in three decades?
They were originally called the "Sengoku University's Swords of Japan"
After all that happened,
I signed on as Deimon's trainer, knowing full well I'd eventually face you.
You put them through a death march?
You're as reckless as ever.
That drunk goof, Doburoku...
Totally just got all hard-boiled on us...
I hate to admit it, but he looks pretty tough all of a sudden.
When it comes to toughness, our coach beats anyone!
Whoa, Kurita, that's your 20th plate!
Gimme another 30 helpings!
Of course, I'm not dating any of our players!
Right, but to be honest, I wonder about Mamo here...
What's with the antenna?
So I heard Ojo's new super move's called the "Ballista?"
Ballista?
I believe that's the name of a medieval weapon.
500 servings of Calbi steak!
Whoever finishes theirs first wins!
Bring it on!
Hiruma...
Did you know there was a real Eyeshield 21?
Of course I did.
It wouldn't have been intimidating if I just made it up.
I guess so...
Forget about all that other junk, just do what you're here to do.
Yay, yay, yay!
I never knew you were such a shorty.
What?!
And also... WHAT?!
Uh... Didn't you have any barbecue?
I eat plenty of meat.
But I've already had the proper amount today.
Proper?
A balanced diet is essential
if you want to have a truly fit body.
A truly fit body...
Umm...
so who would be harder to block,
a tall, fit runner or someone really short, like me?
Oh, I didn't mean anything in particular, I was just kinda wondering...
Assuming everything else is equal?
...Yes.
The tall, fit runner.
You couldn't stop him with a half-hearted tackle.
I figured...
However...
Height alone doesn't determine how hard someone hits.
The real deciding factor is if they have the nerve to stand firm.
Nerve... Stand firm?
If you start feeling inferior now it will cost Deimon the game tomorrow.
No...
I don't feel inferior... I...
I just want to identify my own weaknesses,
and do whatever I can to fix them!
If you're worried about your constitution,
start eating more protein
after games and after exercising.
That's especially important for you since you haven't hit your growth spurt yet.
Barbecue would work well.
Where are you going?
I don't have time to stand still.
Huh?
Hey, you're one of the Deimon guys, right?
Yes...
What're you doing out here?
My team's inside that barbecue place having dinner...
Is Eyeshield there, too?
Maybe...
Is he really any good?
Well, uh...
Eyeshield's the real deal.
Hiruma?
That's easy to SAY, but...
Then do you want another shot at him?
Hiruma?!
That'd be awesome.
Go get Eyeshield.
But-
Just shut up and go get him, you idiot!
Okay, okay!
There he is! That's him, Kakei!
The Eyeshield I met this afternoon.
That's not Eyeshield.
No way!
I realize I'm talking about my middle school days,
but the Japanese exchange student who played as Eyeshield 21,
was the perfect runner.
The perfect runner?
Top class speed, technique, and physique.
No one could beat him.
They couldn't? Why?
He never went down no matter who he collided with.
His height and power were his greatest weapons!
Ah, I get it. Makes sense.
The real Eyeshield 21 wasn't a small kid like yourself.
He shrunk! Right, Eyeshield 21?
It DOES happen, you can shrink over 30 centimeters after you get out of bed.
That's never happened to anyone ever!
Anyways, we'll know after this.
Now come on, Eyeshield!
Try to get past me-
Forget it, Mizumachi.
We'll unmask this fraud at the game.
A tiny, slender boy like you could spend his whole life
trying to catch up to the original, and never even get close.
Did you hear what he just said?
Are you gonna take that, fake Eyeshield?
The real deciding factor is if they have the nerve to stand firm.
I understand.
Huh?
That's what I'm talking about.
You gotta man up.
Okay, brah. Let's do this.
Catch.
Whenever you're ready.
It doesn't matter if I'm the real one or a fake.
I won't try to run!
He's big!
But I want to win more!
Gotcha!
I can make it!
Uh-oh.
Yes!
Not bad.
C'mon, once more.
This time I'll get serious.
Enough!
Mizumachi, we're leaving.
But, Kakei, he-
Save your enthusiasm for the game.
Yeah, the Deimon game's looking a lot more fun now!
You caught him completely off guard... He had no respect for you.
Right.
But a win's a win.
You didn't back down.
Nope!
Hiruma.
I'll keep winning, so we can face Mizumachi's team at the top of their game!
It's rare, but he does do something cool every now and then.
Finishing 500 servings is just impossible...
Okay! Time to get some protein!
I'll do whatever it takes...
...to get us to the Christmas Bowl!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Huh? Eyeshield 21 launched a sneak attack on Zokugaku?
I-I could never do something like that!
If this isn't handled right, both teams could be disqualified!
You're in trouble, Sena!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Beware! The Demonic Chameleons! Ya-ha!
Today's food review comes from a very popular barbecue restaurant!
There's something over to the left!
Shin?!
He added that to his daily training regimen?!