Today's the day...
Yeah.
We should go root for them.
But people from Zokugaku will be there too, right?
That could get ugly.
Someone from Zokugaku beat up a second-year kendo student.
I heard they broke 30 of his ribs!
I heard they sent someone on the soccer team to the hospital!
I heard they hung some kid ping-pong club upside-down by his underpants!
A-Are people from Zokugaku really that scary?!
Help me!
Hey, Sena, you okay?
Cold!
Oh man, they're here!
Run for it! If you make eye contact they'll kill you!
Let's roll!
Yeah!
Beat the crap out of Deimon!
Eyeshield 21 ain't nothin'!
He's dead meat!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Max Catch!
Looks like this'll be interesting.
I hear Rui Habashira's gonna send someone out on a stretcher.
Rui Habashira, second year football player.
The leader of the Zokugaku gang... No one crosses him.
So who's gonna stop me, huh? Let's hear it?
Eyeshield 21.
Make us proud, will ya?
Why the heck do we always have to be walking on eggshells around those little squirts?!
If we just had the negatives from those pictures...
Hey, the game's like, the perfect chance.
Nothing here...
Keep looking!
Shoot, I can't find 'em anywhere!
What the heck is this?
Y-You three... I don't believe this...
You changed your minds!
Hooray, hooray!
There they are!
Go get 'em, Eyeshield 21!
Ugh... Why us...
Wow...
We can't lose now.
Why ya hiding your face?!
You loser!
Quit actin' like you're the man!
Eat this!
Empty cans go in the recycling-
What was that for?
You butt-monkey!
Don't show them what you can do before we even start!
What's gonna happen to us if we lose to those guys?
Mop the floor with them, boss!
Yeah!
Eyeshield 21, I'm gonna snap you in half.
W-What's wrong?
I just felt a chill go down my spine!
Hmm... I dunno how many of our guys will get crushed, I should probably recruit a few extra.
C-Crushed?!
I can't do it... I can't play against scary guys like them!
Please, give me strength.
That's your glove...
Sena?
This thing's kind of like my good luck charm.
Good luck charm?
I'm gonna be a hero too one day, like Honjo!
Honjo, I promise my catching will make me a hero one day!
Monta...
Today's game...
It's not just a scrimmage to me.
It's a decisive point in my life, the chance to prove I haven't wasted my life!
Monta...
That's right, I was the one who convinced Monta to play football.
This is no time to chicken out!
I can't afford to lose, either!
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
If I'm going to face Shin again, I can't go down here!
Please watch me, Honjo!
If we win, we might get a ton of new applicants!
Eyeshield 21, I'm gonna obliterate you.
I'll make every one of you my slave!
Here, have a pamphlet!
Oh... Thank you.
Go get 'em!
Rip their heads off!
Ya-ha!
Tear them apart!
Yeah!
Ashizuka.
Yes?
Okay, the trick to Deimon is knowing that if you stop Eyeshield 21, the rest of them are garbage.
No matter what kind of passes Hiruma throws, none of those babies can catch anything.
So for the kickoff...
The Firecracker Kick.
How are they doing this?
I can't catch it!
Got it!
Max Catch!
Just a fluke...
Crush him!
Pass it, Butt-Monkey!
Monta!
Okay, Eyeshield 21!
Where were you throwing, you stupid chimp?!
If that happens again, I'll rip YOUR head off!
Geez, what's wrong with me?!
Don't worry about it, Monta.
The game's just started.
I missed my chance to be a hero...
Monta...
Great catch!
Don't worry, just keep it up!
Keep it up! Keep it up! Keep it up!
Mamori!
I'll keep it up, I'll keep it up!
Yeah, I'm psyched up to the max!
He's way too easy to manipulate.
Destroy them! Yeah!
The whole atmosphere around here's so hostile.
It feels like an away game.
By the way, how do you even play American football?
Why don't you two take a pamphlet?
Oh, thanks.
I made them especially for people who don't know the rules.
Oh?
So it's played with 11 people, huh?
Cool, it's a battle that takes brains and brawn!
You score points by taking the ball into this "end zone."
Can I have one?
Sure!
Me too!
I'll take two!
I may not get to tape anything at this rate...
Well, Sena's taping from up high, so I guess it's okay.
They've got most of their guys up on the line.
It's definitely a run defense.
They didn't complete a single pass in the Ojo game.
We won't even break a sweat against a team who can't pass!
Set! Hut, hut, hut!
A pass?!
What long arms!
It's too fast, his receiver won't get it either!
Max Goal Dash!
C-Come back!
Yahoo, the long bomb worked! 35 yards!
Monta!
Yay!
Awesome catch!
Monta, that was so cool!
Mamori! YES!
All right!
What's the football team doing?
Are they gonna use the field all day?
Huh? Raimon?
He joined the football team?
That #80 kid's an actual receiver.
Maybe we should keep some of our guys back?
You moron, if we back off, Eyeshield 21 will run right past us!
The Devil Bats are a running team.
Eyeshield will run next time, for sure.
And we'll wreck him!
I wonder what we should do next...
Maybe I'll pass it again?
What to do...?
He looks so mad... Killer.
Set, hut, hut, hut!
Here it comes, he's handing it off to Eyeshield!
Trash him!
Crap!
Wha-
Honjo, I wasn't any good at baseball, but I promise you-
Go for it!
No way.
I promise you, I'll become a football hero instead!
Football Clinic!
Why do you kick the ball after a touchdown?
To get a bonus point!
You can kick it between the goalposts for one point,
or try for another touchdown to get two points! Ya-ha!
I promise you, I'll become a football hero instead!
He did it! What a catch!
Touchdown! We scored first!
No way...!
Hero to the max!
You did it!
Good one, Raimon! Keep it up!
Coach?
What?
I'm, uh, just a little surprised.
Why?
We didn't think you liked Raimon, that's all.
How could I like that klutz?
I'm the baseball coach, I only like people who're good at baseball.
But right now I'm a guy watching football.
So I only want to see people who're good at football!
Raimon! Raimon! Raimon!
Atta boy, Raimon!
Whoo, Raimon!
Monkey!
Emotional to the max...
Monta!
Sena!
High five!
You did it, Monta!
If he kicks you without saying anything, it's a compliment.
I just recently figured that out.
He's really happy, he's never thrown a touchdown pass before!
Too bad Honjo couldn't see that.
Oh, he saw it.
That's true.
We're on D. Let's go!
I don't care how many points those babies score.
Let's rumble, Eyeshield 21!
It's okay, it's okay!
Set, hut!
Touchdown!
We'll win on extra points.
We just need to score twice as many touchdowns.
It's all good, guys!
We're changing our formation this time.
That monkey #80 can actually catch passes.
We'll put three in the left zone to cover him.
The rest go after Eyeshield!
We change our strategy to match the enemy. You win this game by adapting to your opponent!
Watching how the enemy moves takes too long. You win this game by predicting what they'll do!
Set, hut!
The monkey's caged, get Eyeshield!
Go, Track Team!
Crap-
Someone stop him!
Yes, first down!
You know, Track Team...
Everyone's got at least one redeeming quality.
If you're talking about speed, then Eyeshield-
Nope, that's not it.
Sheesh, I didn't even notice #30, he's too plain.
He's not plain, it's more like he barely exists.
I didn't even notice he was there until that last play!
Yeah...
Eyeshield 21.
You're up.
Okay... I need to be like Monta!
It's okay...
Set, hut, hut, hut!
Eyeshield's running!
Finally... I've been waiting for this!
Come, Eyeshield... I'll beat you so badly you'll never stand again!
Those aren't the eyes of an athlete... He just wants to hurt me!
Sena!
What're you doing?!
I'm scared... I'm too scared!
Sena!
Scary... He's so scary...
Sena, Sena!
Sena, are you all right?
Get a grip, dude!
You okay?
Monta?
Man, you had me worried, Sena.
It's all good, you'll get by him next time!
Okay, make sure you block hard!
Eyeshield 21, tackle him!
Sena?
Okay, Eyeshield 21's totally broken.
Time to finish the rest of 'em off!
What's wrong with Eyeshield?
Eyeshield 21, he's coming at you!
What could be wrong with him?
His will's completely broken.
Set, hut, hut!
Eyeshield 21, run it!
I can't be frightened!
No, I'm scared! I can't do it!
Sena!
That's the end for Eyeshield 21.
I'm scared... I'm so scared!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
What're you doing, Sena? Run, run!
B-But, I'm scared!
And you call yourself a hero? A hero doesn't cry!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Terror of the Chameleon! Ya-ha!
Where on earth is he hiding them?
I wonder...
Maybe-