Hey, kiddies, Eyeshield 21's about to start!
Hurry, hurry!
"Today's the finals. Kanto High School Football Tournament's Ojo vs. Deimon."
C'mon, hurry!
Here!
I thought they'd cancel it because of the rain.
They never cancel a football game, regardless of the weather.
It says there will be some heavy rain this afternoon.
Good morning!
Sena, are you ready?
It's Mamori! I've gotta go!
But isn't this amazing, Sena?
You're in both the newspaper and on TV! Right, dear?
I heard about it from Mamori!
You might win the tournament if you win this game today.
I'm so excited since this is the first time I've ever been able to brag to the neighbors about you.
Swinging that around's dangerous!
Isn't Mamori a sweet girl?
It'd be a dream come true if she'd marry my little Sena.
Your mom's in full-blown housewife mode.
You're early like always, Mamo!
Good morning, Suzuna.
Hey, Sena! Hurry!
Mamori, Suzuna, sorry to make you wait!
Oh my. This girl's pretty cute, too!
Sena, you're so popular!
You get a move on, I'll deal with your crazy mother!
Okay...
Sena...
Winning is important and all, but try not to leave behind any regrets.
Right!
Honjo, the day has finally come!
I, Taro Raimon, swear that I will beat Sakuraba,
one of the top four receivers, and become the number one catcher!
All righty!
Hey, Daikichi!
Here's some good luck charms the family sent over!
What?! You and your master will definitely win?!
Great! Good luck, Daikichi!
"I'm busy studying, so please don't disturb me."
Enoshima, huh?
Deimon Train Station Front Entrance
It's raining...
There's nothing we can do about the weather.
I'm glad football doesn't cancel its games, no matter how heavy the rain falls.
Y-Yeah. And at long last, this day's finally come!
Yeah. This weather's perfect for our final game with them.
In our game last year, I...
Deimon's kick was no good!
Game over!
Ojo vs. Deimon!
Ojo wins With a score 99-0!
That game... has never left my mind.
We'll pay 'em back for beating us 99-0.
Th-They're here!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Challenge for Sovereignty!
Everyone looks great.
I'll defeat Seishin Juro!
He's not Seishin Juro! He's Seijuro Shin!
- At least remember his name!
Will this rain help or hurt Deimon in the game?
Today's the finals, huh?
Yeah, Ojo vs. Deimon...
It's a game worthy of being called the finals.
Deimon's strong.
They've grown into a completely different team this year and a half.
I know. I had to throw away all of my data on them from the Spring Tournament.
I've gotta pay back Kurita for that game!
I see everyone's here.
How's the weather?
It's supposed to rain even harder in the afternoon.
The strategy?
All set.
Coach...
Ojo will be victorious.
Our victory will prove Ojo's the strongest.
It looks like the migration of an entire colony
as fans from all over the nation are descending upon Enoshima Field.
The field is really heating up!
Sakuraba, now that you've come this far, you've gotta win!
I've already made a bunch of Ace Sakuraba goods!
- Huh?
- E-Excuse me!
I'm the every-time-super-hype chick,
the high school reporter, Riko Kumabukuro!
It's finally time for the Kanto Tournament B Block's finals!
Ojo White Knights
Deimon Devil Bats
The game between the Deimon Devil Bats and Ojo White Knights is just about to begin!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
White Knights! White Knights! White Knights!
The crowd is more excited than usual!
At last, at long last, the super-offense team Deimon
and the Kings that have never lost a touchdown Ojo will crash against each other!
Sakuraba!
Takami!
Let's give it our all!
Yeah. It's you, me and...
C'mon! Let's go!
I'm counting on ya, Ace Sakuraba!
It's finally time, Sena.
Yeah!
You should already know this, kiddies.
But Ojo's new strategy, the Ballista, works as both defense and offense.
Don't think of Ojo as just a defense-only team today!
I'll have... no regrets!
Everyone ready?
- Yeah!
Then remove your masks.
Wearing this mask was tough, but now that I get to remove it...
...will miss it.
No, I won't.
It was a total pain.
It's finally comin' off!
Let's go, ladies!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What type of goal is it when you try getting points with a kick?
Does everyone remember?
When you score points with a kick, it's called a "field goal."
You get three points from it.
Magnum Kick! Ya-ha!
The time for the finals is now.
The Deimon Devil Bats...
...and the Ojo White Knights...
...have both appeared on the field!
Shin...
Eyeshield 21!
The moment they remove their heart-and-lung-strengthening masks,
the air, turned cold from the rain,
will quietly flow into their bodies.
It will make them feel clear-minded and energized.
Right.
I'll be on the bench...
...helping however I can!
Yukimitsu...
You're one of our great Deimon warriors now.
Go have fun with everyone!
Okay!
- Yuki!
Let's give it best today!
Right!
A coin toss will determine who gets the ball first in each half.
Simply put, the winner'll determine who's on offense first.
The toss goes to Deimon!
What will Hiruma, the brains of Deimon, decide?
There's no need to ask. Deimon's going on offense.
I thought you'd say that.
They're getting straight to business!
Deimon's on offense first!
We're going straight to the main battle of ultimate offense versus ultimate defense!
Ojo's defense hasn't given up a touchdown to anyone in this tournament.
Can Deimon break through their defense?!
At the Spring Tournament...
When we fought against Ojo,
we were a team made up of volunteers from other sports teams.
But now...
W-We've come so far... together...
Why the heck are you crying BEFORE we even start, Fatty !
It's the rain, Hiruma!
Please stop it!
Wow!
Hey, Hey! Since he realized that Kuriton's crying even though it's raining,
Yocchie must understand exactly how Kuriton's feeling
despite the scary front he's putting up, right?
Yeah, you're right...
Did the rain just get heavier?
It did, but football never cancels games over the weather.
I have a feeling that today's finals will be amazing, unlike any we've ever seen before.
Yeah, this game's gonna be amazing!
After all, this is my debut game!
Just wait a second, Ikari. I'll unlock those-
There's no need, Takami!
H-He's so powerful...
His muscles have been well honed.
Onihei?!
He has good balance, too.
He might be the key to today's game.
And if Onihei feels that way,
then he might get in everyone's way!
He'll pay if he gets in my Sakuraba's way!
Ikari!
You all set?
We're going full throttle from the get go!
Okay!
I've never... seen Otawara look so serious before.
Kurita.
O-Otawara!
I haven't forgotten how you humiliated me at the Tokyo Tournament preliminaries!
I'm gonna pay you back with interest!
Kurita...
You aren't scared, are you?
N-No, I'm just-!
Master, together!
Sakuraba!
Takami!
What's your condition?
Excellent!
I, Haruto Sakuraba, am going to steal the "Ace" title from Seijuro Shin in today's game!
I'm countin' on you, Ace Sakuraba!
- Sakuraba!
- You're great!
Here's Ace Sakuraba's victory merchandise!
We're accepting pre-orders now!
Sakuraba, there's no way I'm gonna lose!
Monta, I will defeat you!
Fireworks are already flying between Ojo and Deimon.
The field is filled with a strange fervor!
Peewee...
Hiruma?
Listen, we're going all out on our first play.
You were chosen to crush Ojo...
...by me.
Right!
I... have to defeat Shin!
Peewee, in sports there's the thinking box and the playing box.
The thinking box is basically a box where you think.
It's when you figure what someone's going to do next.
And then the playing box is a box where you play.
Once the game starts, you follow through with your plans...
...and concentrate on the play!
So don't hesitate before the game!
Let's win.
Right!
Sena...
Eyeshield 21...
Shin!
Our final battle is just after the kickoff.
Come to think of it, this all started after I lost to Shin.
Right, it was even raining then.
I've always... always looked up to him.
I've held on to my desire to win because of Shin.
Ever since I was little, Mamori has always protected me.
But now I want to win games in the scary sport of football.
That's why I'm going to defeat Shin in our game today!
Come, Eyeshield!
Here I come, Shin!
It's not "I've gotta win!"
I WILL win!
I said I'd become stronger,
so that the lies would come true.
Well, let's head on out.
It's the final ceremony between kings and demons.
We swear here on our pride as knights to win.
We did not come here to fight our enemies.
We came to defeat them!
Glory on the kingdom!
- Yeah!
Hey, good luck everyone!
Huh? Mamo?
Huh?
Normally in a game we glare at each other before the game starts
and cry afterwards one side's left crying.
Yeah.
But just like with Kurita earlier...
...I think that everyone's going wind up laughing and crying.
Yeah, I think that would be nice.
No, I know you're right!
Listen up, ladies.
We're outta the tournament if we lose the B Block finals.
This is literally our final battle.
Go bring down that impenetrable castle!
We didn't come here to defeat our enemies!
We came here to murder 'em!
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
That's Ojo with it's impenetrable defense! There aren't any openings!
By the time we break down one wall, another strong one's formed!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Fanfare for the Start of the Game!
Ya-ha!
I love the feeling before a game.
It's like... my blood starts to run cold.
And then we all thought...
"Ishimaru's repeating that line again."