It's hot to the max!
Taiyo High School's pretty far, isn't it?
Taiyo Sphinx has the heaviest line in all of Japan...
The heaviest line in Japan?
I wonder if we can compete with them with our level of strength...
Simply being heavy doesn't mean diddly-squat!
We'll be okay to the max!
You're right! We've gotta try our utmost best!
Huh? Come to think of it, Jumonji and his group aren't here. Wonder why...
Maybe they're doing a no-show?
No way! And here they were so pumped up when they asked how to win on the line!
Don't trust the likes of them!
They're probably out playing with some delinquents!
We don't let anyone throw us around!
They'll definitely come!
What's that?!
Humongous to the max!
What's with this school?
A pyramid?!
Welcome...
...to our field!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Lower-class Laughs at Its Challengers!
Welcome...
...to our field!
It's like they're walking on air!
He looks just like the sun god, Ra!
Ouch!
Look closer, stupids!
But why's there a pyramid at school?
It's a watchtower so they can see the enemy formation from up high.
American Football Monthly Cup Game for Right to Represent Japan
There's a lot of reporters here
since this game will determine who has the right to go against the American team.
So they analyze the enemy's ability from up there, do they?
It's common knowledge in football.
But isn't it a bit high up?
Our team has also been using this watchtower as training grounds, yo.
Training?
It's like they're making a pyramid!
How many kilograms does one stone block weigh?
Hey, why don't you guys give it a try?
Here you go!
It's heavy!
Every single one of you will lie face-up on your backs with a weak line like that!
We'll lie face-up...
Kasamatsu!
Quit your jabbering already!
I'll definitely make you lie down face-up!
What's with that?
Ya-ha! It's Devil Bat time!
Laying face-up means that you were pushed flat on your back in a contest of brute strength,
so it's the biggest insult out there for a lineman.
There's no walking away from this one if it ever happens to you, baby!
Showtime's over already?!
I see.
Don't freak out, Fatty!
Th-That's what we should expect from the heaviest line in Japan!
But we've got a whole five people for ours!
But only two have actually shown up...
There's just Komusubi and me?
I wonder what happened to Jumonji and the others.
Kuroki! Togano! Jumonji!
You're late, Ha-Ha Brothers!
We're not brothers!
Now all five for the line are here!
Any OTHER problems?!
Not really...
Why am I stuck sponsoring this game?
But this should be an interesting game.
After all, the infamous Eyeshield 21 is going against the heaviest line in Japan!
Wrap the taping around so that you're mummies.
Stable joints will strengthen our power!
Right!
I'm going to tell the future.
Within ten plays we'll make the Devil Bats want to forfeit!
Let's show them just how different the power between our lines are!
Don't forget those words!
You're a fool to not understand how powerful our team is, yo!
Ten plays is too many!
We'll do it in one!
Hey, chirping chicks, time to experience face-up hell!
You beat us, we'll get you back. That's our motto.
We'll pay you back for what you did two-fold!
No, three-fold!
Ten-fold!
Then I'll do it twenty-fold!
Wanna fight?!
Listen up! Don't use that one move until I give the signal.
I ask thee...
It has 22 legs in the morning, 22 legs in the afternoon and 22 legs in the evening.
Having never been defeated, the team these 11 warriors belong to is called...
Taiyo Sphinx! Ra!
Smash them! Ya-ha!
Ya-ha!
Bawooon!
There's a 90% chance that they'll win.
No, there's a 100% chance that the Sphinx will win, going by the Devil Bats' game play up till now.
I wonder if Kurita and the others are okay...
What amazing pressure!
I've never experienced anything like it before!
They look strong.
It's scary for me even over here.
Don't be a bunch of wienies!
We can't win if we can't knock down that super heavy line of theirs!
Go at them like your life's on the line!
Set, hut, hut!
Behold! This is our Pyramid Line!
They don't even budge!
You're too light! You're a bunch of cheeping chicks!
They aren't strong, they're TOO strong!
Amazing!
This is why the Sphinx's Pyramid Line is said to be invincible!
I just have to kick back and wait for the receiver to run into the safe zone.
He'll be able to get a touch down without any resistance at this rate!
They'll lose the will to fight within one play!
After him!
What?!
No way!
I caught up! This is the opposite of normal!
What should I do?!
Tackle!
Impossible! They were so far away from each other!
Amazing!
That's our ace from Notre Dame, Eyeshield 21!
I... tackled him?
Nice tackle!
You've gotten stronger!
Hey, Peewee, that training paid off, didn't it?
Well, the fight's just started!
Yep!
Kurita...
Despite a big body like that, you fell face-up just like that!
That's so lame!
Darn that Fatty! He's letting them drag him down.
Deimon's line may not be a threat to us, but their back's pretty fast.
We just have to win at the line!
He isn't acting like the usual Kurita at all...
This time let them feel it with their bodies that Deimon doesn't stand a chance!
Right!
Set, hut, hut!
How lame! This is the first time I've ever seen this!
This is the second time in a row that everyone on the line has been pushed face-up!
They're so pathetic it's sad!
I hope they're all right...
They've been pushed back pretty far.
Hey, chick-a-dees! You okay?
Just how long are you going to sleep? Play for real!
Kurita, are you okay?
Don't worry about it!
I was nuts.
I thought that by making it here today, we might be able to do it.
But I was crazy to think that we would defeat the Sphinx's line.
Kurita...
Guys...
I'm sorry I'm making fools of everyone.
The lower-class always laughs at its challengers.
Those are the words of a great player who ignored everyone who laughed at him,
challenged the American team and won beautifully.
Huh?
Who?
Eyeshield 21!
Did you really say something that cool sounding?
But Sena can't go up against an American team...
It's impossible to defeat Taiyo's line?!
In a few months we're going to crush every team in the Kanto area, including Taiyo!
So what'll you do then?!
We might get to play in the tournament if we could defeat Taiyo!
I think that we should be proud of having a five-man line.
But, the way we are right now...
Hey, we're going to the Christmas Bowl, aren't we?
Then quit dawdling around, you darned Fatty!
What'll happen to us if you can't keep your grip?!
The line is the harshest nine meters out there.
The most powerful warriors on the team that make up the line never get to touch the ball.
The line doesn't run the path to victory.
But they OPEN the path to victory!
Kurita!
Master!
That's cool! Who said that?
I forget who.
Eyeshield 21.
Yeah!
Let's work hard so we can go to the Christmas Bowl!
It's about time, isn't it?
Not yet.
Why not?
Just wait!
Take that!
We'll finish them off this time!
Football Clinic!
What's a "formation?"
It's an alignment to set up the players for various strategies.
There's both offensive and defensive formations! Ya-ha!
Set, hut, hut!
We've got five people here!
We can defeat the Pyramid Line!
Touch down!
Nice going, Sphinx!
But this game might actually...
The sky sure is blue...
We're looking FACE UP after all...
It's been a while since I've been this humiliated.
But I kinda feel refreshed.
After being humiliated so much, getting pushed down doesn't really bother me anymore.
Shall we do it?
Today's theme is...
...to crush them!
We can't lose!
This'll be a piece of cake!
Don't get cocky. The fight's still on.
Yo-Yo!
My name isn't Yo-Yo.
I don't care what your name is!
That was our tenth play just now.
Strange, isn't it? I don't see a single player on my team ready to raise the white flag.
What?!
What do you think about that, Yo-Yo?
My name isn't Yo-Yo!
My apologies. We were mistaken to believe that we could break you through sheer force alone.
What?
Especially... Kurita, was it? I'll acknowledge your ability.
From here on, we'll hit you with everything we've got!
Bring it on!
Okay! It looks like Fatty's attacks have left an impression on them.
Now it's time for the Ha-Ha Brothers to make their move!
It's finally our turn!
We're gonna go nuts out there!
But you know...
We aren't related!
What's he mean "finally?"
Dunno...
I think you've been looking up at the sun too much and now you're delusional, Three Chick Brothers!
I wonder what he meant when he said it's their turn...
Set, hut!
Darn little chickling!
Now!
Go!
Don't pull my sleeve!
We don't let anyone throw us around!
We did it!
Awesome!
Barge through! Throw the ball!
Here's our chance!
You can do it!
Hold them back!
You can do it, Komusubi!
Now what'll you do?
We've broken down that iron wall Pyramid Line you're so proud of.
Face-up, huh?
How LAME!
Y-You only did it to me once!
And who did it to you that one time?
You were having a pretty good time making fun of us.
Kept calling us chicks!
Now who's the little chick?
This sucks...!
How frustrating!
They actually made the heaviest line in Japan lay face-up!
What sort of technique was that just now?
I call it "Delinquent Deathblow."
Delinquent Deathblow?
When did they get a move like that?
They trained together with Zokugaku up until right before this game.
So they were together with Habashira...
Habashira, they're finally using it!
But isn't the Delinquent Deathblow against the rules?
Yeah, right! Football isn't some lame girly sport!
Why do I have to help train trash like them?!
That's it!
Grab their sleeve right when the enemy's going to ram into you,
and push diagonally into them.
They'll fall right over!
I see. So grab onto their uniform...
I want to win.
What did you just say?!
Well, since everyone's trying so hard, I thought it would be nice if...
"It would be nice if," my butt! We're GOING to win! That's all there is to it!
Right!
Set, hut, hut!
I can't believe those three actually underwent special training.
Kurita and Komusubi are also working hard on the line!
They're huge!
I can do it! I have to!
I don't mind getting knocked a bit as long as everyone's out there helping me!
He got through!
He's fast!
All right!
I'll crush you!
It's no good! I don't have enough space to dodge him!
Run off the court!
I see. I can run off the court!
There's also a path, but it's so small he might still hit me.
It might be safer to just run from him.
I could definitely avoid him if I ran outside, but...
Run for it!
Hurry and run out!
But is it okay for me to just run away when everyone's fighting?
I can't run away! Not when I practiced so hard! I can do it!
Why?!
That Peewee...!
I WILL get stronger!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Good job, Ha-Ha Brothers!
Show them your manliness!
Okay! Next it's my turn to show off!
But will it go that smoothly?
And what's THAT?! He's like a crazy warrior!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Sphinx's Secret Weapon! Ya-ha!
Happiness to the max!
Sena, you did it!
The game's not over yet!
He's praising you when he kicks you and doesn't say anything.
It's fun! Football is a blast!
Ouch!
It looks like they have the same type of personality as Hiruma.
Sure looks that way!