Ya-ha! There's a game to determine who gets the right to play against an American team!
Monta's struggling against the Sphinx's Kamaguruma,
who appeared in the second half of the game!
Should you be getting depressed to the max like that?!
There's no point in crying over spilt milk!
We'll get the ball back!
Goal!
Is Taiyo getting to do a bonus kick?
Deimon's no match for them!
If they get six points with that touchdown and one point with a bonus kick,
they'll get seven points all at once!
Since we can't kick, we'd still lose even if we got in the same number of touchdowns.
I see. I get it!
So Deimon's an offensive-type team.
That sure matches Hiruma, doesn't it?
Nuh-uh. In a low-score game, they'd lose because of the gap created by the kicks.
But they can make up the number of points lost through kicks by getting more touchdowns.
That's true!
So that's why we've only been practicing attacks!
There's no way someone like him
who only cares about winning would use a strategy because it's their personal preference.
Okay, we're in the final quarter!
Attack! Attack! Attack like nuts!
If they get us once, we'll get them back twice!
That's all we can do!
Darn it!
That attacks got me beat! What should I do?
I've got to... I've got to do something!
We're gonna WIN!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Fly, Devil Bat!
There's only 12 minutes left!
We need at least two touchdowns to win!
Set, hut, hut!
Chariot Bump!
Monta!
Char-iot BUMP!
You're finished!
This stinks!
Char-iot BUMP!
It's no good...
Our attack's not working!
Between this heat and being on an unfamiliar field, Deimon's got it harsh!
And everyone's working on both offense and defense.
Taiyo's already accustomed to this type of heat.
They can't keep on holding us off.
All we've got to do is kill time and attack at our leisure.
We'll stop their passes with our power!
I know! Now calm down!
Char-iot BUMP! Char-iot BUMP! Char-iot BUMP!
Even idiots have their uses!
Char-iot BUMP! Char-iot BUMP!
Kamaguruma only ever practices that Bump of his!
There's no way I can compete against their sheer power!
Set, hut, hut!
Chariot BUMP!
Again!
Set, hut, hut!
BUMP!
He's still trying his best, even though he's getting beaten up!
I've gotta do something!
How long are you gonna sleep? We don't have time for this! Wake up!
I wonder why he keeps throwing passes that won't make it?
Monta's already reached his limit.
Here's the pass!
Don't let him trample you this time!
Um, I probably shouldn't be saying this, but...
Wouldn't it be better to let Sena run with the ball rather than pass it to me?
Monta...
Just do what you're told! I'm giving the orders here!
But...
I don't care if you wanna turn tail and run home.
We've got a clear path to victory with my Chariot Bump!
I... No matter how tired I get, all I can do is try to dash on through with max effort!
There's not even two minutes left. It's clear who will win.
But Deimon might have some sort of dazzling counterattack.
They're finished! But man is it ever hot!
Guys!
You can do it!
Set, hut, hut!
If we can't beat you with our power alone,
two of us will deal with you!
Max effort!
Bump!
It's no good!
Sena!
Deimon 11 yard gain!
Good job!
But there's not even one whole minute left!
They've gotta get 2 touchdowns!
Char-iot BUMP! Char-iot BUMP!
There's 30 yards left till we get a touch down,
and we don't have enough time to carry it there!
Butt-monkey, we'll use the long bomb!
We'll get a touch down instantly!
But I'm being totally crushed by that bump.
Totally crushed? Do you realize what your position even is?
Unlike us, a receiver's fight isn't to swarm the opponent and push him!
Ignore those bumps! Just run up the field!
The wide open field is where you belong!
Am I wrong, #80?
I'm telling you that you can either turn tail and go home
or you can run through an open yard, where you belong!
I see... Hiruma was thinking ahead.
For Deimon to win, we NEED Monta's catching abilities!
That's why he continued to throw those passes,
no matter how many times Monta got pushed down!
Ready to taste another Chariot Bump, huh?
Consider this your last chance.
I'll need everyone's help to make this long pass work!
Yeah!
Set, hut, hut!
Honjo-san...
There was a player who wasn't afraid of hitting the wall, no matter how tall or hard it was!
There was a player who ruled over the open field!
I'm going out, to my yard!
I'll crush you again!
My open field!
It'll take some time to get off a long pass!
Keep up a wall so I can pass the ball!
Football Clinic!
What happens when you fumble?
When you fumble a ball and the enemy takes it, the enemy will get to go on the offense.
Hm, fumble? That's when the player holding the ball drops it! Ya-ha!
It'll take some time to get off a long pass!
Keep up a wall so I can pass the ball!
Looking good! The wall's still holding!
You can do it!
Crush them!
Monta!
Chariot attack!
Now you can't catch!
I don't care if I lose to him in power.
I don't care what he beats me at!
But... I won't lose at catching!
Catching is a three dimensional battle.
Size and speed aren't what determine victory.
Hit those fungoes with all your heart!
It may sound simple, but it's the only way.
The god of catching will smile down upon you...
...for how hard you've practiced come the end of the year.
Monta?!
Did he get it?
No matter how huge the opponent may be,
and no matter how fast the opponent may be,
there's no way I'll ever let someone beat me at catching!
It's so clear now!
I know what I've gotta do!
I'll fight against all the back catchers in Japan, no, the world!
You did it! Nice going, Monta!
Touch down!
There's 32 seconds left in the game!
It's 20-18, with a two point gap-
Do something!
H-How horrible!
It's impossible!
No, they're so devoted.
Their single-minded dedication and their obsession to catch the ball...
It's something we may have lost sight of.
Max Super Catch!
He's just gotta strike a pose!
He just has to do it!
And here he was so cool!
Amazing! Nice catch!
Mamori!
I regained my dishonor, just like I promised! I mean, I did the opposite!
What's the point of regaining dishonor?!
I've returned my dishonor!
I'm sorry to keep bugging you, but...
Return his dishonor and regain his dishonor...
Someone teach that monkey how to speak human!
That's so not cool...
W-Well, next Taiyo's on the offensive.
This was a close one!
Deimon almost became the representative for Japan.
But there's still Deimon's conversion!
They've either got to kick it or a get a touchdown from three yards out from the goal.
They'll get one point for a kick and two for a touchdown.
There's a two point gap, so we'd still lose even if we got the kick in.
So we'll go for two with a touchdown.
Cheap tricks won't work right in front of the goal, so I want everyone to charge in through the center.
There's only 2.7 meters from the line to the end zone.
We'll force our way there!
We're going to attack the Pyramid Line head on?
It'll be a contest of strength.
Double the people in the line!
Listen up! Don't let them through, no matter what!
Kamaguruma, join the line.
Roger!
Their line's growing!
Normally it's only four or five people, but they've got nine!
Don't chicken out!
Concentrate your strength towards the center.
This one play will determine everything!
It's everyone vs everyone!
It's a battle of strength!
Stop them!
Taiyo Sphinx!
Victory's yours if you hold them back!
Go for it!
Go, Go, Deimon Devil Bats!
In the end, sheer power is what will determine who wins!
Be confident! Taiyo's line is the heaviest in Japan!
Show them how great the Pyramid Line really is!
Ra!
You're the one who'll carry the ball.
Don't try to dodge to the side like you always do.
If you dodge or hesitate at all, your charge will lose momentum.
Dash straight on through without looking back.
Straight on through? No looking back...?
I can't do it. They're too big!
21!
We're bound to win as long as the 21 on Eyeshield 21 keeps on looking forward!
Have the 21 keep looking forward?
What's that mean?
21 is...
21 is... looking forward?
What... What on earth does that mean?
You're doing great, everyone!
Master!
I never thought that we'd be able to fight against Taiyo on equal footing.
I'm not the only person in Deimon's line anymore.
We have five linemen now!
Set, hut!
He's strong! He has more brute strength than I do.
Kurita's forcing him back!
Break through those three yards!
If you dodge or hesitate at all, your charge will lose momentum.
Dash straight on through without looking back.
We're bound to win as long as the 21 on Eyeshield 21 keeps on looking forward!
Don't underestimate...
...the Pyramid Line!
They stopped!
That was close!
That's it?!
No, we can win!
I get it!
Both the 21s on my shoulder pads have to look ahead!
I have to hold the ball tight and dash forward without hesitation!
With those legs, you'll make it!
The wall's stuck!
No, don't give up! Just move forward! FORWARD!
Fly!
Ya-ha!
Stop him!
Knock Banba down!
Devil Bat Dive!
Touch down!
Game over!
We tied...
So it's okay to be happy, right?
Of course! You managed to tie with a team like that!
We did it!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Yay! Devil Bats got the right to be the representative team for Japan!
Hm? Sena, why are you sneaking around?
I feel like someone's been watching me...
Could it be a spy?!
Ah, there's a suspicious shadow!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Mysterious Girl Appears! Ya-ha!
We did it!
Quit rejoicing like idiots!
Tying and losing are pretty much the same thing.
Deimon fought on unfamiliar turf with weather you weren't accustomed to.
Everything was in Taiyo's favor.
But despite all that, we tied.
Most impressive!
You earned the right to fight against the Americans.
That sounds too good to be true!
What brought this on?
You taught us about something we had forgotten about.
We had forgotten about being devoted and obsessed with the ball
when we gained the name heaviest line in Japan.
Kurita, it's a tie this time.
We'll continue this fight again in the fall.
Yeah!
The Taiyo Sphinx are starting over again from scratch.
The game against the Americans is too soon for us to be ready in time.
We're even less ready for the Americans!
Don't be a chicken!
We were losers from the start, so we don't have any pride to lose!
For now, we've gotta fight!
Deimon Devil Bats will be representing Japan!
Ya-ha!
What a nightmare!