- Okay, come on!
- Ya-ha!
Bando Spiders vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Amazing! Musashi returned the onside kick just like that!
They stole possession from Bando.
But there's even more
to that onside kick return
than just that.
They've rendered the Spider's Web's infinite loop ineffective.
Musashi!
The kicking battle
between the two of us is the key battle in this game!
This is going to be the greatest kicking contest ever!
And the prize will be the final seat to the Kanto Tournament!
Fine.
I'll go along with that.
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Demon Within the Storm!
This crazily-strong wind storm
is a perfect match for the start
of the stormy second half of the game!
It'll be a raging battle of kicks verses kicks!
The score's 26-15!
Bando Spiders 26 - Deimon Devil Bats 15
Bando's got an 11 point lead!
Bando's on offense and 30 yards from the goal!
Considering Bando's usual plays,
Kotaro will definitely go for a field goal, but...
But then there's this wind.
Who knows how that will affect their gameplay strategy.
Okay!
We've GOTTA get back those 11 points
by the end of the game even if it kills us!
Let's think of this as a friendly wind and cut loose!
Now that we've got a kicker here,
there's no excuse for losing.
Yep!
Yeah!
He's right.
Now that Musashi's back,
all of the Deimon Devil Bats are together again.
We can do this!
But ya know...
No one's gonna be able to give a decent kick in this wind.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Set, hut, hut!
Wow! Kotaro's going for the kick!
This is my Smart Kick!
It's bending off to the left!
Sweet! The kick'll miss!
Yep!
What's this?!
The field goal attempt made it!
I used the wind to make the ball go straight it.
I'm so smart!
Hooray!
"Kotaro's kicks won't make it with this strong wind,
so Deimon will have the advantage."
Is that what you thought?
Did you see that, Deimon?!
We've practiced kicking thousands of balls
in wind and rain and all sorts of situations!
How long are you going to keep this up, Kotaro?!
I'm not done yet!
The Bando Spiders are going to win the finals this year!
Bando Spiders 26 - Deimon Devil Bats 15
Bando Spiders 29 - Deimon Devil Bats 15
Bando's increased the gap to 14 points!
We're supposed to be catching up to them,
but they're getting farther ahead!
Hut!
The game's entering the final quarter!
Deimon's on offense!
Will they get to counterattack?
We're not finished yet!
If they're a Super Kicking Team,
then Deimon's a Super Offense Team!
We'll get back as many points as they take!
Super Max Catch!
Focus in on Deimon's ace receiver, #80!
I think you must be mistaken!
I'm the ace!
I see!
If they're focusing in on Monta,
then they won't be watching out for Taki.
That match up...
...is pointless!
There's just no way...
- ...he'll win!
He's getting in the way?
How can this be?!
- They threw a long pass over to Monta!
- Sweet!
He's pretty heavily marked, but...
It's got a higher chance of success than throwing it to Taki,
who's being marked by Akaba.
Leave it all to me, Hiruma!
I can handle this many people- HUH?!
Whoops! The wind blew the ball away!
Shoot!
Hiruma's pass didn't...
Catch it, Mon-Mon!
Incomplete pass!
Darn it!
It looks like Hiruma and Monta's hot line passes
won't work in this weather...
Passing in this wind is suicide.
The only option Deimon has left
is to focus their offense on runs.
And if it's a duel between mine and Sena's runs...
I will definitely stop him.
These gales aren't smiling upon you.
They're smiling upon the Bando Spiders!
The wind just keeps getting stronger!
Not good!
We've run out of options.
We need to regroup!
Let's call a time out and-
Wait, Coach Doburoku!
Sena!
Hiruma...?
Well, that play just now,
where I dashed to the right...
Would it be okay...
...if I tried it again?
Nah, you can do it again if you really want to...
But Akaba will just use his run force to skip on ahead of you...
...and stop you like he did earlier, ya know?
But have you thought up some sort of counter for that?
No, it's just...
...even if they know what route I'm going to take,
I could just super warp speed through
before Akaba gets ahead of me...
That's what I was thinking or maybe not...
- HUH?
Nah...
No human could do that!
So we're finally entering the world of SF, huh?
Y-You're right!
I-It's impossible, isn't it?
Hiruma, you're laughing too hard.
That's physically impossible!
You're an idiot, Peewee!
I knew it...
Sounds interesting!
Do it!
Do it as many times as it takes.
If we can't pass,
all that's left if our runs.
B-But, Hiruma...
It's his job to think up our strategies.
Musashi...
That's how the three of us have always done things, isn't it?
You're right! Yep!
This is the Deimon Devil Bats' third try at offense!
Will they change their strategy or leave it as is?!
Set, hut!
In order for the Deimon Devil Bats to win...
I've got to surpass Akaba!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what's important when making a kickoff!
The hint is "distance."
When making a kickoff,
try to send the ball flying as far as you can!
The hint is to force the opponent's offense team as far back as possible.
Kick super hard!
Ya-ha!
Sena Kobayakawa got smashed!
He used the same play and got caught by Akaba!
What gives, Deimon?!
Right now, Hayato Akaba,
should be experiencing the same type of fear
that everyone who's fought
Sena Kobayakawa thus far goes through.
Throughout the coarse of a game,
even the same plays, improve without bounds.
But even so,
it doesn't matter how fast Sena Kobayakawa is
if they can use their run force to control his routes.
What are you plotting, Hiruma?
There's only 10 minutes left in this crazy second half!
Will the gods of wind blow in favor for Deimon?!
Go, Peewee!
I'm gonna get past Akaba!
I can't compete with his sheer power or technique.
All I can fight him with
is my dashing ability that I polished
over our 2,000 kilometer death march!
So run faster!
Run FASTER!
Deimon failed to make any gain!
No way!
Akaba suddenly...
...ran faster than he was earlier.
What the heck's going on?
Both Sena AND Akaba are upping their speed!
Long passes are outright impossible in this fierce wind.
So Akaba is able to give his all in going after our runs and stopping them.
That's why he's gotten faster!
The weather is on Bando's side.
Being able to work with unfortunate circumstances
shows one's true ability.
We will never lose our rhythm or beat.
Well people, we're down to a mere nine minutes left!
Bando's riding away on the wind!
Will the Deimon Devil Bats be able to overcome this 14 point gap?!
Deimon's going to have a tough time taking the lead now.
With this strong wind...
Hiruma has probably already determined
that passes aren't an option.
So he's fighting while missing an attack card.
Sena, please whack me a good one!
C'mon! Whack me good and hard!
Like this?
Not good enough...
Let us do it!
How's this?!
Feel better?!
That's overdoing it!
But, why...?
I haven't caught...
...a single pass in the second half!
Darn it!
Curse this stupid typhoon!
This is our big game!
We'll get to go to the Kanto Tournament if we win this!
This truly is our last chance!
And here I'm...
Darn it!
It's all this blasted wind's fault!
I understand... how you feel.
Ya-ha! Ya-ha! Ya-ha!
The wind speed...
...has hit its peak for today!
At last! You're late, Manajerk!
"I'm late?"
So the wind's supposed to be MY fault?!
Yocchie isn't looking anymore.
Peewee's putting up a better fight
with Vampiro than I thought he would.
Guess it's time for the big gamble.
I'm sorry, Hiruma.
I-I'm not being helpful at all...
Stupid! You dumb butt-monkey!
We don't have any weaklings in Deimon!
Listen up, ladies!
From here on, the wind's on our side!
Huh? The wind?
On our side?
If this works, we'll instantly turn this game around!
We'll instantly turn...
...this game around?!
That's just like you.
No matter how bleak things look,
you've always got an ace up your sleeve.
It's game over if they catch on!
This is a trick play that'll only work once!
And if you let it fail,
everyone here's going to see what hell's like!
- Yeah!
Deimon's backed into a corner and attempting their fourth down!
Set!
Hut!
Their rhythm's different from usual.
Woo-boy! I can do it!
Wow! Monta's moving up!
A super long pass?
In this wind?
Pass coverage, get back!
Deimon's line was in a position where they
were protecting Hiruma so he could pass,
but now they're pushing forward!
Rhythm and Blues!
What?!
Deimon's bursting through the center
with their power plus super speed!
Great!
-Yay! Yay!
-Thanks to their long pass feint,
Bando's defense has all fallen back!
Yay! We'll be able to break through!
Why?!
They're completely surrounded?!
Bando didn't fall for our pass trick!
There's no way they'd pass in this wind.
In normal conditions we might have fallen for that.
You should blame the weather.
This is our Rhythm and Blues!
Huh? Why's he facing backwards?
Was Hiruma's pass always that slow?
Don't tell me
he let the wind take advantage of them
so that I'd get this image that they can't pass!
Crap! Fall back!
After drawing in all of the enemy's attention...
I throw a backwards pass to Hiruma!
I see.
This wind hasn't affected Hiruma at all from the very start!
And then he'll throw the ball...
Ya-ha!
The Devil Laser Bullet!
I'll catch it even if it kills me!
Touchdown!
Max Catch!
We did it!
- Boo-yah!
- Yay!
Monta!
So he tricked me into removing everyone
who was marking Raimon.
How interesting...
That's why he had Sena come after me
even though he knew that he never stood a chance from the start.
So it was all for that one pass...
How truly fascinating...
So even your ace is a pawn.
You're wrong on one account, Vampiro!
I had him fight you knowing that he didn't stand a chance?
Like I'd ever do that!
Deimon doesn't have any loser pawns!
You better prepare yourself, Tokyo MVP!
Sena Kobayakawa will definitely defeat you!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Musashi's back and Deimon's doing great!
At least, that's what I'd like to say,
but isn't a certain someone getting in the way?
How can this be?
I'm supposed to be beloved by God...!
How can this be?!
Where do you think you're going during the game?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Man Beloved by God! Ya-ha!
[Bando Spiders 29 - Deimon Devil Bats 21]
Sweet! We're down to an eight point gap!
With Musashi back now,
we'll definitely get in a kick.
So we'll get another point, bringing us to within seven!
- Boo-yah!
Deimon hasn't just gained a kicker.
They're finally playing with a full deck.
Yoichi Hiruma's just gotten considerably more powerful.
Now, even the genius Akaba is going to have to change his plans.
Listen up, ladies!
We don't want a tie!
Musashi's kick'll be a diversion!
We're going for the two points with a touchdown!
Got that?! We'll pull it off no matter what!
- Yeah!