I told you to put your hip into it and push back more, DIDN'T I?!
Ouch!
Right... I'll accept the request you made the other day.
Yes, I will.
I'll find out who Eyeshield 21 really is!
You're a life-saver!
Who's that?
They get all nervous and defensive around me.
Dunno.
Looks hot!
It'll be a huge help if a kid like you does it!
Yeah! Uh-huh! Well, thanks!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
A Mysterious Girl Appears!
Okay! Now I'll get the feature article for this month's issue!
It's a big scoop! The mysterious hero, Eyeshield 21's, secret identity!
Darn him, that idiot!
It's Cerberus' food!
Dogs and monkeys don't get along-
What?!
Hurry up and make your appearance, Eyeshield 21!
Th-That spy sure stands out!
I swear! Quit being so reclusive!
Hey, there!
I'm busy right now!
It's a monkey!
WHO'S a monkey?!
Hey, wait!
There's no way I'll let you escape!
No way!
He's gone! Don't let him escape!
I said not to let him escape!
After him!
Wait!
Wha-?!
What?!
He's a spy!
He's a spy! Catch him!
A...
...spy?
W-What the-?!
Everyone, let's practice our routes!
Owie!
It's a girl?!
Spy!
Wait a sec!
What's the deal?!
That's my line, you spy jerk!
What's with calling a delicate lady a "jerk?!" A JERK?!
Don't play innocent!
You came to spy on the powerful Devil Bat's catching super hero Taro Raimon, didn't you?
Huh? What are you talking about?
And aren't you a little devolved?!
You look like a monkey and keep going on about catching and spies and stuff!
I don't get it!
Hey, calm down!
I know!
If you're not a spy, why were you dressed so suspiciously while watching us practice?
I just came to gather some material on you.
Material?!
Material... on us?!
Well, I guess that's about right...
You're still suspicious!
How interesting!
Tell me more about it.
I'd love to sit back and listen!
Y-You demon!
U-Um... What's your name?
My name's Taki, Suzuna Taki!
M-Ms. Taki?
D-Don't call my by my last name!
And being called "Ms." makes me uneasy, so don't.
Call me by my first name!
Ah, okay... So um, S-S-S-S-Suzuna...
Why're you so nervous?!
She might be a spy!
Be harsher with her!
Hey, little brat, you wanna be called by your first name?
Hey, Taki! Taki! Taki! Taki!
And to top it off, Ms. Taki! Ms.! Ms.! Ms.!
How's that? Irritated?
Spill the beans if you don't want me to bug you some more!
He really hasn't evolved any!
I'm ticked-off to the max again!
Fine, I'll talk.
I've been requested by a certain person to find out Eyeshield 21's true identity.
That's all!
Eyeshield 21's...
...true identity?!
And who asked you?
I can't disclose the client's name due to our contract.
Your contract?
It's a pro's policy!
A pro? But you look like a high schooler!
Even if it's just part-time, I'm still a pro since I'm getting money from it!
It's better than being a monkey!
There! That attitude really ticks me off!
I'm going home!
You're going home?
You see, I just came here to get the dirt on Eyeshield 21!
I'm not someone to be suspicious of!
Eyeshield 21 is the one who's suspicious!
I mean, why's a high schooler keeping his identity secret while playing on some after school team?
He must have some really strange reason why he does it!
You'll go to hell if anyone discovers your true identity! Ya-ha!
Later!
Hey, hey!
Say "hi" to Eyeshield 21 for me!
I'll come by later!
I said to wait a second!
Let her go, Monta.
Okay...
I've got a really bad feeling about this!
Set, hut, hut!
Grab it, butt-monkey!
Manajerk! Speed up some more!(needs halp)
Go, go! Let's go!
Go, go, Devil!
Fly, fly, Bat!
Run, run, Bat!
Show yourself! Show yourself, 21!
Eyeshield 21! 21!
Hurry and show yourself, Eyeshield... 21!
W-What's with that?
She's cheerleading by herself...
Go, go! Let's go!
Go, go, Devil!
That's obvious, but...
She's so not hot!
Fly, fly Bat!
But she's my type...
Run, run Bat!
Show yourself! Show yourself!
21!
What did you say?!
She really isn't hot.
But she's my type...
They've got a cheerleader?
If you're gonna do that, than cheer for us!
No!
Listen up, Devil Bats!
Until I find out who Eyeshield 21 is, I, Suzuna Taki, will continue to spy on you!
You better prepare yourselves! Bang, bang!
It's cold!
She's my type!
Are you okay with that, Hiruma?
Just ignore her!
Next, I want guys on the line to come here!
Is this okay...?
All righty! Leave things to me!
I'll protect Eyeshield 21's secret identity!
Too loud!
Whatever. Just leave things to me!
But... I think we should just let the issue drop.
I know, I know!
Hey!
What?
I've got a message for you from Eyeshield 21.
A message? You do?
I... I'm his best friend!
So?
"You won't get the dirt on me!"
"And you won't find out my secret identity!"
"If you don't get outta my hair, you'll go to hell!"
You're getting carried away!
Really?
Fine! I'll leave.
I'm glad you get the picture!
But...!
First he must duel with me!
If he wins, I'll leave without getting any information on him or finding out who he really is.
But if I win, I get all the dirt on him and can tell everyone who he is!
It'll be great!
What's that?!
Don't tell me your not sure if he could defeat a small little girl like me?
Eyeshield 21's pretty lame.
Y-Y-Yeah, right! We and our Eyeshield 21 are invincible!
So it's settled.
I'll write an article about how Eyeshield 21 is a stupid lying chicken jerk-face if he doesn't show!
The place, time and how we'll fight are all written down here.
A letter of challenge...?
Give him my regards!
"Give him my regards?!" When the heck did she write this?!
She was plotting this from the start...
I'm sorry, Sena! It's all my fault!
No point regretting it now.
I-I've gotta compete with her like that?!
Football Clinic!
How do you start the game?
Kick-off!
You kick off from your team's 35 yard line! Ya-ha!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The Eyeshield 21 you've been eagerly awaiting is over there!
Eyeshield 21!
Let's go over the rules, okay?
We'll start from here at the same time and I win if I can catch you before you reach the goal,
the Torii at the foot of the hill.
You win if you make it there without getting caught.
Got it?
Let's go!
All set?!
Then let's start!
Ready...
Start!
Even though I can't beat his take-off speed, I'll be faster than him once my speed picks up!
Here I go!
It's hard to run!
I can't run down hill very well!
Not good! She's catching up with me!
I can do it!
All I have to do is keep my balance and going down hill will naturally increase my speed!
It's no good! I can't run like I want!
Crap!
A parking lot with flat ground!
Here I can...!
He's quick on flat ground, but I won't lose!
Okay! I'll be able to pull throu- Another slope?!
But, I should be way in the lead!
Why's she ahead of me?!
I jumped on ahead! Come on!
S-She'll catch me!
No way!
That's why he's Eyeshield 21!
But I'm not going to give up!
No way!
No! Help me!
Someone help me!
Huh?
She's not following me.
Did she jump on ahead again?
Someone!
No way!
How'd she get there?!
This is bad! What should I do?
I've got to save her!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Someone!
Okay!
I'm scared.... but I have to save her!
Here I go!
Oh no!
N-No way! No!
Gotta make it in time!
Thank goodness!
This was pretty far down.
But why isn't Sena here yet?
Hey, are you okay?!
Over here!
Where are you?!
Hey! Where are you?!
Over here!
What are you doing?
I-I thought I was gonna die!
What am I doing here?
Eyeshield 21 rescued you. You were in serious danger.
I see...
A-Are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
So now what?
Huh?
The duel! What's going to happen to Eyeshield 21's secret identity?!
I give up...
Are you sure?
Of course, I might have won if I hadn't fallen down.
But he did save me and if he wants to keep his identity a secret that badly, I say we let him.
Are you... really sure?
Yeah. And I know that Eyeshield 21 isn't my big brother, now.
I see... Your BROTHER?!
What's that about?
Well, you see...
The real reason why I took on that part-time job to discover Eyeshield 21's true identity was
part of my search for my brother.
Why are you searching for your brother?
My brother... He left home, saying that he'd become a star in the football world.
Now we don't know where he is.
I feel sorry for my mother, who's really worried about him.
So?
So then I thought that Eyeshield 21, who has a secret identity, might be my missing brother!
Missing and secret identity... They do kinda match!
Monta!
Right.
When he saved me, I realized that he's not my brother.
Really?
I was so absorbed with the race that I didn't notice it at the time,
but my brother isn't that much of a shrimp!
She called him a shrimp!
But aren't I about the same height as him?
This is my brother!
You're right. He's gotta be at least 180 centimeters tall.
I don't think he goes to our school...
I see. I'll check around the other schools, then.
We'll let you know if we find him.
Thanks.
Why?
Why would he do this just over football?
He even left home... and Eyeshield 21 keeps his identity a secret...
W-Well...
I think... they're probably out searching for their real selves.
Their real selves?
I think that Eyeshield and your brother leaving home...
...will graduate from that sort of thing once they find themselves.
Plus, they've got new friends!
I see.
Tell Eyeshield 21 "thank you" for me.
Later!
Hey, she's pretty cute when she's being open with us.
Yeah, you're right.
"How are you doing?"
"Now I'm in New York."
New York?!
Right after the incident with us, a nice friend told her that her brother is in America.
He's in the home of football: America.
A nice friend?
Who's that?
Don't tell me...
Hiruma?
He's a demon!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
The NASA Aliens are here!
That coach is constantly mocking Deimon!
But, they've got some great players!
I've never seen someone run with such light feet before!
It's like he's flying in the sky!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Weightless Man! Ya-ha!
Mail? What'd I get?
A shocking picture! Eyeshield 21's true identity?!
It's finally here!
Great!
Hiruma...
Who'd you send an e-mail to?
He really is a demon!