ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Half-Second Bodyguards!
Sakuraba!
Why are there so many girls at a district game?
They're here to see Ojo's Sakuraba. Look!
Oh, the celebrity.
Sakuraba!
Please look at our camera!
Even so, Ojo has a whole lot of players.
Yup. They're a famous school, after all.
That guy's amazing!
Oh yeah, remember how I told you about Ojo's MVP, Seijuro Shin?
He's an incredible player.
That's enough!
Time for one last light meal.
Make sure you get plenty of carbs and vitamin C!
Aren't you gonna eat, Shin?
I consume all the nutrition my body requires on a fixed schedule.
You always say that.
Well, more for me!
Hi, Sakuraba!
Sakuraba!
Hello, Sakuraba.
Mr. President?
What do I always say, Sakuraba?
Make sure you wear your sponsor's hat whenever there're TV cameras around.
One more, Sakuraba.
You should wear a sticker on your helmet, too!
And then-
The crowd's going wild, wouldn't you say?
Everyone's cheering on "Ace Sakuraba's team," the Ojo White Knights.
They're not really MY team...
Our REAL ace is-
Aww, you're just being modest! How adorable!
He's got it rough, as usual.
I figured they'd show up!
The Shinryuji Nagas, the other half of Kanto's "top two powerhouses!"
We can't afford to look incompetent in front of them!
Right, now put your pants on.
Make sure you record every move Shin makes.
Roger. What about Sakuraba?
You lamewad, no one cares about Jari Productions' poster boy.
Today's game's got a whole different premise from the last one.
THAT was playing house, THIS is war!
Yeah, Shin's gonna be playing, isn't he?
I kinda wanna go home...
Man, I don't even wanna think about last year's scrimmage!
Did something happen last year?
Two of our borrowed players ended up with broken bones.
Broken bones...?
Everyone relax.
Eyeshield 21 will carry the ball.
He'll be the one taking all of Shin's tackles.
Oh yeah!
Now I feel better!
If anyone's gonna break a bone, it'll be him!
No way, no way! I gotta run!
That's right, we just have to give it 110%!
It'd be pretty pathetic if we just gave up right after the team finally won a game.
With Eyeshield on our side, things will work out somehow.
Huh? Sena?
Went to buy tapes. -Sena
If you want good cake, try-
Hey, where'd Manajerk run off to?
Sena? Hmm?
You did NOT just call him a "jerk."
Sena went to buy video tapes!
Don't talk about him like he's slacking off!
Video tapes?
That little punk...
He ran away!
Cerberus!
Hunt that cowardly Manajerk down!
Found him already?
It's Eyeshield!
That's a pretty elaborate entrance!
We've been waiting for you!
Go teach the White Knights a lesson!
Sena, we thought you went home.
No... I figured it'd be really bad to run away after everyone was finally motivated...
In reality I'm just a gopher and a newbie... A bogus hero.
But I'll try as hard as I can.
Sena...
C'mon huddle up.
What?! Why're you mad at me now?!
He's trying to get you pumped up.
Uhh...
How'd it go?
Knights, knights!
Oh! We swear here... on our... pride as knights... to win?
We didn't come here to... fight our enemies...
We came to defeat them!
We ain't here to defeat our enemies.
We're here to murder 'em!
Glory on the kingdom!
Rip their heads off, ya-ha!
YA-HA!
Yeah, this isn't gonna go like the Koigahama game.
Hmm?
Shin's on the bench?
Guess it's because they're playing Deimon...
For real? Then why're we even here?
This's our chance.
Eyeshield 21!
Everyone in the stands is writing us off.
So it's your time to shine!
Grow a pair!
It's okay...
Set, hut, hut, HUT!
Run!
They've already surrounded me!
Don't let 'em get it!
Hold them!
Football clinic!
What's Kurita's position?
A lineman!
He holds off the enemy defenders and opens a path for the offense! Ya-ha!
They almost intercepted it, you moron!
I-I'm sorry.
Inter-what?
Intercepted.
If Ojo had caught the ball before it hit the ground, their team would get to go on offense.
The one with the eye shield...
He's the one who scored the winning touchdown against Koigahama.
What do you two think?
Huh? He's, uhh... really fast, I guess?
That's it?
What about you, Shin?
I can't discern everything from one play,
but I'd wager he's a flag football player.
He's formed his own style after many years with no coach.
Those cuts...
You can't learn that overnight.
He can't be new to the sport.
But I sense trepidation in his running.
He's noticeably afraid of being tackled.
There's a difference between dodging your opponent and running from him.
I don't believe he poses a threat to us yet.
He got all that from just one play... Impressive, as always.
What makes you say he didn't have a coach?
He has no idea how to carry the ball.
How have you been carrying the ball when you run?
Well, like this-
You pinhead, you don't even know how to hold the ball?!
Watch.
Put the end between your fingers, and tuck it into your armpit!
End between my fingers...
Tuck it in my armpit.
Agon, what do you think of that one?
Even jobbers like the Devil Bats have a diamond in the rough...
Great legs... Dynamite thighs...
Wish they were mine.
I can tell even with those pants on.
And those hips-
Who have you been looking at?!
Yeah, yeah, Eyeshield, right?
A loser team recruited a knock-kneed amateur with decent speed.
Nothing more, nothing less.
With no one decent on their line, he isn't even worth worrying about.
Now what is this "line?"
The front row of players who shield the runners.
Basically, without a solid line you'll never get anywhere, no matter how fast you are.
Same play as before.
Eyeshield 21 will run around the line on the right.
And you line-GIRLS better block for him!
That's easy for you to say...
They're so much better than us...
I don't expect perfect blocking.
Half a second!
Each of you has to hold your assigned man off for half a second.
That's enough time...
...for Eyeshield 21 to break through!
N-No way!
Th-They'll kill me!
Sena, Sena!
Kurita?
The White Knights' defense is arguably the best in the nation.
Trying to get past them all alone would be really tough on you.
Just think of us linemen and Ishimaru as your shields.
We'll be the shields that protect you!
That way you can run without worrying!
Sh-Shields?
Kurita and the line... are shields?
Set, hut, HUT!
It sounds nice, but they're still scary!
The spikes really worked last time...
They don't slip at all, and it feels really safe.
Like my legs are armored.
Now I know how to hold the ball.
And everyone is my shield.
I can do this!
Charge!
Double team?!
His running... The fear has vanished!
I...
I trust you all!
30 yards to the goal!
It's pointless now... If he slips through...
...there'll be no way to stop his speed.
He's at the 20!
The 10!
Touchdown, ya-ha!
Sena!
We have the lead against the White-Freakin'-Knights!
That ruled!
You got past all those guys by yourself! This guy rocks!
Oh yeah, if I don't change my voice they'll find me out...
No, we made this touchdown together.
If I didn't have you all blocking for me, I'd never have made it to the goal.
They're really getting into it.
That's right, I made it because I had them... because I had my shields!
We've just bore witness to a completely unexpected event!
In the opening minutes of the game,
the relatively unknown Deimon Devil Bats have somehow taken the lead!
This is ridiculous!
How could we be in this situation against DEIMON?!
Coach.
I made a mistake.
He appears to have the speed to run the 40-yard in approximately 4.6 seconds,
and makes those superhuman cuts...
I now believe he's undergone years of special training to develop explosive running power.
Awesome... That Eyeshield person has never even been tackled once!
I wish Sena could see this! How someone that small fights so hard!
Time for the extra point.
Extra point?
It's like a bonus round after you score a touchdown.
If you kick the ball through the goal posts, it's one point.
If you score another touchdown, it's two.
C'mon.
We don't have a kicker, so I handle the kicks.
But all I can do is kick the living crap out of the ball.
It won't go in.
Which means...
Set...
This is no good, Otawara is confused.
Hut, hut, HUT!
Kick? Run? Run? Kick?
Stop thinking, Otawara!
Lunkheads like you are only there to smash through!
Yeah!
I'll just crush 'em!
They're running!
It's him!
Eyeshield, that's enough, get out!
Ah well, we were never gonna force our way into the end zone with this team anyway.
If that guy tackles me, he'll squash me like a bug!
The Devil Bats lead 6-0!
Here comes their kickoff!
Well, that's that.
Okay, we're on defense, huddle up!
Defense... That means I won't get tackled any more.
Everyone pay attention.
With our amateur defense, there's no way we'll stop the White Knights.
There's a 100% chance of failure, against their pass AND their run.
Huh?
So, Eyeshield 21...
What?
No way! That's insane!
Insane's what we need!
There're no coincidences in football.
If you wanna land a lucky punch, you gotta work for it.
You got it, Eyeshield 21?
This can't be happening!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
Yay, Sena made a touchdown!
But there's no time to relax, because Ojo's Seijuro Shin's about to come in!
Eyeshield 21, I respect your speed. However...
Can Sena make it past him?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Pierce of the Spear Tackle! Ya-ha!
I've been wondering, what's all this "hut, hut" business?
That's how they signal the start of the play!
Signal?
Yes. The team decides beforehand how many times they'll say "hut" before moving.
I get it!
Man, you really don't know anything...
Ooh, Sakuraba!
Ugh.