Okay!
Oh, they're in full swing!
They look pretty fired up.
Say, Kobanzame!
I-Is this what they call "spying?"
No, no, we just HAPPENED to come here
and Deimon HAPPENED to be practicing.
If we bring back data on Deimon to help with tomorrow's game,
Master Kakei will be very pleased.
Wha- Master Kakei?!
Switch with me!
If that's the case, his top pupil Hiroshi Ohira, i.e. ME, should be doing it!
W-What'd you say?
Master Kakei's top pupil is ME, Hiroshi Onishi!
Just the fact that a useless bum like you shares my name makes me mad, now let go!
I'm his top pupil!
I am!
- Me!
Huh? Where's Hiruma?
Yocchie went home. Said he had to do something.
What? But we play the Kyoshin Poseidons tomorrow!
What could Hiruma be thinking?
Oh, he said to go buy these once practice is over.
Astroturf cleats?
Bring it!
S-Stilts?
Hey, everyone on the Kyoshin line's a giant, right?
If we practice on stilts like this, it'll pay off tomorrow!
That's not gonna work, either.
- Me!
- No, me!
Height doesn't matter!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Man Who Remembers #21!
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
This meeting of the Kyoshin Poseidons is called to order!
In order to prepare for tomorrow, we're gonna rehearse our game plan!
Where'd ya get the lump, brah?
Kobanzame suffered this mortal wound in the name of Master Kakei!
- Master Kakei, we went to Deimon to-
- Enough with the "Master."
We're all freshmen.
First is Kakei's rival, the fake Eyeshield 21.
He's not strong, he's not ongstray,
but he's astfay fast!
Uh, don't get mad at me for praising him, Kakei.
He's weak.
His legs are incredible, but his body's fragile.
Deimon doesn't have good enough blockers to defend him properly.
If we can surround him before he gets moving, he won't be a factor.
Right, right!
You came to the same conclusion as I did, very impressive!
He's fast, but so are paper airplanes.
Our wall is impenetrable.
That frail physique is the main proof that he's a fake.
Hey dude, you don't have some kinda secret cleats, do you?
Something that can make you two meters tall without anyone notic-
They don't exist, stop being dumb and get the astroturf cleats.
Yes'm...
Perfect! 40 centimeters.
- Holy cow!
These cleats are 150% perfect for me!
Excuse me, do you have these one size bigger?
Yes sir, of course.
Oh, Yoichi, would you bring out our full inventory of cleats?
- Huh?
- Yoichi?!
Yes, sir!
What the heck is going on?!
Oh, didn't I tell you guys?
I work here part-time starting today.
Part-time?
I'm gonna quit this afternoon, though.
Wha- You're kidding!
Oh, boss, these were a special order from Kyoshin High,
would you like me to deliver them now?
Huh? Oh, sure...
Excellent.
A delivery to Kyoshin High...
Don't tell me...
What a coincidence that work is taking me over there.
And if I HAPPEN to witness the Poseidons practicing,
that's not spying, now is it?
That's why he took the job...
But...
Why us, too?
Man, I need bigger stilts.
Not that again.
Hey, you two!
Who are you? What're you doing here?
Well hello! We're from Kimidori Sporting Goods!
Oh, our astroturf cleats!
I was worried they wouldn't get here in time for tomorrow's game.
W-Well, you're all set!
- Please come again.
- Bye!
Hold it!
C-Can I help you?
Don't I have to sign for these?
Man, I thought we were toast.
I'm sorry, I completely forgot!
Please sign here!
Y-You're!
From Deimon!
Spies! Deimon spies!
Uh oh, we're blown! Run, Sena!
What are you doing?
Kakei...
He's only pushing with his palm, but I can't move an inch...
This is unforgivable!
I don't tolerate underhanded things like spying!
Have some sense of sportsmanship!
- It's despicable!
- Maybe we shouldn't have told Master Kakei...
...about how we tried to spy on Deimon.
Umm, what should we do?
We don't have much choice... Let's just apologize.
We're sorry!
We admit we were wrong!
I told you I wasn't gonna let this go!
Merely spying isn't enough to defeat the Kyoshin Poseidons.
Huh? Oh, yeah, right!
Who cares about a little spying?
Very well, you're acquitted! Go home!
- Thank you so much!
We'll be on our way then.
We're terribly sorry!
Yeah, I guess it's rough being so short.
I feel bad for you.
In a fair fight, you dudes wouldn't even stand a chance.
So you gotta lie, cheat and steal to get ahead, right?
I get it, I get it!
I mean, take that Omusubi kid...
You don't get anything.
Say what?
We gotten this far on skill.
Komusubi, me, Se...
Eyeshield 21, too!
He's not Eyeshield 21, he's just a fake.
Is the real one...
...that good?
He was flawless.
The crowd is going wild!
The long-awaited game between Phoenix Middle School and the famous
Notre Dame affiliate middle school!
Amazing! Eyeshield 21 strikes again!
The miraculous player from the far east!
I'll stop him.
I'll stop him dead!
Stop the famous Eyeshield 21!
Move it!
Close, but no cigar! It's a touchdown!
Argh!
I couldn't make it in time.
Eyeshield 21.
I'll stop you next time, I swear it!
I swear!
I don't care who he really is.
And I don't care how many people he fools into thinking he's the ultimate runner.
But the fake's explosiveness has nothing on the genuine article.
He'll never be better than the real one.
His use of the name "Eyeshield 21" is a disgrace to the real player.
Spies and impostors, Deimon's such a sneaky team!
- W-What'd you say?!
- I don't...
I don't know who the Eyeshield 21 you met in America was...
But...
Our Eyeshield...
...is better!
Sena?
Dude! He's pretty confident!
Then what do you say we figure it out right now?
Go back and get your team's Eyeshield 21.
I'll take him on.
I kinda took it easy on him last time.
This time I'll be serious.
No.
It's my turn.
I'll show him exactly why he's an impostor!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to catch the ball!
The hint is "triangle!"
When you go to catch the ball, make a triangle with your thumbs and pointer fingers.
Everyone get that? Ya-ha!
A one-on-one run against Kakei?!
You really agreed to that?
Mano-a-mano? Good deal.
Of course! Sena wasn't gonna let those insults go unanswered!
Right, Sena?
What do I do?!
This is way out of control!
The game is tomorrow, I didn't have to face him now...
Peewee, remember what you said at the restaurant?
The restaurant?
It doesn't matter if I'm the real one or a fake.
I won't try to run!
That's right, I said I wouldn't run.
Then stop thinking and go.
The battle's already begun.
Yes!
It's all about the first moment.
Blast off and end it quick!
Yeah.
Fakeshield 21.
If you really think you're on par with the real thing,
then break past me.
One time will be enough.
Come on!
I'll prove to you that a copycat is only capable of mimicry!
I can do it!
He got stuffed!
- All right!
- Way to be, Kakei!
I'm scared...
It felt like being swept away by a tidal wave!
Don't you dare take me lightly.
I know...
...but my legs...
Eyeshield 21!
Show him what Deimon's shorties can really do!
That's right...
Physique doesn't matter.
Short people have their own methods of winning!
One more time, please!
Let me see it...
The Devil Bat Ghost!
Here it comes.
You'll never make it past me!
Yes! The Devil Bat Ghost!
N-No way... He got past Kakei...
Oh man, it is ON, little dude.
I knew it was coming, but I couldn't stop him...
That was the Devil Bat Ghost.
You're the man, Sena!
You should've seen Kakei's face when you pulled out the Devil Bat Ghost!
I bet we blow 'em outta the water tomorrow!
Enough celebrating!
Hiruma?
What are you doing out here?
Just passing by... Just a coincidence.
Coincidentally, I stumbled upon Eyeshield and Kakei going at it.
And by pure coincidence, I caught Kakei's every move on my camera.
Coincidence, he says...
Kakei's way better than that.
I guarantee he's still hiding something.
Yes, I thought so too.
But even knowing that, I'm glad I went to face Kakei.
Ow!
He's proud of me, I guess.
Yup!
What's going on here?!
You two went to pick a fight with Kyoshin?!
Oh, no, that wasn't Sena, it was Eyesh-
Are you okay, Sena? Did they hurt you?
Oh no, I'm fine!
Eyeshield 21...
Oof!
Ah, I figured you'd be here.
Man, you really ate it today.
I definitely underestimated him.
Oh ho ho, you admit it!
It won't happen in the game.
We WILL win tomorrow.
Yup, you bet!
He's definitely fast.
But we're tall!
Besides Kobanzame and our backs, we're all over 180 centimeters.
"Height is our main weapon."
"It's how we'll win the championship."
That was all you had to say to get me to switch to football.
Remember, we made a pact to go all the way.
So we'll keep the streak alive tomorrow!
Yeah... You got it.
Wait for me, Fakeshield 21.
I will defeat you!
Yay! Sink the Poseidons!
If that big bomb is the Poseidons,
then we're just little spinners.
We zip around like crazy, then go pop at the end.
That's got its advantages, too.
Let's do our best tomorrow, as the Deimon shorties!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
The Poseidon game begins!
But it's already turning into David vs. Goliath!
Height doesn't guarantee a win!
We'll show 'em our hidden powers!
Hey, even David scored a lucky shot!
Snap your fangs into them and don't let go!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Devils vs. The Sea Gods! Ya-ha!
I swore I'd come back with Komusubi...
I can't return empty-handed...
Excuse me... Have you seen a seen a boy who only says, "Hngo hngo!"
Huh? "Hngo hngo?"
Yeah, there's a ton of 'em over there.
KO-MU-SU-BI!
You've gotten so plump and round, like a little piglet!