I know it...
Someday I'll be out there playing with everyone else!
I have to keep...
Shoot, it's pouring.
Maybe I'll call it a day...
Hey, that's...
Unsui Kongo... from the Shinryuji Nagas!
Training all alone in this downpour...
He's... incredible.
W-Whoa...
Unsui Kongo's Agon's brother, right?
He hasn't missed a single pass.
He must be crazy talented.
He's not.
You know about him, Yuki?
I believe he got that good
by training much harder than anyone else.
I'm sure of it.
Unsui, huh?
Okay, then!
Let's go scout out Unsui's weak spots!
S-Spy on Unsui?!
Inside voice, Yuki.
C-Can I come with you? To help spy?
Uhh... well sure, but...
I want to see Shinryuji's Unsui Kongo in action!
Yikes... What's gotten into you, Yuki?
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Wall called "Talent."
'Sup? Heading out?
Why don't you practice with the team for once?
Forget that.
Target sighted.
Looks like he's going somewhere.
There's no point in spying if he's not at practice...
No.
He might be leaving for some kind of secret training.
Let's follow him.
Why's he going to Kyoshin High?
Maybe he's gonna ask them for info on us.
Nah, I don't think...
Is Unsui apologizing to them?
Kakei!
Deimon?
He's always going around to the schools his team's faced
I guess he's making amends for the guys his brother injures.
He's a lot more conscientious than his brother, huh?
I don't believe it...
...even if they are brothers...
What's... what's the point... of him doing that?
Come on, Unsui.
You're the older twin - Agon's riding perfectly on his first try.
Agon! Agon! Agon!
I've asked myself thousands of times...
"Why did Agon get all the gifts? Why not me?"
Set... Hut!
Agon has natural talent, and I have nothing.
But if I keep training, one day...
Shinryuji Athletics Admission Program
Letter of Acceptance
No way... Did they really choose me?
Shinryuji's famous football team...
accepted me on the athlete's program?!
I see, so YOU'RE Unsui...
Oh man, they're twins, we must've chose the wrong one...
Well, they're both named "Kongo,"
same address...
We actually chose your brother Agon for the athlete's program.
Chose your brother...
Did you come to make fun of me?
Uhh... I guess.
Don't wait for me when I don't have your talent.
It's all about ability, pity doesn't do anything for anyone.
The skilled have to tread on the average to advance.
Believe in your natural skills!
That will be enough for me!
I don't need you to tell me...
I already know.
I want to forge my brother into the ultimate player.
I'll take full responsibility for all of his actions.
A harsh road to travel indeed.
I... am prepared.
Don't you know you're being tailed?
Get your head outta the clouds.
Uh oh!
Who's there?
Hiya...
Good day...
Eyeshield 21...
Stop being such a failure!
Y-You're being...
...too harsh!
Shaddap, trash.
I'm talking to HIM.
He... he's doing it for you!
I told you to shut your worthless mouth!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
I told you to shut your worthless mouth!
Stop, Agon!
The game's soon. Enough.
Whatev.
I'll just destroy you on the field.
Man, what's up with him?
It's like he's pure evil.
He's scary.
Go home, and stay away from us!
Why?
Even if he is your brother,
how can you let him do whatever he wants
and then take the blame when he gets in trouble?
I have my reasons, and nothing will change them!
I've saw you training like crazy in the rain.
I want to keep working hard and become a player like you!
"Working hard?"
W-We're sorry!
He's been studying like a madman so he's really stressed out...
Then I'll teach you...
...why I do things the way I do.
Come with me.
Y-You jerk, you think you can take all of us?
I'm in a bad mood... this is just what I need.
W-What's with your football?!
Why's it so heavy?
Lead. The inside's coated in it.
It's a special ball I use when I'm training.
You train with this heavy thing?
I'm going to throw a pass to you, with that ball.
See if you can catch it.
But why...?
You wanted to know why I take responsibility for Agon?
Okay.
Yuki...
Get ready.
Right.
Tranquil Reflections.
The ball's vibrating!
Yuki!
W-What was that pass?
It just started shaking?
Maybe it's black magic?
No!
The lead inside makes the ball's weight uneven.
It shifts the center of gravity
and causes the ball to start moving erratically.
It makes any pass into the worst kind for a receiver.
An everyday receiver could never catch it.
One more... one more pass, please!
Please!
S-Shoot...
I'll catch the next one!
I won't allow it!
No interference.
This is between me and him!
W-Wait, WHAT'S between you and him?
When did this turn into a fight?
I don't...
I don't understand...
Why...
Why do you do so much... for him?
Done already? Man.
Now you've done it, you little twerp!
That's more like it.
Come on, enough! He can't take it!
Clearly...
You can't catch that ball.
No!
I still want to know... your answer...
I've already given it!
Agon caught that ball on his first try.
One-handed.
His first try?
Seriously?
There is a difference between Agon and me
that no amount of work will overcome.
That difference is the talent he was born with?
Talent?
Yes.
An overwhelming gap in our skills as football players.
B-But don't you train to close that gap?
No.
I stop Agon so he won't get himself disqualified from the tournament.
That's...
I exist to keep his power in check.
But... but you...
Hello?
Agon what?!
Aww yeah.
C-C'mon, stop.
W-We give up!
No way, pal.
I haven't had enough yet!
I got a lot more beatings to give out.
I'll wreck all you losers!
Y-You little...
Why're you here?!
One of the students called me.
That's enough.
You always have the worst timing, Unsui.
That goes for you idiots as well.
Stay away from him!
We'll remember this!
Weak...
Listen up, all of you.
I train myself to help him...
...become the number one football player in the world.
Because that...
...is my role in life.
What's with those two?
He trains to make his brother the best...
That's his "role in life...?"
I see...
He's not just strong because he trains hard.
Unsui Kongo...
I've never seen someone with so much conviction.
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Ya-ha!
The Kanto Tournament starts tomorrow!
Everyone ready?!
We've done all we can.
Now it's time for the real thing!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Devil Bats Move Out!
Ya-ha!
A lone ball by the river, begging to be kicked.
No one around...
It's about 60 yards to the other bank...
It'll be a new record if I make it!
Prepare for the smartest world record in history!
N-Not smart...