Oh!
Strong Golems vs. White Knights
Boobs!
You're pushovers!
That won't work!
Boobie Crush!
Even Otawara-!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Ultimate Spear!
Oh no! Otawara was easy knocked down by Kyotai!
Kyotai is running straight for the end zone!
He's running!
That was too easy!
The Way of the Boobs is invincible!
Whoa boy! Shin's going after him!
Shin...
Shin and Kyotai are going one-on-one!
Here I go, Seijuro Shin!
Boobie Cru-!
Kyotai tripped!
What force!
How horrible! Will he be all right?
That was nothing!
It didn't hurt him at all!
He's tough and stupid.
But man, Kyotai's really strong!
Sorry, my bad! My bad!
I was only looking at my opponent's boobs!
Kyotai, looking at boobs is fine,
but you'll trip if you don't watch where you're going!
I can't believe he was able to get by Otawara so easily.
The Way of the Boobs is invincible!
Did you see that?
It's the Way of the Boob's ultimate technique, Boobie Crush.
B-Boobie Crush?!
Th-They stick with their beliefs!
Is their strong belief the source of their power?!
That's right.
In order to keep from losing to the enemy,
you just have to dive into your enemy's boobs with a bang.
Dive in...
...with a bang!
Dive straight into your enemy's boobies!
All men love boobs!
Utilize that energy!
That is the true meaning behind the Way of the Boobs!
It's just as you said, Master!
Yep!
This is nuts!
The Way of the Boobs is awful!
Huh? What's that?
Boob Time
B-Boob Time?!
Boob Time is the best.
He's got hot milk and cookies...
It's like tea-time.
Wow, he's relaxed.
How fascinating.
Wow!
Yocchie's gone into his evil mode when games have surprise endings!
No, even if heaven and earth swapped places,
this game's outcome won't surprise anyone.
What do you mean, Musashi?
Whew, he got me! Got me good!
Sado's on offense again!
Surprisingly, Sado is giving Ojo a hard time!
Shin!
The super powerful running back,
Susumu Kyotai's run has given Sado their first down and continued offense!
Let's go, Kyotai!
Yeah, Boss Iwashige!
- Boobs! Boobs!
Go, my disciples!
They passed the ball to Kyotai again!
And Otawara's going after him again!
Otawara, you gotta stop him this time!
Take this!
Boobie Crush!
He got me again!
No way!
Now Shin's going after Kyotai!
His speed's accelerating!
He's completely mastered my Rodeo Drive.
Seijuro Shin is a hard-working genius.
That's it!
One more time!
Boobie Crush!
That's his perfected Spear Tackle.
I can't breathe... or scream!
Shin recovered the fumble!
He's zooming fast!
He's getting past all of Sado's players!
He forced a clean turn over and scored a touchdown!
A-Amazing!
With his super powerful lightning fast tackle,
Shin skewered Kyotai and stole the ball!
Hey, ya did it, Shin!
From defense to a touchdown!
The first points go to Ojo!
Shin's... great!
But what was that tackle just now?
By suddenly accelerating,
Shin's Spear Tackle turned into a powerful spear split three ways!
Riko?
This is just like...
...like a trident.
It's a Trident Tackle!
By combining Shin's Spear Tackle with the Rodeo Drive's speed,
he's created the Trident Tackle.
An already formidable monster...
...just leveled up into an even stronger one.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic
Do you know how many referees are at a football game?
The answer's in 60 seconds!
There are seven referees at a football game.
They keep a close eye on the game!
Learn all the rules! Ya-ha!
Not yet! I'm not, not, not done yet!
He may have defeated Kyotai,
but that won't work on my rock-hard body!
What's with him?
How's that?!
What power!
I'm counting on you, boss.
As your boss, I'll be sure to avenge you!
I'll show them what a perfected Boobie Crush is like!
Shall we hit them with everything we've got now?
I guess so.
Meaning...?
Otawara...
I've perfected my Trident Tackle.
You don't have to let them through anymore.
What's... that mean? Huh? What?
We're telling you...
...you don't have to intentionally lose anymore.
Oh, okay, okay!
Sweet! I'll give them all I've got!
Sado Strong Golems 0 - Ojo White Knights 7
Ojo's got a seven point lead!
How will Sado counter them now?!
Set, hut!
Kyotai's making a run for it again!
Shin, I don't have to fall down anymore, right?
Don't you dare make fun of me!
Shin may have defeated me,
but I can still crush you with my Boobie Crush!
He's fast!
Otawara's true power isn't because he's stronger than everyone else at Ojo.
Right. In a match of brute strength,
Kurita or Gao could probably defeat him.
But his incredible speed for his massive body size
doubles or triples his strength when crashes down on his foes.
It took an entire week to explain that to him.
- That long?!
He's as fast as a running back.
He's been working on increasing his running speed.
Boobie-
- He's gonna smack right into him!
It's Boobie Crush verses the stupidly powerful frontal assault!
I'll show you that a lineman's power doesn't lie just in his muscles!
Muscle-men and power are... Huh?
What about muscle again? Whatever!
Why?!
Master, the power of our love for boobies isn't working!
Kyotai, there's just one problem with this technique.
Men don't like other men's boobs!
I wish you told me that sooner!
His brute strength won!
Where's the ball?!
Uh-oh! Shin intercepted them again!
But Iwashige's going to try to stop him!
Who cares about some Trident Tackle?
I'll stop you!
Boobie Crush Explosion!
There it is!
His Trident Tackle grows more powerful each time he uses it!
Touchdown!
The super linebacker Seijuro Shin has counter attacked two times in a row now!
That's impossible!
I-I-I-I-I-I-I am Ganjo Iwashige!
Ew, what's with him? He's like...
...a kid.
I'm still just a junior,
but no one stood up against my rock-hard body in the regionals!
But-But-!
I can tell after hitting you just once,
your body truly is as hard as a rock.
Really?
But...
But?
But the Trident Tackle can pierce stone.
It's as simple as that.
Shin neither overestimates or underestimates his opponents.
He only sees them as they truly are.
Teach me the Rodeo Drive.
I...
I've done something terrible.
Shin is great!
He's a diligent, hard working genius.
He's grown even more impressive.
But so have I! Just you watch!
Where would you like to go?
To Enoshima Football Field.
Sakuraba!
It's their Everest Pass!
Holy cow! He jumped so high!
Touchdown!
Ojo's offense isn't letting up!
Sakuraba's definitely the best in the world!
What'cha think of Ojo now?!
Th-They're too much...
They're too strong!
Game over!
The game has ended with Sado unable to score a single point!
Ojo is the winner!
They're strong! They're almost TOO strong!
Ojo didn't have any openings at all!
Master!
This sucks!
Don't cry, Ganjo, Kyotai.
There are no losers for those who follow the Way of the Boobs
even if you just lost a "well fought game."
- Right, Master!
Boobs! Boobs! Boobs!
Hey, Sena...
Do you think you could win
if it was a fight between your Devil Bat Ghost and his Trident Tackle?
Well, I guess... I'll never know until it happens.
It'd be nice if I could win, I mean, I've gotta win and all...
- I'm not really confident about it, but...
- I'm getting worried.
Don't talk like that, Sena!
T-Taki?
Don't pop outta nowhere like that!
You've gotta be cool and say "I'm gonna win."
After you say it, you'll have to stick to those words in the finals.
Even idiots can hit the nail on the head sometimes.
But only sometimes.
Even idiots, huh?
He's such an idiot.
But I'm a genius!
- You're a genius at being stupid!
So that decides our two teams!
The finals for the Kanto Tournament B Block is between...
the ultimate offense team, Deimon Devil Bats
and the ultimate defense team, Ojo White Knights!
But one if them will have to lose!
That...
...means...
...it's finally happening, Sena.
We've been waiting for this since forever!
Yep!
Shin...
Shin's amazing.
Whenever I think I've caught up with him,
he does something that puts him further ahead again.
Speed was my only weapon I had to defeat Shin!
And now his speed's on par with mine.
What should I do?
How can I defeat Shin?
Shin, our next game will be our fated game against Deimon.
The Deimon Devil Bats aren't that weak little team we defeated in the past anymore.
They're our ultimate rival in this tournament.
Yeah, I know, Shin.
We'll give them everything we've got,
even the Ballista.
Yeah!
I will consider this game as the true finals for the tournament.
It's finally time for us to settle the score!
Sorry, Sena.
He's greater than I had imagined.
Shin mastered a technique even greater than I could have imagined.
Riku, he would have perfected that technique eventually,
even if you hadn't taught it to him.
I've... I've been waiting for so long.
I've been waiting for the day I would play against Ojo and Shin again!
Sena...
Shin...
Yoichi...
It's been a while.
I was hoping that I might be able to see you,
so I've been waiting by the entrance.
But you never came out...
I've got a flight to catch, so I'm going now.
I hope that you make it to the Christmas Bowl.
I know you don't think of me this way, but as your father-
Hiruma...
Sakuraba's Everest Pass...
I wonder how I can block that thing.
We've got...
...Otawara with his speed plus power...
...to deal with, too!
And this wasn't all Ojo's got up their sleeves.
They've got the Ballista.
Yeah.
But... finally... we're up against Ojo.
Thinking back to when we lost the Spring Tournament to them with a score of 68-12,
fighting them in the Kanto Tournament's semi-finals is...
...like a dream come true!
Don't let the dreaming end there, Fatty!
We're gonna win!
We have to pay them back.
Yeah, after all, our goal is to make it to the Christmas Bowl!
No, we're not just going to it.
We're gonna win it!
Our goal is...
...to conquer the nation!
Conquer the nation?
That sounds pretty cool!
Let's go for it!
Yeah!
Let's conquer the nation to the max!
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
Ojo's school festival is ever more impressive than I had expected!
There's a red carpet and a dude in armor at their festival.
What type of fantasy world is this?!
Anyway, we've gotta find out about their Ballista!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Ojo High's School Festival!
Ya-ha!
I got hungry after watching that game.
I'm only human.
You over there!
You're just the person I was looking for!
You look like you'll make a great successor to my Way of the Boobs!
Join the Way of the Boobs!
Fill your heart with the sense of having done a good job!
National domination with the Way of the Boobs!
- Boobs! Boobs!