President... The game?
Who cares about the game?
How are you going to work with an injury like this?!
Now we can't do your photo shoot!
I heard that after the accident, Eyeshield managed to score a touchdown.
He was able to get through? Past Shin?
The first year student who went in for you scored a touchdown, so don't worry.
You should concentrate on healing up first and foremost.
Your team can handle themselves just fine.
They can handle it, huh?
What the heck am I doing? I'm supposed to be a second year student here!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
A Hero's Qualifications
The crowd can't keep their eyes off of Ojo's ace, Sakuraba, after his super catch!
The best highlights in football games involve catching!
I knew it! This is my road to glory as a star catcher!
Ah, it's Eyeshield 21!
Huh?!
That's some running!
Unfortunately, due to an accidental collision with Deimon's ace player Eyeshield 21,
Sakuraba had to leave the field.
That's right...
I wonder if Sakuraba's okay...?
Eyeshield 21 has released the following statement in regards to the accident:
Did you catch my Homicide Tackle?
Accident schmaccident, I did it on purpose!
He may be a great runner, but this guy's attitude is the worst!
Sakuraba is currently hospitalized and working towards a compete recovery.
He's been hospitalized....
Hey, Manajerk and monkey boy! Quit wasting time and start practicing!
Crush them! Smash them!
Can't we have a bit nicer cheer?
Meat dumplings! Chow mein!
Okay, ladies, now to work on real-game passing exercises.
Yeah!
Real-game exercises can be pretty dangerous, so I want you to sit this one out.
Oh? I think Eyeshield just went into our club room.
Go get him already!
A-Ah, right!
Eyeshield... Will he really come?
He's here!
It's Monta! It'd be bad if he found out it's me!
Eyeshield!
H-Hey, are you a new teammate? Let's work hard together!
What the heck are you doing, Sena?!
No, um, I'm Eyeshield...
You're even using a goofy voice.
Uh, you see... Well, um...
Hey, look at my cut!
So YOU'RE that lousy jerk!
Monta!
Which means that HE made that statement, not you.
Right, Hiruma did most of it.
He did all of it!
But we've got to keep it a secret that you're Eyeshield, Sena.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to deceive you.
Okay, I get it.
Let's work hard together!
Y-Yeah!
You work towards being a hero with your running!
I'll work towards being a hero with my catching!
Isn't it great? It's so nice! We finally got a receiver like we wanted!
Okay then, let's practice!
What's wrong?!
Come to think of it, I haven't gone to visit Sakuraba yet.
Are you going to go as Eyeshield?
Huh?
Well, your true identity is a secret, right?
It would be pretty crazy if any of Sakuraba's fans found you while you were dressed up as Eyeshield.
What should I do?!
How about going as the manager on behalf of Deimon? And take a get-well present with you.
As manager...
Let's do it!
Don't worry, I'll go along with you!
Sakuraba from Ojo is a catcher and a super-popular celeb.
I should ask him for some tips on how to get popular.
Did you write up an apology letter?
More or less.
"I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. You've had to go through so much because of my carelessness.
It was all my fault."
What an apology!
I'm used to it 'cause I've had to apologize a lot since I was little.
You've had it pretty tough, huh?
I wonder if Sakuraba's angry after hearing that comment...?
There's no point in worrying about it.
You'll just have to put forth max effort!
See? There's a whole bunch of his fans here.
You'd have gotten yourself lynched if you came here dressed up as Eyeshield.
Sakuraba's pretty impressive!
Sakuraba?
Do you know what his room number is?!
Tell us!
We can do it! Follow me!
Y-Yeah!
By the way, what was his room number again?
Hiruma said that he's in room 418.
Where does he get all this info from?
Got it!
A football...
It's my ball. Give it back!
I said give it back!
I swear, you are just standing there like idiots.
You're so slow!
Man, what an annoying brat!
Ah, we're here.
What's keeping you? Hurry up and go on in.
W-What'll I do if he's angry?
What are you saying? We've made it this far!
Just apologize with everything you've got.
Y-Yeah.
Hello!
Hey, Sakuraba! You still alive?!
Guys!
Can you turn your neck already?
I'll make it turn!
Eh?! Um, there's someone behind the door!
H-Hey!
This isn't Sakuraba's room!
He's here!
Are you okay?
Sakuraba!
What's going on here?!
What should we do?
We can't get out...
Somehow we managed to defeat the Sankaku Punks,
but I sure had to work hard to find a good target to pass to.
We could have won with a whopping 100 point difference if we'd had you there with us!
After all, Sakuraba's our ace!
W-Where am I?
You were unconscious. Were you beaten up by the hospital ghost?
Judging by that horrified look of yours, I'm guessing you saw something quite gruesome.
Yeah, your face!
Later, then.
We'll do some weightlifting when you come back!
Shin...
Please tell me the truth.
Would it have been an easier win if I had been there?
No...nothing would have changed.
I see...
It's getting harder and harder for us to barge in...
Yeah...
So nothing would have changed even if I had been there?
Let's see, since we're using the Japanese syllable system and you're after me, is this read as "Shin?"
Yes.
I'm Haruto Sakuraba! Nice to meet you!
Hey, you're really tall!
You'd make a great receiver.
You gotta join the football team!
There'll be about 30 middle schoolers trying out this year, but about half of them will drop out quickly.
But there's several students with potential.
For example, there's Sakuraba. He's a seventh grader and already 175 centimeters tall.
I'm sure he'll make a great receiver.
Who's that guy behind him?
Hmm, what was his name again?
Don't let him join another team, no matter what!
Huh?
Okay, great!
What are you doing?
Extend your hands out first!
That's when the gap between us started to grow.
And that's when... I met President Ito.
Hey there, boy!
Huh?
You see, I'm from this company.
Jari Productions?
Right! How would you like to be on TV?
It's not like they need me at Ojo anyway...
Let's jump out! It wouldn't be quite so awkward if we jump out all happy-like!
Uh, okay then.
On one, two, and-!
Sakuraba! Time for a surprise interview!
It looks like Ojo had a tough game without their ace present.
Please give us a comment, as team leader.
Shut up!
Football Clinic!
What type of game is flag football?
It's related to football!
Instead of tackling players, they remove the flag wrapped around their waist!
Some schools even hold competitions! Ya-ha!
What's with you?! It's so noisy in here!
Ah, it's that brat from earlier!
It's common knowledge that you're supposed to be quiet when you're in the hospital!
Sorry about that.
Just give us one second, kiddo.
Ow!
I'm going!
Hey, sorry about that.
We got pretty loud.
Sorry...
Who're you?
I'm the manager for Deimon High.
I-I came here to apologize on behalf of Eyeshield 21...
U-Um... I can promise you that he didn't collide into you on purpose.
I know. I'm the one who carelessly wandered onto the field.
Thank goodness he's a good person!
Besides, it's not like you'd get any merit out of colliding into me.
Even if Haruto Sakuraba isn't there, Ojo's strength won't dwindle at all.
Ojo? Sakuraba?
No way! I can't believe it! I didn't even notice!
You're the real deal! You're Sakuraba!
I want your autograph!
An autograph? I you like, I've got a signed CD right here.
Huh? A CD? Why'd I want that?
Huh?
I watched a bit of the game.
The Ojo White Knights' receiver, Haruto Sakuraba, is my hero!
Please sign it "To Torakichi."
O-Okay....
Do you play football?
I want to, but they don't have football for sixth graders, so I play flag football.
Flag football?
It's like normal football, but instead of tackling the opponent, you stop them by taking their flag.
That sounds nice! It isn't scary at all.
It was last year while I was going home!
I just so happened to see some of the game between Ojo and Deimon while walking home.
That game, huh?
Ah, they're playing football!
Football?
Sakuraba!
Wow! It's high!
I can't believe he caught it!
Touch down!
I did it! It's my first point in high school...
I'm a shrimp now, but I'll be a giant when I'm an adult!
And then I swore to this ball that I would become a hero like Sakuraba someday.
I know... I know how you feel.
You're just like me and how I admired Honjo's catching.
Next month I have my first and final game.
I finally became a regular player when I entered the sixth grade!
Ouch!
Are you okay?
I want to be able to move my legs again as quickly as possible so that I can get discharged.
I don't want to waste any more of my time over that dumb car wreck!
I can't say it. I'd like you to tell him instead.
Otherwise, I'll curse you.
V-Very well.
So that's why Sakuraba's my hero!
It was just luck that I was able to catch that pass...
Oh, the modesty! Don't tell me you're embarrassed 'cause he called you his hero!
It's the truth.
Ojo wouldn't change any regardless of whether or not I'm there.
What are you saying?
H-Hey, Monta...
Haruto Sakuraba isn't a hero, an ace or anything like that.
That's just an image others have created for me.
There's a hero image out there that has absolutely nothing to do with me.
You guys probably can't understand the pressure that puts me under.
No, I think I can...
Everyone overestimating you and expecting you to be great...
A hero? It's nothing but a hassle!
Hey, hey! What's your problem?!
Can't handle being a hero?!
That's not something you should be telling your fans!
You've disappointed me, you loser.
You stupid loser of a receiver!
I'll call you "max lamewad" from now on.
What did you say, you chimp?!
Sakuraba isn't lame!
Who'd you call a chimp?! Huh?!
Come on, you two!
No way I'll stop!
Stop it, monkey!
WHO'S a monkey?!
Give it a break!
Could you tell him that there's no point in apologizing?
Tell Eyeshield 21 that I'm sorry I got him tangled up in this whole accident.
Why...?
Why'd... you say something so pathetic?
Could I have a moment?
No way! There's no way!
The game's next month!
It's just not possible.
It's going to take a bit longer before you'll be able to walk again.
I'm sure you'll be able to by the time you enter middle school if you work hard at your rehab.
I don't care about rehab!
I've always been a substitute player!
And now that I'm in the sixth grade, I finally got to be a regular player...
And here I tried so hard...
What the heck was I trying for?!
My year as a sixth grader...
What on earth was I fighting for?!
But it's not like you won't recover. You'll be able to play football if you work hard at your rehab.
That's right! Just keep at it!
What would you know?! Like you could!
Take that!
Be careful.
This really means a lot to you, doesn't it?
Unlike me, you've still got a future ahead of you.
I'm not qualified... to be a hero!
Who should Torakichi use as his role model when you spout crap like that?!
Enough already! Just get out.
But...
Monta, let's go.
Hey, Sena!
Is it okay for us to just leave him?
He's mistaken.
E-Eyeshield 21!
To Sakuraba, from Eyeshield 21!
Um...We really caught a break by taking you out, because now Ojo's passing game is in the toilet!
That's right!
We wouldn't have stood a chance if Sakuraba the Ace hadn't been hit by my Homicide Tackle!
Torakichi!
The player you saw and admired was the real deal.
You've used Sakuraba as your role model to help you work hard!
Your hero really is Sakuraba!
My hero...
Sakuraba, I'll be waiting for you on the field.
You've gotta make a comeback!
As Eyeshield 21, I know your true strength better than anyone!
Sakuraba got a goal within one play!
I'm number one!
I've... made up my mind.
I'm going to make that super catch that Torakichi saw... not just get lucky.
I'm going to train hard and become strong!
I'm...I'm going to rehab so hard it might kill me, just so I can stand on the field again!
I'm going to become a great player like Haruto Sakuraba!
Torakichi...
Let's promise each other that we'll never give up!
Yeah! YEAH!
That's how it should be!
Let's all work hard together!
Friendship to the max!
Yep!
You're the enemy, aren't you?!
Get outta here!
Come on, dude.
That was scary!
But football is amazing, isn't it?
To think that just one play could move someone like that.
That was some great acting.
But, I think we may have taken up the villain's role again.
Yeah, but that's okay. I don't care.
Huh?
I've gotta get stronger so that the stories become reality.
Yeah! Effort to the max!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
They determined who we're up against in the next game!
It's the Zokugaku Chameleons, run by the super-evil Rui Habashira!
T-They sound scary, but we've gotta do it!
It's all so I can fight against Shin!
You sound pretty confident, ya know!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Oath Under the Setting Sun! Ya-ha!
It's gone! It's gone!
My pillow's gone!
Whoops, I brought it with me!
The cursed pillow...
There's an old saying about those...
Since your cursed pillow's gone, I'm sure you'll be discharged from the hospital soon.
You're even scary when you laugh!