Distance to Las Vegas: 1622 km.
Death March - Day 7
A city?
A city!
I haven't taken a shower in forever!
Max Jump!
I feel alive again!
Hey, Hiruma.
Can we afford to not do any team practice?
Team practice isn't gonna do anything if we don't get our individual skills up to snuff.
We'll have to cram it all in during the few days when we get back.
What're these?
Each card has a single play drawn on it.
We have to learn all these?
Hey, here's the Sweep we did against the Aliens.
Why are there pictures?
There's no time to memorize all the diagrams,
it'll be quicker if you associate each play with the image.
Man, we've got lots of cool plays!
Can you handle such a wide variety of attack patterns?
You don't even have a tight end.
tight end?
Which is... what?
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
OH! My sister!
Okay, a tight end can either be a blocker or a receiver.
tight end
Their role changes depending on the play.
Essentially, a football jack of all trades.
In other words, with a tight end,
you can modify your plays in a new set of ways,
adding a whole new dimension to your playing style!
Incidentally, I played tight end back in my day.
Then if we had a tight end...
We could execute all these sweet-looking plays no problem!
It has to be someone who can block, catch, anything at all!
Let's find one!
Someone here will find our tight end!
If only finding one was that easy.
Keep moving!
Ya-ha!
Brake without losing speed...
Rock on, Sena!
You're right up here with us today!
He's getting the hang of it.
You lose that stone and I'll make you start over.
W-Wait! My rock!
I'm separated from everyone.
But more importantly...
How did I end up in this scary place?!
Hey, boy, whatsamatta?
You lost?
N-No... I, uh... came from Japan...
I'm an American football player...
Football?
Say, we met a Japanese girl on our way here...
She said she was looking for a Japanese football player...
Maybe she meant you?
It must be Mamori!
Yes! Yes, she must have meant me!
Okay, hop on!
Hang on tight, we don't want you falling off!
Time to step on it!
Th-Thank you very much.
No problem!
That little Japanese girl must have come all the way here to see her boyfriend!
How exciting!
Oh, there she is!
We found the football kid you were looking for!
Mamori!
Uh-oh!
Why?!
C'mon, hug, hug!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Y-You're...
You're... Ms. Suzuna Taki?
I told you not to say that. It's too formal!
Anyways, why'd you let me crash into you?
Well, I, uh... Sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
If we'd arranged ourselves a little better we would've been fine.
Arranged?!
I know all about that!
They must be lovers arranged to be married!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Would you please cut that out!
Bye bye, lovebirds!
Sheesh!
Anyways, who are you again?
Sena Kobayakawa.
So the whole Deimon team's having camp here in America, huh?
It's more like crazy intense training rather than a camp.
Eyeshield, too?
Uh he's kinda... here... but not...
What?
S-So why are you here, Suzuna?
Him.
Oh?
I told you about him, right?
My older brother, Natsuhiko Taki.
Hiruma told me he'd come to America.
I've been looking for him forever, and I finally heard he was here in this city.
Hiruma told you...
What a terrifying coincidence.
Your brother left home to try and become a football superstar, right?
Yup.
He's such a brainless doofus, you know?
But our mom's really worried...
So somehow, I have to find him and take him home.
But this city's huge, finding him here will be tough.
It'll all work out somehow.
I've chased him this far, haven't I?
See ya!
If you run into my brother, let me know!
H-Hey, wait!
Taki!
Don't call me by my last name!
I don't wanna be associated with my stupid brother!
I had no idea it was that bad... What on earth...
You got separated from your friends and now you're lost?
Yeah, and I'll be pretty hopeless all by myself.
Are you serious?
You need to learn to do things on your own, not just rely on others!
Yeah, I know...
I've always had Mamori...
...whenever things got rough.
Oh, whatever.
C'mon, we'll go together.
Okay!
Finding your brother will be easier with two people!
I don't expect much help from someone who's lost himself!
Where the heck did Sena disappear to?
This is a pro football tryout!
Hey, maybe...
My doofus brother might be here trying to make the team!
Yeah!
Football Clinic!
What's a tight end's role?
Whatever the next play requires him to!
Block, catch, run, whatever it takes! Ya-ha!
Man, these guys are gigantic.
What're you lookin' at, pipsqueak?
If you bump into my prized anaconda boots and get 'em dirty,
I'll bite your pointy little head off!
From the looks of him, he might really do it!
Stick with me, or you'll get lost again.
Suzuna!
Hey! What brings you here, my sister?
Have you come to celebrate the start of my career in the pros?
I-I think I understand why you don't want to be associated with him...
My sister!
You never even called, you brainless idiot!
Do you know how worried mom's been?!
Suzuna...
You think you can just take our money and waste it like this?!
Was my loving greeting too much for you to bear?
I get it, I'm sorry!
Think about it, Suzuna.
What?
I can't be confined to just Japan.
Today's the day I enter the pros!
Yeah, yeah.
Go ahead and try out.
You'll learn exactly where you stand.
You've never been on a football team, never played in a real game...
A professional team would never take you!
Have you come from Japan for tryouts, too?
Oh, no, I-
Americans don't respect humility!
Obviously, it'll be tough to get very far
without a well-built physique like mine.
But effort can make up for your small stature and lack of definition!
Good luck!
I can tell he's not INTENTIONALLY acting like a jerk...
Behold my graceful step!
Oh, I got soda on my shoes.
Better clean that up.
You messed up my awesome boots, you twerp!
It's him again...
This is bad!
Oh, my apologies.
It didn't come off, eh?
Well, don't sweat the small stuff, right?
Just let it go, huh?
We're all here to take the same test, right?
We're practically family!
Again, I know it's not INTENTIONAL...
He's really mad now!
You've got a heck of a build there, friend.
If you try really hard, you might do pretty well for yourself!
I'm gonna remember this, you snobby jerk, you little shrimp!
Both of you are gonna get it, big time.
W-Why me?!
There's no need to worry.
We're all comrades aiming for the same goal!
Bosom buddies, as it were!
I'd never forget you.
He's just making it worse...
Things are getting worse and worse...
All athletes report to the field immediately.
Wait, I'm not-
I'm not playing!
I said I'm not playing!
There's probably a phone over there, Sena.
You can call your friends... Huh?
Why am I trying out?!
200 kilograms!
45 kilograms!
Only 45 kilograms?!
Is he joking?
It's finally my turn. I'm counting on you all!
90 kilograms!
Wow!
That was on purpose.
Was there an earthquake just now?
Or did my incredible strength just loosen the rack?
H-He didn't even notice.
It's cool.
Next time.
The 40-yard dash is next.
Sena?!
What's he doing?
Hey, wiener! You're up!
Sorry.
The 40-yard dash...
I do want to see what the death march has done for me...
And I haven't timed a full-speed run in a while.
He tripped?
Not very impressive.
5.01!
He's pretty fast, too!
Tell me to do anything, I'll do it better than anyone else!
Wow, he struck that pose without having a jacket to take off...
Jack of all trades, master of none, as they say.
Wait, if he can do anything...
Okay, a tight end can either be a blocker or a receiver.
Their role changes depending on the play.
I bet this guy would make a perfect tight end!
The final test will be a scrimmage.
Uniforms and equipment have been provided, all athletes are to dress immediately.
I'm with her brother on team B.
And we're against...
It's clobberin' time!
Could this get any worse?!
Sena!
What're you doing?!
I found a pay phone over here!
Hello? Hiruma?
Who let you run around goofing off, Manajerk?!
Get your lost butt back here right now!
Yes... Near route 21?
Then a right at the sign?
Got it!
I think I'll be able to find them.
Great!
Thanks for everything.
We flatten 'em into pancakes in the first five seconds!
That stuck-up preppy and that pipsqueak...
They're gonna have a bad "accident."
When we're done with 'em, they'll never be able to play football again!
Hey, you'd better get outta here!
If you try to fight those giant wrestler dudes, they really will squash you flat!
B-But-
I need to tell my brother-
Oh, my sister!
Do you need to talk to me?
How do I look? Like a future star player, right?
You know you don't stand a chance. Just quit.
Please, don't worry! Our victory is in the bag!
What if you get hurt?!
Mom's been worried 24/7 and it has to stop!
It'll be fine.
Sit down, relax, and make sure you're watching the moment I make the cut.
He's completely hopeless...
See ya, Sena. You'd better get going.
I'll go stop him.
Wait!
If the two of us drop out now,
then all those other men, men with the same dream as your brother, will be at a disadvantage.
I understand why you said that, but you want him to make the cut, don't you?
Of course I do.
He didn't get into a single high school, so he can't play football at all.
So he came all the way to America.
He may be dumber than a brick, but going pro is his dream!
Once I'm in the pros, I'll make a million-no, TWO million dollars a season!
Then you and I will live in America, Suzuna!
Of course I want to see him succeed!
Then the best thing to do is stay here and cheer him on.
And I'll do everything I can do, too.
Sena...
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima blaze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Sena, why're you trying out for a pro team?!
It's simple!
As long as he's alongside THE Natsuhiko Taki, Sena will make the cut easily!
No, I mean, he's in the middle of the death march, and...
Wait, ANOTHER new character?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Signs of a Ghost! Ya-ha!
Okay, gentlemen!
Let's do our best to have a good, clean game!
I-I can't stop!
How can this be?!