Sena, can you believe that the last death game's
against the NASA Aliens?
Y-Yeah....
Finally! Panther and I will...!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Last Death Game!
Wow, they're really late.
I thought they'd be here by now.
Y-Yeah...
Sena!
How've you been doing?!
You're heavy!
Hey! Thanks for coming to pick us up.
It's the NASA Aliens!
I bet you're tired after that flight!
Here! It's a gift!
Huh?! A banana peel?
In Japan it's customary to give "unimpressive" gifts, right?
Note: It's considered polite manners to say "It's nothing impressive, but please accept it."
We may call them that but we don't mean it...
I bet you did that on purpose!
Oh, it's Coach Apollo!
Thank you for coming all the way out here
just for a practice game with Dei-
Don't get the wrong idea.
We've come to fulfill the promise we made at the Cream Puff Cup
to defeat Deimon by 100 points.
I don't remember promising that...
Man, this old fart's nuts!
But is it true that you won't be able to play
in the Kanto Tournament if we beat you?
Yeah, that's what Hiruma said.
Well, now you know why we can't afford to lose.
I see...
Sena, I can't wait to fight you!
Yep!
Hey, hurry up! The bus is gonna leave!
Phew! We barely made it!
Coach Apollo, Watt and Homer are missing!
I told you to buy your souvenirs on the way home!
Sorry. We'll just have to use a taxi now.
I can't believe they had the gall to leave without me!
When will we arrive at Deimon High School?
Pretty soon.
Thank goodness!
We should be able to make it in time!
Hey, you sure this is the right place?
Huh?
Hey, isn't this Deimon High?
Deimo High School
No, it's Deimo High school.
It's not...
Deimon
Deimon High.
Deimo
It's Deimo...
Everyone, here at Deimon High School we'll be holding
the fifth and final hellish death game!
However...
Yeah, Coach Apollo, Homer and Watt
from the NASA Aliens still haven't arrived yet.
We can't start the game yet!
Man, they're such a handful!
I wonder if they're okay...
I came up with a good idea!
Apollo had an extra necktie in his suitcase.
Cerberus can pick up his smell and hunt him down!
Good luck!
This was a great idea!
But what'll happen to them after Cerberus finds them?
Ah!
This is all your fault! You're pronunciation stinks!
Leave this to me.
Hey, taxi!
Take us to Deimon High School.
Sure thing!
'Kay, we're at Deimo High!
What trickery is this?!
Hello?
Oh, Watt?! Where are you?
Where is this?
Dunno.
It's Deimon!
Just send someone over to Deimo High to pick us up!
I said DEIMON!
Deimon!
Deimo High?!
Let's see...
Deimo High's... over here!
It's kinda far off...
But it's not that far if we go over the mountain instead of around it.
Huh?
Sena, let's go get them!
Sure!
Now that we're running, I wanna fight you right now!
So let's race, Sena!
Sure, Panther!
W-What was that?!
I knew it!
Huh?
You've become even faster, Sena!
You, too!
Just you wait!
I'm not even going half as fast as I can!
Same here!
I'll jump it up to 60%!
Then I'll go 70%!
80%!
90%!
Haven't they sent a car over yet?!
Hey, that's...
Sena and Panther!
You're late! What took you?!
- 100%!
We tied!
I'm amazed you kept up with me.
Most impressive, Sena!
But... things'll be different in the game!
Panther...
The fastest runningback...
...is me!
I can't afford to lose!
Same here!
We'll finish this during the game.
Right!
Hey! How long do you plan on ignoring me?!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
They're finally here.
I'll let this slide if you were late
because you were afraid to lose.
No, no. I'm sorry we were so late.
As a sign of my apology,
we'll remove some players from the team-
Then we'll just have these two play!
Then we'll play air football!
That doesn't require a single player!
Quit acting like little kids...
Geez, boys will be boys.
Well, sorry to keep everyone waiting!
The game's just about to start!
Neither Deimon nor NASA will have any handicaps during this game.
It's a fair fight, befitting the final match!
NASA Aliens vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ownage!
Ya-ha!
Oh, boy! They're starting off with the Moonsault Formation!
It looks like they're going out at full-throttle from the start!
Panther's coming!
Everyone, stop Panther!
Stop him, Komusubi!
Hoo-wee! Panther's using his gravity-defying running!
- Flatten him!
He's pulling ahead?!
Hey, someone stop him!
I've gotta... stop him!
Amazing! They flew into a kickoff return touchdown!
Panther from the NASA Aliens
is still improving upon his gravity-defying light run!
What drive!
All right! It's my turn!
Stop Eyeshield!
I'll put everything... into winning!
Ya-ha!
Touchdown!
Way to go, Eyeshield 21!
He used his Devil Bat Ghost to score some points!
Set, hut!
Max Catch!
Neither team's giving up an inch! It's a battlefield out there!
Both sides are desperately fighting for points.
We're always improving,
so you're wrong if you think we're the same
as when you fought us last.
And you're mistaken if you think
you're the only ones who've improved.
They worked hard to clear the death climb.
Set, hut, hut!
Komusubi, let's show them how much we've improved!
Improvement!
- Belly Block!
They broke the muscle barrier!
Now sack QB!
Destroy launch site!
You can't throw!
Good thing I trained as a pro wrestler for a while.
Homer was forced to make a Shuttle Pass!
All right!
Max Intercept!
Uh-oh, the ball bounced away! Who'll get it?!
Eyeshield caught it!
Offense goes to Deimon!
Everyone's working together! Now for the touchdown!
Panther?!
It's a duel, Sena!
Touchdown Deimon!
NASA Aliens 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 14
And with the extra point, they've brought it up to a tie.
NASA Aliens 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 20
NASA Aliens 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 21
But we'll pull ahead again!
We won't let you!
We'll hit you with...
...all we've got!
Speed!
Power!
Technique!
It's the Ha-Ha Triple Team!
The Shuttle has crashed!
The Aliens are having a rough time!
But wait!
This team's still got Panther's Gravity-Defying legs!
Panther gracefully slipped right through them!
Go, Panther!
Score us a touchdown!
Panther's so fast!
Keep up, Sena!
But don't you dare catch me!
Touchdown!
He's fast!
He gets faster each time he runs!
But... I won't lose to him!
Deimon, touchdown!
NASA, touchdown!
Touchdown!
Wow, amazing!
Neither Sena nor Panther has been able to catch each other.
Deimon's on offense,
the score's tied and there's 21 seconds left!
This play will determine the fate of the game!
Wow... I'm under so much pressure!
I just can't catch him!
But this type of pressure...
I oughta be mad since I haven't caught him once, but...
...is the ultimate high!
I've never felt this way before!
You're amazing, Panther!
You're amazing, Sena!
- Football really is...
- ...the best!
Don't you lose, Sena!
Get a touchdown, Sena!
I did it!
Caught ya!
Touchdown!
The Deimon Devil Bats won!
The games are all over now!
The Deimon Devil Bats have cleared the Death Games!
- Ya-ha!
Yay! Now we can play in the Kanto Tournament!
Why so happy?
Huh?
This just means we're at the starting line now.
We're fighting Shinryuji.
The real battle's just starting.
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Hiruma's friends with AGON?!
What a shocker!
They do seem kinda similar...
This wreaks of trouble!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Demon God Agon Kongo!
Ya-ha!
You beat us, so you'll do great at the Kanto tournament!
Yeah, thanks, Panther.
Pass this on to Hiruma...
Huh?
We'll accept a challenge from him any day of the week.
- Okay! Sure thing!
Sena, be sure to win the Kanto Tournament!
Then go to the Christmas Bowl!
Okay!
If I want to fight Panther again someday,
we have to go to the Christmas Bowl!