Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Oh!
- Ya-ha!
There's just three yards to the goal line.
It's our last chance to take the lead.
Our last chance...
Let's fly together with the Devil Bat Dive!
Sena...
Ojo White Knights 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 15
Sena and Monta...
...together...
...doing the Devil Bat Dive?
I figured we could use the Devil Bat Dive to get over Ojo's walls,
and have everyone else focus on holding them back.
E-Everyone?
So we aren't going to leave any of our catchers open?
No...
I want Monta to go out and be ready to catch a pass.
We'll go either with the Devil Bat Dive or a pass to Monta.
Once the game starts, Hiruma will determine what to do,
I guess...
...that'll confuse Ojo, too...
...maybe...
He'll have a split second to decide,
so...
I guess that won't work.
What was I thinking?
Forget everything I just said.
- He lost confidence at the end there.
Hiruma?
Not bad...
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
A Form of Desperation!
Well, we're down to just three yards!
In three yards, Deimon can steal the lead from Ojo!
But Ojo's walls are thick!
They're just like castle walls guarding a king!
Will Deimon seize victory, or will it be Ojo?!
There's just 1:21 left!
We've gotta...
...make this work!
What type of strategy will Deimon choose with such a muddy field?
Set, hut, hut!
Monta!
Let's go, Sena!
He's passing to Raimon!
No, you don't!
Sakuraba's blocking him!
No, he's too quick!
No, it's to Eyeshield!
Monta was just a decoy!
Deimon's using its own unstoppable specialty,
the Devil Bat Dive!
That's right! No one's been able to stop it so far!
Not even Kyoshin or Shinryuji!
Not my Devil Bat Dive!
Did it work?!
Almost... there!
Th-They stopped him!
The Devil Bat Dive has finally been defeated!
Sena!
I don't care what comes at us! We'll stop any and everyone!
Did you see that, Deimon?
That's just how powerful Ojo's Captain, Makoto Otawara, truly is!
He has height plus weight along with a muscular physique and speed.
Neither Kyoshin nor Shinryuji had a tank like Otawara with them.
The Devil Bat Dive was their final hope.
Now Deimon's in serious trouble.
Sena!
Sena?
Is the goal line the only thing he can see?
Mamo...
It seems that won't be necessary after all.
Guys...
It's not like we're completely out of luck.
That's right! We'll just push them back next!
They're coming up with some sorta lame plan!
If they're going to hit us with both of their aces, we'll do the same in return.
Sakuraba, don't take your eyes off of Raimon.
Okay!
As for Eyeshield...
I WILL stop him.
Deimon's unable to crush this three yard thick wall!
Will this spell out victory for Ojo?
Set, hut!
Let's go, Monta!
Yeah!
We must...
...stop them!
Will he throw to Monta this time?!
What?!
Hiruma just feigned throwing the ball!
Eyeshield's running again!
Will he try for another Devil Bat Dive?!
That won't work!
This strategy utilizes Ojo's tall players, including their QB, Takami!
Now!
He went low?!
He went through the path created by Kurita and Komusubi!
It's a super low-altitude Devil Bat Dive!
Crap!
You're not getting through!
In the end, agility is my weapon!
I'll use my speed to turn myself into a powerful cannonball
and pass through Shin's arms.
He got stopped with one centimeter left!
Next up is Deimon's final turn at offense!
This truly is their last chance!
The final battle is being fought over one centimeter!
I can... keep playing...
Let's fly together until the end, Sena!
Yeah!
Shin...
Deimon will put everything into this next play.
We must defend against them.
Yeah, 'cause we're going to win!
Well, there's just one centimeter!
Just one meager centimeter until the goal line!
We'll take the lead if we can push Ojo's defense back one centimeter.
But that one centimeter is insanely huge!
That's right.
The closer they get to the goal line, the stronger Ojo's defense becomes.
Why?
Because they have less area to worry about defending.
What will you do, Deimon?
Which is it?
They'll do the opposite of whatever you predict.
It'll be one of the two!
That's not fair, Onihei!
There's only 1:15 left!
Deimon's about to begin their final offensive move!
Set!
We'll keep them them wondering who's taking the ball for as long as possible.
Hut!
We're gonna be marked by Shin and Sakuraba.
Even if you both come at us, we're not playing by ourselves here!
Hut!
I may not be a natural like Shin, but no one can beat me in the air.
Sena, let's win this together!
Yeah, let's fly together!
HUT!
Will he give it to Eyeshield?
Or pass it to Raimon?
Monta made a huge jump!
Will the last ball go to Monta?!
It went to Eyeshield!
Tackle 'em!
No, that's not right.
He's going to pass it to Raimon from his Devil Bat Dive!
I warned you! I said that the two shrimps were going to fly together.
He dropped the ball!
Not a problem! Sena, I can catch ANY ball!
I won't let you!
Sakuraba?!
Sakuraba's hands... he's going for an overhead catch!
Monta!
Go, Sakuraba!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we'll be talking about the secrets behind being a good quarterback.
The key point is to always make the right choices at the right time.
Quarterbacks control the flow of the game! Ya-ha!
I know Sakuraba can do it!
He IS the number one receiver!
No one can defeat him!
I'll catch it this time!
Just you watch, Torakichi!
I swear I'll take your wrist bands to the finals for you!
And then at the finals I'll proudly announce that...
...I'm the number one receiver!
He's reaching out with one arm like Shin when he's tackling!
He caught it with one hand...
Impossible! You can't do that even if you wanted you!
It's not like I wanted to.
But it was the only way to beat his towering height.
Sakuraba sure is amazing.
He pushed me to the extreme, clear to the end!
Touchdown!
- Monta!
Baseball Boy!
A-Amazing! There's only 1:10 left to the game!
Deimon has miraculously taken the lead!
Ojo White Knights 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 21
This game's over. Deimon's going to win now.
Deimon's... gonna win?
Ojo's... gonna lose?
Huh? What about the Christmas Bowl?
Is this the end... of my final game?
It's all... over?
No, no, no!
NO!
Not yet.
It's not over yet.
You never know who will win until the very last second.
The game will resume with Deimon's kickoff.
We might win.
We might defeat Shin and the Ojo White Knights.
I'll stop you!
We're going to win and go to the finals TOGETHER!
No! We're going to crush you! The Ojo White Knights are going to win!
Otawara's determined! He pushed back Kurita despite his massive build!
Ojo's managed to return to the center of the field in just a few seconds!
White Knights! White Knights! White Knights!
In just a few seconds...
Darn it!
Stop 'em even if it kills you!
You bet!
We're gonna win!
Deimon's gonna be victorious!
We'll stop them! We must!
We can flip the score within 30 seconds.
We WILL win!
- Yeah!
Well, everyone's putting their lives on the line in the final minute!
Just listen to the audience's cheering.
Both sides are passionately cheering on their teams as the game reaches its climax!
The stadium is going absolutely wild!
Set, hut!
One minute left! It's over in one minute!
Time to finish this!
Ojo's far from finished!
So they put you on offense, too?!
But we can't afford to lose either!
Sorry to keep my fans waiting.
Pass cut!
I failed!
It's war! It's an all-out war out there!
Yeah, this is an amazing battle.
Everyone's so worked up!
And here I couldn't even stay on the field until the very end.
Ishimaru, are you okay?!
This is great. I love this atmosphere.
It makes my blood run cold.
W-What should we do, Hiruma? Huh?
We have to put someone else in.
All that's left is Omosadake, and he'll never keep up with Ojo's speed.
Then there's Yamaoka and Satake, from the basketball team.
I've gotta put one of them on the field...but which?
Who's your replacement?
We want...
Yukimitsu...
Number 16, Yukimitsu.
But Yukimitsu doesn't have enough stamina left to be useful in any of our plays.
Why him?
He's desperate.
He'll fight clear till the very end.
His drive for victory makes him the most likely to help us win. That's all.
"Desperation" improves the odds, huh?
That's just like you.
Ojo's quickly pushing them back!
But we're down to the final ten seconds!
Will they pull through?
We've still got a long way tol the endzone.
Should we take a chance and go with a kick?
Takami.
Please just hand me the ball.
I promise, I will not fail.
Just ten seconds!
We win if we can defend against them for ten seconds!
Shin...
Set, hut!
Amazing! Shin took the ball and is running!
Shin's... coming!
He's going to force his way through.
He's bulldozing through!
Shin's flooring everyone!
He flew by Sena and Yukimitsu!
It's no good. I didn't slow him down at all!
- Stop him!
He's not stopping!
He's a monster!
Go, Shin!
Oh no! He's going almost at the goal!
That's it! If I can't slow him down...
Touchdown? Did he make it not?!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Did he score a touchdown?!
There's one second left...
We're going to the Christmas Bowl!
The final battle between Deimon and Ojo's almost over!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Final Moment.
Ya-ha!
Hey, did I stand out any when my nose started bleeding?
Hey, did I stand out?
Remember how I got a nosebleed?
Hey, hey! Did I stand out?
You're a really annoying person.
Hey, do I stand out more than those crows?