Effort, fortitude, will!!
The Yuhi Guts!
Fight!
Effort, fortitude, will!
They're our opponents for the second round!
Fight!
Effort, fortitude, will!
This is it!
THIS is football!
Everyone's rushing at each other with everything they've got
so that they can win their way to the Christmas Bowl!
Atsumi!
We won't hold back!
We'll take down the Yuhi Guts with everything we've got!
We'll be ready!
Please understand, Atsumi.
Sir.
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
A Battle of Effort, Fortitude, and Will!
It's time for round two at last!
Yeah!
We're going to fight Atsumi... with all we've got!
Those are the Yuhi Guts' players.
Well then, let's put on the pressure before the game!
Hey, aren't you Atsumi?
This is the LAST GAME OF OUR LIVES!
WE'LL LOSE OUR MEANING TO LIVE if we lose!
He's making me nervous, big time!
He doesn't hold back, no matter who we're up against!
He's the type of person you don't want as an enemy.
I bet you've studied the videos from our game against Amino, but..
Sorry, we've been hiding a guy who got scouted by the pros!
That'd be me, my sister!
- There's no need to hide me!
- Should we chain him down...?
I know that bluffs and mind games are the Devil Bats' way.
That means you're coming at us with everything you've got, which is great, but...
But we, the Yuhi Guts, won't be able to show you our way!
The coach's made his mind.
Quit your whining already!
And here everyone had worked so hard...
Why can't they play in the game?!
A bunch of huge guys just came out.
I thought Yuhi Guts was a small team with just ten guys?!
What the heck's going on?!
Atsumi...
Sorry, but we need the extra credit, so you've gotta lose, Deimon!
Who're you guys?!
We're Yuhi High's sports all-star fill-ins!
Yuhi Guts' football players stink so bad, you see,
that we were asked to play in this game.
See ya in the game!
Those guys are nothin' compared to us!
Got that right.
The jerk! He's their ace baseball player who went to Koshien!
Koshien is the All-Japan Baseball High School Championship
Just as promised, anyone who plays in the game will definitely get extra credit!
Extra credit!
Does that mean that the real Yuhi Guts'... are on the bench?
That's horrible!
More like dirty!
It's not horrible or dirty!
Deimon's got fill-ins, too.
It's only natural to want the best possible players,
even if it stops real teammates from playing.
BUT that's only it's actually stronger with a bunch of fill-ins, you see!
It's the second round for the All-Japan High School Tournament!
Yuhi vs. Deimon!
Yuhi High has replaced all of its regular players with fill-ins,
making it the Sports Super-Stars Yuhi Guts!
It's truly a dream team!
Has Deimon's fate been sealed?!
- Determination!
- Ya-ha!
Set, hut!
Catch it, butt-monkey!
Come on!
I'll stop you!
I-It hurts!
What awesome defense!
Set, hut!
He's fast! What a beautiful intercept!
Offense and defense are swapping out, so Yuhi's on offense!
Even though the team was put together in a rush,
each individual player has great potential.
They oughta be pretty tough!
That's all the infamous Eyeshield's got?!
- We won't...
- ...let you through!
Take that!
Touchdown!
Awesome!
Yuhi's seven points in the lead!
Yuhi Guts 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Deimon's in a pinch!
No way!
Hey! What's going on here?!
It's 100%!
Huh?
We've got a 100% chance of winning at this rate.
They stopped both Monta and me and we're constantly getting pushed back,
so what's with this "100%?"
I told you, didn't I?
Are the fill-ins really better than the regular players?
Extra credit!
Yay!
Yuhi, great play!
Everyone's individual strengths speak for themselves!
This is the only way.
Right!
We can't even show them the Yuhi Guts' way!
This is kinda maddening.
Huh?
I mean, none of them are doing this because they love football or anything.
They're just doing it for extra credit, right?
I can't believe they're forcing us back!
What was the point for all the blood we shed over training?!
The same goes for Atsumi!
They've worked so hard,
but have been forced to give up before they even get to fight!
And here they worked so hard!
That's right.
I want to fight against Atsumi... and the enthusiastic Yuhi Guts!
I really wanna fight against Atsumi!
A fight against people who don't even want to fight isn't a real fight!
Then we'd get to fight against people who can fight and... Huh?
If you fight, when you fight, go fight!
I don't get it!
Yeah, I got confused somewhere in there myself.
ANYWAY, if we make them realize that a team of fill-ins can't defeat Deimon,
they might let the real Yuhi Guts play!
- Ouch!
- Good thinking!
Now he gets it!
- Okay, let's go!
- YEAH!
Everyone's worked to death to get here!
We can't let their effort have been in vain!
Football Clinic!
How many people are needed to play football?
One team gets eleven people!
Deimon's a small team, but normally a team swaps out players for offense and defense! Ya-ha!
I'm amazed they're doing the same thing again.
How STUPID!
Here it is! Everyone's marking Raimon!
Aren't they forgetting someone?
Right, besides Monta's wide-reaching pass....
We've got the handy short-pass!
- Awesome!
- Sweet!
T-That's...
Touchdown! Good going!
Yuhi Guts 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
You did it, bro!
Look! He's actually done something great for once, and I mean for once!
Sure he did!
Boo-yah!
We got our points back! YES!
Hey, we weren't told about this!
I can't believe someone besides that monkey can actually catch passes!
Good going, Taki!
But you're stupid!
You're awesome, Taki!
But you're as stupid as they come!
Thank you, everyone!
Please come get my autographs after the game!
He's always carrying something to sign...
You idiot, bro!
That new guy, #37...
He hasn't just doubled Deimon's offense with passing.
Okay, now for a mind-blowing run!
Does everyone remember our strategy cards?
Power of Tackle.
Eyeshield's going to squeeze through by chin-fuzz!
Okay!
It's your time to shine, Taki!
Of course, it's meaningless if you can't break down the enemy's wall of defense.
Me?
It's a tough job.
Wonder if you're a big enough genius to handle it?
It's a tough job...
Enough of a genius.
Enough of a genius...
Leave it to me!
In a way, he's the easiest guy here to control.
I'll definitely draw Atsumi and the others out to the field!
Set! Hut, hut!
He's passing to the monkey!
Okay!
It's not a pass! Eyeshield's gonna run!
Too easy!
Huh? What?!
That's Eyeshield 21!
What amazing speed!
I want to fight him!
How far would our three years go against him?
He just got a ten-yard gain!
Yay!
Deimon's offense is really improving!
Of course!
They've got a guy who can block and pass!
If only the Captain could play...
You'd be nuts to ask such a jumbled team to deal with that team's offense.
Touchdown!
And another touchdown!
Yuhi Guts 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Yuhi Guts 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
Yuhi Guts 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 18
Yuhi Guts 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 24
Yay! Yay!
Good going, Deimon Devil Bats!
What a wonderful combination!
This proves it wasn't just luck that they won against Amino!
What amazing speed! And such amazing destructive power!
Their strength is the real deal!
Eyeshield 21...
...your speed's overpowering!
But Haibara might have been able to stop you...
If only someone who understands football could fight you!
I want to fight!
I wanna fight!
Man, I can't keep this up!
- I quit! I quit!
- I can't do this!
What'd happen if I got hurt?! This stinks!
If we keep losing, we won't get any extra credit anyway.
And getting hurt would stink! I'm quitting!
Hey, guys!
It's okay.
But...
The high-ups won't be able to say anything if they go and quit on their own.
That means...
Coach!
Captain!
- Captain!
Let's go!
Okay!
For me, Akaboshi, Minami and Fukuse, this is our last chance at the tournament!
Let's go all-out!
Yeah!
Go, Yuhi Guts!
You can do it!
Yuhi Guts!
To the Christmas Bowl!
YEAH!
It's Atsumi and the others!
Sweet! We drew them out!
Their chances of victory just rose from 0% to 1%.
This is really our last chance!
Don't let Eyeshield 21 get through!
Atsumi... He's really fired up!
But... We can't afford to lose either!
Set! Hut, hut!
The Yuhi Guts gain two yards!
They feigned handing it over!
It's a pass!
It's Yuhi Guts' first down!
The Yuhi's defense is five short and two deep!
Beware their bumps, butt-monkey!
Use the classic double cover!
I-I don't really get what he's saying...
Deimon's most recent data is on our defense is from last spring.
We'll cut from behind and whack them with a blitz!
Yeah!
Effort!
Fortitude!
Will!
Effort!
Fortitude!
Will!
Effort!
Fortitude!
Will!
Yuhi!
Neither team's budging a single step!
Yuhi Guts, you're on fire! You're burning up!
They're like a hurricane of tears!
Go, Eyeshield 21!
We won't let you pass!
We're betting our...
...three years on this!
We'll beat you with our teammates!
Atsumi!
I challenge you, Eyeshield 21!
I'm betting my past three years on this!
I'm not done yet!
For a small, weak team like ours to even hope to win, we've gotta train like mad!
Yes, sir!
Hey, look. It's the weak lil' football team!
Darn it! Our budget's zero again this year!
How maddening!
Calm down. We'll come up with something.
This is our last fall season!
We're gonna throw everything from the last three years into it!
Yeah!
Here's the roster for the fall season.
It's mostly got ace-players from other teams.
I'm getting in trouble with the high-ups.
They're annoyed with our football team's performance!
They'll shut down the football team if we don't win this year.
Please understand!
I'm Daisuke Atsumi from the Yuhi Guts...
And this is my last play!
Atsumi's... sure fired up!
I'll hit him with everything I've got!
Game over!
Yuhi Guts 7 - Deimon Devi Bats 56
The Deimon Devil Bats will move on to round three
of the All-Japan High School Football Tournament!
It's over...
Yuhi Guts!
His running... was the real deal...
- Boo-yah!
- We did it!
We did it! We did it!
Listen up! You've still got next year!
Never give up, Yuhi Guts!
Effort, fortitude, will!
Good luck, Deimon Devil Bats!
You go, Deimon Devil Bats!
Deimon Devil Bats! Deimon Devil Bats!
We have to win...
Yeah!
We've got to do our best for those who have lost!
We'll win no matter what!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Who the heck's this old fart that suddenly showed up?!
He's Onihei from the Hashiratani Deer!
In my heart, he's my master!
And he's a high schooler?!
He's too mature! Way too mature!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Refined Spirit of a Lineman! Ya-ha!
Congratulations to me on my game debut!
Congratulations Natsuhiko Taki on your Debut
Autographs
Well, everyone who'd like an autograph, please line up!
No one's coming...
I'm going home, bro.
How can this be?!