Eyeshield 21
Stompity stompity stompity stompity...
Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Ya-ha!
- Oh!
This isn't the Devil Bat Ghost he stopped last time.
Come, Eyeshield 21!
Start the Devil Bat Ghost...
Wha-?! He's too fast!
A-Amazing...
The Trident Tackle struck a moment before the Devil Bat Ghost began!
That was Shin's power...
So close... it's now 4th and 3!
But against Ojo's top-class defense, it must seem like well over 30 yards!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Ikari's Prison Chain.
Hmm... if Deimon can't get a first down here, Ojo will take possession.
But I believe even moving three yards against Ojo is no small feat!
They decide to play it safe and call in Musashi for a punt
instead of their trademark 4th down gamble.
Go ahead and punt, I'll flatten your kicker before his foot touches the ball!
Set, hut hut!
I'm close enough...
I can tackle him before he kicks!
What?!
A trick!
Charge, Peewee!
This time-!
A fake punt - they're running it!
Sena!
Run!
Almost there... a little more and it'll be a first down!
Sena!
Stop, Ikari!
He doesn't realize the play's over!
The play's over, jerk!
- The... BALL!
- W-What's this guy's-
That's enough, Ikari!
Sorry, guys, he gets tunnel vision, you know?
Even his brain's made of muscle!
Despite being stopped, Deimon squeaks out a first down!
My arm's numb...
Now then Riko, we've got an incredible new addition to Ojo's line, don't we?
Umm... here we go.
Today is lineman #66's debut game, his name is Ikari!
He's got speed and power to spare, everything you'd want in a lineman!
Ikari...
Like in..."Prison Chain" Ikari?
Prison chain?
Back in middle school there was this insanely strong guy everyone called "Prison Chain."
Everyone feared him because he was always clinking these chains he carried,
and flipped out at the slightest provocation.
How'd a delinquent like that end up playing football?!
Why would ANY delinquents start playing football?
Look who's talking.
I never thought I'd meet "Prison Chain" on the football field...
Jumonji... you're...
Ikari, I want you targeting Jumonji every play.
Let Shin handle Eyeshield!
Yes, sir!
Ikari's finally usable.
Yes.
Today he's a full-fledged member of the Ojo White Knights.
Back in middle school, he was an uncontrollable maniac.
Pfft... Ojo? Forget them.
That school's for pampered babies, am I right?
Who called Ojo a bunch of losers?!
I didn't say losers...
Wh-Who are you...
No one badmouths Ojo and gets away with it.
Man, I'm stuffed!
60 servings of gyoza is too much, even for you!
You're Ojo's eating champion.
More like Ojo's garbage disposal!
Ojo... garbage?!
What part of Ojo is garbage?!
Nice punch, and fast, too.
You shouldn't start fights, though!
If you really wanna run wild, play football, American football!
Football...?
Football's the best!
On the field, you can be as rough as you want!
And the rougher you are, the prouder your teammates will be!
Not quite, but hey...
That was when Ikari joined the White Knights.
Until that day, he was just another violent delinquent...
But Otawara saw his potential immediately.
Otawara...
You introduced me to the world of football... I'm really grateful to you!
I introduced you to football? Really?
Yes!
And I...
I'm putting it all on the line for Ojo!
I see.
Well, forget the small stuff, it's time to let loose!
Yes, sir!
Letting Otawara handle him was a good decision.
Agreed.
Set...
I'm... I'm not the same guy I was back then, either!
Hut!
No one beats me in a fight!
I'm taking Ojo...
...and Otawara...
...to the Christmas Bowl!
Hiruma abandons the pass play and spikes the ball!
BALL!
The ball!
He popped it!
Ikari jumps after the ball... and destroys it.
What incredible strength...
J-Jumonji...
What're you so afraid of?
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What do you call it when someone drops the ball during a play?
It's six letters!
When someone drops the ball during a play, it's called a "fumble."
Whichever team picks up a fumble takes possession!
Capitalize on the opponent's mistakes! Ya-ha!
What're you so afraid of?
What's your problem, Jumonji?
Get up, Kazuki!
Did something happen between you two?
Because it sure looks like you two have some kind of history.
Jumonji...
The... first time I met him...
...I was in middle school.
So you're this "Prison Chain" guy from Ojo we keep hearing about.
The guy from the town next to ours who's never lost a fight.
Meaning if I beat you, then I'M the new top fighter.
You ready?
Leave me alone. I promised Otawara I wouldn't fight anymore.
Chicken, huh? I knew you Ojo guys were all worthless.
What about Ojo is worthless?!
And you two!
Help us-
We're sorry!
So that's what happened...
You moron, this's no time to have flashbacks from middle school!
We're not the same guys we were back then either!
We've all powered up!
Besides, this is a football game, not a street fight.
There's nothing to be afraid of!
Right...
You're right.
Okay, let's rock!
We'll get a first down this time, right, Kazu?
Set...
Hut...
Man...
Hut!
Yocchie!
Hiruma!
The ball!
What a smooth move!
One of Hiruma's patented trick plays!
A great move by Hiruma!
Hiruma turned around, appearing to protect the ball from Ikari,
when in fact it was a short back pass straight to Eyeshield!
And Eyeshield 21 has taken off!
All right!
Not good enough.
There's the Trident Tackle!
Ojo's defense trumps Deimon again!
- Sena!
You okay, Sena?
I'm fine...
Why...?
Why won't...?
Why won't my body do what I tell it to?
What the heck am I doing?
Jumonji!
What is wrong with you?!
Why don't you fight back, you wimp!
Say something!
What happened to you?!
This isn't like you at all!
Wake up, Deimon lineman!
Quit wussing out!
You big chicken!
Am...
...I still running away?
Kazuki!
Dad? What're you doing here?
You come out here to mock me, too?
"Throw away your trash."
That's a little rule we have in the corporate world.
What are you trying to accomplish?
I guess I am just...
Don't quit, Kazuki.
Don't quit!
You aren't trash.
Dad!
You found your own path, all by yourself.
I never saw you take anything seriously until I saw you on the field.
That's all I ever wanted from you.
I don't care if you're scared, or even if you mess up... So...
So please...
...don't quit!
Dad...
Don't make me laugh.
I haven't wasted my 16 years on this planet.
I just got a little sloppy for a minute, that's all!
I'm won't run away again!
Looks like you're finally back, Jumonji.
Took you long enough, Kazu.
The Three Ha-Ha Brothers are revived to the max!
- We're not even related!
Sorry I had you worried, Sena.
But I'll be all right now!
Okay!
Can Deimon crack Ojo's formidable defense?
It all depends on their lines.
Set...
"Prison Chain..." you're not the only one who's got friends counting on him!
Hut!
Get ready!
Come on, Kazuki!
I'll show you!
I'll tell you what I tell everybody else:
I DON'T LET ANYONE THROW ME AROUND!
I-Ikari-
He tackled him!
Jumonji...
Sena...
Jumonji!
Holy cow!
Deimon's MVP, Eyeshield 21, rushes through the hole where Ikari once stood!
He's headed right for the end zone!
I won't let you through!
Eyeshield 21-
Was a decoy?!
Too late.
Ya-ha!
No one's there!
All right, leave it to me!
No one out-catches me!
Max Catch!
Complete! Deimon gets the first down!
Yes!
You're pretty good, Deimon lineman.
You, too.
Okay, let's keep it going!
- Yeah!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Nice job, Monta! Let's see another Max Catch!
Now that Sakuraba's on the field, it's time for the real fight!
I don't care if his legs are longer or if he's taller I'll catch it and-
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Knight who Controls the Skies!
Ya-ha!
Max Catch!
Complete! Deimon gets the first down!
Of course...
Taro Raimon...
Takami, let me-
Calm down, Sakuraba. The game's barely begun.
Monta...
Get out here, Sakuraba...
We'll find out who the number one receiver really is!