Huh?
What... is this?
Oh, that! It's Rice Man.
Rice Man?
Yeah. He's named for Jerry Rice,
a super receiver who holds the record for most successful catches in the NFL.
We made it back when it was just Hiruma and me,
since we didn't have anyone for him to practice with.
Now that we've got a receiver...
Me?
I don't need Rice Man anymore!
Ya! HA!
Really, Hiruma's probably the happiest person here to have you join us, Monta.
Huh?
Hiruma's the quarterback, so he's in the throwing position.
Even though he's practiced a lot, he's never had a chance to show it off!
Ya-ha!
Wow, nice catch, Rice Man!
Hiruma...
Huh?
It'd be nice if we got some more friends soon, wouldn't it?
"It'd be nice," my butt!
We'll get more!
Hey guys, come crush Rice Man!
Don't drag them into this!
Sena, what should we do?
Mamori will get mad, so...
...I'll give her a really good apology later!
Yep!
Sena!
It's so nice to have more friends.
From now on we'll work hard together!
And then someday, I'll catch up to Shin!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Oath Under the Setting Sun.
One, two... Ack! Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Hey, are you okay?
I'm okay! I can handle it!
But boy do I ever get thirsty when I'm out there practicing.
Almost there!
You're pumped up!
That'll be 2,880 yen.
'Kay!
Huh?!
"Ojo's era is already passed."
"Shin hasn't improved his running at all."
7 to 6, huh? It's a close game.
But isn't Ojo the team that beat us to a pulp?
Are they the type of team that would struggle after three games?
No, they're not supposed to be that way.
There's no way Shin would... There's no way!
What's the deal? You're getting in people's way just squatting there like that!
What's it to ya?!
He looks scary!
I-It's Zokugaku! Crap!
S-Sena, let's go already!
Y-Yeah...
I-It's long!
What's this?
Shin's finished if he's having a tough time against the Sankaku Punks.
But hey, now it's time for the great Rui Habashira from the Zokugaku Chameleons
to be the most powerful linebacker!
Ya-hoo!
N-No way! Shin's...
Huh? You got a problem?
Stupid! Sena, come on!
Those guys were students from Zokugaku!
They're quick to threaten and blackmail people. They're full of bad rumors.
You need to be more careful!
Yeah, but it looked like that one guy also plays football.
Yeah, come to think of it. He mentioned something about a linebacker, I think.
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Was it heavy?
Hurry up and sit down! I'm going to explain practice games to you.
Practice games!
S-So who're we up against?
The Zokugaku Chameleons!
No way!
It's the linebacker from earlier whose hand could stretch out real far!
Blinders!
Punch!
Kick!
In other words, they're like dirty players on parade. They'll do anything.
How horrible! There's no need to do such horrible things while playing a practice game!
But you see, they're pretty formidable.
"Zokugaku Chameleons instantly jumped up in ability
when their ace linebacker, Rui Habashira, joined the team."
"His main characteristic is his long arms.
He has a long reach that can grab just about anything moving.
It's an ability that even Shin lacks."
He's greater than Shin? Is it really true?
But Eyeshield 21 could beat him at running anytime.
Yeah!
Even though you're saying I could win, I only managed to get past Shin once.
Aren't we in the middle of the spring tournament?
For them to be playing against us, they've gotta be a weak team that lost the preliminaries, right?
Um, that's not quite right.
What'd you say?! Huh?!
It says they lost their qualifications for this spring
and are being looked at as the dark horse for the fall tournament.
He was really scary!
H-He's lucky all they did was take their qualification away.
They're really long!
He's like Shin... Or is his even longer than Shin's?
No way...!
Let's get started on practice!
Gather everyone up!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
10!
Sena!
Ow, ow, ow!
Are you okay?!
Hey, quit goofing off!
You've gotta be sure to strengthen up your neck or else you'll get trashed at the game!
That's got nothing to do with Sena!
Well, since it's all set up I thought I'd do some muscle training with everyone...
Seriously! It's nice that you're trying your best, but don't over do it, okay?
Are you okay? Does it hurt anywhere?
Ow! Ouchie-ow-ow! It hurts here and there and everywhere!
Huh?
It hurts so bad! But I'm sure that I'll get better if Mamori gently strokes me...
I'll massage you!
No, no, I don't-!
See?
Putting that aside, has everyone shown up?
Well, I can't find Ishimaru anywhere.
Huh? Is he on the athletic field?
Nuh-uh. I didn't see him in his classroom or on the athletic field.
Um... I've been here from the start.
I've been with you ever since you started watching the video in our room.
You were there?!
No charisma!
Being told you lack charisma's not a compliment in football.
Sure isn't. You want to show off in front of everyone at the practice game.
Well, of course!
It's our lunch music time!
Now then, today's music will be...
Hiru...ma?!
YA-HA!
I've got some explosively big news!
We're having a football game this Saturday here at school!
Stop him!
Naturally, the Homicide Tackle-using Devil's hero, Eyeshield 21 will be there!
You're not a man if you don't come!
Really!
It's against Zokugaku!
Will they really crush them?
It'd be sweet if we won!
N-Now there's no way we can lose!
Y-Yeah...
But HE'LL be there...
Awesome!
Huh? What's awesome?
I'm sorry!
Who's the most impressive?
Hashibara, of course!
Listen up! It doesn't matter how fast that Eyeshield is, 'cause they don't have a prayer!
We'll crush them!
Football Clinic!
What is Sena's rival, Shin's, position?
He's the linebacker!
It's the position where you get to tackle the opponent holding the ball.
You've got to be both strong and fast! Ya-ha!
Hey!
Morning! Our practice game's tomorrow!
Yeah.
What is it?
A message from Eyeshield 21?
It's tomorrow, so don't miss it! Zokugaku Chameleons VS Deimon Devil Bats
"We're bringin' those Zokugaku losers down!"
"Come see my awesomeness as Eyeshield 21! Ya-ha!"
How did he do that?!
So, is this how you grab the ball?
Isn't it like this?
No, no! Just use your thumbs!
And then to the side right near your neck... and down!
Back then?!
Now they've done it!
But Zokugaku isn't going to stay quiet when they see this.
I bet some blood's gonna be shed over this!
B-Blood shed?! What should I do?! I'm scared!
I-I-I-It'll be okay!
They're such egomaniacs!
T-They're from...
Go buy me some bread, Sena!
They're going to pick a fight with me again!
What's with them?
Y-Yeah, I wonder what's wrong.
Curse you, Hiruma!
Why do I have to sneak around like a rat?!
If only we could get the negatives from those photos.
Wait a sec! Tomorrow's the game, so no one will be in the football club room.
That could be our chance!
This is the sports shop Hiruma was talking about?
Kiddies, go buy the preparatory protective gear for tomorrow's game!
And we're running!
Is that it?
Yeah, I'm sure it's that sports shop.
Max Dash!
Wait up! Hold on!
I-I see. Shin doesn't know what I really look like...
Eyeshield 21?
Shoot!
Y-Yes?
What's he doing?
Well, whatever. I'll go buy the stuff.
Sweet!
Crap!
That's quite the catch!
Give it back!
Like you can catch up, stupid!
The team funds!
T-That's horrible!
Wait!
Wait up! Stop!
I... can't!
Shin?!
Since they're caught up in the traffic jam by the bridge,
it's not like we couldn't catch up to them with our legs if we tried.
Go at them from the left rear!
We'll sandwich them in!
Okay!
T-They're fast!
Here we go!
Right!
He's fast! It's like he's even faster here than he is out on the field!
I see him! I'm almost there!
What?!
They'll hit!
Leave it to me!
Max jump!
We did it!
Wha-?!
What... are these guys?
You chose your enemies poorly.
Amazing! Shin really is amazing!
T-Thank you very much!
Thanks!
So you found a receiver?
Get everything prepared for the fall tournament.
Ojo will be several times more powerful by then.
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
H-He's so COOL!
That's right...
There's a tournament in the fall.
I can run together with Shin again if we win!
I could run together with Shin, who's stronger than anyone else and still getting stronger!
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
He was WAY cooler.
Then you give it a try!
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
We're back!
You're not even looking!
What's with this bike? It's in the way...
R-Rui Habashira!
So, why'd you call us here?
I'm Eyeshield 21!
What's he doing?!
And tomorrow I'm bringin' you vermin to society down, so look forward to it!
Eyeshield 21, you jerk! I'm gonna pound your face in!
Oh, so you still think you'll win?
Whichever side loses will become gophers and have to do ANYTHING the others say.
Bring it on!
You losers even lost big time to those Ojo losers.
Scary to the max!
D-Don't! We gotta leave before they find us!
So Ojo are losers, huh?
Of course! I, Rui Habashira, am currently the best linebacker!
What's this?
Shin?
He's trash.
Sena?
Move it, shrimp!
Sena, what are you doing?!
Shin... is the strongest!
HUH?!
Shin is definitely the strongest!
I'll see him at the finals!
He won't lose to anyone!
You say something? Say it again!
H-His arms are really long!
Stop it!
A chick's protecting you!
He won't lose? And what could a cowardly shrimp like you do?
There's just no way... that he could possibly be stronger than Shin!
Gotta problem?
Sena?
I may be weak, but I'm not the one who'll be fighting you.
So you're relying on others! So who'll fight me? Spit it out!
Eyeshield 21!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
Yeah!
Just because he threatened you some,
doesn't mean you and Monta should be terrified of the Zokugaku Chameleons' Rui Habashira!
But they're scary!
Hey, hey! You gonna be okay?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Max Catch! Ya-ha!
Why do we have to be the ones doing this?!
He'll go nuts otherwise.
We'll get it done by tomorrow!
We're hurrying!