Please... I don't wanna lose.
Not here... Not now...
But in two seconds...it's all...
It's all gonna end!
With a final score of 35-28,
Deimon vs. Shinryuji is over...
Time is up!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
A Huddle with no Answers.
No way... time's up...
Just one more touchdown...
We would've tied it...
Man...
Are we really out of time?
We still had four seconds when Mon-Mon got tackled...
Why didn't the clock stop?
They would have if Monta had been knocked out of bounds.
But Agon made sure that didn't happen.
He managed to tackle him in bounds so the clock would run out!
That fat lump of garbage sealed the deal, too.
You couldn't waddle your stupid,
giant butt of yours to the line fast enough.
Guaranteed time up.
And poof! Your dream is dead, scumbags.
This year's our last shot at going to the Christmas Bowl.
It's over.
It's all over...
They put up an amazing performance
and overcame many strong opponents,
and came within an inch of another victory, but in the end,
the miracle they needed never happened.
We never asked for a miracle.
We just needed to win this game.
I can't believe it's over...
A miracle...?
I got sick of waiting for miracles.
Monta?
You gotta MAKE the miracle happen.
Timekeeper, turn back the clock!
That divot...
Out of bounds!
The receiver was already out of bounds when he was tackled,
the clock stopped when he went out!
It's not over, Max Catch!
The time for catching's over, chump!
You couldn't have...
What do I always say?
No one outdoes me when it comes to catching!
You... You're the man, Butt-Monkey.
He was out of bounds!
Monta's hand went over the sideline before he was tackled!
R-Riko...
Four seconds will be put back on the clock!
- MONTA!
The Deimon Devil Bats survive by the skin of their teeth!
This game's not over yet!
Our dreams of the Christmas Bowl... aren't dead...
That stinkin' monkey scum ball!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
We were dead and gone,
but this crazy Butt-Monkey just brought us back to life
and set the stadium on fire - this is our chance.
For our last play, we'll use the crowd.
- The CROWD?
20 yards in one play... It's going to be rough.
They're up against a wall.
And the game resumes!
Was he really serious?
I mean, I always knew he was a demon...
Is his heart completely black?
A trick play's only a trick if you use it when no one thinks you will.
This one play is really our last chance.
What a crazy plan but...
I trust Hiruma!
Listen up, you drooling football zombies!
We need your support if we're gonna win this!
Cheer until your throats fall apart!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
More! I can't hear you!
Come on, that's pathetic!
Look at the guy next to you and blow out his eardrums!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Wh...
What's he doing?
Now we're talking!
Devil Bats, Devil Bats!
C'mon, Kakei!
Right...
Devil Bats, Devil Bats...
Can't hear ya, brah!
Devil Bats, Devil Bats!
Otawara... he didn't ask for drums.
More!
We need more!
Hiruma is working the crowd into a frenzy
before the Deimon Devil Bats run their final play!
I can't hear you! Louder!
I hate you, Hiruma...
You always pull these flashy, crazy stunts...
It's so dumb it makes me wanna puke!
Don't let it bother you, Agon.
They're just another team getting trampled by Shinryuji,
they could have the crowd doing uber-cheers
and it wouldn't faze any of us.
Come on, that's not enough!
Don't bother.
Time for the cheerleaders!
Make some noise, everyone!
More, more!
Louder, louder!
Louder!
Th-The center completely forgot about Hiruma
and snapped directly to Sena!
Hiruma's cheerleading the crowd...
He was the man in motion for the play!
Just like when they ignored Agon...
Except this time his team ignored HIM!
Go, Sena!
We have to win, I don't care what happens to my legs, I'll run!
Shinryuji's already on him!
Even after we surprised them!
Two trick plays using the man in motion in a row?
It might've been surprising before, but...
...we don't fall for the same trick twice, scum!
It's a pass, they knew how fast Shinryuji would react!
Who?! All of Deimon's receivers are covered!
Raimon, Taki, Yukimitsu...
And it's Hiruma who makes the catch!
Don't miss the second half!
Eyeshield 21!
It's Hiruma vs. Agon!
Agon Kongo... how much better can he get...?
Make it to the goal, Hiruma!
I already know how fast you are, trash boy.
You run the 40 in 5.2 seconds.
I'm just close enough to take you down!
How old is your info, Mop-Head?
My best these days is 5.1.
It took me a whole year to shave that tenth of a second off,
but while you were skipping practice at Shinryuji,
I never missed a day.
Touchdown!
No time left!
The Deimon Devil Bats makes an incredible comeback touchdown,
scored by none other than their leader, Yoichi Hiruma!
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 34
Just one point to go...
That means...
Once Musashi makes the extra point...
We'll be tied!
- Yeah!
- All right!
He even used the crowd as players...
We're right on the brink, losers!
Woo-hoo!
Time to turn the tables!
Let's win this!
We still have to survive the overtime.
Don't celebrate yet.
Over...time?
Sena! Your legs are-
I'm fine.
I can still run, don't worry.
Enough. Your legs won't last through overtime.
We can't win in overtime without the Peewee.
Mop-Head will never run out of energy.
But we don't have to settle for a one-point kick.
We can get two with another touchdown!
Yeah, that's our only shot!
We need to take the chance,
try for a two-point conversion and win it all!
They're just like every other team.
They finally get within reach of Shinryuji,
then try to force their way to two points.
When we've practiced the counter-play for that a billion times.
I-I've just come across an amazing stat!
The Shinryuji Nagas
haven't allowed a single two-point conversion this season!
Agon's superhuman reflexes and Ikkyu's aerial prowess.
The Devil Bat Dive won't work against them.
Do we go to overtime or try to win?
Both paths take us straight through hell.
It all comes down to what you guys want to do.
"Do we go to overtime or try to win?"
Which are we supposed to pick?
There's no right answer.
Either way, our chances of winning are almost 0%.
But we've still gotta pick one.
If it's all the same, we should just go with our gut, right?
I say we go for it!
I don't back down from a fight!
You said it, Jumonji.
I say we go for it, too!
Me too!
I wanna play overtime...
Are you serious, Kurita?
Well... I wanna keep playing football with you guys,
even if it's only for a few more minutes.
After so many years of looking forward to attending Shinryuji,
I was crushed when I didn't get in.
But now...
I wouldn't trade my time playing football with you guys for anything in the world!
That's why...
I wanna keep going, into overtime, even if it's only for a little bit.
I don't care if we lose in overtime!
I do!
I wanna play more games with everyone!
Komusubi...
He's just as scared of it all ending as the rest of us.
You're just trying to make yourself feel better.
You DO care if we win or lose, don't you, Kurita?!
Well, I think...
Shinryuji's says they'll do whatever it takes to win,
but if you look at it from another perspective, that means...
...they'll do whatever it takes to keep things as they are now.
All right, then!
If it comes down to gambling or playing it safe,
the Shinryuji Nagas will pick the latter!
Then the Deimon Devil Bats will take the gamble!
Guys...
You're the last one, Eyeshield 21.
Do we go into overtime, or try to win it all?
I say...
The Deimon Devil Bats play it by the book and set up for a kick!
Set...
Hut!
Musashi prepares to kick the tying point for the Devil Bats!
Hiruma... I didn't think for one second
that you'd try a regular extra point kick.
Here comes Hiruma.
They're forgetting about overtime and trying to win the game right here!
No! Instead of kicking,
Musashi continues dashing forward with Hiruma towards Kurita!
They're trying to break open Shinryuji's line!
Hiruma, Musashi, Kurita!
The three original Devil Bats
are trying to blast their way up the center!
But they don't budge!
Shinryuji has set up an impenetrable wall!
Open up a path for Hiruma!
It doesn't matter...
...if we get destroyed!
Push, you weaklings!
They've stopped! The Shinryuji line holds!
Crap...
Just one more step... they stopped us...
Even though we bet...
...the last of our strength...
...on this final gamble!
What?!
Soar past 'em all with the Devil Bat Skydive!
You're kidding me,
he's going to make a midair catch
while flying like a speeding bullet?!
I just said it's our final gamble using the last of our strength!
I don't care if it sounds crazy, I'll catch it!
Agon! Ikkyu!
The ball!
You're finished, you Deimon scum!
My center of gravity's getting messed up... from the side?!
He may not have any speed,
but on the other hand,
YOU can't move him either!
This is impossible! It's four on one!
Kuri...ta!
Show them!
Show them what Shinryuji gave up!
Show them the power you've got instead of speed!
Ryokan Kurita and his 160kg bench press!
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 34
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 36
Deimon...
...touchdown!
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
- The Deimon Devil Bats
- make a huge huge HUGE comeback!
We won... We beat THE Shinryuji!
Their era is over!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Post-Battle!
Ya-ha!
This incredible clash lasted two and a half hours...
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 36
The final score is 36-35.
The Deimon Devil Bats have unseated the football gods of Kanto!
YA!
HA!