Second round's coming.
This is our "Anti-Yuhi Guts" planning session!
Umm...
Why are we doing this out here?
The sunset's so pretty...
Effort, fortitude, will!
Fight!
Huh?
Effort, fortitude, will!
Fight!
Hey, look!
Effort, fortitude, will!
Fight!
In this day an age...
Sumo fundoshi?
She's...
Satake, did you see something?
Amazing...
She's wearing bloomers...
That high school must be Shangri-La...
The key man is the guy up front.
Key man?
I can't hear you!
Fight!
Effort, fortitude, will!
Come on!
Fight!
- Effort, fortitude, will!
- Fight! Fight!
The Yuhi Guts...
Effort, fortitude, will!
Our second-round opponents.
Once more!
Effort, fortitude, will!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
They're on fire! The Guts!
Come on, Yuhi Guts!
Effort, fortitude, will!
Fight!
We play them in the second round?
Running a marathon on the beach, huh?
They're really jazzed up... Such are the passions of youth.
That's gotta be murder on their feet.
How tough are the Yuhi Guts?
American Football Monthly gave them a "D" rank...
From a purely objective standpoint, Deimon has a 99% chance of winning.
That's great!
Our first opponent that's ranked below us.
We're a lock to win!
And a 1% chance of losing.
They've been playing football for three years.
Your fundamentals are every bit as good as theirs,
but three years of experience makes for a big gap.
Don't stop!
Get up, you two! We're almost done!
No more... I'm done!
Please... just leave us behind.
Have you two already forgotten...
...about our dream to play in the Christmas Bowl?!
Of course not!
But all we ever do is lag behind, and-
The two of us should just stay on the bench...
How can you say that?
We've ALL made it this far through hard work and effort!
- Captain!
We're only the Yuhi Guts when all of us stand together!
NO ONE on this team belongs on the bench!
- Captain!
We're sorry!
We were wrong!
If you mean that...
Get up!
Effort!
Fortitude!
Will!
Come on!
We go to the Christmas Bowl together!
Yes!
So... passionate.
You all...
Those uniforms... You're from Deimon!
Err, we just happened to-
We're not here to spy or anything!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
Captain of the Yuhi Guts, Atsumi.
We're honored to be facing the Deimon Devil Bats,
especially with all the publicity you've gotten!
Let's have a good, clean match and leave it all out on the gridiron!
R-Right...
Yuhi!
Guts!
Effort!
Yeah!
Fortitude!
Amazing... They've kept up that energy for three years?
But if they're seniors, this is their last shot.
That's right... This is their final chance...
There's so many people!
Well, it's the first set of second-round games.
I guess Ojo's the main attraction, huh?
Yup.
The Sankaku Punks only lost to Ojo by one point during the spring tournament.
Will Ojo stay ahead of the curve,
or will the Sankaku Punks push them aside?
This is today's main event!
Everyone's focused on Ojo.
The Seibu Wild Gunmen.
Atsumi?
You're here too, huh?
Sorry boys, but Yuhi's going all the way and facing Ojo in the finals!
Right, men?
Yeah!
The game is about to begin!
Ojo! Ojo! Ojo!
The Devil Bat Ghost didn't work on Shin at all.
How much have the Ojo White Knights grown?
Haven't seen you since the spring tourney.
Let's have a good game.
Indeed.
I still have doubts about that one-point game.
I'm convinced the refs were favoring Ojo.
The referees are always impartial!
Regardless, my team is thirsty for revenge.
I'd advise you not to assume they're the same players they were in the spring.
- The Punks...
- ...are freaky!
Hey, Sakuraba, your fan section...
...really seems to have shrunk.
Yay, Sakuraba!
Jari Productions' Sakuraba.
Ojo's foolish to be playing a worthless receiver like him.
That's one less player our secondary needs to cover!
I feel like I let all my fans down by quitting Jari Productions so suddenly.
But I'll make it up to the ones who stuck with me
by succeeding on the field!
Sakuraba!
Hooray, hooray, Sakuraba!
Torakichi?
That buzz cut made you a hero to kids, huh?
Sakuraba...
His build is completely different from the spring.
We can't be not the only ones.
I'm sure Ojo went through some incredible training over the summer.
Shin...
Here we go.
Ojo, Ojo!
Punks, Punks, Punks!
Set, hut!
Wow!
Their pass defense is solid!
Sakuraba's triple-teamed.
But...
So high!
Did he miss?
Where're you throwing, Takami?
I thought your aim was your one redeeming quality?
You buzzed your hair, Sakuraba?
You seem completely different now.
He does?
Right, you notice people's muscles, not their faces...
By the way...
What did you mean by new attitude?
Takami.
I want to change our usual training regimen, including pass practice!
Why's it so high?
The balls too high, he'll never catch it!
Yay! Football Clinic!
How many minutes is a game?
You still don't know?!
One game is 60 minutes, broken up into four 15-minute quarters.
Remember it! Ya-ha!
Sakuraba?!
Rats, he's too high!
Sakuraba is still the coolest, the COOLEST!
Th-That pass...
I'd never have gotten my hands on that, it was too high.
Sakuraba's unbelievable.
Keep watching.
The NEW Haruto Sakuraba's gonna strut his stuff!
I see you're as snotty as ever.
Set, hut!
Sakuraba makes another dash up the center!
Man, I knew he was going there, but-
Here it comes, block it!
Another catch!
Takami's using his formidable height to create a tall launching pad,
and combined with Sakuraba's long limbs,
targets an extremely high point downfield!
This is, without a doubt, the highest pass in Japan! Mt. Fuji level!
We KNOW he's passing there, but...
...we can't even get a hand on it!
Sankaku Punks 0 - Ojo White Knights 6
Touchdown!
Ojo scores first, and takes a six point lead!
- Takami!
- Way to go, Sakuraba!
Sakuraba...
This is only the beginning.
Yes.
They scored first!
All right!
You're cheering for Ojo?
Hmm? They're enemies?
Well, I kinda promised we'd see them at the finals, so...
Plus, you gotta respect how good they are.
That play was carefully planned,
and they invested a lot of effort and fortitude in developing it.
It's the WORLD'S highest pass, higher than Mt. Fuji.
That's the Everest Pass!
Everest Pass?
They're really smart...
To think they turned their height into such an effective weapon...
Did you get all that?
Yes.
I wrote down every last bit of data!
Good.
Atsumi... No, it's not just him.
Everyone's motivated.
What's up, Sena?
The Yuhi Guts are so driven...
And this is their last year...
I'll feel bad for them if the lose.
Sena, what're you-
Shin, Shin, Shin, Shin!
Shin!
Set, hut!
He breaks through!
A brutal Spear Tackle forces a fumble and Ojo recovers!
Wow...
Whoa! That's the real Ojo!
Hold on tighter, you reject!
No...
I don't wanna run anymore...
Don't give me the ball!
I've experienced it first hand...
But Shin's become faster AND stronger over the summer.
Yeah.
He's certainly a different player than he was in the spring.
His whole tackling style is new.
How much training did he go through?
You mean you did this much research in the spring, too?
Way to go, Guts!
This is it!
THIS is football!
When our common goal is on the line,
and the opponents are rushing in....
That's what I live for!
Sakuraba, Otawara, Takami and Shin... and Atsumi.
Everyone's rushing towards one thing...
...the Christmas Bowl!
They're here to fight!
Pity and mercy are...
And a 1% chance of losing.
We've only advanced one round.
If the Yuhi Guts seize that 1% chance,
our journey will be over!
Glory!
That's the game!
The Ojo White Knights dominate!
The mighty kingdom has been fully revived!
Atsumi.
We won't hold back.
We'll take down the Yuhi Guts with everything we've got!
S-Sena?!
Sena did a 180!
We'll be ready!
Yuhi!
Guts!
Effort, fortitude, will!
Fight!
We'll win... by playing our hardest!
Yeah!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
What?! The Yuhi Guts' first stringers are-
They replaced them with guys from the baseball, soccer, and other sports teams!
Take those ringers to the cleaners!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Battle of Effort, Fortitude, and Will! Ya-ha!
The guys up in the ivory tower told me we HAVE to win this year.
In my opinion, this is the only way the Yuhi Guts can beat Deimon.
Effort, fortitude, will!
Fight!
- Effort, fortitude, will!
- I can't hear you!
- Fight!
Please understand, Atsumi.
Sir.
Is he really not going to play us, Captain?
Captain?
Why...
Why?!