I wonder if Sena's all ready to go.
You can go to school by yourself from now on.
It's not like you're a little kid anymore.
Well, I'm off!
Take care!
Wait up!
I'm going, too!
Come to think of it,
Mamori never came by today...
I think she went to school early today.
Well, later!
Take care!
How's school going?
Okay. It's fun!
That's good.
Well, I'm turning here.
Right... Later!
Dad!
Huh?
Thanks for cheering me on.
You sure have grown up!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Deimon's Half-time Show!
So I've just gotta get a ticket to the Christmas Bowl this year!
So that's what you want for Christmas this year, right?
Er-
Grand Palace Deimon
Your college entrance exam's next year, isn't it, Manabu?
Yep.
Were you up late last night studying?
What a doll!
It's imperative that focus on your studies now.
Make sure you don't get yourself caught up in any of that club nonsense!
I-I know!
T-T-T-There's no way I'd join a club!
I know!
Please...
Please help us win the Kanto Tournament
so we can go to the Christmas Bowl!
Hmm... So he's finally becoming somewhat religious...
To the Christmas Bowl!!
W-What the-?!
For sure!
What?!
You're going to make it to the Christmas Bowl for sure?
Dream!
What?!
All because that's your master's dream?!
I'm so proud!
Your master's dream... is also your dream.
Never lose sight of that determination!
Very good. I'm proud of you, my boy!
- Give it your all!
- I'm amazed you can understand him...
You've gotta win!
Man, I'm tired!
Hey, Teach!
What gives?! We haven't done anything bad!
So what gives?!
You guys did great.
C'mon! Come in, come in!
Congratulations on making it to the Kanto Tournament, Devil Bats!!
Congratulations on making it to the Kanto Tournament!
Jumonji!
What's with all this?
Everyone was already partying like this when I got to school.
We're really popular now!
I'm a big fan of yours!
Please have some of this!
Huh?
Try some of mine, too!
And mine!
Don't forget to eat mine!
I'm so jealous, Kazu!
You've got some new fans, Kazu!
Please try some of this!
This was made with love!
- I-It's for us?
- Mine, too!
Well, I guess that means everyone's
finally realized how cool and awesome we are!
Please try some of this!
- Them, too?!
My, you've done so well.
I bet a lot of students will want to enter our school next year!
It's all thanks to the football team!
Then you should give us some sorta reward!
It's tough when you're famous 'cause ya stand out so much!
Doesn't that girl look just like Ishimaru?
Huh?
And he's the spitting image of Ishimaru!
He looks like Ishimaru, too!
They're all Ishimarus!
You forgot to bring your lunch, bro!
Bro, you forgot your textbooks!
Your shoes!
Your book bag!
Thanks! Thanks!
And so the Meiji Era was a very dramatic time period.
I'm so tired from practice...
And this is when Ryoma Sakamoto takes the scene!
Hey, Yukimitsu!
Explain to everyone how Ryoma fought for the Meiji Restoration!
First down!
Ojo White Knights in "The Men on Different Levels"
Sweet! I swam a whole kilo!
How many kilos is Shin at?
Huh? Do you mean kilometers or...
...do you mean kilograms?
Second down!
The Deimon Devil Bats in "Artistic Souls"
Today we're going to use a model for our sketches.
He has a really nice body!
Deimon! Deimon!
I love you, too!
Third down!
The Deimon Devil Bats in "Artistic Souls, Part 2"
Ack! K-Kurita?!
Quit drooling over that picture!
But ya know, Sena's gotten pretty tough.
He's nothing like the gopher he used to be!
Oh, c'mon!
Let's see, we're on page 21 today.
Whoops! I forgot to bring my map.
Hey, Sena,
could you run to the teacher's office and grab the world map?
Okay.
I don't have a globe, either.
Sena!
Okay!
I don't have any more chalk
- and I forgot my transparencies.
- And yet he's still a gopher.
Must be a genetic thing or somethin'.
Okey-dokey!
Let's work hard to the max at today's practice
Hey, hey, Mamo, what's your favorite type?!
What? Mamori's type...
Let's see... I like them white...
She like them white...
With fluffy hair...
And short legs.
Sweet! I've got that one down!
And I really love it when they cry.
When they cry? Got it!
Okay! One-two, one-two!
Then this cat is perfect for you!
Yeah, that's it! It's a white Persian!
W-What?!
Wig.
Fourth down!
Zokugaku Chameleons' "The Way of Bikers is the Way of Naughtiness!"
Oh, it's Habashira from Zokugaku!
Hey! It's their demonic leader!
Wow! That bike's way powerful!
I want one of those babies!
Hm?
You want a bike like Zokugaku's infamous Habashira's?!
Don't flatter yourselves!
Hey, hey, hey!
He's happy because they complemented his bike.
Men are so weird...
In short,
recent theories state that modern Japanese society
That's enough.
is based off of the Meiji Restoration being a people's
You've said plenty, Yukimitsu...
movement as well as a movement against totalitarianism-
You jerk....
We coulda won the Tokyo Tournament
so much more easily if you'd come back sooner.
Now you're gonna pay, ya old fart!
Okay. So why're we at a barber?
"You're gonna pay with your head!"
is what I'd like to say, but...
What type of haircut would you like?
Something to strike fear into our enemies.
Huh?
You've already got a rough-looking face,
so all that's left is a scary haircut to strike fear
into the hearts of our foes!
Leave it to me!
M-Musashi!
Yeah! This is kinda nice!
Well, I guess it's the best one we've seen so far.
I don't look like a high schooler.
You never did.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us about Yocchie's position as quarterback!
The hint is to make good passes!
The key is to make sure that you have
good control over the ball so that you
can make precise throws under various circumstances.
The ball should go where you aimed!
Ya-ha!
Ramen Gyouza TONTON Special Jumbo Gyouza If you can eat a whole one, you'll win ?10,000.
Hey, gramps, you sure about this?
You bet! You just have to eat it all!
Fair enough!
This should be...
...easy for us!
Sorry for the wait!
Start!
All done...
You gotta be kidding me!
C'mon!
Fifth down!
Ojo White Knights in "Extreme Training!"
You don't have to have the newest
equipment out there to enjoy effective training.
For example...
The train during rush hour makes for a perfect training field!
What's he doing?
We're in a train...
Just what I'd expect from Shin!
But, Shin,
you really shouldn't ride the train with your shirt off.
And you should make sure you're always wearing pants!
Who cares about little details like that?!
Sixth down!
Deimon Devil Bats in "Rush Hour!"
Let me on!
Oh, I'm sorry! It's all my fault.
I'll push you all back in.
Sorry, but we'd like to get going...
I'm sorry!
Seventh down!
Deimon Devil Bats in "Best Subjects!"
Sena, let's split our homework!
You do your best subjects and I'll do mine!
What? Isn't that like cheating?
Oof!
Sena, which ones are you gonna do?
Let's see, my best subjects, right?
Geography
Best subjects...best subjects...
Japanese
Physics
Math
Best subjects... Best subjects...
English
Chemistry
Best...
...subjects...
- There aren't any!
Eight down!
The Demon Devil Bats' "Cream Puff Hunter Mamori!"
Welcome!
Hi, I'd like four cream puffs...
S-She's cute!
T-Today we've got a 10% discount if you buy ten of them!
Oh, but I couldn't eat that many!
Can I pick them out myself?
Sure, sure!
Thank you!
Which ones should I take...?
Which one...?
There!
H-Her eyes changed!
This one's 5 grams heavier than the others!
Ninth down!
The Bando Spiders' "Smart Man!"
Most impressive.
I could never do that.
How smart...
...or not.
Hey!
Huh? You say something?
Oh, this is the newest model!
Oh, congratulations on making it to the Kanto Tournament.
Thank you very much.
But you know,
I never realized that you were the Lightspeed Eyeshield 21.
Sorry to burst your bubble.
Yes, yes, I'm coming!
Hello. This is Kimidori Sports.
Huh? The wrong items got delivered?!
I'm so sorry about that!
Right, I'll mail over a new shipment right away.
Huh? You're in a hurry?
You want them right now?
I-I'm sorry, but I can't...
Okay. I'll have my lightspeed dasher send them on over.
Kimidori Sports, here to deliver your order!
Oh, thank you.
I-It looks like I made it in time.
Ya-ha!
Hiruma?!
Listen up, Devil Bats!
We're undergoing special training tonight!
It starts at 8:00 P.M.!
We'll meet up at
Deimon Distribution's central building
on the roof!
Huh?
Don't be late!
Anyone late won't live to regret it!
Got that?!
Ya-ha!
J-Just what is Hiruma plotting this time?
Mamo, is this really the right place?
This is definitely the place Hiruma said...
I wonder what type of training we're going to do up on the roof?
I've got a bad feeling about this...
No one's here...
What gives?! He can be such a bossy jerk...
That's awesome to the max!
Don't get too excited! Look there!
- Hiruma!
Hiruma's in a helicopter...
I'm starting to feel sick.
Where do you think you're going, Peewee?!
Your training's already started!
I-It's already started?
- Where are we training?!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
What this?! What's this?! WHAT'S THIS?!
Where on earth is he taking you this time?!
In order to prepare for the Kanto Tournament...
...we're undergoing special training...
...in AMERICA?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Let it begin! The Cream Puff Cup!
Ya-ha!
Tenth down!
The Ojo White Knights' "Ultimate Decision!"
Mineral Water, Sports Drink, Orange Juice.
Geez, which one should I drink?
Should I hydrate myself with natural water?
But a sports drink will give me an energy boost.
Oh man, Shin!
I keep telling you to be more gentle with machines!
The Captain of the Ojo White Knights is saying
that you should be more gentle with machines!
But putting that aside, Otawara...
Put on some pants already!
Quit worrying about the small stuff!