First we make it to the Kanto Tournament,
then we MAX won the Cream Puff Cup!
We're really on a hot streak, aren't we?
Let's ride this wave
all the way through the Kanto Tournament!
The Kanto Tournament?
Think bigger.
Way bigger.
The Christmas Bowl-
Too!
Don't get to excited,
or a certain someone will drag you back to earth.
Nah...
Ya-ha!
H-Hiruma?
- Why's he on TV?
The Deimon Devil Bats have one last training
to undergo before the Kanto Tournament.
The "Death Game."
- Death Game?!
W-What is it this time?!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
"Farewell, Onihei!"
First the Death March,
then the Death Climb,
and now your special training for the Kanto Tournament is
the Death Game?
What does that entail, exactly?
The alternate name is the Five-Game Gauntlet.
Scrimmages against other schools to get us prepared.
Just scrimmages?
But if we lose even one game,
the Deimon Devil Bats
will drop out of the Kanto Tournament!
Is he for real?
You bet I am!
- Hiruma!
- Yocchie!
Don't get cocky
just because we won the Cream Puff Cup.
The Kanto Tournament's not nearly as easy as you're thinking!
But forfeiting if we even lose once?
That's a bit much.
The final stats for the season
were one loss apiece for Ojo and Seibu,
and none at all for Shinryuji.
On the other hand, our team...
Tell 'em, Manajerk.
Hiruma, I swear, if you call me that one more time...!
Uhh...
We lost our second game in the spring season...
The Ojo White Knights beat us 68-12.
The American Football Monthly game against the NASA Aliens,
we lost 33-32.
And in the fall,
we lost to the Seibu Wild Gunmen 44-42.
We haven't beaten one team at Ojo's or Seibu's level.
The Kanto Tournament is single-elimination.
If we can't even beat all our practice opponents,
we won't stand a chance in the Kanto Tournament!
Dropping out if we lose just one game...
I wish Yocchie hadn't broadcast that on TV...
Yeah, you can't just take back an announcement like that.
It just shows how serious Hiruma is.
He's cornered us in the hope
that it'll make us rise to the occasion.
Hiruma isn't playing around!
All right.
Death Game, Gauntlet, whatever it's called,
we just gotta win!
Yeah, let's all do our best!
Our best!
- Whoo!
Death Game...
Yeah, I've gotta give it my all!
Hey, Kurita!
Kurita!
Hiya, mister,
the kid here will have some oden,
and I'll be having sake.
Sure! What can I do you for?
Let's see...
Daikon, kelp, egg, fish paste, tentacles,
fried goose, beef, sweet potato, and...
...konjak!
You're gonna eat all that?!
Talk about a growing boy.
Yeah, ten orders of that!
What, are you trying to put him out of business?
You can have some of mine, Kurita.
O-Onihei!
Atta boy, Shoji...
That's why we're the Swords of Japan...
How 'bout some sake, pal?
Sorry, gents, I'm sold out for the night.
What?! You're quitting football?!
Yeah, I'm going right into the workforce
instead of attending college.
This will be my last year.
But... I mean, there's a league for working professionals...
It's not that simple.
I'd be lying if I said I don't regret
not making it to the Christmas Bowl...
But I won't feel as bad knowing that my lineman's spirit
lives on in you and your teammates.
My check, please.
Good luck in the Kanto Tournament.
I'll be rooting for you.
Onihei...
Good work, everyone!
Hey, Sena,
you know who our first Death Game opponent is?
It's just a practice match for the Kanto Tournament,
they probably won't be that tough.
Then it's gotta be the Ojo White Kn-
One of our opponents wouldn't agree
to practice against us!
Well, Kurita?
Who do you think it'll be?
It's Hiruma's choice, there's really no telling.
But...
If it were up to me, I know who I'd play.
There's a team you want to play?
Quit flapping your gums and get back to practice!
- Okay!
What'd you want to talk about, Musashi?
Kurita, is the team you want to play
the Hashiratani Deer?
Or rather, Onihei?
You want to play him one more time, don't you?
Back in middle school, when I first met him,
he taught what football was really all about.
Football's no fun if you're not serious, Kurita!
I prayed that I'd get another chance
to play him in high school...
No!
But the Deer lost in the first round...
Deimon never got a chance to play them.
I wanted to show Onihei how far I've come...
But now...
Onihei's going to quit playing football when he graduates.
So...
The Death Game's my last shot
at playing against Onihei in a real game.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what you need to be a lineman like Kuriton!
The hint is "wall!"
You need to use your body as a wall to protect the QB
so he can throw accurate passes!
Don't give 'em an inch!
Ya-ha!
The first match of the "Death Game" is upon us!
But where's the opposing team?
It looks like the Devil Bats don't know, either!
There!
The... Hashiratani Deer!
Onihei!
The first game will be against the Hashiratani Deer!
This promises to be a good, clean game!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I never thought we'd get to play each other again, Kurita.
Let's make it a good one.
Right!
You planned this, huh?
Planned what?
Hashiratani, huh? No prob.
It's a scrimmage, remember?
Today the old man, Butt-Monkey
and Chinfuzz are riding the pine.
- Huh?!
The pine...?
I don't get to play?
Oh no, no one will get to see my brilliance...
How can this be?
Are you nuts?
Remember what I said!
If we wanna survive in the Kanto Tournament
we've gotta be ready for all kinds of situations!
Now get in position, all of you!
Deer vs. Devil Bats
Ya-ha!
Without a kicker or receiver, we can only run.
I can only run!
Hiruma thinks he's being clever...
Don't let them pass you!
Rip open a path for Eyeshield!
I'll be charging at full strength, Onihei!
Set, hut!
You've grown, Kurita.
But you're not there yet!
Onihei makes the tackle.
He knocked Kurita down so easily...
Onihei's as sharp as ever.
Stopping him will be tough.
Amazing...
Onihei's really good.
What now?
Sena's our only option here.
Yeah, and they know it.
We've gotta do something about Onihei.
Kurita, if you can't handle Onihei,
we'll use you as a decoy.
Huh?
While you distract him,
we'll knock out those other nobodies
and open up a hole for Sena.
Sena, you run through.
Got it!
Sound good?
Y-Yeah...
Deimon lines up again.
I can't wait to see what pattern they'll run next!
Set, hut!
I can handle him.
I'll win this time!
Onihei's-
- Huh?!
He caught us!
Do you know who I am, you brats?!
Onihei makes the tackle again!
Onihei...
Shoot, he figured it out!
Now what, Jumonji?
We'll toast if this keeps up.
No...
I'm going to have to beat Onihei myself.
I'll do it.
I can stop Onihei!
Onihei's last battle will be with ME!
Nuts, Kurita's getting owned over and over.
How can this be?
Is this part of your plan, Hiruma?
Crap!
I can't... I can't believe this...
This is Onihei's last football game...
This is my last chance to finally beat him!
You still don't get it?
I'm disappointed with you, Kurita.
Onihei?
Do you even know why you're playing today?
Umm... well...
I wanna beat-
You idiot!
Don't look at me, look at them!
You're a lineman, you fight for THEM!
Listen, Kurita.
Both offense AND defense revolve around the line!
You are the vanguard on both sides.
You are responsible for your teammates' safety.
Never forget what it means to have the soul of a lineman!
The soul of a lineman...
The soul of a lineman!
Kurita...
I'll put my faith in Kurita and run right through!
Please, beat Onihei for me!
Set...
Yeah... it doesn't matter if this is his last game.
Hut!
We have to win this game and go to the Kanto Tournament!
And the Christmas Bowl! I can't lose now!
I won...
I beat Onihei!
Well done, Kurita.
He did it!
Get a touchdown, Sena!
You got it!
Touchdown!
Game over!
24-0!
The Devil Bats rout the Deer
in the first match of the Death Game!
You've surpassed Onihei, Kurita.
I'm passing my lineman's soul down to you.
I'm very grateful.
Hey now.
It doesn't come with money or anything.
Later.
You'd better win the Kanto Tournament!
Onihei...
Thank you for everything!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
The Death Game - you lose, you're done!
The next opponent is Zokugaku, huh?
And we've got a serious handicap!
We're only playing freshman, meaning Hiruma's out!
And our quarterback is...
Oh no! How can this be?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Chameleons Strike Back! Ya-ha!
Are you really quitting?
Yeah.
I see...
Take care of Kurita for me.
Right!
Congrats on a great career.
Now let's drink the night away!
- Bartender!
- Another round of milk!