Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Ya-ha!
- Oh!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
#21, Defeated!
H-How...
No way...
He... stopped Sena.
Folks, there is no longer any doubt that Seijuro Shin is THE complete package.
The goddess of speed has given him her blessing!
He has invaded the world of light speed, a world previously known only to Eyeshield 21!
That ruled, Shin!
Yeah!
Go Ojo!
Hiruma...
I trained day in and day out...
...to step into your world, the world of light speed.
And now, it's settled.
I win, Eyeshield 21.
Seijuro Shin...
...has taken the title of "Japan's Fastest High Schooler!"
Sena...
Sena! You okay? Hello?
Quit sulking!
We're running it again, Peewee.
U-Umm...
You got mud in your ears?
I said we're running it again.
Okay...
I don't believe it... Sena...
I can't let it upset me, too!
Hooray, hooray, Sena!
Hooray, hooray, Deimon!
Set...
I became the wind itself... I know I did.
It was perfect... light speed wind that no one could have seen.
But he still...
No.
There's no time to think about anything else.
Right... I'll have to become the wind again, and a again!
Wind that blows faster than anything else!
Hut hut!
Deimon's making a last-ditch run!
- Open a path!
He's through, and it's Seijuro Shin vs. Eyeshield 21 yet again!
Sena has been stopped three times,
and with everything on the line, this fourth round will be make or break!
Will Shin earn a shutout victory over Eyeshield 21?
Or will Eyeshield 21 land a counter-blow against Shin?
I've gotta get through, I've gotta beat Shin!
It's not enough, Eyeshield 21!
Remember, I live in the world of light speed now, too!
Gotta get the ball...
Shin...
Is this really all you're capable of?
Sena Kobayakawa, the man I've always viewed as my rival...
...is this really the best you could do?
It's all over!
Seijuro Shin has completely defeated Eyeshield 21!
And now, he's stolen the ball for Ojo!
He's running at top speed and going for a touchdown!
- Stop Shin!
Touchdown!
Overwhelming! Invincible!
He is the perfect player, Seijuro Shin!
Ojo White Knights 13 - Deimon Devil Bats 3
No...
Sena... lost again?
You can't help but be impressed.
He's reached the absolute limits of human speed,
the ability to run the 40 yard dash in 4.2 seconds.
Shin's combined his power with the same speed as Sena...
Sena...!
Sena, are you done already?
You promised me we'd face each other again.
Are you gonna let it end here?!
Shin...
Sena...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we're talking about throwing good passes!
To throw a pass correctly, you need to turn your body until it's perpendicular with your target.
Keep practicing till you get it! Ya-ha!
Set!
Hut!
Deimon has chosen to run it on 4th down! What a risky gamble!
And they've chosen Taki as the back! Gamble is an understatement!
Don't forget about me!
A light speed Trident Tackle from Shin!
He blasts Taki with his incredible strength!
And that was Deimon's last chance!
They fail to make any progress against Ojo and fall behind to 10 points!
Ojo White Knights 13 - Deimon Devil Bats 3
13-3 right at the start of the 2nd quarter...
This is getting dangerous.
They've got us cornered.
Mamo...?
I figure you guys know already,
but we don't have any way to stop Shin.
Not now.
Hang in there until halftime.
Don't let them score again.
The 20 minutes we've got at halftime is where we start fighting back.
I've got Manajerk working like crazy researching footage of Shin's plays.
20 minutes...
Give her 20 minutes, and she'll find a way for us to overcome Shin.
There's seven minutes to halftime.
If we can run away and kill seven minutes without letting them score again,
we've still got a chance.
You got that, everyone?!
Hold them back even if it kills you!
I'll stop them from scoring... to the max!
Good, let's go!
Get your head in the game.
Deimon doesn't have anyone that can sub for you.
Oh... right...
Set...
My legs feel so heavy... my running...
Doesn't work anymore...
Eyeshield's useless now.
This is our chance to pull ahead and cement our win.
Deimon vs. Ojo, Ojo leads with 7 minutes 21 seconds to go until halftime.
And Ojo is back on offense!
- We won't lose!
- We can't lose!
Even if I run...
Wake up, Peewee!
Are we going to see another Everest Pass to Sakuraba?
No, it won't be that simple!
I don't think so!
Leave it to us!
Deimon has double coverage on Sakuraba!
Have Monta and Taki joined forces?
Please, bro, do something!
Don't worry folks, I'll answer those cheers!
You won't get the chance!
Okay! I'll take you on!
Otawara vs. Taki?!
It's like an idiot title fight!
This showdown...
It's this play's biggest battle, in a sense.
Then behold!
My new super move, my own evolution of Sena's Devil Bat Hurricane!
Prince Gentle Hurricane!
That's just a spin!
Lifting your leg up won't do anything!
Well, he would've gotten him anyway.
My idiot brother...
I won't let you catch it!
Monta's still covering Sakuraba!
You see, Deimon,
we're at the level where we can ignore your counter-schemes when we run our plays,
and succeed anyway!
Crap!
- Get it, Monta!
Freeze!
The Everest Pass is good! First down Ojo!
But Deimon is still hanging in there!
You can't take your eyes off the field for a moment!
Look, Sena...
Look at them.
Look at how they...
...how we're ALL still fighting.
Set!
Hut!
Argh!
Eat this!
Hold them back even if you're dying, you wimps!
Somehow, Deimon stops them!
What incredible effort! Deimon's got just as much dedication as Ojo!
Guys...
But they're almost to the goal.
Can Deimon hold back Ojo's offense?
With this touchdown, the gap will be widened enough to guarantee Ojo will win.
Set, hut!
Here comes my blitz!
Sakuraba takes off!
Monta?!
I'll stop you to the max this time!
Takami fakes the pass and hands it off to an unguarded Nekoyama!
What?!
Good eye, Takami!
Nekoyama's totally free,
he'll run it in for a touchdown!
- Not on our watch!
- What?!
I'm gonna squash you three-
- Double Kuri-Hammer!
Nekoyama fumbles!
Get it!
Pick it up!
We're getting this touchdown!
- No you're not!
- Yes! Taki!
The Deimon defense's tenacity wins!
Ojo has looked completely flawless so far,
but Deimon's got them beat when it comes to spirit!
Deimon stops Ojo's drive with pure guts!
Yay, big bro!
Devil Bats, Devil Bats, Devil Bats!
Just 1 minute 20 seconds to go!
This is likely to be Deimon's last drive of the half.
Musashi is lining up to kick another field goal!
Deimon's not done yet!
Set, hut!
Deimon adds three points, and the score is now 13-6!
Ojo White Knights 13 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
Halftime!
Everyone's...
Listen, Peewee.
There's no more time to stand around trembling.
In this world, NO ONE is invincible!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
What do I do? What?!
Halftime's the key.
We'll find a way to beat them before it's over!
Hiruma's not kidding!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Our Fate Lies in Halftime!
Ya-ha!
So Mamori's supposed to be coming up with a new strategy during halftime,
but how's she doing it?
Wait, maybe she's making us special lunches to give the power to come back!
Dude, I want a banana-themed one!
Gotta have mango pudding! I'm only human!
Rice balls!
That makes no sense!
Boys can be so silly...
Cretins...