Distance to Las Vegas: 1595 km.
Death March - Day 8
Ah, Taki!
I can't wait to pound you into the ground, pipsqueak!
Let the preppy know he's in for it, too!
They're totally gunning for us...
I talked a big game in front of Suzuna.
What do I do?
Something wrong? You look pale.
No... You're really flexible.
My suppleness is what lets me excel at anything and everything.
So what position do you play, Taki?
Position?
Yeah.
I don't waste my time being concerned with positions.
I can play them all.
It couldn't be...  You don't even know the rules?
Nope. He's never played in a real game,
so he doesn't know the rules, the positions, or anything.
A-And you're still here trying out for a professional team?!
That's completely insane!
I told you he was a moron.
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Signs of a Ghost!
This last test will heavily influence our chances of making the cut.
Huh? This guy kinda reminds me of someone...
We're the offense-heavy team,
so focus on scoring lots of touchdowns it'll make a big impact on the coaches!
Of course, it'll show off our prowess and give us a better shot at winning as well.
In other words, everyone on team B will share the same fate,
so lets go out and win!
I'm Jimmy Simard, and I'll be playing quarterback.
Let's do our best.
Jimmy Simard...
Ishimaru!
Hmm? Do I know you?
Oh-no, never mind!
Both teams line up!
How can he be so confident when he doesn't know the rules
and is playing for the first time?
Little runt!
I knew it, they're after me!
Set, hut, hut!
Okay!
Can't pass there...
Him!
I really am the best!
Pass is caught!
Yay! You did it!
How?! He doesn't know the positions or anything, and he still caught it!
Set, hut!
Maximum...
...Bomber!
Whoops, sorry 'bout that.
Your arm slipped, right?
Oh geez, sorry! My legs are acting up, too!
How dirty... First they clothesline him, now this?
Now he won't be able to throw passes accurately!
This's as good a strategy as any.
All right, next time it's their turn!
They're out for blood!
What do I do?
Set, hut, hut!
Nice!
Now to run it in for a touchdown!
Don't celebrate just yet!
Eat this!
Well, I was ALMOST perfect that time.
Wow... His flexibility's not just for show!
I never seen anyone bend like that.
We'll stretch him till he snaps!
Set, hut, hut!
Hey!
Why not me?!
Smash the preppy!
H-Hey! What do you two think you're doing?!
You all right?
A-Am I all right?
Of course, I'm not so fragile that a little roughhousing will stop me!
A little roughhousing?!
It ain't over yet!
They're locked on Taki.
What can I do?
Set, hut, hut!
Another nice catch!
My bad, looks like we hit a little too hard.
And the games just started...
You okay, you stuck-up jerk?
O-Of course, I'm fine.
Again?! Sheesh!
You two had better knock it off!
This is getting dangerous...
How... How can I stop this?
Set, hut!
What the-!
Not yet!
This is nothing...
H-How terrible!
This is going way too far!
Please, I didn't feel a thing...
Taki...
Talk about stubborn...
That kid should've quit a long time ago!
Whatever, we've got this game in the bag anyway.
Mr. Hoity-Toity there is trashed.
He can't perform anymore.
Which means...
At this rate, he'll fail!
Stop... Stop it already, you big idiot!
You'll end up getting really hurt if you keep this up!
Just... Just quit football!
I-I can't do that...
I mean, I'm destined to be a football star!
Taki...
That's right... We all feel that way!
That's why we're here!
You thick-headed...
Suzuna...
Of course I want to see him succeed!
Then the best thing to do is stay here and cheer him on.
And I'll do everything I can do, too.
There's one thing...
No matter what, I'll...
Sena...
Set, hut!
Hey!
I won't let us lose!
Football Clinic!
What does a Safety do?
He stays back the farthest on defense to stop the opponent!
Make that tackle and stop 'em dead! Ya-ha!
They're completely covered.
I can't throw good passes with my arm like this, either.
Here!
A run?
What unbelievable pressure!
Watch out, Sena!
Trash him!
Say goodnight, baby!
But...
I can't let it beat me!
What's happening to me?
Why... Why are they moving so slowly?
Could this... Could this be thanks to the death march?
Get him!
That's...
Eyeshield 21?
Huh?
Yeah... Sena is Eyeshield 21!
T-Touchdown!
W-What was that strange feeling?
Ooh! Well, that certainly was interesting!
Set, hut!
Forget the others, just get the runt!
Clobber him! Knock his head off!
Eyeshield isn't half bad!
But let's see you all stop me!
I'm...
...being ignored.
Sena's smaller than me, but they're covering him anyway...
How can this be...
How can this be?!
Freeze, wimp!
Denied!
I'm back in the spotlight!
W-What? Take a hike!
YOU take a hike!
No way! He can block, too?!
Shut him down!
Not a chance... I can't get through a wall that solid!
Taki Block!
I'm gonna crash!
Did I... just get past him?
It happened again...
No, it was different from the first time.
I cut without slowing down at all.
Wait, that's it!
The way to brake without losing speed!
Not yet! I'm gonna stomp you flat this time!
Okay, let's try it again!
Change your stride suddenly...
and brake without slowing down!
H-He's becoming a blur...
Touchdown!
The game is over! Team B wins!
W-We did it!
You won!
D-Did everyone see my amazing offensive and defensive plays?
I did it!
Hey, it's over. What're you standing around for?
A ghost...
I just saw a ghost...
You did it!
Ow!
Why do you always crash into me!
Wait, never mind, you're Eyeshield 21!
Oh, well, I... keep it a secret, okay?
Sorry.
What're you apologizing for?
Right, right.
Thank you.
I said thank you!
You're welcome...
The following people have passed the first round of tryouts for the Armadillos.
Anthony Reeves.
Brian Adams.
They're going alphabetically.
Seems like it.
Jimmy Simard.
Yes! I made it!
Nathan Smith.
Natsuhiko Taki comes right after him, so I should be next.
That call will be the fanfare that heralds my pro debut!
Oscar Wilder.
They skipped his name? He didn't make it?
It's not surprising...
You wouldn't expect someone who knows nothing about the game to pass.
How can this be?!
He's losing it again.
Natsuhiko Taki, is it?
How can this be- Wha?
Your power and speed aren't quite at the professional level yet.
But watching you use your flexibility to make those difficult catches and blocks
really caught my eye!
I-I caught your eye?
I implore you to get three solid years of experience
playing for a quality Japanese high school team.
You have the potential to be a great athlete.
The San Antonio Armadillos will look forward to seeing how far you can go.
W-Wow, bro!
A professional coach just complimented you!
Yeah!
That's great! He said you have potential!
I suppose it makes sense!
Clearly he COULD sign me today, but since I'm underage,
he wants me to complete high school before I try out again!
N-Not quite, but...
Either way, you're satisfied now, right, bro?
Mom's been so worried!
There's no getting around the age limit.
Come back to Japan with me and get into a high school next year.
Then if we had a Tight End...
We could execute all these sweet-looking plays no problem!
It has to be someone who can block, catch, anything at all!
Well, if it's all right with you...
Why don't you enter my high school and play on my team!
R-Really?
Yeah, that'd be perfect!
You have to do it!
What are you saying, Suzuna?
You act like I want to play so badly I don't care whose team I'm on!
Anyways, let's go, I'll introduce you to the team.
Do I get a signing bonus?
Of course not, you dork.
Samuel O'Brien.
Yahoo!
Sena Kobayakawa!
Sena Kobayakawa?
Huh... Sena?
Why's Sena coming from back that way?
Brake without slowing down...
Change your stride suddenly without losing any speed...
Ghost...
That little brat's better than I gave him credit for!
Sorry I got lost...
Sena, you're starting the next level tomorrow.
Kick the stone in a zig-zag as you run forward.
Zig-zag?
It'll definitely get you to master that demonic running style before we get to Vegas.
D-Demonic...?
Yup. Also known as the "Devil Bat Ghost!"
YA-HA!
The Devil Bat Ghost?
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima blaze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
And he's down!
Yukimitsu collapses in a heap!
I... I... will make it to the end, with everyone else!
Let's see what you're made of, Baldini!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Solitary Death March! Ya-ha!
And that's that. Glad to be on the team!
Now I remember!
The Deimon entrance exam!
You dropped something.
This is yours, right?
I could tell just from the cover!
Here's your favorite food as a gift, teammate!
I am really getting agitated...
He's not being a jerk on PURPOSE...