Max Bump!
These bumps are our anti-Kid's Quick-and-Fire technique.
They're getting pretty good at it.
We're doin' great, right?
How dependable!
Let's keep at it!
I don't see those two from the basketball team.
Satake and Yamaoka both have a basketball game today.
- A game?
They asked me to go cheer for them,
but I just couldn't leave you guys.
So Suzuna went instead.
Those two are Deimon's hole!
Who cares about some puny basketball team?
After all, we've made it to the top four!
We're goin' to the semi-finals!
The entire school is watching us.
Just today I was asked 50 times if I'm the real Eyeshield 21!
So cool!
- Whatever, man!
Hey, wait...
Aren't we missing one more person?
Um... Oh! It's Ishimaru!
You're talking about Ishimaru.
He's probably around here somewhere.
He's so hard to notice, ya know.
Everyone, there's just five days left till the game against Seibu.
Let's practice with all our might!
Down with Seibu!
- Yeah!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Spinter's Sena!?
Koigaoka 106 - Deimon 32
What are you doing, Yamakins, Takekins!?
Bump them! BUMP! Smash them!
Suzuna...
Bumps are against the rules in basketball.
- Huh?
Game over!
It's hopeless!
I wonder how yesterday's basketball game went?
I heard they lost big time.
The opponent's score was triple theirs.
It must be tough for them since they lost by triple their own score...
Speak of the devil!
It must have been a real shocker.
Yeah...
Yamaoka! Satake!
Just leave us alone.
After all, we're just part of the weak basketball team.
Aren't you part of the football team?!
Hey, I wanna see Eyeshield 21!
Let us see him sometime!
Well, you see... It's just...
- Hello!
Hey, hey, girls!
We're part of the football team, too!
The wide receiver is an important position!
Without me, they wouldn't be able to play!
Right, right!
- Amazing!
I guess they'll be just fine.
Pass the ball!
Here's my genius catch!
I'm always training with the football team, you see.
Who's he again?
Hey, it's him. He's...
Stupid Natsuhiko!
Stupid?!
The idiot!
Hey, I wouldn't mind girls squealing over me some.
Yeah. I'm so jealous!
What nonsense!
It's a waste of time!
Jumonji!
I made this for you!
Eat up!
- And power up!
- Yay! I finally gave it to him!
I'm so happy!
Aren't you the popular one, Kazuki?
You go, Kazu!
This...is...so...stupid!
Don't be shy!
You're so happy!
- Hey, this's great!
- Shut up!
Let it drop or I won't give you any!
Everyone sure has become popular!
You should eat it in front of everyone!
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Around this time last year we didn't even have a full team,
let alone get to go to the semi-finals.
We may be able to defeat Seibu after all.
It won't be that easy.
Ishimaru!
I need you for a sec.
Welcome... Devil Bats?!
Welcome Devil Bats, huh?
It looks like our room's been remodeled again.
Cerberus and Piggyberus's houses have gotten more luxurious!
Hiruma made the principal promise to remodel the place,
if we made it to the semi-finals.
I bet Hiruma blackmailed him again.
- Yep.
Amazing! It's got an automatic door!
Huh? HUH?! And I mean "HUH?!"
It's for healing a tired man's heart after a long battle.
- Old fart, you rock!
But it really is amazing!
Yeah!
We've mastered bumps and now we're gonna be victorious to the max!
Down with Seibu!
Yeah!
Quit getting so excited, kiddies.
Look at this.
The Taiyo Sphinx versus the Seibu Wild Gunmen.
This is our enemy's final practice game during summer break.
Taiyo has the Pyramid Line,
which prides itself in being the heaviest line in Japan.
Yeah.
They're really amazing.
Banba and Kasamatsu
are the number one most powerful linemen in the Kanto area.
They broke through Seibu's wall!
Good going, Banba!
Pay attention, Fatty.
It's a trap.
A trap?!
Kid drew in the ever-annoying Banba as far as he could.
He's fast!
The ball just barely made it over Banba's head!
The pass worked!
And then he just ran off!
It was brilliant...
They've made a touchdown!
We struggled so hard against those guys
and they managed to effortlessly get six points.
Fatty, can't you even read the scoreboard?
Seibu Wild Gunmen 60 - Taiyo Sphinx 0
60 to 0?!
No, I can't watch any more!
H-Hey, what about the bump?
The Taiyo Sphinx are good at bumping.
R-Right! The bump!
Here we go, Chariot Bump!
It's Kamaguruma's ultimate move.
He can do it!
That amazing bump didn't even work a little.
And here that bump drove me nuts!
That's just how great Seibu's Iron Horse Tetsuma is.
In other words, in order to defeat Seibu,
you must master a bump that's even more powerful than Kamaguruma's.
A bump greater than Kamaguruma's...
And we can assume that Seibu's powered up since this video was taken.
If we're going to battle for points,
offensive power is the key to victory.
H-Hey, what's our chances?
What's our chance of defeating Seibu?
Practically...
...0%.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to make a feint!
The key point is where you're facing?
When you want to make a feint,
make sure to run in the opposite direction that your body is facing.
It's about where you're facing!
Ya-ha!
Practically...
...0%.
No way! We-
That's if we stay as we are.
In a game where we're fighting over points,
the difference in the kickoff is what will kill us.
In other words, since Deimon doesn't have a kicker...
Even if we got the same number of touchdowns,
we'd still lose because we couldn't get those extra points.
I must...
...defeat Riku.
We've got five days left until we fight Seibu.
In order to increase our chances by even a little,
we need to focus and work on improving whatever we can!
He's right.
Worrying about it won't help any.
We have to WIN!
Manajerk, have you made the list of signals yet?
Y-Yeah...
Signals?
What's with that?
Remember how I tried telling you stuff from the bench
during your fight against Kyoshin but failed?
So we thought it'd be nice if I could do some signals,
like sign language, to pass data on to you guys.
I memorized them.
What's he doing?!
Did you really memorize them?
Let's see...the disciplinarian...secretly ate...cream puffs!
Calm down, Mamori!
I'm sorry.
It's Musashi's kick-tee.
A difference in the kick...
Musashi...
It's not just the kicker.
There's no point in mentioning it now,
but Deimon has too few players.
We'd be finished if just one of you was off the team.
That's our main weakness.
If just one of us was missing...
Come to think of it, where's Ishimaru?
Huh? He's not here.
I wonder where he went.
I'll go look for him!
Ishimaru!
That's a track team uniform...
Sena?
Why are you dressed like that?
Well, you see...
You may have forgotten, but I'm originally from the track team.
That's right! I'm sorry.
We're about to start practice, so let's go.
Well, I can't... go for a while.
Individual side events aside,
the only way the track team can make it to the finals
is if I win the 800 meter relay.
Just as it's Hiruma and Kurita's last chance at the Christmas Bowl,
this will be my last tournament.
I'd be letting all of my teammates down if I didn't go participate.
And you know,
they've been practicing just as hard as the football team.
I want to give it my all!
That way I won't be upset if we don't make it to the finals.
But...
I don't see why any of us even bothered with the track team,
if we're willing to let it end like this.
I'll return to practice as soon as it's all over.
Please wait until then.
I understand, Ishimaru.
Are you okay?
- Hey, what happened?!
- Tokikori!
Quick, get a stretcher and take him to the nurse's office!
It'll take three weeks to fully recover.
He was the central member in the relay.
Now the relay's out, I guess?
A football game?
Yeah, sure.
Count me in.
Ishimaru has always helped out the Devil Bats without complaining even once.
Now it's my turn to help him!
Eyeshield 21 will?!
Yep! I'll ask him to help out, so don't worry!
Thank you! I really appreciate it!
N-No, it's nothing...
Sena, thanks so much!
Stop jokin' around!
There's no way Eyeshield can skip practice at a time like this!
I won't let you!
B-But, without our other running back,
Ishimaru, Eyeshield couldn't-
He's never really stood out all that much.
Right!
But, he does work pretty hard.
Even though he's simple and plain.
I wish we could help out somehow...
Yeah.
But that still doesn't mean HE can go!
That...
...demon's in the way.
I knew it...
This'll be tough.
But the team manager...
But I wouldn't mind letting the team manager
take the day off instead of Eyeshield.
I see. Makes sense.
Sure does.
We could let the team manager go.
Yay! It's settled!
I feel like we've just...
What?
Just what?
No, it's nothing.
I just feel like...
...we've become a real team.
We will now hold the Tokyo Area High School Track and Field Preliminaries.
Eyeshield can't make it?
That's too bad...
I'm sorry.
But I'll run in his stead!
Sena, you will?!
Yep!
But having you run is a bit...
I've been a gopher ever since I was little, so I'm decent.
Please! Please let me run!
You're a good guy, Sena.
Even if Eyeshield couldn't make it,
I appreciate the thought.
Please join our team and fight with us!
Okay! I'll run with all my might!
"Gone to support Ishimaru in his track team's race,
so I won't be at practice today."
"From the Football Team's Manager, Sena Kobayakawa."
It doesn't really matter if the manager's out for the day.
Team Three for the Men's 800 Meter Relay Race Preliminaries!
Yay!
Let's get pumped up!
You can do it, Sena!
Sena...
You're the third runner.
Right.
Don't get nervous.
It's okay if someone gets ahead of you.
Without you, we couldn't have entered the relay to begin with,
so we're all grateful.
It's nothing...
Let's try our best!
Right!
Ready!
You're in last! Come on, Sena!
I'm counting on you, Sena!
This will be my last tournament.
I want to give it my all!
We can't lose!
Eyeshield?
Good going, Sena!
Go, Tecchie!
Ishimaru, here you go!
Thank you, Sena.
Leave the rest to me!
We did it!
Deimon's going to the finals!
Ishimaru!
You were great, Sena.
That running style... Are you...?
I'm sorry I've kept it a secret for so long, Ishimaru.
I'm...
...Eyeshield 21!
Sena, good going yesterday!
So what place did you get?
Well, we won 8th place!
That's like, last place!
Y-Yeah...
I'm Deimon Devil Bats' #30,
running back, Tetsuo Ishimaru!
Ishimaru!
Anezaki doesn't know, right?
Let's keep working hard together, Eyeshield 21.
Well, let's go practice!
We're all going...
...to the Christmas Bowl!
- Yeah!
There may not be many of us,
but I don't think that's a weakness.
As long as our hearts are one...
...we're a TEAM!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Sena's brother figure, Riku, is part of the Seibu Wild Gunmen?!
Yeah, but he doesn't know that I'm Eyeshield 21.
Can you really keep something important like that a secret?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Three Made a Promise! Ya-ha!
Hey!
I brought the three super fill-ins!
What a pain, I'm only human.
Don't complain!
I'll treat you to some mango pudding later, okay?!
Mango pudding?!
Well, I guess I've gotta do it, then!
I wanna eat mango pudding!
I am only human, after all.
I'm a human, not a pig!