Shinryuji Nagas vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha!
I'll give you credit for coming back out here
knowing you're about to get evaporated.
Even though you couldn't catch up with me after I nailed you last time.
Impossible!
Who? Who could be running up the middle now?!
No, it doesn't matter, I've got the timing...
"Tranquil Reflections"
If I throw it with at full power, Ikkyu's got it.
I can make the-
What?!
Eyeshield 21 runs straight up the middle and intercepts!
What a guy.
They left Agon undefended!
That's WHY we ignored him.
You stinkin' scum!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Will of a Warrior.
Th-They took a huge risk
completely ignoring Agon for a whole play, but...
...it paid off, and the Deimon Devil Bats take possession!
That little stunt Hiruma and Musashi pulled...
...put the idea that Eyeshield 21 was coming back to stop Agon
at the front of everyone's mind.
Yeah! Go, Sena!
Please, God, let Sena's legs last till the end!
Agon!
Whoa, Agon's coming!
He's got him!
Uber-nice!
Shoot, it's no use.
Even if Musashi punching Hiruma was a good act,
there's no avoiding the fact that Sena's legs are at their limit!
Sena!
Run, Eyeshield! Make a break for it!
Take him down, Agon!
If you stop him there'll only be five minutes left!
We can run out the clock!
I'm not waiting five minutes!
I'm gonna put this punk on the bench permanently!
Is this it?
Is Agon inescapable?
I spent every day since I was a kid running all over the place.
Hey!
You made Sena cry again!
Back then, I wouldn't have even dreamed of playing football.
Ya-ha!
The 40-yard dash in 4.2 seconds!
No one can run better than you!
You've been running every day for 16 years!
No matter how good that Mop-Head is,
his ghost's just a copy!
Leave Agon in the dust!
They're right...
Every day of the last 16 years
has all been for these last five minutes.
Even if I'm against Agon...
there has to be a route... there has to!
I have to find a way to dodge him!
Do I use the Devil Bat Ghost to the right?
The left?
Go straight through with the Devil Bat Hurricane!
They're all dead ends!
But I've gotta do something!
Don't you get it? I see through all your moves!
I can't do it!
Agon's reaction time is inhuman!
No matter how you cut, or how fast you move,
there's no way to completely escape!
Sena Kobayakawa...
...that running style can't beat him!
Time to take out the trash!
Here comes the chop...
If you have any pride,
you'll sacrifice your body to protect the ball!
Riku taught me that my body exists to defend the ball.
Even if I'm tackled, the ball must stay safe!
That's right, knowing when to give up is a virtue as well.
Focus all your energy on holding the ball.
Fortify your defense!
If you think that's the right idea, Onihei, then...
Don't forget what I said, Sena!
A footballer values the ball's safety more than his own!
Give it up, scum ball!
You AND the ball are going down!
Here it comes!
We all promised...
...we'd go to the Christmas Bowl.
That's why...
I can't run away.
I'll protect it!
This isn't just a ball!
It's not just about me...
Everyone's hopes,
their dreams,
all of it...
It's all in this ball!
Sena!
Smash through him!
- Use the REAL Devil Bat Ghost!
The Devil Bat Ghost I perfected over 2000 kilometers...
I didn't do it alone...
Everyone was there for me.
I managed to keep going because of them!
It's game over for you, guaranteed!
What were you trash saying about the Christmas Bowl?
Please, win!
Eyeshield 21!
Yay! Keep going!
It's game over for you, guaranteed!
Okay... this...
...will knock him off balance!
What're you trying to pull?
Go to sleep, tubby!
Wait, what were you talking about?
You losers have nursed that stupid dream for four years.
And now it's game over for you, guaranteed.
Say your prayers!
He's not using his arm to protect the ball!
You... attack ME?
You little RAT!
You're going down!
You're going down, Agon!
Again?! You stinkin' runt!
The field is a war zone.
The one thing that the small-built Sena Kobayakawa lacked...
The drive to fight off hordes of enemies for the sake of his teammates,
even if it means resorting to brutality.
The will of a warrior!
He's through!
Amazing!
He made him focus on his arm, and then...
Will this Ghost-Hurricane combination carry him away from Agon?!
No... not yet!
He can't escape his superhuman reflexes?!
It's too late,
his reflexes let him react the instant he sees me do anything!
The instant he SEES...
That's it!
You're finished!
He grabbed Agon's helmet from his blind spot!
Even his incredible reflexes can't fight what they can't see!
Sena!
You scum... You SCUM!
He... he got past Agon!
He didn't protect the ball by sacrificing himself,
he did it by going on the attack!
Sena's outgrown what I taught him...
He's improved again!
Touchdown!
- Yes!
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 21
I-I can't believe it...
Sena Kobayakawa just became the biggest threat on the field!
He didn't exactly fortify his defense, did he Onihei?
- Sena!
Sena Sena Sena Sena Sena Sena!
Sena Sena you did it you did it you did it you really did it!
Eye-Eye-Eye-Eyeshield 21...
Sena Kobayakawa has just scored his first touchdown of the game.
The Deimon Devil Bats have shown incredible tenacity.
This half looked completely hopeless at the start, but now...
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 27
They're a mere seven points behind!
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 28
One touchdown and they tie it!
They're closing in on Kanto's strongest, the Shinryuji Nagas!
This is bad, Unsui...
We can't have any more messing with the Dragonfly.
It's time to play this safe and run out the clock.
H-H-He's right.
There's only five minutes left, Unsui.
We're almost out of time!
What do we do, Hiruma?
Shinryuji's gonna try to run out the clock!
If they were that dumb,
I could predict their plays and pull something off.
Shinryuji can't take any risks here.
The safest plan is for them to play defensively and eat up time.
So that means...
Snap the freaking ball to me!
I'll crush Sena Kobayakawa and the whole lot of 'em!
Don't forget about passing to me.
I'll prove to that stupid monkey that he can't beat me twice.
There's just no guarantee that what we do will finish Deimon for good.
We'll run out the last five minutes.
So we'll play it safe?
No.
We'll run out the clock with an all-out offense...
The Golden Dragonfly.
What the heck?!
They've got one... two... THREE quarterbacks now?!
Now, Agon, Unsui AND Ikkyu are playing quarterback?
The Golden Dragonfly?
A twisted version of the Dragonfly with three quarterbacks lined up.
They're using such a wild formation NOW?
I never would've expected Unsui to be such a daredevil!
Set, hut, hut, hut!
Who's taking the snap?!
Two was bad enough...
But which of the three-
It went to Unsui!
What?
Ikkyu!
He passed it so fast!
They'll catch the short passes with 100% accuracy.
Which of the three will take the snap...
will he pass it, run it, or hand it off?
He smashed through the middle!
First down Shinryuji Nagas!
They remain on offense!
Four minutes and change...
And I don't get any more timeouts...
Somehow... some way... I have to last...
This time Unsui's running up the middle!
If they tried to hang back and play it safe,
Hiruma would see right through them.
So they're using three quarterbacks to run around
to mess with their minds,
and slowly advance at the same time.
The Golden Dragonfly can eat up time
while remaining completely unpredictable.
What the heck do we do?!
Forget this Golden Dragonfly junk, we just gotta do our job!
Don't let 'em score!
And don't let 'em run out the clock!
We're going...
...to the Christmas Bowl!
Go, Deimon!
1:30 remaining!
A flock of bats nipping at the tail of a golden dragon!
It's a life or death clash of wills!
Yay, Sena-Mon double tackle!
Yes!
Ikkyu...
- ...got crunched!
All according to plan.
This ends now.
They're uber-finished.
What could be Shinryuji's last play, is a long punt!
The ball lands deep in Deimon territory!
It doesn't matter if you stopped us,
we only needed to kill some time and gain some ground.
It was obvious you were using your timeouts
to let Eyeshield rest his legs.
You have no way to stop the clock now.
There's no way you can move down the whole field
with just one minute left.
The Shinryuji Nagas have won!
One minute, huh...?
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
You know there's only a minute left, right Sena?
Someone stop the clock!
I've gotta keep going.
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Timeouts: Zero!
Ya-ha!
Very nice, Deimon.
Perhaps, if you just-
Enough already!
Just start cheering for Shinryuji!
Everything you say is the exact opposite of what happens!