Barbecue-cue! I'll have a fun time with Mamori eating barbecue-cue!
I'll get full at the barbecue-cue!
What a pain!
But we're stuck doing it.
Hiruma's the sponsor, ya know.
Barbecue-cue! I'll have a fun time with Mamori eating barbecue-cue!
Ta-da! Have you ever seen this before?
Ah, isn't it that new type of gum?
What happened to the usual one?
I heard that they discontinued it.
Man, I really like it, too! Come back, Prism Gum!
Come back!
Hey...
Don't tell me...
...he's dead?
W-What the heck?
Good grief! Where on earth did he go at a time like this?!
Darn that Tetsuma!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Kid and Iron Horse
It's fun having a barbecue with everyone!
Guys, over here!
Mamori is lovely to the max in that apron!
Here, Monta! Open up!
It's so good, Mamori!
Just kidding, just kidding!
T-That hurts, Monta!
I'm the most pumped up to the MAX!
Mamori!
Stop!
Don't tell me you're after Mamori, too?!
Like hell no!
I'm sorry!
Take a look at this!
Huh? Up? Zig out? Long post? Corner? Square in?
It's a route, isn't it?
A route?
Um, isn't that the lingo used in basic football strategies for how to pass the ball and run around?
Yeah. You can't pass the ball if you don't know where everyone's running.
You're really amazing, Yukimitsu!
No, it's nothing.
But routes are complex!
How are routes related to our barbecue today?
I'm going to quiz you now.
Quiz us?!
The rule is that only people who go where the route tells them to get to eat the meat!
Man, that's good!
Those who can't remember the route aren't qualified to eat the meat!
But then it's not a quiz!
I can't memorize something this complex that quickly!
I wouldn't have to retake tests if I was that good at memorizing stuff!
You don't have to memorize everything.
Just practice two or three good routes.
Quit trying to go easy on them, Fatty!
They've gotta memorize all of it!
Besides, we can't reach the Christmas Bowl if we can't do something basic like this!
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Shoot!
This picture is...
Don't show everyone!
We'll do that route...
...or whatever!
Why does Sena have to do it? He's just the team manager!
B-But it's a quiz and I want to eat some meat.
I see.
Number 1: Slant!
You better run if you want that meat!
Start!
Max meat! Max meat! Max meat!
Slant's over there!
Easy enough!
Thanks for the fo-!
Ah, my meat!
It's nothing! Yeah...
Next: Come back!
Doesn't come back mean to go straight back?
Next is, Up!
Fade!
Post!
Oh, no! Can't anyone get a single one right?
At this rate, no one gets to eat meat!
Like I care!
Long post!
Okay, I'll get it this time!
My meat!
Tetsuma, stop!
So this is where you were. I've been looking for you!
W-Who the heck are you?!
No one worth mentioning.
Huh?!
Don't tell me you haven't eaten anything this whole time
because Coach said not to eat much before a game?
Mm-hm.
Tetsuma, why can't you do things within reason?
Hey, hey, could it be THE Tetsuma?
Yeah. It looks like that's THE Tetsuma. So the other one must be The Kid.
Anyway, let's go get something to eat.
Hold on!
Why not just eat here?
But it's up to him whether he gets to eat any meat or not.
You've still got some time, right?
Don't blame me if you end up regretting this later.
Got that?
Yeah!
It's our meat! There's no way we can let someone like him eat it! Right, Sena?
So, I wonder what'll happen.
Okay, slice in!
Um... slice in is...
Left?!
Oof! I'm sorry!
Next is quick out!
Max meat! Max meat! Max meat! Max meat!
Square out!
Yum!
Zig out!
He's doing too good today.
Nothing good ever happens on days when he's doing so well...
Poopy! I'll get it next time!
Up!
Leave that one to me! It's straight!
Max Catch!
I hate bell peppers!
We're outta meat!
N-No way!
I told you that you'd regret this, didn't I?
Tetsuma, it's just about time. Let's go!
Meat thief! Give back my meat!
It can't be helped.
We didn't get a single route right, after all.
Besides, these veggies are pretty good.
I wanted to eat meat!
Darn! Who cares about routes!? He's just having fun torturing us!
That's not true. I'm sure this is important.
I'm sure Hiruma has a reason why he's doing this.
So why then?!
Well...
See?! You don't know either, do you?!
You just need to keep moving forward in football, right?
We just need to have Eyeshield run while I catch the passes!
Why should we care about going right, going back, or circling around?!
We don't need a route map!
Monta! Sena!
Ah, I'm through! Finished!
I'm so hungry!
Let's go eat some cold ramen or something.
W-Wait! Um... you see, there's a good reason why we need routes.
Give it up, Fatty!
But-!
Guys, I'll show you why it's so important if you really wanna know!
Ya-ha!
It's the Tokyo Tournament's Finals...
The finals were today! Where's the pamphlet?
It's the Ojo White Knights up against the Seibu Wild Gunmen!
It's Ojo!
Shin!
It's him!
Hey, Kurita! How you've been doing?
Are the Devil Bats spying for info on the enemy?
N-No, it's just...
Well, watch us! Our defense is like an iron wall!
We won't let those Gunmen get a single point, right?!
We can't let our guard down.
We're up against a team that's made it to the finals.
We should give them everything we've got.
You've got me there!
Just what I'd expect from Shin!
Ojo has Shin with them, so Ojo will win!
Wild Gunmen!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
What a cheer!
It's because their coach likes that sort of stuff.
Far out!
Wild, Wild Gunmen!
Tetsuma, come back!
Those guys were players for the Seibu Wild Gunmen?!
Football Clinic!
Tell me about routes, okay?
It's the route the receiver takes when trying to catch a pass!
By following the strategy to a T, you should be able to catch the pass for sure! Ya-ha!
Jo Tetsuma, can run 40 yard in five seconds flat and can bench press 115 kilos.
Awesome!
But his numbers aren't the only awesome thing about him.
That's right!
Jo Tetsuma's unparalleled running has given him the nickname "Iron Horse."
Sakuraba and Torakichi! You're here, too?
Yeah, I got permission to take him on a trip outside the hospital.
Ojo's in the finals! Of course I'd come!
You're as snotty as ever!
Even if Tetsuma's said to be the best at following routes, there's no way Ojo can lose!
Routes...
What, you guys don't even know about routes?!
No, we know about routes, but...
I'll show you why routes are so important if you really wanna know!
So he meant that we'll understand why routes are important if we watch this game?
What's that?!
It's a shotgun formation!
A shotgun?
It's a type of attack formation.
Set, hut, hut!
Do a slant, Tetsuma!
You see, it spreads out the receivers who can catch the pass the way a shotgun sprays out bullets.
It's a strategy that perfectly focuses on passes.
That's awesomeness to the max!
It's all about passes, isn't it? Passes beat routes!
Shin alone can't handle all of those receivers.
If he can't handle all of them, then I'll crush them before they can throw!
Deal with the three of us!
Cool!
That's our position!
Don't get worked up over it!
They have a pretty solid line, too.
This is part of our strategy!
Good going, Shin!
Go! Spear Tackle!
That's the Shin I know! His speed's amazing!
All right, I crushed them!
He probably doesn't have enough time to search for a target.
Unfortunately, we're doing too good today!
What?!
He closed his eyes!
I can see where he is even with my eyes closed!
I don't need time to search for a receiver!
He's so quick!
But he'll be way off mark if he throws the ball over there.
No, it's a slant formation!
Touch down!
Kid, nice pass!
Tetsuma, nice catch!
I can't believe Shin...!
Nice run! Yay!
Isn't the slant formation...
A route.
Tetsuma doesn't stray from the decided route, even by a mere ten centimeters!
In other words, Kid didn't miss his target but sent the ball right where he wanted it to go.
Ojo, you can do it!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Don't underestimate Quickdraw The Kid.
Long post!
Square out!
I can't believe it....
I can't believe Ojo's losing!
The passes will definitely get through if they can run routes without any mistakes,
even with Otawara and Shin there.
They sure are throwing passes like nuts.
Watch carefully!
This is how the Gunmen managed to climb their way up to the finals.
So this is why Hiruma was saying routes are so important!
But I've got a bad feeling about the second half of the game.
What are you saying? Keep attacking with your Gun-Guns!
After all, we've got Quickdraw The Kid and Tetsuma on our team!
Tetsuma, you're our courage!
Drink plenty of fluids, Gun-Gun!
Cross!
He truly is an Iron Horse!
He's a locomotive, and no one can change his course!
But nothing good ever happens when we're doing so well.
Well, last year certainly was pretty horrible.
When I told him to run like mad, he ran non-stop for three whole days and utterly exhausted himself.
We had to quit after the very first game.
He follows his orders to the T. We had a close call again this year, too.
But he ate a bunch of meat, so he's okay.
I see! But judging by the first half, I'd say there's nothing to worry about.
I told him to drink plenty of fluids, Gun-Gun!
Gulp them?
Hey, hey! Are you okay?
We'll begin the second half momentarily.
Set, hut, hut!
T-Time out!
Tetsuma, are you done for the day?
It looks that way...
W-What'll we do without Tetsuma?
What are you complaining about? We're in the lead, aren't we?!
B-But...
See? I told you, didn't I?
Something bad always happens when we're doing so well.
Game over!
The winner of the Spring Tokyo Tournament is the Ojo White Knights!
The Wild Gunmen probably would have won if Tetsuma hadn't stopped playing.
There'll be strong people like them in the fall tournament...
We have to defeat all of them if we wanna win?!
The path of a hero is tough!
WHO'S a hero? You'll be lucky to be a lamo side-kick!
Without Sakuraba there, Ojo looks like cider that's lost its fizz!
Get everything prepared for the fall tournament.
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
Shin!
Lazy bums!
I can't believe they scored a whole 20 points!
Our mental carelessness is what brought this upon us!
There's no way we'll make it to the Christmas Bowl like this!
Right...
I can't hear you!
RIGHT!
What am I doing?
This game was so pathetic!
Shin, good job!
Ojo was really backed into a corner!
Huh? Where's Shin?
Oh, he said he'd run home or something.
Huh? Just how far does he think that is?!
I swear, there's just no competing with him!
What a guy.
Huh? Is Shin...?
What's wrong, Sena?
Ah, well, I was thinking that I might run home for my afternoon exercise... or something.
He's all pumped up!
Sena, that's impossible! You'd get too tired!
Wasn't it a slant formation?
I'm talking about those routes!
They sure were cool!
Here! And there! All their passes went through!
I realized that I need routes in order to be cool and catch all the passes!
From here on, I'm using routes to the max!
Monta!
Okay, let's go!
Yeah!
Slant!
Ouch!
Are you two okay?
Slant... You go straight and then rotate...
That's a slice in!
For a slant formation you go straight and to the left, so you goofed up, Monta.
Sorry to the max!
This is really nice!
It's okay.
Sena, we'll win for sure!
Yeah!
We're going to the Christmas Bowl, after all!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Wow, they're huge! Who're they?!
We're the Taiyo Sphinx.
Thanks to that accursed Hiruma's trick, we're playing for the right to represent Japan.
Hey Jumonji, time to get pumped up already!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A Slacker's Pride! Ya-ha!
You'll be playing in the Christmas Bowl, won't you?
Yep!
You've absolutely gotta win!
Yeah!