Touchdown!
Deimon's pretty good!
This game's really heating up!
That was clearly a fluke!
That little jerk's name was Hiruma, right?
I hope his whole team gets the stuffing beaten out of them!
Scum like Deimon trying to represent Japan... That in and of itself is shameful!
Here's the deal... We're completely surrounded by enemies.
Every single person here expects us to lose.
If we keep going down, we're just gonna make them and that rat of an editor happy.
Let's blow their minds!
YA-HA!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Sphinx's Secret Weapon!
Set, hut, hut!
Now open a path for me!
That is your job!
Break down the Pyramid Line!
Normally the line can only give you three or four seconds on a pass play.
You have a scant three seconds to find a receiver and throw a good pass.
But the Pyramid Line is different.
Their quarterback, Harao...
I can leisurely wait until a receiver is open.
There it is!
The Delinquent Deathblow!
Harao's being pressured!
Komusubi, that was beautiful!
Master!
Let go!
Where's the ball?
This is madness!
This is the circus play of the year.
Grab it!
The normally unshakable Taiyo offense is in chaos...
It's like the people staging a revolt against a pharaoh!
There's more to Taiyo than its line!
We've got speed, too-
Yes, he got it!
Take him down!
I'll get you this time.
I'm going through!
He got slammed...
He didn't fumble...
Nice job, Peewee.
Thanks!
Eyeshield's something else.
Everyone's doing great!
We can win this game!
What is wrong with you plebeians?!
I ordered you to open a path for me.
What happened up there?
Don't drop back!
We'll blow them away this time.
Your name's Kurita, yes?
You're about to learn what the title "The Invincible Pyramid Line" really means.
He got sacked!
What?!
Ya-ha!
The "sack" means you tackle the quarterback before he can throw a pass!
It's a lineman's attack. Don't forget it!
Ya-ha!
Well done. THAT'S more like my line.
Just keep it up.
I bet he felt that one!
Now they can't even pass. Deimon's backs are all amateurs!
Don't be so sure.
Not throwing was the correct choice on that play.
Protecting the ball is always your top priority.
That's all well and good,
but Harao's never been sacked once in his life.
Taiyo's Pyramid Line is flawless!
This is so interesting!
Harao, defended by his powerful line, a quarterback raised in the lap of luxury.
Against Hiruma, left out in the cold,
a quarterback who's scraped and clawed his way though his whole career.
My line will trample you until there's nothing left!
Set, hut, hut!
Ignore him, he doesn't have it!
The pass route where you run to the gap, the slant!
It doesn't make a difference if we sack you, eh?
Deimon's line has always been nothing but novices.
Hiruma's had to contend with being sacked in every game.
That's how he's developed such quick reflexes.
When he has to protect the ball...
and when he has to dodge and throw!
Those harsh conditions gave birth to a moving cannon!
An incredibly agile quarterback!
Killer!
Hero to the max!
What an awesome quarterback!
His name's Hiruma, I think.
Taiyo's ball!
You stupid butt-monkey!
Never let your guard down!
Set, hut, hut!
All we need to win are my passes!
There's no room to throw!
Deimon's ball!
Harao just got sacked!
What were you doing?!
I've never endured such humiliation!
He won't get through again!
Have faith in our line, eh?
All right, line-girls.
The odds are against us in a head-to-head clash.
We're gonna switch up our coverage.
So!
Big bro!
I'm not anyone's brother!
We keep...
Telling you...
We're not brothers!
Insult that big buffalo like crazy!
This'll be simple.
I just need to get him riled up.
Let's rumble!
You turkey!
Pig!
Gorilla!
That's elementary school stuff...
Excuse me?
Was that you?
"Squeak squeak?"
You must be the three squeaky brothers!
We are NOT BROTHERS!
You're not supposed to let them taunt you.
But he said-
Man, something smells like rancid milk.
It's you!
You're in high school now, tell your mom you're too old to be breast-fed!
He's the devil.
What, you're mad now?
Come and get some, ya big plodding mummy!
Set, hut, hut!
The red-nosed kid's gone?
Who's the mummy now?
He broke the line!
Sack him! Go!
It's a trap, Kasamatsu! On your right!
Being big isn't always enough to win.
Humans aren't built to get tackled from the side.
What a combination! Everyone did great!
Deimon gains 12 yards!
Woohoo!
W-What is this?!
Four yard gain!
Eight yard gain!
14 yard gain!
This is so unsightly.
Touchdown, Deimon!
Why're you rooting for Deimon?!
Well, we did practice with 'em and stuff...
We are the Taiyo Sphinx, how can we be playing so disgracefully?!
Yo-Yo...
Your Pyramid Line's nothing to write home about.
Is it, you spoiled brats?!
My name's not Yo-Yo!
Football Clinic!
What kind of play is a "sack?"
It's when you tackle the quarterback to prevent him from passing!
It's a huge deal when you totally squash the opponent's pass! Ya-ha!
This is fantastic!
Only a one-point difference at halftime!
We'll take the lead in the second half!
Monta?
You saw me at my worst during the first half...
I promise to make up for that fumble.
I'll make a Max Super Catch and regain my shame!
Whoa, that was cool!
R-Right, good luck.
I'd prefer you didn't REGAIN your shame.
Try ERASING your shame,
or REGAINING your honor.
It's okay, he's doing his best, it's just semantics!
That was lame...
Seven to three, I'd say.
That's how I'd rate their lines.
Deimon's got a decent handle on them, but with the pressure Taiyo puts on them, it's seven to three.
Well, of course. They're Japan's heaviest line.
They simply can't lose.
But when you look at the backs, Taiyo's being outdone by around three to seven.
Especially their quarterback, Hiruma has incredible moves!
Why are you jumping on Deimon's bandwagon?!
Your analysis displeases me to no end!
No, I'm only commenting as a spectator!
You hopeless dunce!
That slapdash line shoved you all over the place!
We've only got a one point lead against Deimon, of all teams!
Sorry, eh?
How much humiliation do I have to endure before you're satisfied?
Are you trying to ruin my reputation?!
Calm down, Harao.
How do you expect me to calm down?!
Just tone it down a little.
All of you have one job, to protect me-
I told you to shut your trap.
The line is certainly key to winning football games.
But it by itself is not enough.
Harao, you need to reflect more on your own mistakes.
You get careless when you go to pass, and raise your arm too high.
W-What're you implying?
You're inviting them to strip the ball from you.
A top-tier quarterback can make a pass even when the line collapses.
Hey, are they arguing over there?
Dissension in the ranks?
Keep the ball low and close before you throw.
You're more than capable of doing it.
Man, he's gonna change how he passes.
No more easy fumbles if we break through the line.
Banba's definitely the foundation of their team.
All right, everyone! From now on we aim to dash in and intercept Harao's passes!
We're on offense!
Defense is on offense!
Attack, attack, attack!
Prepare yourselves, Sphinx!
Mamori, keep your eyes on me!
I'll catch, and catch, and catch and catch and catch and catch my heart out!
R-Right, good luck, Monta!
Mamori wished me luck-
Everyone's so easy to understand...
This is the manager reporting in.
Eyeshield's run is more or less unstoppable.
But as long as the line holds, he won't get very far.
Additionally, if you can eliminate their receiver, #80, they have no passing game at all.
Go get Kamaguruma.
Kamaguruma? He's just a little freshman, eh?
No, it's about time we used him in a real game.
I concur with Banba's opinion.
Kamaguruma.
Is it finally my turn?
The second half is about to begin!
They put in another giant!
I assume you boys think Taiyo is nothing but the Pyramid Line.
If my senpai are the Pyramid Line...
I'm a war vehicle of a cornerback!
Ancient Egypt equals war vehicles!
That's what my textbook says.
War vehicles?
No, you're thinking modern warfare, I'm talking about ancient stuff!
Listen well, Kamaguruma... You're to demonstrate how superior we truly are!
Yes, sir!
A cornerback's job is to stop both runs and passes, so aren't they usually short, speedy types?
Everyone at Taiyo's a heavyweight, no matter what the position...
I'm not scared!
A giant like you will never be able to keep up with my speed!
You think so?
I'll show you why they say I'm a chariot.
Set, hut, hut!
Kamaguruma, get him!
Chariot Bump!
Their timing-
It's too late!
Char-iot BUMP! Char-iot BUMP!
You okay, Monta?
The second I took off, he slammed me in the chest... and knocked the wind outta me!
That's a bump, it's how they mess up our timing when we pass.
I see... Does that mean we won't be able to pass like we did in the first half?
Char-iot BUMP! Char-iot BUMP!
Set, hut!
Bump!
Again?!
We can't pass!
Nice bumping!
Adding Kamaguruma to the mix completely threw off the balance between the teams.
I can't say the backs are three-seven anymore... At best it's four-six, maybe even five-five.
Bump!
BUMP!
Monta!
You all right? Can you stand?
I think so...
Hiruma!
We're not changing anything.
Quit taking so long, you butt-monkey.
Right...
Monta...
Set, hut, hut!
I'll catch it this time.
Max jump-!
Power wins, even in the world of catching!
There's nothing you can do to stop my Chariot Bump!
If the backs are even, and the lines are seven-three Taiyo...
Then at some point, Deimon will lose.
How can I be the only one failing?
I promised Mamori...
I can't dodge and slip through like Sena...
I can't force my way through with raw strength like Kurita...
Not football, too...
Is just catching not enough for football, too?
Am I no good at this, either?!
Monta...
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
The battle to represent Japan reaches its climax!
The Sphinx are finally getting impatient!
Go, Devil Bats! Get 'em, guys!
Go go, run Sena, dash, jump!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Fly, Devil Bat! Ya-ha!
Is this really the score?
Hurry up and lock in the win.
I'm tired of waiting!
We're losing beach time!
Those are all surfer tans?!
That's right...The Shonan area's right by the bay.