White Knights! White Knights!
It's the second semi-final as these teams
battle for a ticket to the Kanto Tournament!
A clash between the Ojo White Knights and the Bando Spiders!
The Seibu Wild Gunmen were the victors in the first semi-final.
Which team will Seibu face in the finals?
Will it be Ojo? Or Bando?!
Bando has defied all expectations in making it this far.
I can't wait to see what kind of game plan
this revived Ojo team will use against
an opponent like Bando!
Sena, Mon-Mon, come on!
Whew, we barely made it!
Look, Sena, it's Ojo.
Hey, guys!
Hello, Otawara.
What's shakin'?
How long has it been?
Ah, it doesn't matter!
Long time no see!
Oh, you guys are Deimon players...
Sakuraba...
Haven't seen you in a while either.
You always look so goofy.
Torakichi?
And you're as snotty as ever, I see.
Ow, no hitting!
Take that.
You guys had a close game in your semi-final.
But if you win the third place tiebreaker,
both our teams will be in the Kanto Tournament.
But...
Now we won't get to face Ojo...
Shin said he'd be waiting for me in the finals...
I couldn't live up to his expectations.
Is Deimon out of the fall tournament?
Shin!
Ojo will defeat Bando with its full strength.
Make sure you beat them, too.
We'll wait for you at the Kanto Tournament instead.
Y-Yes!
They'll be waiting as champions.
We're still in it.
That's right...
There's no time to be depressed about losing.
If we're in the Kanto Tournament,
we still have a chance to face Ojo.
We have to win the tiebreaker!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Spider's Sting!
They are of the odds on favorite to win the championship.
The Ojo White Knights have arrived!
Man, the Ojo guys all look focused to the max!
I'll say...
But Sakuraba definitely looks like he's the most ready!
Sakuraba!
What a huge chant!
Looks like everyone here's a Sakuraba fan.
Sakuraba!
The crowd's voice sounds a lot deeper this time, though.
Of course.
Sakuraba's our hero.
Sakuraba! Sakuraba!
Sakuraba!
M-Mr. Miracle Ito...
I know he USED to be Sakuraba's agent...
W-What's he doing here?
You've been hard at work!
Maybe the model life wasn't for you.
But there's always a market for handsome superstar athletes!
And a superstar athlete who played in the Christmas Bowl
would be a huge selling point.
That's a much more preferable campaign,
don't you think, Sakuraba?
Yes!
Then I'd say we have a new agreement.
Good for him.
Good luck, Sakuraba!
Oh ho, the Bando Spiders are here too!
The Ojo game is finally here.
This'll be so smart!
It's Kotaro.
An electric guitar?
They're cheering just as loud as they did for Ojo.
Why's an athlete playing guitar?
And at a stadium?
And be so freaking good at it?!
- It makes no sense?!
Hayato Akaba...
He's a key player.
Keep your eyes on him.
Hayato... Akaba.
Wonder if there's any more football stars here...
You!
I see you noticed me!
I'm afraid I can't talk to you now,
I prefer to stay focused when there's a game going on!
Excuse me.
How can this be?!
You guys expected too much.
You, you with the guitar!
You have the look and the "it" factor of a true star!
So noisy.
Anyways.
It's time for our pre-game meeting.
The ambivalence of mind and muscle...
Even against Ojo, we can emerge victorious.
So did that little "BYEOW" mean anything?
- Another one!
Dude, it's so NOT SMART.
Guitars have nothing to do with football!
Football isn't a sport
where only hyperactive people like you win.
Why do you two always have to argue?
He has no sense of rhythm.
Of course,
there's no denying that there's a certain beauty
to some types of discord.
Geez, you guys...
Well, I guess we're gonna see
your harmony on display today, right?
Yup! And it's gonna be smart!
A rockin' beat and a ear-splitting shout!
Bando Spiders!
- Rock and soul!
Show them the soul of a kicking team!
...Red eyes?
We swear here on our pride as knights to win!
We didn't come here to fight our enemies,
we came to defeat them!
Glory on the kingdom!
Okay, come on!
The game is underway, and Bando will receive!
Bando's Tempo will return the kickoff!
The Spear Tackle strikes!
Seijuro Shin is in top form today!
- Killer!
Shin is incredible!
The Bando Spiders are 40 yards from the goal.
Can they make it through Ojo's iron defense?
Set, hut!
These guys are like flies to me!
And so is Otawara!
I'm gonna squash your QB!
Kotaro, here comes your chord!
What?!
It's good!
What a perfect kick, it was almost elegant!
Kotaro Sasaki and the Bando Spiders score first!
A 40-yard field goal in the opening minutes of the game!
Now that was smart!
Nice!
The Kotaro chord's melodious sound...
There's nothing more pleasing to the ear.
Nothing less from Tokyo's number one kicker!
Just when it looks like they'll go for it, they kick!
This is the true attack strategy of the Bando Spiders!
Bando Spiders 3 - Ojo White Knights 0
H-Hey, isn't this the first time...
That Ojo's been scored on in the tournament?
After giving up three points, Ojo will no go on offense.
How will they mount their counterattack?
One step at a time.
We'll make it up!
Set, hut!
Still haven't learned your lesson, have you?
Otawara's just gonna squash him the whole game at this rate.
He's way too big for them.
They showed some guts during the field goal,
but I guess that was all they had?
Doesn't look like Bando's anything to worry about.
You never know what can happen in these games.
That's right...
Bando managed to make it this far.
They won't go down easily...
The strongest point in Ojo's line is #60.
I'm gonna roll right over you!
Now!
Somehow, someway, Kanto's greatest lineman Otawara
has been flattened by a much smaller opponent!
What's your analysis of this, Kumabukuro?
I-I have no idea...
What'd he do differently?
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to block!
The hint is "palms!"
The trick to blocking
is to push into the opponents armpits with your palms.
Don't wimp out!
Ya-ha!
Only five minutes to go in the 4th quarter,
Bando Spiders 3 - Ojo White Knights 0
and the Ojo kingdom is struggling!
Who would've predicted a score like this?
Can Ojo turn things around with this possession?
Set, hut!
Sakuraba, corner!
Got it, Takami!
Target locked.
He always plays the same note.
The only receiver to focus on is Sakuraba!
Here!
I'm surrounded?!
The pass is incomplete!
They know our pass routes...
I don't see how, but it does feel like it...
Is this just a miracle?
Have they cast a magic spell?
Perhaps the "Bando Spider Illusion?"
What do you think, Shin?
I believe it's Hayato Akaba.
Somehow, he must be signaling his team in mid-play.
Why?!
Timeout, Ojo White Knights!
Our miracles...
...are infinite.
They're reading Sakuraba's pass routes 100% of the time...
This is nuts...
Such a small player knocking down Otawara so easily...
There's no such thing as magic, but then how...
Bando is really tough.
What do you mean?
I thought Bando wasn't anything special.
They obviously had a tough time this year,
but last season they came in second place.
The greaser made two kicks, but they lost 7-6.
They were the only team to score at all against Ojo's "Golden Generation."
The one on the bench, Akaba,
was voted tournament MVP.
M-MVP?!
Then what's he doing on the bench?!
Bando's rating went down because all their members
from last year were lured away by a school in Kansai.
A-All of them?
But for some reason...
Vampiro over there decided to come back.
At this rate, Ojo...
...might just...
You doofus.
Watch the field carefully.
I can't believe how lazy you bums are!
Otawara, explain yourselves!
Their blocking got really strong... or something...
Takami.
They're predicting every pass route we run.
Sakuraba.
...I don't know.
Shin.
Yes?
Take care of them.
Yes, sir.
Seijuro Shin takes the field once again.
Can he halt Bando's advancing offense?
Shin!
Set, hut!
You're mine!
This time I'll-
The Spear Tackle!
Seijuro Shin runs it in for a touchdown!
Wow, Shin is the best!
You didn't think Ojo was gonna go down, did you?
Now it's Sakuraba's turn.
Skill is all that counts.
I don't fall for tricks!
There's no need to get upset, Otawara.
Just do what you usually do and you should beat them easily.
Okay, I'll get 'em this time!
That's right, we've forgotten what got us here!
How Ojo plays!
Let's believe in ourselves and play how we always do!
Set, hut!
I've had enough of you!
It doesn't matter if they know the route!
We've got our height!
Yeah, it's the Everest Pass!
So this is it...
Touchdown! Game over!
Bando Spiders 3 - Ojo White Knights 14
Ojo delivers!
Ojo really showed us what they're made of today.
Don't give your opponent any opportunities,
no matter who they are.
That's how Ojo fights.
Aww, man...
I said we had a chance to win...
But they were a bad match for us.
We hit our limits.
And the Tokyo tournament final will be
the Ojo White Knights against the Seibu Wild Gunmen!
Sakuraba's the best!
Way to go Ojo!
They're amazing!
Shoot, if only Akaba had been able to play...
We couldn't do anything about today.
But today is exactly six months since Akaba transferred back to Bando,
so from now on he can be an active member of the team!
Unlike Ojo, we match up against the Deimon Devil Bats...
...very well.
Very smartly!
Shin!
I swear we'll win the third place tiebreaker.
And then we'll play Ojo in the Kanto Tournament...
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Bando is strong.
With Akaba on the field, they'll be even better.
Right!
Hey, Shin!
Get on the bus!
No, I think I'll run back.
The tournament isn't over yet.
Shin...
We won't lose.
We'll beat Bando!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Last year's Tokyo MVP, huh?
Do we have another rival waiting?
Huh?
What's that kick tee for?
That's Musashi...
Musashi? You mean the high-schooler who looks like he's 40?
Yeah, what's he up to?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Come back, Musashi! Ya-ha!
What's "boioioioing" supposed to mean?
What're you sulking for?
You only snapped a string, go get a new one.