Okay, come on!
Ya-ha!
Bando Spiders vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Set, hut!
Akaba had been anticipating this!
Whoops! Kobayakawa's been squashed again!
They've got 45 yards between them and the goal.
This'll be tough...
Akaba's stopped both our passes and runs.
All that's left is kicking...
Like we've got someone here who can make a 45-yard kick!
Darn it!
We desperately need a kicker with us now!
There's only one other person who could do it!
This is the game that will determine
who will get the final seat to the Kanto Tournament.
It's the ultimate battle between
the Bando Spiders and the Deimon Devil Bats!
Will Bando win? Or will it be Deimon?!
The score's 20-6!
Bando's got a 14 point lead!
You're late!
You're 13,297 hours and 49 minutes late!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Time has Begun Again!
You're late, Old fart!
Musashi!
Musashi...
He's back... to the max?
Musashi is...
...an ancient...
...old fart?
Mu...sa... MUSASHI!
You've come back to us!
You're back-!
Sorry...
...I've put you through so much, Kurita...
That's okay!
Don't worry about that any!
We don't have time to be gettin' all emotional, Fatty!
Y-You're right!
This isn't the time to be crying!
Here's the kicking tee you were supposed to use way back when.
It's even got dirt on it from then.
And coincidentally,
we need you to kick a 45-yarder just like we did then.
Go finish what you left behind!
Up until now Deimon hasn't had a kicker.
That was Deimon's greatest weakness.
But even so, Hiruma never went searching for a new kicker.
It was all for today!
He believed in him more than anyone else.
He believed that Musashi would return to the field!
Well, the legendary kicker,
the 60-Yard Magnum Musashi,
has finally returned to Deimon!
So he's finally made his appearance.
Show me what you've got, Musashi!
Let's see your kicks!
Will he be able to nab this play?!
There's 45 yards to the goal!
It's just like the 45-yard kick we needed in that last game
the three of us played together.
It's like time has begun again!
The time that had been frozen is moving once more!
Don't tell me you've gotten soft
after not having played for a year and half, ya old fart!
Don't make me laugh, ya stupid demon!
We've gotta block for him!
Musashi's finally come back to us!
It'd stink if we didn't block well and he misses the goal.
You bet!
Leave it to us!
We're awesome when we wanna be!
That's way men oughta be!
I-I feel like my blood's running cold...
But it's... a good feeling.
Set, hut!
Block!
The kicking lane-!
They got through!
How can this be?!
The kicking course's been blocked!
The field goal was good!
Did I just do something now?
How interesting...
Yay!
Musashi!
- You're cool!
Good goin', Musashi!
So cool!
You're awesome!
Bando Spiders 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
The first half's over!
Bando Spiders 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 9
Deimon's behind by 11 points!
I can't believe he was in Deimon!
It's the legendary 60-Yard Magnum,
Takekura Gen!
A-Awesome!
Did you see that...
...just now?
J-Just watching that made my blood run cold...
M-Musashi...
No, Mr. Musashi!
We always knew that you'd come back!
We believed in you.
Sorry I made you worry.
Please let me go with you...
...to the Christmas Bowl!
- Sure!
Bring it on, Musashi!
Now the contest to see who's the number one kicker will begin!
You ignoring me?! HUH?!
Welcome back, Musashi!
Old fart!
You're really awesome!
Of course he is!
He's not like you're typical old-looking high schooler!
Sweet!
So the kicker Deimon's been waiting for has returned!
Let's zoom to the lead in the second half!
- Boo-yah!
This is a great feeling!
Just that one kick has changed our entire attitude!
We can do it!
Coach,
I know this is shameless of me,
but I've returned to the field.
Thanks for coming back.
Musashi!
Lookie, here's a cake to celebrate!
I've kept it for the past year and a half,
believing that we'd be reunited again someday!
It's a year and half old?!
I'll pass.
It's probably covered in mold.
He calmly turned it down!
He's gotta be the warrior type!
He's the same type as me!
- Get real!
Huddle up, ladies!
Listen up!
We've gotta break free from
Bando's Spider's Web if we're gonna win!
That's right.
Just because Musashi's back doesn't mean...
If we don't do something about their offense,
Kotaro will get off another kick before we even touch the ball!
They sometimes feint doing a field goal...
...and have Akaba run instead.
What a pain!
Y-Yeah....
Quit dilly-dallying and go at them
like your lives are on the line!
Right?
Got that right, Old fart!
Let's go!
Quit lazing around and get going, kiddies!
He's right.
We've got to take the lead!
We're finally all together!
All of the Deimon Devil Bats' members are together!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
When do you get to kick?
The hint is that it depends on the game.
There's the kickoff at the beginning of the game
and the field goal kick when you're going for points.
Remember that there are different types of kicks for different situations.
Ya-ha!
Well then, the second half's starting!
Deimon's down to just an 11 point gap,
but will they be able to take the lead?!
We've got Musashi with us now!
There's no way we can lose!
Their courage has increased a hundred-fold
with Musashi joining the ranks!
They've already stolen back possession!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
- Yay!
This is great!
We can do it!
It's all thanks to Musashi coming back...
Deimon's gained more than just a kicker.
They've gained more courage.
Up until now Yoichi Hiruma's been supporting them by himself...
But now we've got all the support we need!
We can do it! We can really do it!
For better or worse,
the Deimon Devil Bats have always been
Yoichi Hiruma's one-man team.
But it'll be different now.
Deimon needs to be watched carefully now, more than ever before.
Deimon's Musashi has gone for the field goal!
It's insanely powerful!
T-The uprights...
...it's gonna hit them!
It barely made it!
Bando Spiders 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 9
Bando Spiders 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
They're down to an eight point gap!
That barely even made it, you stupid old fart!
Who cares if it goes in?
As always, your kick's powerful but wild.
That was smart!
They did it!
It was a beautiful kick!
How's that, Musashi?!
It doesn't matter if you're on Deimon's team again!
The Bando Spiders are still the strongest kickers out there!
Bando Spiders 20 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
It's back to an 11 point gap!
Bando Spiders 23 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
They truly are a master kicking team.
That's our Bando Spiders!
They bet all of their youth in kicking!
They cry when they kick,
laugh when they kick and come back to life when they kick!
They're a bunch of rockabillies!
You're really excited aren't you, Sanada?
But now that Musashi's back and Deimon's really pumped up!
But will they be able to break free from the dreaded Spider's Web?!
Here it comes!
There it is! The onside kick!
Go, Peewee!
As long as I know where it's landing...
Too bad, Sena.
I won't let you get it!
Amazing! Musashi kicked back the ball!
It's a free ball as long as it's in the air since it's still onside.
Wow! Watch it go!
And go!
That's just how high it's going!
Your exaggerations are a good match for Sanada's.
Don't get it!
Sena will grab it if you fumble!
Wait for it to go outta bounds!
At last! At long last!
They've broken free of the Bando's Spider's Web!
- They did it!
- Yay!
They stole possession from Bando.
But there's even more to that onside kick return than just that.
They've rendered the Spider's Web's infinite loop ineffective.
Musashi!
The kicking battle between the two of us is the key battle in this game!
This is going to be the greatest kicking contest ever!
And the prize will be the final seat to the Kanto Tournament!
Fine.
I'll go along with that.
H-He actually said that!
He's so cool!
He really is a warrior, a true warrior!
Fine! I'll go along with that!
- This doesn't involve you!
Somehow the Bando Spiders have moved
from just barely in front of their goal to
just 36 yards away from the opponent's goal!
I'm the number one kicker!
He did it!
Kotaro scored another field goal!
Bando Spiders 23 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
Bando Spiders 26 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
Bando's attacking again!
Now Musashi did it!
Bando Spiders 26 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
My, oh my!
Bando Spiders 26 - Deimon Devil Bats 15
It's a raging battle of kicks verses kicks!
I-I've never seen a fight like this before!
You're pretty good, Musashi!
Back at ya!
This has become a pretty smart-looking kicking contest!
But you see...
I'll NEVER lose in a kicking contest!
For the sake of our coach that had to quit because of us,
I can't step down even a little!
I can't step down, either.
I'm fighting for my friends who've been waiting for me!
I've got to clean up what I left behind way back then!
Neither one of them... is relinquishing even a little!
What a fierce wind!
This is some pretty nasty weather.
The sky's even turned dark...
Maybe a storm's coming?
What a wind! Something's in my eyes!
That's right...
I'm not wearing my eye shield anymore.
This wind's really strong!
I can spin around more than usual now!
I feel like this strong wind is making my blood turn cold...
You've already used that line!
That's your third time! Your THIRD TIME!
You trying to stand out or something?
But this wind really is something.
What on earth's going on here?!
This fierce wind is absolutely crazy!
Are the heavens saying that they won't let anyone
easily steal the final seat to the Kanto Tournament?!
This is the first time we've played a game in such wind.
This will have a huge impact on who will win the second half.
This fortissimo gale...
It could be the Bando Spiders...
Interesting.
This is the Deimon Devil Bats'...
- ...big chance.
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Ya-ha!
With Musashi back, Deimon's a hundred times more powerful!
Now we've got a max clear path to victory!
But will he be able to kick against these strong winds?
Just let the winds help push the ball along!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Demon Within the Storm! Ya-ha!
Mama, lookie!
Three advertisement balloons are whirling around!
I'm a human!
I'm a HUMAN!