Let's see, our next opponent will be
the winner of the Dokubari Scorpions and Jujika Priests.
I wonder how tough they are.
Either way, we'll smash 'em to the max!
We got it!
Master!
Watch out!
H-Holy cow!
Y-You're so slim but you chucked a giant like Kurita over your head...
How did you do it?!
Are you all right, Kurita?
Y-Yes...
W-Wait, you're-
O-O-Onihei!
Onihei...?
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Refined Spirit of a Lineman!
Kurita, I watched your game the other day.
O-Oh!
You've formed a pretty decent team.
Y-Yes, I think we might be able to hold our own against yours, Onihei...
Are these your teammates?
Y-Yes!
They're awfully small.
But football's not just about size and power.
It's about here.
Kurita, this is my last year, too... My last chance.
O-Oh...
This year... I'M going to the Christmas bowl.
Ah! We won't lose, either!
You've gained a lot of confidence, I see.
Later.
O-Okay!
Kurita... that guy...
Who was he?
Right, well,
he's the captain of the Hashiratani Deer, Onihei Yamamoto!
The #1 lineman ever!
The Hashiratani Deer?
That means...
That face...
And posture...
He's still in high school?!
High schooler
You three!
At least try to remember what the star players on the tough teams look like!
Oh, Coach Doburoku...
Is he really that great?
He's been a linebacker since he was in grade school,
and his experience is second to none. He's the ultimate veteran player.
The ultimate veteran...
He took a huge guy like Kurita and tossed him around like nothing.
Onihei's been polishing his moves.
The Hashiratani Deer...
if we both keep winning, we'll play them in the third round!
Onihei!
Why is he so excited about our opponent?
Well, to Kurita, Onihei's like the master of his dreams...
...or something.
Master of his dreams?
Master's master?
Basically, Kurita came to love REAL football because of Onihei.
"Real" football?
The first time I met Onihei
was after Hiruma, Musashi and I formed a football team in middle school.
As the Mao Devil Bats,
we challenged all sorts of other teams so we could get some experience.
Of course, everyone besides the three of us were just loaner players from other teams.
But regardless, we still managed to win our fair share.
What do you think?
We could be in trouble.
A-Are you okay?
You mean THE Onihei Yamamoto?
You got a problem with that?
N-No, not really, it's just-
I like it.
Everyone seems to think this Onihei guy's a formidable lineman.
That's exactly the kinda I guy I wanna face!
B-But we're not really that good yet...
That's exactly why we're playing him, Fatty.
You think we'll be okay?
Do we really measure up to them?
What're you so afraid of!
Well, his name means "Ogre Soldier," it sounds kind of scary...
And strong... And violent...
He's a middle schooler, just like us.
There's nothing to be scared of.
I-I hope so...You're sure?
See, he looks scary!
- You're all first years?
- Yes
You're big!
Y-Yes!
I'm in my second year at Hashiratani middle school - Onihei Yamamoto.
You are?
Kur...ita.
Nice to meet you.
Y-Yes!
Set, hut, hut!
Hmm, he's pretty good.
You live up to your reputation.
You're not so bad yourself.
You've got a solid line.
You okay?
Onihei, we can't even move that Kurita kid an inch.
We need to slip past him and-
Slip?
You wuss, don't run away!
Charge straight at him!
- Got it?
- Yes!
Set, hut, hut!
Hey... Could he be...
Set, hut!
I'm sorry...
That lousy bum...
Setting a trap?
W-Why?
Set, hut hut hut!
Touchdown!
W-What happened?
Why, why?
I guess he figured us out.
Football Clinic!
What's a "scramble?"
When the quarterback holds on to the ball and runs.
It's an emergency fallback play when you just can't complete a pass! Ya-ha!
Kurita...
You were held in place by a slim guy like him?
So... how'd he do it?
Basically, he exploited Kurita's biggest weakness.
His biggest weakness?
What is... What is going on...?
How can you stop me all by yourself?
I'm bigger than you... How are you...
Wait, I mean, umm-
That lousy jerk!
Leave 'em alone.
Fine... I'll explain it.
Set, hut, hut!
Don't underestimate real football!
What?!
H-How...?
Stand up, Kurita!
The game's not over!
Touchdown!
This... This is just...
Kurita, do you understand why you can't tackle me?
Y-Your technique is too-
Wrong!
As a lineman, your size is an incredible weapon!
But you're too nice,
and that niceness makes you hold back from tackling at full force.
You handle them with kid gloves!
K-Kid gloves...?
You're thinking, "If I hit too hard the other team will get injured."
I-I am?
That kind of defense has no effect whatsoever
on a true berserker offense!
N-No way...
Look, Kurita.
Your soft-heartedness is destroying your teammates.
Someone who isn't thinking, "I'll crush them with everything I got
and protect my team even if it kills me!" doesn't deserve to take the field!
Also, Kurita...
If you don't play seriously, football's no fun.
Y-Yes!
If you understand now, hit me at full blast!
And I'll try to break through with everything I've got!
You totally set that up.
Who, me?
Set, hut, hut!
That's it! Good, Kurita!
That was when I finally got it,
what it really means to put your heart and soul into blocking.
Heart and soul...
Wow...
Onihei's an incredible person!
Yup!
So we're gonna have to play this incredible guy, huh?
I want to see for myself...
I want to see what kind of moves Onihei has!
Hashiratani's game is tomorrow.
Okay! We gotta go watch!
Yeah! We'll cheer them on!
Yeah!
Today's final game is about to commence!
The Kyoshin Poseidons against the wily veterans,
the Hashiratani Deer!
It's them!
It takes but a look at his back to understand this man's long, storied history!
Lead by the venerable Onihei Yamamoto, the Hashiratani Deer!
Onihei!
What's up with our section?
It's all dudes...
I... understand.
Ah, you came, Kurita?
Y-Y-Yup!
We're going to win this game... and you'll be next.
We won't hold back.
R-Right!
Holy smokes!
He went right into serious mode!
Y-Yeah.
You da man, Onihei! Go!
Go, Hashiratani!
They went right into fan mode...
Most of the guys on both teams are pretty short.
Their height might be the same, but their skill levels are totally different!
- Nice.
- He got through!
They've got killer blocking teamwork.
The Hashiratani Deer break through the center!
Go, go, Deer!
His build's nothing special...
So what is it about this Onihei guy?
He's mastered the basic things you three learned on the death march to the highest level.
He worked his way up step by step, then?
Yeah.
Touchdown!
Kyoshin Poseidons 0 - Hashiratani Deer 6
The Deer take a six point lead!
Within three minutes!
Wow!
Set, hut, hut!
Uh oh, Kyoshin's quarterback gets sacked!
Yeah! Onihei, Onihei!
The Hashiratani Deer are simply overpowering!
This is shaping up to be a David and Goliath situation!
Onihei really is awesome!
Onihei shows us the refined spirit of a true lineman!
A man, 18 years old, in his final season!
Kyoshin Poseidons 0 - Hashiratani Deer 14
It's no good... We can't stop 'em...
Ahh well.
Whoa, who're those big beanpoles?
They've gotta be 180 centimeters...
No, maybe almost two meters!
What's this? Kyoshin's sent in some new blood!
And look how tall they are!
Bigger isn't always better.
Just because they're tall doesn't mean they're any good!
Onihei!
Kyoshin Poseidons 23 - Hashiratani Deer 14
Kyoshin Poseidons 24 - Hashiratani Deer 14
I wasn't blessed with a football player's build.
But...
My technique and spirit's always been enough
to blow past linebackers twice my size!
Don't get cocky, kid!
I've got ten years of experience!
No... This is my last chance...
Losing to these smart-mouthed jerks...
...at a time like this...
No!
Kyoshin Poseidons 31 - Hashiratani Deer 14
Game over!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
A fearsome new opponent shows up in the form of the Kyoshin Poseidons!
Is this really the time for Deimon to be hanging out eating barbecue?!
While too much of any food can be harmful,
when building your physique, meat is suitable nourishment.
Oh, serious business!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Courage to Stand Firm! Ya-ha!
Hey, Mr. Senior.
I guess this WAS the battle of David and Goliath, huh?
On-Oni-Onihei...
Sorry I had to drag you guys out!
Why'd we have to reveal our secret weapon in the early rounds?
This is a TOURNAMENT.
If we lose, we go home.
O-Onihei...
...lost?
Who are they?