Shinryuji Nagas vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha.
This's why 11 of me would make the ultimate team!
Guess they're not that dumb...
We... we have to do something!
Peewee!
Yes?
From now on,
you're gonna blitz Agon at lightspeed
on every single play.
It doesn't matter if he's carrying the ball or not.
You've thought this through?
If Sena runs that much on defense too,
his legs will give out after a few minutes.
Of course I've thought it through, you old fogey.
If they even score one more point, the game's over.
It's our only hope.
Set!
I know my legs.
I can tell exactly what they're capable of.
If I sprint at lightspeed over and over again,
they'll be worn out in minutes...
But if I slow down even one bit...
I'll never stop Agon!
Hut!
Ahh... Gonna blitz me, huh?
Cheap tricks won't work on Agon.
He can react to anything you do, the moment you do it.
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Power of the Rank and File.
Set, hut!
So you wanna go one-on-one with me till the bitter end, huh?
I have to make it.
Push yourself! Blitz at lightspeed!
Bring it.
Sena!
Pass complete, for a 12 yard gain!
In one smooth motion,
Agon knocked Eyeshield 21's lightspeed blitz aside
with his godlike reflexes
and moved right into a pass!
18 minutes to go with a 25 point difference!
Shinryuji Nagas 32 - Deimon Devil Bats 7
They're trying to stifle them with a blitz.
Eyeshield's going to charge straight for Agon.
It's not a bad plan, but...
Their opponents are too far beyond quirky formations like that.
Agon and Sena are ool-cay, man...
TOO cool...
I mean, if it was me out there, I'd have booked it
and he'd have tackled me before I could even think about passing.
Shoot, it's not working!
That dread-head only has to wait a moment to see what you're doing,
even speed can't trump his crazy reflexes do.
No one expected you to get him on the first try.
Mop-Head's got plenty of excuses for being a pompous smart alec.
Agon Kongo is a true blue prodigy.
I knew it, I...
Even still...
Keep up the pressure, keep fighting him one-on-one.
Concentrate every cell in your body on taking him down.
Turn your legs loose on him.
You're the only one who can do it.
Set...
Don't think about anything else.
Just focus on Agon's movements.
Don't think about anything...
Don't think...
Bu-Bu-But can your legs handle the strain?
All those lightspeed charges are gonna wreck them!
You're hitting your limits!
Can they really last much longer?
The more I try to clear my mind,
the weirder the stray thoughts get...
Brain off!
Concentrate... every cell... all my leg strength!
Hut!
I'm trying to tell you, it ain't gonna work.
You and your garbage team's fall tournament run is done.
"The Christmas Bowl?"
You losers have nursed that stupid dream for four years.
And now it's game over for you, guaranteed.
A short pass!
A four yard gain!
Did he do something?
Nah, nothing major. Nothing at all.
You all right?
Jumonji...
Yeah, I just stumbled a little...
We won't let you carry the whole burden.
'Cause we don't let anyone...
...throw us around.
I'm not going down again, either!
Me neither!
Let's do it!
Guys...!
Peewee's blitz just gave Mop-Head
30% less free time to find a receiver.
Keep up the blitzing!
What do you think, Shin?
Is Eyeshield going to blitz Agon every time?
Playing defense well demands you read the opponent
with an almost animal instinct.
Set...
He doesn't have enough experience to possess that instinct yet.
However, if he only has one target,
and remains completely focused on a single opponent...
Hut!
We're no fools, Deimon!
The Dragonfly can adapt to anything!
Is it Agon or Unsui?
"Shishi Hakuto!"
Neither!
Running back #20 is going up the middle!
Another of our many illusions!
It's a back pass to Agon!
Watch Agon.
Only Agon.
Stinkin' trash...
Watch Agon!
- Sena!
He blocked Sanzo's back pass to Agon!
That should've been in Eyeshield's blind spot!
How did he fly in from the side?!
Humans can't move like that!
He wasn't even paying attention to the ball.
Eyeshield is so focused that he was simply mirroring Agon's movements.
- Get it!
Shinryuji reacted too fast!
They're all at the ball already!
Don't let 'em touch it!
When did he-?!
Monta!
Where the heck did Monta come from?!
He got a head start.
The moment he saw Eyeshield 21 make that sideways leap, he...
...he was already chasing the fumble!
I knew he'd do it!
I knew Sena could block that pass!
F-Faith!
"Optimistic" would be the better word!
Sena and I are taking back the ball!
What?!
I told you, you can't win.
You'll never be tops in the air as long as I'm alive, monkey man.
No way...! I started way before him!
Yes! Nice work, Ikkyu!
Smash that whole nest of bugs with your super splash,
the "Kuri-Hammer!"
What incredible force!
Enemy and ally alike are squashed!
You big-!
Jumonji!
The Delinquent Deathblow!
He's got it!
Jumonji picks up the blocked pass!
And now it's a mad dash for the goal line!
Yes, no one's behind me!
They're still flat on their-
What?!
Here comes Agon!
He was just trapped in that mess, and he's already closing in!
Jumonji!
On no! He's stopped just inches from the end zone!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
On no! He's stopped just inches from the end zone!
Shoot...! This hurts...
He's so fast... and so strong...
You've been taking him on this WHOLE TIME, Sena?!
Then I can't go down without a fight either!
I may not have a lifetime of leg training like you, Sena...
I've punched,
tackled,
and fought my way through life since middle school!
Sorry, dread-head...
I'm taking one last step!
T-Touchdown!
Yes!
This is Jumonji's first touchdown, isn't it?!
Actually, it's the first time he's ever carried the ball!
Riko, Riko.
Anyway, despite playing a position that's never meant to touch the ball,
Jumonji shows his tenacity and scores a touchdown!
I'm very impressed! Back to you.
Oh, uh...
The Deimon Devil Bats have descended on him!
Rock on!
That was max awesome!
Nice!
You rule, Kazu!
Even though they're outmatched individually,
together they wrench the ball away for an incredible play!
The Deimon Devil Bats go from a dire situation, down 32-0,
Shinryuji Nagas 32 - Deimon Devil Bats 14
but have rapidly closed the gap to 32-14!
Hey, Sena.
We're all sick of that rastafarian freak
calling us trash and garbage.
Rip him apart!
Right!
Oh no... My legs...
We've got a chance to come back... and I'm...
Sena? What's up?
Uh oh... This can't be...
You forgot to go pee during halftime, didn't you?!
No no no no...
Your legs...
Time out.
His knees are on fire!
I thought he'd last a little longer.
Doesn't matter, Shinryuji's about to go on offense again.
If they even score once, we're cooked.
If we bench Peewee now,
we've got no one left who can stop Agon.
Hiruma!
I mean... I know...
You're right, but...
What calm, cold rage...
In Agon's eyes, everyone out here is like a worm crawling in the dirt.
His eyes only see one thing now...
Sena Kobayakawa.
He hasn't had that look since he went up against Shin last year.
Good.
That's good.
Keep looking at whoever's got your attention.
Even a million rank and file players...
...could never awaken your true power,
that unstoppable violence!
Presenting Doburoku's patented sub-zero ice wraps.
This will cool down your muscles
and prevent your ligaments from stretching too far.
It's temporary, but it's better than nothing.
Wow!
They feel so light now!
Sweet, max healing!
That's better than casting white magic!
You dunce. All I did was numb the pain with extreme cold.
We've only got two more timeouts we can use to ice you down...
It all comes down to how long you can last.
I want to stop him...
Sena, please...
Mamori...?
Sena!
Win...!
Right!
What's Deimon's plan?
Knowing Hiruma,
- he's gotta be prepping for some crazy-
- Huh?
We just have to keep wrecking them with the Dragonfly.
Fine... the Dragonfly it is.
Eyeshield's on the ropes,
we can't give him any time to rest.
Set!
The Dragonfly again.
They're trying to finish it.
Agon's acknowledging him...
Hut!
Acknowledging that Sena Kobayakawa...
...has set foot into the top tier of players!
But you're the strongest of them all, Agon!
I'll make sure you are... through the Dragonfly!
Beat him!
Here it comes...
Crunch him!
Agon keeps the ball and runs for seven yards!
Sena actually tried to block Agon's chop!
But he still got knocked aside...
Dude, that was cool to the max!
Way to go, Sena!
I mean, you got slammed...
...but you blocked his hit with your ARM!
That was like watching two karate masters going at it!
Oh, no... it wasn't anything special,
I've just been watching Agon so closely
and didn't feel like getting hit again,
so I just kinda thrust my arm up, or something...
- Yeah, and it was awesome!
Remember girls,
don't even think about quitting!
- Ya-ha!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Oh man, Sena's legs are at their limit!
You're gonna have to step up, Butt-Monkey!
Shoot... No matter what I do, I can't beat Ikkyu!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Fighting to be Number One!
Ya-ha!
Eyeshield 21 is, as usual, evolving as the game continues,
and Agon Kongo has realized he's a threat.
How far can you climb, Eyeshield 21?