- The Cream Puff Cup?!
Wha-?
What the heck's that, Hiruma?
Tell 'em, Manajerk!
Really! I wish you wouldn't call me that!
Okay, let's see.
Take a look at this world map.
The Cream Puff Cup is...
an international good-will tournament
held by high schoolers from around the world.
First off we'll start with the team representing America,
the homeland of football.
They're the NASA Aliens, now known as the NASA Shuttles.
The NASA Shuttles?
You don't mean...?
It'll have Panther!
And Homer and Watt! They're in the Shuttles!
Don't forget the Gonzales brothers' Muscle Barrier...
That was so annoying.
Representing Africa will be the Savanna Survivors.
And representing Russia and all of Europe
will be the Northern Light Blizzards.
I've never heard of them before...
Of course not.
After all, countless high schools
from all around the world have football teams.
And finally, representing Asia will be the Deimon Devil Bats!
Sweet!
- I've heard of them before!
- You better have!
That was so lame...
...that it's not even worth joking about.
These four teams will fight each other
in order to win the Cream Puff Cup.
But...
I've never heard of that tournament before.
I know! It just started this year!
The Americans in charge of this
invited us to participate in the tournament
after the NASA Shuttles recommended us.
So basically,
the Shuttles want a chance to get revenge, right?
Their coach's so spiteful.
What a coach!
But we were the ones that lost...
So then,
this is a quick little competition that's being held between
the Tokyo and Kanto Tournaments.
So Ojo and Seibu...
...and all of the other power houses
will be doing last-minute training.
Listen up, ladies!
It's important for our team
to gain some more real game experience!
So we've gotta win!
- Ya-ha!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Let it Begin! The Cream Puff Cup!
Oh, my! Long time no see!
Oh! You were here last time.
Aren't you the same stewardess as when we
came to America for the death march?
I see that you've made some more friends.
Enjoy the flight, little stuffed doggy,
little stuffed piggy
and little stuffed sumo wrestler.
But I'm a human!
No way...
There's no way this thing can fly!
Not hungry, Kazu?
It's pretty good!
There's no way this hunk of metal can fly!
What are you doing?
Huh? Er, well...
I thought I'd take some pictures
of the heroes who led Deimon to victory...
Ta-da!
Has an angel bless them or a demon charmed them?!
It's an outright miracle that the Deimon Devil Bats
made it to the Kanto Tournament!
That's...
- T-That voice-!
I talk as fast as a machine gun shoots
and pump up the crowds like nothing else!
I'm Machine gun Sanada!
And this here is the burning hot
Bomberhead Kumabukuro's beloved daughter!
This lovely high school reporter's cute little eyes
glimmer with the fierce passion that only youth brings!
I'm Riko Kumabukuro.
You mean Mr. Kumabukuro's...
The announcer's...
I'm going to the Cream Puff Cup
to be an announcer and cover it live for Daddy.
So wish me luck!
Calm down!
Jumonji!
There's no way this lump of metal can fly!
Looks like you've got a pretty lively team.
I should take some pictures!
Long time no see!
Panther, you're heavy...
You were amazing, Sena!
Devil Bat Ghost!
Devil Bat Hurricane!
I saw it all through the internet!
Man, I wanna fight you so bad!
Yeah, I'm really looking forward
to competing with you in this next game.
Woo-sha! Woo-sha!
Welcome, Deimon!
Watt, what the heck are you doing?!
We're celebrating this glorious reunion Japanese-style!
In Japan you celebrate times like this with festivals, right?
That's not...
...quit right.
How have you all been doing?
Huh?
Team Deimon,
we may have only beaten you by one point last time,
but we'll beat you by 100 points this time!
Isn't that...?
Yeah, it's Coach Apollo.
Mr. Apollo, I hope you're not underestimating my Deimon.
As their trainer, I've...
Are you their trainer?
No, I'm not. He is.
I'm just a worthless drunkard of a trainer, after all...
It's been a while, Apollo!
Hmm...
So you're STILL playing football.
M-Morgan?!
Who's Morgan?
A former super-star that's currently working as the NFL's figurehead.
He's the one who got Coach Apollo kicked off the team
back when he was still playing.
So why's he here?
The winners of this year's Cream Puff Cup
will be my Northern Light Blizzards,
representing Russia and Europe.
The Northern Light Blizzards?!
My, my!
The fires of animosity
- are already blazing brightly!
- Picture time!
This is a big scope! Flash 'n snap!
I've turned the Shuttles into the best team out there!
Everyone's put a lot of hard work into their training
in order to win this tournament!
There isn't a team out there that could stand up to us!
Worked hard? Trained? What nonsense!
That's about as worthless as snot
when going up against people with superior physiques.
T-That's uncalled for...
The fact that I'm a top player is a proof of that!
And I'm gonna beat everyone again!
Think back and remember!
Which one of us...
...always wound up on top, me or a you, a third-rate player?
What?!
Coach isn't a third-rate player!
He was able to turn us into the ultimate team!
We'll never lose to you!
How interesting.
You're mistaken if you think that you're a good coach
just because you were a good player.
We'll prove to you just how great we are!
I challenge you, Morgan!
It's between us,
no the Blizzards or the NASA Shuttles!
The losing team has to disband!
Now he's done it...
Can't blame him, though.
Yeah! There's no going back now!
Very well. I accept your challenge.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us about Yocchie's position as quarterback!
The hint is good decision-making skills?
The key is to be able to quickly decide where to throw the ball.
And when you can't throw it, it's okay to make a run for it.
Don't be indecisive! Ya-ha!
Hurray! The first annual Cream Puff Cup is about to begin!
We weren't given a budget, so we couldn't rent our own booth...
Let me introduce the participating high school teams!
I'll start off with the crowd's favorite,
the team representing America!
It's the NASA Shuttles!
Let's see...
This team was originally known as the Aliens,
but had to change their name to Shuttles when they lost a bet
by failing to beat the Devil Bats by ten points.
Ya-ha!
And next up is our team representing Asia!
It's the super-offensive demonic team,
the Deimon Devil Bats!
Although they used to lack a kicker,
they now have the legendary
60-Yard Magnum Musashi on their team.
Between him and their lightspeed ace Sena Kobayakawa,
also known as Eyeshield 21,
it'll be impossible for anyone to keep their eyes off of them!
And representing Africa we've got a team
that prides themselves on their speed and great jumps,
the Savanna Survivors!
They all look the same!
Yay! It's the first time
they've ever said "Ha-ha" in America!
I'm afraid not, Suzuna.
They did it plenty of times during the Death March.
Our manager...
...sure remembers...
...strange things.
All of the players in the Survivors are over two meters tall!
They're huge!
Isn't our first match...
...against them?
And last by not least
are our representatives for Russia and Europe!
They've been instructed by an NFL super-star,
Coach Morgan!
They're the Northern Light Blizzards!
Let's see...
This is... well... a complete mystery!
I can't find anything on them.
They're like those mysterious crop circles
or maybe the Russian version of Area 51!
I-I have no idea what you just said...
In that case,
why don't we give them
a fabulous little demonstration?
What is he up to?
The Northern Light Blizzards'
quarterback, Nikolai Nikolaevich.
Goodness gracious!
His fast yet super accurate pass managed
to hit a bird when it was in mid-air!
Did you see that?
That was Nikolaevich's Soyuz Pass!
The Soyuz Pass is named after the Russian spacecraft Soyuz.
He's gonna be a handful...
And next is our linebacker, Ivan Ivanov!
Bring it!
He's supposed to be a linebacker like Shin,
but he's so big!
Mammoth ATTACK!
Amazing! He split that log right in half!
That was Ivan's Mammoth Attack.
One hit from that, and you're outta the game!
Amazing!
At this rate, the Shuttles...
...are going to get killed!
But they've got Panther and Watt with them.
I know that the NASA Shuttles'll win!
Whatcha think, Apollo?
You can forfeit now before you die
of embarrassment during the game.
I'll even let you out of your little bet
if you forfeit before the game.
Enough! The Shuttles are gonna win!
We can do it!
Yeah!
This should make for a good game!
Space!
Blizzards vs. Shuttles
Mammoth!
At long last the first round in Block A is about to begin!
The first game in the Cream Puff Cup
is the NASA Shuttles versus
the Northern Light Blizzards!
I'm excited... and happy... and excited!
The Blizzards are amazing,
but there's no way the Shuttles will lose
as long as Panther's with them.
The Blizzards are starting the game with a kickoff!
Panther made a super fast return!
Wow, he's fast!
Go, Panther!
Amazing!
So that's Panther's famous Zero-G running!
His Zero-G running's gotten even faster!
They keep popping up no matter how many times I pass them!
W-What's going on?!
This is the Northern Light Blizzards'
Russian Roulette Formation.
They got Panther!
They're really strong!
I can't believe he stopped Panther!
But at this distance,
Homer should be able to use his
Shuttle Pass to score some points.
I doubt that.
I don't think they're that stupid.
Huh? Yocchie, what...?
What do you mean?
The Blizzards have that Snowman's Mammoth Attack.
If I was the Blizzards' coach,
I'd want to use that Snowman
to either stop Panther
or keep Homer from making Shuttle Passes.
Stop him?
You see, the Shuttle's primary offense
is centered around Panther and Homer.
Even if they could catch up to Panther,
it'd cost them some precious time,
so they'd go after...
Homer!
Set, hut, hut!
Use Muscle Barrier!
Don't let them pull off a blitz!
The Shuttles are protecting Homer with their Muscle Barrier!
Run for it, Watt, Panther!
- Okay!
Let's do a Shuttle Pass!
Mammoth ATTACK!
The Mammoth Attack bursts forth!
It landed a direct hit on Homer!
T-That was really powerful!
I wonder if he's okay!
Homer, are you okay?
His shoulder's hurt!
Homer's shoulder has been injured,
so he's out of the game!
Now the Shuttles are in a real bind!
Football's a battleground where you must kill or be killed.
It's just like Hiruma said.
B-But this is cruel!
The Shuttles failed to gain their first down,
so offense goes to the Blizzards.
Set, hut!
It's went low?!
Touchdown!
They did it!
They made a super low, light speed pass!
I've never seen a pass this fast before!
It really was amazing!
So that's Nikolai's Soyuz Pass!
He threw the ball between the line's legs!
No fair!
Those players are working as blinders,
making it impossible to see where his pass'll go.
It's 31-14!
The NASA Shuttles aren't the likely candidate
to win the Cup anymore!
See that, Apollo?
We're natural geniuses!
Hard work and training are worthless!
If only Homer hadn't gotten injured!
Don't be a sore loser.
Our players are nothing more than parts of a machine.
If one of them breaks, just replace it with a new one!
You should have had some spare parts ready beforehand!
No way...
We're not "parts!"
No, that's wrong! It's messed up!
I can't believe this team was representing America.
Both the players and the coach were all third-rate!
And now you have to disband, just like we agreed.
We've worked hard and practiced...
And we've come this far by believing in each other.
There's no way were just some parts!
That can't be true!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Hey, hey!
Are the Shuttles really disbanding?!
They're all going their own ways.
We can't let that happen!
We've gotta do something!
Hey, Sena, go knock some sense into them!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: A New Trial. Ya-ha!
Please remember to take all of your belongings.
Here's a stuffed dog,
a stuffed pig,
and a stuffed sumo wrestler.
But I'm a human!