Deimon...
...touchdown!
YA-HA!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Post-Battle!
Shinryuji Nagas 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 36
Folks, we have just witnessed a true miracle.
The best team in Kanto, the Shinryuji Nagas,
have, unbelievably,
been eliminated from the Kanto Tournament
in the first round!
And the tenacious Deimon Devil Bats score an upset victory!
Deimon is just... incredible!
I'm moved!
Oh, what's this?
Devil Bats, Devil Bats!
The stadium has exploded into a gigantic Devil Bats chant!
We... we won...
Sena...
C'mon, Mamo!
I'm so happy...
...that I played football...
...with my friends!
Your happy tears are celebrating the same victory as them.
But this time you should be joining in the celebrating, too.
Get out there.
Right!
Hey, Yuki!
You've earned this... for playing so hard...
...Kurita!
Try to think ahead, guys.
Idiots...
Way to go, Deimon!
There's a celebratory cheer for ya!
I was thinking about what it'd mean
if they beat Shinryuji, an opponent even WE couldn't beat.
In terms of offensive strength,
Deimon has become the most capable team in Kanto.
They've gotten really good...
they're a dangerous opponent.
Bow!
- Good game!
Ikkyu...
Good game!
Taro Raimon... I'll remember your name.
Yeah...
I don't lose.
Where're you going, Agon?
Get back in line.
Clam it, you blind sack of garbage!
You say monkey boy's hand went out of bounds?!
I'll never accept it!
Stop it, Agon!
Agon!
Shaddap!
There's no way a gifted prodigy like me
could lose to a bunch of trash like Deimon!
A team with 11 of the same player
might end up being really easy to beat.
YOU...!
Agon... forgive me.
A man like you is only born once in a hundred years...
...and I wasn't able to draw our your full strength.
It's my fault we lost!
The spring tournament!
Next spring, you Deimon trash are dead meat.
Yes! We've got all the time in the world now!
We'll take the Dragonfly to the next level!
If any of you drag me down,
I'll toss the lot of you into the waterfall.
Agon...
One more year...
I wish I could play football for Shinryuji for one more year...
All I ever wanted was to play with a serious, motivated Agon...
So the Shinryuji Nagas could be their best!
Ikkyu, you're in charge of the Nagas now.
Understood.
Those guys are way too happy.
We've got a REAL monster waiting for us in the semi-finals.
Yup.
Unlike that slacker Agon,
HE'S a prodigy who's spent his whole life trying to improve.
Ojo will advance very soon, too.
Wait for us, Eyeshield.
I will, Shin.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What do players wear under their uniforms?
It's to save them when things start getting rough!
The gear we wear under our uniforms
that absorb some of the impact are called "protectors."
You get that? Ya-ha!
Are you all right, Sena?
I'm okay...
I don't think so, your knees are so swollen...
Yeah, they look a lot worse than before.
The bones are fine.
Get a good long night's sleep and you'll be all right.
Whew...
Thank goodness.
Now go home, rest, and let your legs recover.
Yes, sir.
I'm home!
Owww...
They're really throbbing.
What a war.
But... we won...
It's all thanks to them that I managed to do it...
Honjo...
I did it.
The ball...
...is mine!
Max Catch!
What?
You helped your teammates pull off the upset?
That's my boy!
Great job, now eat up!
Huh?
You're so full of emotion you can't eat?
I'm taking one last step!
No one can call us trash...
...not anymore!
What's going on here, Kazu?
Don't tell me you're crying.
O-Of course not, dingus!
I noticed you weren't at the convenience store...
Didn't think you'd be out here bawling like a baby!
Lil' ol' Kazu's a big ol' softy!
I said I wasn't crying!
It's cool, man!
Your secret's safe!
I TOLD you-!
Everyone worked so hard.
They beat THE Shinryuji...
It's like a dream...
Sena?
Mamori, Suzuna...
What's up?
I dunno, I couldn't sit still at home...
Sena!
What's up?
We didn't feel like staying home.
I think today...
...calls for a bigger celebration!
Like a team party!
A victory party!
Guys...
I've been through so much...
Discovering football... meeting everyone...
There were tough times, but we stuck it out,
and we beat Shinryuji.
The day Shinryuji rejected me was the saddest day of my life...
But I finally understand.
It was so I could go to Deimon and meet everyone.
I figured you'd be here.
Musashi... Hiruma...
That's close enough.
If Shinryuji couldn't even handle all your power,
I doubt we'd survive.
You did a great job, Kurita.
D-Don't give me too much credit...
You, Sena, Monta, Yukimitsu, the Brothers...
Everyone played their hearts out...
Everyone... I'm just so happy!
Yeah, you're right.
If any one of us had been missing,
we never would've beat Shinryuji.
Hiruma, you're the one who made this wonderful team!
Thank you!
It's a miracle!
Who told you to start putting your faith
in vague things like miracles?
Hiruma...?
Miracles are a load of bull.
We can't rely on them to get to the Christmas Bowl.
Hiruma...
He was about to blush.
Hiruma always says stuff like that when he's really happy.
Oh yeah, we should celebrate!
Let's call everyone!
Good idea.
No one picked up their phone...
I was hoping we could all have a big party...
Don't say that, you and me will have a good time anyway.
Hey, come on, you could at least stop looking depressed!
I guess everyone went to bed early.
Guys!
Kurita, Musashi!
Great timing, we were just about to call you guys!
Everyone felt like celebrating tonight.
And here we are.
I guess we all felt the same way!
Okay, everyone!
- Cheers!
I can finally have sake again!
Hey, Sena!
Ladies and gentlemen,
Deimon's great hope,
Sena a.k.a. Eyeshield 21,
will now give a speech!
C'mon!
Yeah!
Go for it, Sena!
Make it a good one!
You can do it!
Do your best!
Sena!
- S-Sorry, th-thank you, umm-
- There it is!
Classic pointless bowing!
Even beating Shinryuji hasn't changed him.
Come on, Sena!
I never dreamed we would actually win against Shinryuji.
I believe we won because everyone was united in their desire to win.
If any one of us had been absent, we would have lost for sure.
As long as we stick together, we'll win the next one too!
We'll win again and again and again!
Until we...
- Win the Kanto Tournament
- AND the Christmas Bowl!
Yes!
Next game, we beat Ojo!
- Yeah!
I'll be cheering!
I'm already pumped!
Now I'm gonna karaoke to the max!
I've got card tricks!
I know magic!
That's the same thing!
Is not!
Is too, doofus!
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
The Taiyo Sphinx vs. The Hakushu Dinosaurs!
We gotta check this out!
Banba and the Sphinx's heavyweight line aren't gonna lose!
W-What the...? Who's that huge monster?
Next time on Eyeshield 21:
The Dreadnought Team - The Dinosaurs!
Ya-ha!
Hiruma...
You were great.