Oh, I don't care what you say...
I'm a wanderer, wanderin' across the world...
Whatcha think? How's it feel to ride on the "Devil Bat Big Rig?"
This is so cool, one lone road that goes on forever!
The only thing to see outside of town is the horizon.
America's a big country!
Well, you sure saved our bacon.
With this guy in tow, we'd never have been able to hitchhike.
Oh, no, we owe you all for putting us up at your ranch.
Only two more days till our super training!
Boy, someone sure didn't plan ahead, did he?
We're here, Ben Ranch!
It's huge!
Y'all better eat your fill!
Let's chow down!
Get away, Cerberus!
Get away!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
At the Gates of Hell!
I can't eat another bite!
What is wrong with,
you imbecile!
Where's Musashi?!
The three of you made a promise to each other.
To go the Christmas Bowl together!
Shut up!
Musashi will come back.
My plan's perfect.
Then go get him right now!
Right now?
We're not at that step yet.
You lousy...
What was that all about?
Hmm... Who's Musashi?
See, Musashi...
He's our friend, mine and Hiruma's.
Back when we were in middle school...
You made us uniforms?
You always jump into things head first.
We'll call ourselves the Maoh Devil Bats.
If we start playing now, we'll have an advantage in high school.
We're all going to the Christmas Bowl, right?
Y-Yeah! Let's do it!
The Devil Bats?
A giant linebacker who's nothing but pure power.
A long-distance kicker with the face of someone twice his age.
And Satan himself for a quarterback.
They're strong. This team could really be something.
That's Musashi...
Musashi...
The same one who signed that TV?
Yes, all three of us wrote "To the Christmas Bowl!" on there.
So why did he quit?
He... Well, a lot happened.
I see... Now I understand.
What?
Why Hiruma's never looked for a kicker.
He believes Musashi will come back one day.
He's sure.
Hiruma always plans a hundred steps ahead.
There's got to be something more to this training in America, something we don't know about.
So what am I supposed to do...
Sena, I'm ready.
We're gonna get on a huge winning streak!
That'll get this Musashi guy off his butt and make him come back!
I'm sure it will!
Guys!
You're right! Let's win all our games!
We'll win till Musashi comes back!
We're all going to the Christmas Bowl!
They're a good team.
It's so early, what're they doing?
Morning practice?
Tetsuma, slant!
He really explodes out there.
That kind of skill gap is what cost us the Aliens game.
The Gunmen are tough, and they're only getting tougher.
Time for Indian running!
This'll teach you boys how to explode, too!
Jogging in costumes?
How is this gonna help us rush like them?
This is so lame.
Hey, last in line...
Dash up to the front!
Ah, I remember what Indian running is...
You're in last!
It's a Native American ritual, an endurance race wherein the last person in line
must run up to the front, over and over, until everyone's completely exhausted.
By alternating between sprinting and jogging, they alternate between aerobic and anaerobic exercise,
they increase their cardiovascular ability and lung capacity, raise their speed,
and improve their ability to accelerate from-
Too complicated...
Basically, it's practice for explosive dashing.
Anyone who stays in last place for more than a second gets a boiling bath!
That kid has amazing legs.
That's Eyeshield 21.
Even Ojo's Shin can't match him in pure speed.
Still boiling!
A lot's happened, but America's been fun.
It kinda stinks that we're going home tomorrow.
Yeah.
Coming here has really opened my eyes.
I love football as much as Hiruma and Kurita.
I was always a gopher, with no real friends...
Now I have lots of them.
I want to go to the Christmas Bowl with all of them!
And to do that...
I have to beat Shin.
Hey, kiddo.
I hear you wanna be better than Shin.
Try and get through me.
We'll see if you've got a chance.
Okay!
Football Clinic!
What does the offensive line do?
When you're on offense, they protect the QB and running backs!
Blow 'em away with your power! Ya-ha!
Let's see if you can take me.
Come on!
Right!
Awesome cut! You got it!
Here's a little hint for you:
It doesn't matter how fast you are.
That old codger guy's no ordinary drunk!
If a broken-down fogy like me can see Eyeshield's fatal flaw...
then a real defense will mop the floor with him.
Fatal... flaw?
During all those one-on-one runs against Shin and Panther,
did you ever manage to carry the ball straight through either one of them?
So what's his weakness?
Telling you now would be pointless.
Pointless?
You can't beat Shin as you are now.
can't beat Shin...
Your Indian running performance gave me a solid understanding of Deimon's level.
Say this horse is Koigahama...
And the teams get better as you head towards the door.
Koigahama, Zokugaku,
The Devil Bats, and lastly, the Sphinx.
W-What about Ojo and the Seibu Wild Gunmen?
Behind the fence.
Same for the NASA Aliens.
You guys were beyond lucky to come within a point of beating the Aliens.
Also, Seibu and Ojo have a few aces up their sleeve for the fall tournament.
Where would you put Shinryuji?
I'd say... over on America's west coast.
Th-That far?!
Yep, saw that one coming.
You guys are still second-years.
Your last chance will be the fall... of your third year.
I wonder how far you'll all come in a year...
Deimon sports teams can only play up to their second-year fall season.
W-What?! Are you s-serious?!
That's why we're gonna make ourselves into the strongest team with the 40 days we've got left.
Don't be stupid! 40 days isn't nearly enough-
We're doing a death march!
What's that?
Death march?
Marching... to our demise?
No.
That's the one thing I won't allow.
That's not training, it's torture!
The death march is short-sighted stupidity
that can end an athlete's career,
and I'm living proof!
Oh, so you have another way we can become a championship-caliber team in 40 days?!
Well?!
It's our only option!
I came to America ready and willing to do it!
They won't follow you!
I don't care! We're doing it!
You will die.
Never! Not until we're in the Christmas Bowl.
He's desperate... Hiruma's got to do this for himself...
Going home to Japan?
Yes, our training camp ended today.
Here's the deal... Fattycakes and I are staying here in America to train.
Anyone who's sticking with us, cross the line.
No one has ever endured the death march and come out unscathed.
Collapse, and we leave you behind!
There's no guarantee you'll even survive.
So we aren't forcing anyone!
But this fall's tournament has the most competitive lineup in history.
This is the only road to victory.
What's everyone doing out there?
Get on that plane, and you go home to your mothers and a nice warm bed.
But if you're willing to tempt death to get stronger,
rip up your ticket to heaven, and follow us into hell!
This is no one's decision but your own.
Will you return home to peace and quiet?
Or commit suicide by hopping on the Devil Bat Rig?
There's no quitting the death march once you cross that line.
You either endure the 40 days in Hades, or perish!
There's no pressure!
You can still get on the plane and have a nice easy summer vacation back in Japan!
Summer vacation?
That's true... There's a lot of fun to be had back home...
Fireworks, festivals...
Nothing but good times.
But...
Is that really okay?
Is this something I need to do... for myself?
Taro Raimon, #80.
Position: Wide receiver!
My blood type is B!
My favorite food is bananas!
My favorite word is "effort!"
And my favorite sport is-
Okay, okay, that's plenty-
My favorite sport is now American football!
Good!
To me, festivals have always been things I gazed at from my desk.
No more...
Just once, I want to join in the fun!
I'm sick of studying.
Manabu Yukimitsu, #16.
I... don't have a position yet!
Daikichi Komusubi, #55, lineman!
Komusubi!
Pretty cool...
They're gonna spend their vacation doing it up Sparta-style.
Let's roll, Jumonji.
You sure?
These guys are way weaker than us and they're going for it.
Like Yukimitsu...senpai, and Eyeshield 21...
...or rather, Sena!
You're not fooling anyone.
Are you just gonna stand around forever letting people call you useless lost causes?
Skipping class again?
I suppose it's just as well, no high school would ever admit scum like you three!
Jumonji has been hanging out with a bad crowd lately.
Stay away from them.
Bad apples spoil the bunch.
You scream like a girl!
And your stupid blond hair gets on my nerves.
I'll KO you from behind. Koji Kuroki's the name, fighting dirty's my game!
Manga addict, Togano- You're RIPPING it!
Forget the manga!
But now I can't-
Good lord...
Worthless punks...
Remember how we blocked the Aliens for that one second?!
Win, and everyone will respect you. That's what football's about!
What do you think, Togano? Jumonji's all psyched up.
It's gonna be rough not having any manga to read,
but I guess American comics will do.
One, two...
Kazuki Jumonji, #51. Position: Lineman!
Koji Kuroki, #52. Ditto.
Shozo Togano, #53. Same here.
Guys!
That's it... Everyone's playing football to become the men they truly want to be!
I know what I have to do... I want the same thing!
I'll train hard with my friends and get stronger!
I want to win!
Sena Kobayakawa, #21. Position: Running back!
Sena's Eyeshield 21?!
YA-HA!
Then it's settled.
Participating in the death march across America is...
...the entire Deimon Devil Bats team!
We're all going to... the Christmas Bowl together!
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima baze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
Go, go, run, run, it's the Death March!
Stop treating it like a joke!
Shin and Panther are climbing their way to the top, too.
I have to...
You'd better not slack off!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Minds Made Up! Ya-ha!
You guys are awful!
Mamori, we were hoping you'd come!
You tried to send me back to Japan all alone!
No, we never meant to...
Huh? Where's Cerberus?
Tough dog...