10 yard gain!
Don't chicken out on me!
Okay, we've got nine seconds left.
There's only one guy who can run the forty yards to the goal in one play.
The "Lightspeed Running Back."
Eyeshield 21...
Blaze a path down the field!
Nice kick!
Go!
Who's that?!
High schoolers don't run that fast!
Blow past 'em!
Smash him!
Why you-
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Man With the Lightspeed Legs
Deimon High School Exam Admission Card. Sena Kobayakawa, Test No. 021
Hey, Sena! Over here!
Mamori!
I'm just gonna go home, I know I failed.
No way.
021, 021, 021...
There, 021!
Great job, Sena!
That's the first compliment I've been given in 10 years!
Even though you were so terrible at math and English!
It's all thanks your teacher...Mamori!
Wow... You'll be in the same school as me.
For the first time since elementary school.
Hey, you!
You made Sena cry again!
Aren't you happy you get to walk to school with your beautiful childhood friend? I bet you are!
Yup.
I'm really glad.
Congratulations, Sena.
Oh yeah, I'll go grab you the new student handbook!
Later!
Hey, wait-
Mamori was crying...
I spy fresh meat.
You passed! Way to go! Ya-ha!
No one's ever tossed me up like this in my whole life!
Please, inform your dear parents about your success.
I-I can use your phone?
Absolutely.
Thank God the upperclassmen here are so kind.
Hi, mom? Guess wha-
Hiruma-!
He is the ONE student that is off limits!
Yes! I passed!
You passed! Way to go! Ya-ha!
Who was he?
Listen up Sena, I don't want you fraternizing with him, no matter what.
His name's Hiruma, he's evil incarnate, and you catch his eye, you're finished!
He'll eat the flesh off your bones!
Hi-Hiruma...
Mmhmm.
Recruiting members?
"To the Christmas Bowl?"
Ya-ha! Come play football!
It's the ultimate battle sport, combining power, speed, and tactics! Join the football team! Do it!
What the heck is going on?!
You'll shoot up in no time, so go a size up!
This'll be more than enough...
Oh yeah, my present for getting in!
It's so mature-looking!
But no one'll call me...
Mamori's the only person in my address book...
Morning!
Your tie's loose!
Okay Sena, this time you've gotta make some friends!
Hey, I had friends.
Like in elementary school, and middle-
Those are NOT friends!
You were their lackey, their gopher!
You're in high school now, you have to make real friends, on your own!
And figure out what kinds of activities interest you!
I know, why don't you join a club?
Go get 'em!
Sweet, sweet!
The soccer club...?
Here I come, Wakashimada!
Overdrive sho-
Maybe not a sports club.
Mamori's right, I need to make friends.
If someone tries to make you their lackey, say, "We'll play rock-paper scissors, loser buys."
I'm not a KID...
I wasn't very good at English in middle school, so I hope to improve this year!
Next is Kobayakawa.
That's me!
Umm, I'm Sena Kobayakawa.
As a high schooler, I'd like to avoid being a gophe- I mean,
being unmotivated like I was in middle school, and really put my heart into everything!
I made it.
Everyone looks nice, I think I'll have a nice time in this class.
I've got a bad feeling...
A club, huh...?
Hey, Sena.
I'm Kazuki Jumonji, what's up?
And I'm Koji Kuroki.
Let's be friends, 'kay?
Shozo Togano, I think you'll really fit in with us.
Hi...
I know this's sudden, but go buy us some bread, would you?
Bread? Uhh, well, let's play rock-
N-Nothing!
Three yakisoba sandwiches.
We'll be hanging out behind the school.
Don't be late... Or else.
Why does this always have to happen?
That was quick!
They were out.
There's no way you went to the store and back that fast, you loser!
I'm telling you, they were all out!
You really think we're falling for that?
This's your punishment.
Hold up.
Let's use that shed.
The football team?
Well?
You look like a dork.
Shaddap.
Time for tackling practice.
Time to start!
Football Clinic!
How many players are there on one team?
Football is played with 11 players at a time!
You can change players whenever you want, so they switch groups for offense and defense! Ya-ha!
No way... Are you all...
Here to join?!
Don't mess with us.
We're using this place right now.
Turn around and beat it, now.
Why you-
You wanna be a lineman?
You big...
...fat pig!
Okay, when you're pushing back a blocker,
you have to put your palms under their armpit, squeeze, and-
Oh no! Are you guys okay?!
And they were our only applicants so far, too...
There's still one left!
Let's take care of this in here, okay?
Want some tea? Or coffee? Or-
Umm, I'm actually not here to join...
Yikes, he is REALLY depressed.
How much sugar?
Just one's fine-
That must be incredibly sweet.
How many players are there on a football team?
You need 11 at the bare minimum.
We have to borrow players from the other clubs during inter-school tournaments.
Last year two of them got knocked out, and we lost in the first round.
Knocked out?
We won't even make it to Christmas, let alone the Christmas Bowl.
"Christmas Bowl?"
The nationwide championship match!
It's only held once a year, right around Christmas time, and the two best teams play each other!
It's so cool!
They show all the replays and stuff on Tokyo Stadium's "Aurora Vision" and everything!
It's the ultimate championship stage!
And one day we're all gonna stand on that field!
That's why I want to enter the tournament, no matter what it takes.
It makes me so excited,
working together to reach a common goal, running right over our opponents on the way!
What does that mean, "managers?"
Oh, managers do a lot.
They go on scouting missions and analyze our opponents' plays,
set up our games,
and essentially work as the top administrator for the team.
I've discovered the opponent's weak point, Coach!
Wha- You've figured them out ALREADY?
You're a genius, Sena!
We're only here in the Christmas Bowl because of you!
You have to make real friends, on your own.
U-Um...
Do you think I could be your manager?
O-O-Of course!
Yahoo!
Let's shoot for the Christmas Bowl, together!
Mamori Anezaki.
Ryokan Kurita.
Was that fat pig your friend?
Tell us where he lives, and we'll let you go.
You sure one bat's gonna be enough for that monster?
It'll be fine, I'll call the cops beforehand.
The cops?
We just need to start a fight.
I'll tell 'em fatso came at me me with that bat, gave me this scar,
and they'll kick him off the football team.
Brilliant!
Let's shoot for the Christmas Bowl, together!
Come on, already. I told you we'd let you go.
If you even think about running, we'll really let you have it.
Forget it.
If you wanna beat me up, beat me up!
I'm not telling him to come out here!
I guess we'll just ask with our fists.
Hey, this wuss has a phone.
Give it-
Looks like there's some chick's number, too.
It's that Kurita guy, right?
Get the girl's info, too.
Wow... You'll be in the same school as me.
That's why I want to enter the tournament, no matter what it takes.
You little-
Get him!
Surround the station!
No way!
Hey, he's...
Blend in with the crowd?
No, take another alley?
I can't, they'll jump me at the station no matter which way I go!
There he is!
Get back here!
What a cut...
Now I've got you!
Ooh, a spin!
I won't make it!
Sure you will, with those legs.
Jump!
Jumping onto the train is very dangerous, please refrain from doing so.
S-Sorry.
Jumping onto the train is very dangerous, please refrain from doing so!
That little punk!
Touchdown! Ya-ha!
What are you doing?! Knock it off!
There'll be three of us from now on.
I caught one! He'll make a killer running back.
S-Sena?
I'll do it, I'll do it! Please let me join!
Ooh, #21! And the eye shield looks neat!
We'll need to hide his face during games, or the other clubs'll try to steal those legs from us.
Games? But I wanted to be manage-
During a game, you don't answer to "Sena Kobayakawa."
Your code name is...
Eyeshield 21!
Eyeshield 21?
But I'm supposed to be the manager!
Congratulations, Sena!
Ya-ha!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
Yay! Unbelievable!
Sena the gopher, joining the football team?
And gets thrust right into playing?!
How can they play with only three people?!
How am I supposed to know?
Guess you'll have to go back to running errands!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Let's Play Football!
Ya-ha!
Don't touch him again or the bats are coming off!