Very Lucky Fortune
Yay! It's "very lucky!"
Last try!
Kurita and the others are really pumped up.
Let's not let them beat us!
Our first game in the fall season's just around the corner.
Just one week left!
I'm so excited!
Our first opponents are from Amino High School.
Aren't they a famous school affiliated with a university?
I wonder what their team's like...
I've heard that their nickname is "The Game Stealing Amino."
What? Game stealing?
Every year they get involved with one sport
and then have the entire student body collaborate to steal the championship.
In other words,
they're putting all of their knowledge and aptitude into American football this year.
It's amazing that they work towards excellence in sports
even though they're affiliated with a university.
But we can't lose to ANYONE, no matter what!
Right, Mamori?
We did manage to complete that death march, after all.
That's right!
Okay! Let's work ever harder tomorrow!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Night Before the Game!
Decrease your body fat by another 0.2%.
Defense, offense, bench work, we're superior in every way.
We also collected excellent data on other teams.
There's no excuse for the Amino Cyborgs to lose!
We slide and block like this!
It's a hook block, ya know?
That's pretty tight. Think he can squeeze through there?
He wants you to go between him and Kuroki, Sena.
Uh, sure...
Hey, you, move it!
You're interfering with our meeting!
Hey, those aren't your seats, are they?
W-Well, why don't we take our time and do this after class is finished?
Let's go practice!
Yeah!
Patience! Endurance! Patience! Endurance!
Yay!
Just three days left!
I wanna play in a game soon!
Fuji Cafeteria
Ma'am, please give me the usual!
Sure thing!
One order of the Kurita Meal Set!
Be sure to give him a whole bunch of rice!
Thanks for the meal!
More! More! More! More! More!
This really is a tight squeeze, ya know.
Are you saying he can't do it?!
Why don't we set it up wider?
Those aren't your seats!
But we can't maintain the passing wall till I get there if you make it too open.
And you're not supposed to be in this class!
Let's go practice!
Yeah!
We did it!
Just two days left!
I can't wait!
More! More! More! More!
- What? Are you saying it's my fault?
- Those aren't your seats.
We need to be focusing in on how to win the game, not on our desks!
You aren't even supposed to be in this class!
Calm down! As long as I'm here, there's a 150% chance of victory!
You aren't even a student here at Deimon, are you?!
I transferred in during the middle of the semester 150%!
Let's go practice!
Okay!
We did it! We did it! We did it!
I already memorized the sweep...
You're amazing, Sena!
Mamori! What's so amazing?
You're acting like you're a player yourself!
Ah, well, you see...
But you know,
this is my first time ever seeing you get so enthusiastic over something.
Even if we don't play in the game, we're still members of the team!
Yeah...
Good work!
Hey, Mamori, could you go do THAT for me?
Sure!
There's just one day left!
I wanna play in a game NOW!
I wish it was already the day after tomorrow!
But you know...
I'm starting to get a bit nervous.
In this tournament, you're finished if you lose just once.
So it's through the moment you lose.
That means we can't lose no matter what!
Well, there's no way we could lose!
Y-You're right! T-There's no way we'll lose!
You betcha to the max!
Well, see ya!
See you around!
My shoe lace broke...
How ominous!
I-I-I-It's okay!
Thanks for the food...
Oh, finished already?
Are you feeling bad?
No, it's nothing like that...
Your game's just around the corner, isn't it?
Here, eat this so you'll grow healthy and strong!
It's on the house.
On the house... Honorable defeat?!
"On the house" and "honorable defeat" are pronounced the same in Japanese.
So it's through the moment you lose.
I-I-I don't need any honorable defeat!
Thanks again for the meal!
Ah, hey!
Fortune Slips
It's okay! We worked so hard during practice!
Very Unlucky Fortune
V-Very unlucky!
That means we can't lose no matter what!
I-I-I-It's okay!
Katsuo...
Kaori...
Fin
In this tournament, you're finished if you lose just once.
At times like this...!
You're finished if you lose.
We can't lose no matter what!
It's no use! It's no good!
Football Clinic!
What do you do when on offense?
You get to be on offense four times!
If you get a first down during your possession, you get to remain on offense!
Make sure you understand that! Ya-ha!
Fall Tournament
Here I go!
The Devil Bats, huh?
Musashi!
Have you decided to come back?
You should start looking for a new kicker.
Don't be stupid, you old fart!
You should know better than anyone
that we can't turn just anyone into a good kicker over night.
That's not my problem.
My plans have never failed me yet.
Please enter, Mr. Kumabukuro.
Last year was soccer and the year before that was basketball.
If you pull out your body's utmost potential,
you can master any form of competitive sport.
Please take a look at this.
That's Eyeshield 21...
Deimon is merely a jumble of a team.
And we've already discovered their only hope, Eyeshield 21's fatal flaw.
Eyeshield's flaw?
Please keep what I am about to show you off the record until after the game.
I understand.
T-That's...
Master's...
...gone missing?
I haven't heard from him, but his parents say he already left the house...
And here the big game's tomorrow!
For now let's split up and try searching for him!
Let's go!
- Kurita!
What should I do?
Kurita!
We're finished if we lose...
And here we've worked so hard...
And we became such good friends...
Let's go!
Yeah!
It's no use. We're finished!
So this is where you've been, Fatty.
Whenever you get scared outta your wits you come hide here.
Hiruma!
Huh?
Do you believe... in reincarnation?
HUH?!
I wonder if I could be a high school student again...
This is totally different from last year's fall season!
Back then I thought that I still had one more chance at it.
But this year's...
This has been a dream of mine since elementary school.
I was so happy when you and Musashi joined...
All of it... Tomorrow all of it will...
In the end, Musashi never rejoined...
Hey, Hiruma, do you think we've got a 100% chance of winning tomorrow?
Of course not! No game's guaranteed "100%."
Then if we lost...?
It'd all... be over.
No!
We were finally able to make great friends and create an awesome team!
Why is this our last chance?
I don't want to play in tomorrow's game!
So, what then?
Do you want me to try to baby you?
Do you want me to put you at ease by saying that we'll definitely win?
Quit being a baby, FATTY!
We're alone on the field!
Nobody's gonna save you!
That was a gun!
I heard it come from over there!
Max dash!
That TV...
We'll make it to the Christmas Bowl! 1-2 Kurita, Hiruma, Musashi
Now you're hiding here, Fatty?
Hiruma, remember that?
Look, it's that TV!
You, me and Musashi wrote that our three-man team would make it to the Christmas Bowl.
See!
Kurita!
Master!
Hiruma, earlier you said that we're all alone when we're on the field.
We're not. I know we're not!
We aren't alone anymore!
Kurita!
Max relief!
Sena! Monta!
Kurita, you made us worried sick!
Master!
Kurita!
- There he is!
- Problem solved 150%!
Guys! Sorry I made you worry.
But, I'm okay now.
Let's go, ladies!
Go?
Go where?
Tokyo Stadium!
I-It's HUGE!
It's held in such a cool stadium...
The Christmas Bowl...
About three years ago Hiruma, Musashi and I
looked up at it just like this and made a vow.
We swore that we'd definitely make it here.
And we will!
But in order to do that we've gotta beat Ojo, Seibu, Shinryuji and everyone else.
That means we gotta crush the Amino Cyborgs tomorrow, too.
Okay!
Let's do it!
Come on at us!
Let's try our best, Kurita!
Yeah!
Down with the Amino Cyborgs!
YA-HA!
They're perfect...
At this rate, Deimon's going to lose their first match.
Prepare yourself, Eyeshield 21!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Our first match is against the Amino Cyborgs!
What's with that super artificial-looking muscular body?!
And where the heck am I?!
Am I lost?!
I won't make it to the game in time!
Where on earth are you going?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Ace's Missing?! Ya-ha!
Great, it's done!
It was surprisingly easy to fix.
Let's test it out just to be on the safe side.
Kurita, could you try jumping over it?
Sure! Here I go!
Kurita!
Are you okay?!
We may be doomed tomorrow...