- Drown!
- Ya-ha!
Kyoshin Poseidons - Deimon Devil Bats
There's just seven minutes left!
Sanada Who will win, the Devil Bats or the Poseidons?!
I guess we've got no choice but to use THAT.
We'll show them what the Kyoshin Poseidons are made of!
You mean...
...THAT?
We're only supposed to use that formation
to guarantee victory after we're already in the lead.
That strategy really eats up time.
Wouldn't using it when we're losing actually hurt us?
We're all going to the Christmas Bowl, aren't we?!
We can't lose here and now!
I see. This might jab Deimon in their weak spot.
Mizumachi, let's do it!
Sweet! That's the spirit!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
How Terrifying! The Moby Dick Anchor!
Huh?
W-What's with that formation?
Huh? I don't see Mizumachi...
And here he's been in the front line from the start!
There he is! He's way back there!
He's next to Kakei... All four tall players are lined up!
What is this?
Who cares?!
It doesn't matter what tricks they pull now!
I dare them to even TRY to stop both our run and passes!
We'll take that dare and stop you!
We're finished if we lose this game!
Ohira, let's call a truce over who's the best pupil for now and play as a team!
Yeah, Onishi!
No mortal can get through our dream formation,
the Four Heavenly Kings!
Set! Hut, hut, hut, hut, hut!
Ya know, we really weren't supposed to use this formation so soon!
Let's go!
This is the Kyoshin's ultimate form of the High Wave, the Poseidon!
WHAT?!
All four are charging in a straight line!
Amazing!
It's a huge defensive wave!
Argh! If all of those heavyweights come at us at once...
...we won't be able to block them!
And the High Wave was impressive with just the three of them...
And now they've added...
...another person!
Mizumachi took advantage of his height to cut off the pass!
Leave it to me!
Taki managed to save the ball!
We're so close!
You're great, Mizumachi!
It truly looked like Kyoshin's god, Poseidon,
appeared from out of a huge wave!
Formation "Poseidon," huh?
By having their four aces line up in the back,
they've created a broad defense.
It defends against Taki's long passes
along with Eyeshield and Raimon's outside runs.
I can't believe it's blocking our passes and runs!
Can it really be that perfect?
There's no such thing as a perfect formation.
Hiruma!
Of course there's holes in it!
That's right, guys!
Thanks to Mizumachi's going to the back,
the line's opened up some!
It's our big chance to burst through the center!
I was a bit surprised earlier, but it won't happen again.
Yeah, we'll open a huge hole!
So dash on through, Eyeshield 21!
Yeah!
It's only natural that they'd attack the center
since the taller members of the line are all in the back.
But the problem's... Kakei.
Set, hut!
Open sesame!
It's open! Now I can...
No you don't!
It didn't work!
Eyeshield couldn't get through!
Sweet! That was perfect!
Now do you understand, Fakeshield?
Your legs truly are fast...
But you need the right build to be able
to force your way through the center of a line.
That's what makes you...
...so different from the real Eyeshield 21.
That's the best that you can do with your poor physique.
Listen up!
If you can't get past him,
going to the Christmas Bowl is just a dream within a dream!
Got that, Peewee?!
Yes!
Are they going to use the same play?
Why are they having Eyeshield go again?
Well, you see...
He's our ace!
Set, hut, hut!
Set, hut!
Go, Eyeshield!
Amazing!
It might work this time... All right!
This time I'll use the Devil Bat Ghost!
- Great!
- Go!
It's no use!
Moby Dick Anchor!
It just isn't working...
Can't Deimon counter this somehow?
The outcome will always be the same.
You can't get through me.
After all,
I'm here so that I can fight against the real Eyeshield 21.
So I can't lose to a fake like you!
Poseidons! Poseidons!
They were so close!
Deimon failed to get their first down!
Offense goes to Kyoshin!
Set, hut, hut!
So scary!
He's fast!
He's also fast at getting rid of the ball!
Kobanzame, their quarterback,
hasn't been intercepted because he runs away so quickly.
Guys like him are the most difficult to deal with.
That's right! You've got it!
He doesn't let a good pass course slip him by!
I'm scared!
Okay!
Touchdown!
Goodness me!
Kyoshin Poseidons have taken the lead with a score of 23-18!
Dude, you're the BEST!
Ow, ow! Ouchie-ow!
There's a five-point gap...
What should we do?
There's only two minutes left?!
We're out of time!
What should we do?
What should we do?!
Let's go for a touchdown on the conversion!
If we can get those two extra points,
Deimon won't be able to take back the lead
even if they get a touchdown since they can't kick.
Right!
Simply put, we're going for two more points!
I-I was just about to say the same thing!
Okay!
Let's go get... those two points!
So they're giving up on kicking...
Hey, linemen!
What is it?
Stop them from getting a touchdown, even if it kills you!
O-Okay!
- Yeah!
Butt-monkey, Chinfuzz!
Yeah?
You steal their passes!
You mean intercept them?!
Hey, wait a sec!
No one's ever been able to snatch the ball away from Kobanzame!
Peewee!
Yes!
I want you to tackle whichever receiver jumps out first.
Huh? But what about the center?
I'll tackle over there.
Chinfuzz and the Butt-monkey
need to run to the opposite sides of you.
The ball will definitely head out towards one of them.
How you you know that?
The enemy's QB is afraid of Eyeshield,
so he won't throw the ball near him.
That only leaves the area around you two open.
I see!
I totally get it, 150%!
Just so you know, it's sink or swim.
Whether or not you get that pass
will determine the outcome of the game.
Intercept that pass even if it kills you!
Got it?!
- Yeah!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to throw while running!
The main point is your waist.
When you want to throw while running,
keep your body facing forward
and twist your upper body at the waist.
Be sure to twist at the waist! Ya-ha!
We'll lose the game if they gain any more points.
Set, hut!
Let's see... Eyeshield's over there!
CRUSH HIM!
He's scary!
All right!
What?!
Come on, baby!
- Oh my God!
- Okay!
The catcher's entered the building!
Oops, Deimon's intercepted Kyoshin's ball!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
And here the Kyoshin were so close to making a touchdown!
They don't get the extra points!
They're good!
My pass was...
Kobanzame, it was a nice pass.
Ka-Kakei...
We just have to defend well now!
Y-You're right!
Okay, I'm counting on you!
They're both equally likely to win.
But either Deimon or Kyoshin's
gonna be kicked out of the tournament.
We need more time!
We've gotta get the ball again!
And here we've gotten the same number of touchdowns!
The five points we're losing by...
...all came from kicks!
Musashi...
Down to just 18 seconds.
That's not enough time to attack.
Hey, Peewee, listen up!
O-Okay!
I don't care if it's impossible or not,
you've gotta get by Kakei.
Got that, Peewee?
If you start running with the ball,
Kakei will go at you one-on-one.
But we'll get a touchdown if you can get by him.
We're losing by five points and there's 18 seconds left.
We'll get six points if you get a touchdown, so we'd win!
That's some pretty lucky math there!
Yep...
B-But we're outta time and that's the only way.
B-But the Devil Bat Ghost isn't working on Kakei.
What should I do?
There's no point in trying
if you don't think you can get by Kakei.
We'll just have Hiruma change the game plan.
Do you know what an ace's job is?
I know a pretty simple answer.
An ace's... job?
It's to win!
A team's ace can't lose, even if it kills him!
So if you're saying that you can't win,
then I'll be Deimon's ace!
No, it'll be me!
It's up to you, Peewee.
Can you or can't you get by Kakei,
who was an ace in America?
I haven't forgotten.
I'll never forget...
the time I saw you run for the first time on that fateful day!
There's no way someone with such an
awesome running style could possibly lose!
J-Jumonji...
Kill 'em!
You'll pull it off!
I can get through!
It doesn't matter how you feel about it,
we're down to the last 18 seconds!
Deimon can't win if they don't pull off another touchdown.
You can do it!
Please, guys!
Go for it! Go for it!
Poseidons! Poseidons!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Don't let your guard down till it's over!
Okay, Master Kakei!
We'll be the ones victorious!
I'm on FIRE!
Set!
Hut!
Go!
They've entrusted this death match for the right to play
in the semi-finals to their ace, Eyeshield 21!
Man! There's no way we can lose here!
Here's the results of that hellish training we did in America!
Don't underestimate us!
There's no way I can lose!
The results will always be the same, you fake.
That running of yours won't work on me!
It's no good!
His tackle's so quick!
He'll catch me!
Don't you dare lose!
The ace ALWAYS wins!
Please!
I want to get through...
No, I WILL get through!
I won't let you!
You're mine! You're finished!
C'mon!
He did a...
...a spin?!
The day of the school opening ceremony...
He spun around like that!
No, it's different!
This is even better than that!
He added a spin to the Devil Bat Ghost!
On top of disappearing from eyesight,
he can spin by you if you're about to catch him!
It's the Hurricane Ghost!
I can't believe this punk!
He evolved the Ghost on his own!
There's no one left!
I can get a touchdown now!
We're winning!
We...won!
Yay!
YES! I can get a touchdown!
We're going to the semi-finals!
The semi-finals-!
I won't let you!
No way!
D-Did we get a touchdown?
How's the time?!
Stop the clock!
Time out!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
No way!
We've only got two seconds left?!
We've almost got a touchdown!
But Deimon'll lose if we fail! What should we do?!
There's just 30 centimeters left! Just force your way through!
Next time on Eyeshield 21:
Attack and Defense for 30 Centimeters! Ya-ha!
Time out!
You stopped him!
You're awesome!
Kyoshin!
Kyoshin's Mizumachi just barely managed
to stop Eyeshield 21 at their goal line!
Amazing! It's too amazing!
Deimon Devil Bats called for a time out!
There's two seconds left to the game.
Just TWO SECONDS!