Hiruma, did you say losers' bracket?
What's... that?
What, he didn't tell you the tournament rules?
Of course not.
They would've just phoned it in if I told them beforehand.
W-What is it?!
Yo, Manajerk! Pull up the tournament homepage.
W-W-Wait a second.
I'm not really good with computers...
Let me in there!
There we go.
Ya-ha!
I'm here to explain the road to the ultimate football championship,
the Christmas Bowl, so listen up!
Listen up!
Watch this for starters!
This is the what everyone's aiming for,
the location of the final championship game,
Tokyo Stadium!
Yeah!
Western No. 1 - Eastern No. 1
The top team from western will battle it out here
against the top team from eastern Japan.
And the top eastern team is the winner of the Kanto tournament!
Kanto Tournament
Only eight teams from the multiple tournaments
in east Japan will make it that far!
Eight teams!
EIGHT teams?
M-Master!
I'm totally clueless,
will you teach me how many teams from the Tokyo conference
get to play in the Kanto tournament?
Hi-ya!
Open up those gigantic ears and listen carefully!
Yessir!
The Tokyo champion!
The Kanagawa champion!
The Shizuoka champion!
The Hokkaido champion!
The S.I.C. area champion!
The Tokyo runner-up!
The Kanagawa runner-up!
And the final spot goes to...
Goes to?
The third place Tokyo team!
Third place?
I see, it must be because Tokyo's so big!
We're in third?
So since we lost in the semi-finals,
there must be a tiebreaker to see who comes in third next week...
If we win that game...
We get third place in Tokyo...
We still have a road to the nationals... to the Christmas Bowl!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
A Pact Between Rivals.
Now then...
I oughtta kill you for fighting with the ref, Butt-monkey!
If you'd gotten us disqualified our chances would be dead and buried!
I'll kill you a million times!
The wind'll be blowing through all the bullet holes I put in you!
I-I-I'm sorry!
That's right...
If he hadn't stopped me, we'd be finished...
T-Tetsuma...
Tetsuma...
Thank you so much.
I... I'm really grateful!
If... If you hadn't stopped me...
I... I'd...
Yeesh, who was it?
Who ordered Tetsuma to save him?
No one, Coach.
Oh?
He's the first opponent who beat Tetsuma in a catching match.
Taro Raimon of the Deimon Devil Bats.
He wants to face him again, in the Kanto tournament.
Yeah... Tetsuma acted on his own.
I swear we'll come in third, and...
And...
We'll meet again.
Yes!
- Good game!
- Way to go!
- That was awesome!
Devil Bats!
Wild Gunmen!
We... owe you guys one.
Don't sweat it.
You may not care about winning or losing,
but I can't help it.
Yet you don't bat an eye when you talk about it.
We only won today because lady luck hung with us for a little longer.
Don't give me that.
Hmm?
I see right through your act.
You're more obsessed with the championship than anyone.
Of course, when you get too worked up, you get burned.
Nothing good happens... when people start hyping things up too much.
We'll pay you back in the Kanto tournament, with interest.
Actually, I hope we don't end up facing each other.
Facing the number one QB again? No thanks.
Like I said, YOU'RE the best...
...for today.
Riku!
Umm, Riku...
I just wanted to say...
Uhh...
I've come this far... thanks to your-
One time.
You haven't beaten me yet, not with just one win.
Once... It was only once.
But with that one win...
Eyeshield 21...
Keep your chin up, Sena.
Men have to always look forward.
I'll make sure to protect Mamori until you move back!
It's a deal!
Take care, Riku!
Sena...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to tackle someone!
The hint is "your head?"
When you tackle someone, keep your head up and aim for your target's belly button.
Don't wimp out!
Ya-ha.
Isn't it great how they happened to be holding a festival today?
Yeah, the game's not until next week
and we have the day off from practice!
One time.
Hey, Sena?
Something wrong?
Oh, no, it's just...
Is this okay?
What?
What else? We're still in the tournament.
Don't be a worry-wart.
What'd Yocchie say?
The body needs a little R&R every now and then! Ya-ha!
Right?
Yeah, it's hard to believe he'd ever say that...
Anyway, today should be a nice change of pace, Sena.
Actually, I asked someone else to join us.
Ooh, who, who?
Who'd you call, Mamo?
A boy.
A boy!
No way!
Who who who?
Ya-ha.
Welcome to the Festival of Doom.
So the boy you called...
I totally called it!
I always knew you had a thing for Yocchie, Mamo!
N-No, not him!
I would never!
What ARE you doing out here, Hiruma?!
Why is everyone here?
The three of us...
...got caught in the arcade...
...by the station...
We all got called...
...for an emergency meeting...
And it wouldn't be a festival without me!
You said practice was canceled today.
I said we needed rest, not that it was canceled.
Here's the first stop!
- The ring toss?
Why bother?
It's a scam.
I've got it!
Go, go!
Go go go go go!
- Holy cow!
Let King Koji show you how it's done!
You're a ring toss master?!
Way to go, kid!
Awesome! Keep going!
Why are we doing this, again?
I know, this must be a way to practice
accurately judging distance and position!
Hiruma's a genius!
I get it.
Okay!
Now it's my turn, lemme at it!
What a riot!
Run, boys!
Riku?
Rikky, you came!
So the boy you called was Riku-Riku?
That's right.
Here's your next task!
O-Our next training is goldfish catching!
Good luck, boys!
W-What's going on, Mamori?
Forget them for a minute.
Let's set these off together, like we used to.
Huh? O-Okay...
They're so pretty... Remember, Sena?
When you were little,
you were so scared of sparklers you wouldn't touch them.
Oh come on, no way.
It's true. Don't you remember?
All fireworks scared you, you never let go of my hand!
Geez, I was just a kid...
Mine fell off.
Okay, this one's next!
You're sure? That's a spinner!
I'm not a kid any more!
Are you okay, Sena?!
Help!
Maybe it's just my imagination...
What?
Nowadays it seems like Sena's really... responsible.
Of course, Mamori.
Sena's growing up.
Getting bigger and stronger.
You're right.
There goes mine.
Are you lost?
My mommy's not here...
You poor thing, don't worry,
I'll go find her, so you just sit right here with my friends!
'Kay...
I'll find someone in charge,
can you two keep an eye on him?
Sure.
Don't cry, we'll find your mom in no time.
We'll stay here with you until she comes back.
Okay?
'Kay...
My balloon!
There.
Thanks, Mister!
How much longer?
How long are you going to hide behind your Eyeshield mask?
Mask?
Sena.
You're not a scaredy-cat or a gopher any more.
You're an American football athlete.
You've gotten faster...
Or stronger, rather.
Riku...
You'd better win the third place showdown.
If you do, we'll...
We'll meet again in the Kanto tournament.
It killed me to admit that you beat me fair and square.
That's why I...
Well, the next time we face each other,
you're going down!
I'll make you taste the same bitter defeat that I did!
Or something.
Hey, sweetie! I found your mom!
Mommy!
Later, Sena.
R-Riku!
Take care of Mamori.
Yeah. I will!
I have to win...
We WILL be in the Kanto tournament...
Absolutely!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
The other semi-final is Ojo vs. Bando!
Bando's who that kicker Kotaro plays for, right?
Right, he's the one always going, "How smart!"
Hey, there's some weird guitar player with him, too!
Who's he?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Spider's Sting! Ya-ha!
Look, just go home already.
We don't let anyone throw us out!
I ain't leaving till I get at least one!
Gimme every net you got, tubby!
What amazing focus!
This must be what Hiruma wanted us to do for his special training!
I did it! I'm the man!
Hey, King Koji had his eye on that one!
Say what? I don't see your name on it!
Outta my way, you rejects!
Underwater Diving Catch!
Nice!
Don't give up!
Good luck!
The place is packed!
You really came through for us!
All these customers gave us tons of business!
Here's a 10-person supply of takoyaki!
And 20 chocolate-dipped bananas.
30 caramel apples.
You're most welcome.
Though my silly football teammates seem to think it's some kind of training.