- Drown!
- Ya-ha!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
This is bad! Things aren't looking good!
We're not done yet! We've still got a chance!
It's okay, Kobanzame!
Huh? Yeah...
We're no pushovers.
The real fight's just getting started!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Wow! Everyone's really getting fired up!
Kyoshin Poseidons 17 - Deimon Devil Bats 18
The score's 17-18, so Deimon's in the lead by one point!
I, Machinegun Sanada, will be shooting out the commentary!
And the frizzy-haired perm man will be shooting out the explanations!
I give you Bomberhead Kumabukuro!
No, I'm not called "Bomberhead..."
This is what I like to see.
The tide'll change in our favor if we can stop them here.
Hang in there, defense!
Stop them!
Set, hut, hut!
That's super powerful!
The Poseidon's attack failed!
We did it!
Pot-belly Tackle!
Yay! Nice going, Kuritan!
Good, good.
Don't pull back!
Next!
We CAN'T lose!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
Obsession with Victory!
Set, hut!
We can't...
...lose either!
They got squashed again!
- Boo-yah!
Good going, Deimon!
You're awesome, Ha-Ha Brothers!
We're not related!
Kobanzame, let's go with our Tempest Formation.
Ah, okay!
I-I was just about to suggest that.
L-Let's use the Tempest!
Well, this is the Poseidons' third attack!
Set, hut, hut!
Is it a Shotgun play?!
But what's with that receiver?
It's just like a storm...
I get it! A "tempest" is a storm!
Huh? Meaning what?
They're going to run around the field like a storm
and pass the ball to Kobanzame.
It's the Tempest Formation!
Ack!
Guys, crush Kobanzame!
I won't let you!
You annoying pest!
First down!
Through sheer determination
the Poseidons were able to steal their first down!
Their quarterback's Osamu Kobanzame...
His pass may not be flashy, but it's effective.
You could say that this formation makes the most out of it.
I won't let you near Kobanzame!
Earlier your QB said that Deimon
doesn't have any worthless weaklings in it.
The same goes for us!
The Kyoshin Poseidons don't have any weaklings either!
We're all working hard together so we can WIN!
Set, hut, hut!
I'm... scared!
Poseidons gain three yards!
Poseidons! Poseidons!
He's also quick and nimble.
Kobanzame is a good quarterback.
Argh!
Quit running away!
C'mon and fight us, you wimp!
Put a lid on it!
Kobanzame isn't a wimp!
Mizumachi...
Kyoshin Middle School
There!
Awesome! I got a perfect 100%!
You're awesome, Mizumachi!
You're the most athletic student at Kyoshin Middle School!
A sports master!
A real genius!
Please join the gymnastics team!
No, join the basketball team!
Track and field is what sports are all about!
The baseball team's waiting for you!
Well, I don't know who to join when everyone's asking all at once...
Hey, Mizumachi, please join the swimming team! Please!
You see, they're going to disband our club
if we don't win some games next season.
Disband?
What are you talking about?
Shh! Just play along!
Th-That's right, Mizumachi!
Please! The swimming team's my life!
If we lose the swimming team, I'll...
You're our only hope!
Guess I don't have much choice, do I?!
I'll give you a helping hand!
Let's all aim for nationals!
Yeah!
You can't swim?!
Wasn't he a master at sports?
It's okay! I'll catch... up soon... enough!
One more kilometer left for morning practice!
He's a monster...
Just the other day he couldn't swim at all!
Winner of the Men's 50 Meter Freestyle goes to Kengo Mizumachi!
Sweet!
I did it, guys!
Now they won't close down the swimming team!
Let's aim for the entire team winning next time!
Then we'd be No. 1 in Japan!
Y-Yeah...
This is the only way to become national champions!
Let's all work our butts off!
It's already ten at night!
You're... really weird!
Huh? But didn't we agree that we'd aim for nationals together?
Bluntly put, we can't keep up with you.
So that was all a lie?
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to get better control over the ball!
The key point is your shoulders?
When you throw the ball,
make sure you keep your shoulders in line with your target.
Keep your shoulders straight!
Ya-ha.
We can't lose... no matter what!
So that was all a lie?
What gives, you guys?!
Mi-Mizumachi!
Why aren't you coming to practice?!
We'll never win at this rate!
It's impossible!
No matter how hard we practice, we can't make it to nationals.
You can go there by yourself!
What?!
- Move it!
- Don't.
Think about where you are.
Don't get in my way!
If you want to cut loose, do it on the field.
Who's that?
You don't know?
It's Kakei from Homeroom 4.
Oh, is he the guy who just came back from America?
They say that he was playing real football while he was in America.
Resignation from Team
I won't lose! I WON'T LOSE!
I promised Kakei and the others that we'd become national champions together!
National champions!
You're just like Kakei said! You'd make a prefect tall player!
Please join our Kyoshin Poseidons!
Kakei here was playing in America until just last year!
We're doing awesome!
Next year we might make it to nationals!
- Nationals?
- Yeah...
Like I'm just gonna believe that.
What?!
First you'll have to prove to me if what you said is true or not.
That's our Kakei!
Let's go at it one more time!
Okay!
We're not done yet!
Let's scream with enthusiasm!
- Yeah!
One more time!
Go for it!
Take that!
Scream with enthusiasm!
- Yeah!
We're... not done yet...!
Let's keep... practicing...!
We're... not stopping now!
- Yeah!
These guys... are serious!
I've made up my mind!
I'm joining the football team!
Shoot! He made a pass! Go, Kakei!
Leave it to me, Mizumachi!
Deimon's pass is incomplete!
For every step forward, we take another back.
The game's hit a stalemate, hasn't it?
In a situation like this,
the game will go to whoever manages to get through in the end.
The Poseidons can't lose!
Okay!
Next let's do 100 laps around the school!
Hey, Mizumachi...
We just... finished climbing up the stairs 100 times!
Huh? Done already?
N-No...
I was... about to say the same thing!
Kobanzame!
Let's go...
100 laps around the school!
Yeah!
Please wait, Master Kakei!
We'll follow you anywhere!
Where's Kobanzame?
He's not done yet.
Last I saw, he was way behind us.
I bet he collapsed somewhere along the way.
Kobanzame, there's just 100 meters left!
Just 50 meters! You're almost there!
Just 10! Just five!
W-We can make it... to the Christmas Bowl... can't we?
You bet we can, Kobanzame!
We're gonna be national champions!
Okay, one more time!
Yeah!
How're ya doing, Kakei?
Almost there...
I've just about got it down!
Okay then, let's try one more time!
Are you okay, Kobanzame?
Want us to switch out with you?
Yeah, I'll do it!
I'm fine, I'm fine!
Let's do it!
They're amazing!
Those three have been practicing the exact same drills for three months now.
How inspirational!
In order to stop two people at once...
...I must read the enemy's movement and quickly anchor them down!
I mastered it!
Y-You did it, Kakei!
That was so cool!
The Moby Dick Anchor...
The Moby Dick Anchor?
Well, I was wondering what you'd think of calling it that!
Let's stick with that! I like it!
Kobanzame,
thank you very much.
I-It was nothing!
And you too, Mizumachi.
We're friends.
And this is where I belong!
This is what I've been searching for!
And now I've finally found it!
Mizumachi is going to stop Eyeshield,
who breezed past those two!
I won't let you through!
Eight yard gain!
So close, but now Deimon's going to start pushing them like mad!
Come on, man!
You guys still have your last year, ya know.
Kobanzame is a third-year student now,
so this is his last season.
So there's no way we can afford to lose!
Deimon doesn't have any third-year students on the team, right?
Sorry, but you've gotta lose this year!
Deimon's still got next year.
Next... year?
That won't work.
Hiruma...
Kurita...
Yuki...
And even Musashi...
This is their last year!
We don't have a "next year!"
The Deimon Devil Bats can't afford to lose!
I wonder whose desire to win is stronger...
That desire is what will determine who will win!
Got that right.
Set, hut, hut!
We can't lose!
It's not just Mizumachi!
We all feel that way!
The Poseidons are the ones who will make it to the Christmas Bowl!
It's 18-17! Deimon's got a one point lead!
There's just seven minutes left!
Who will win, the Devil Bats or the Poseidons?!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
What on earth is that?!
The Poseidons pulled out a new formation towards the very end of the game!
All four tall players are attacking at once!
Is this the Poseidons' great formation, the High Wave?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: How Terrifying! The Moby Dick Anchor! Ya-ha!
Well, I'd say they're glowing hot!
What do you think, analyst Bomberhead Kumabukuro?
Man... I keep telling you not to call me "Bomberhead."
Hey, by the way, I call him Kumafukuro!
Fukuro means owl in Japanese.
Kumafukuro...
- Kumafukuro... Kumafukuro...
- I don't like that, either...
Kumafukuro! Kumafukuro!