Distance to Las Vegas: 1568 km.
Death March - Day 8
A total newbie trying out for the pros?
Ah well, it's not like your chances were all the way at zero.
Yup, they're only zero if you never try at all!
I believed I had a 100% chance of making the cut.
I apologize for my brother.
We've got us a true blue dunce over here.
I can't say I hate fearless people like him.
That's right, I need to talk to Hiruma about letting him join...
You're both high school freshman now, right?
He was born in April,
and I was born in March.
So, Hiruma...
What do you think about making Taki our Tight End?
No way.
You expect me to take in this novice Chin-fuzz doofus
just because he's here?
I guess I understand...
We've got exactly one month left to cross America.
If you survive the rest of the death march, I'll CONSIDER it.
Please, I'll finish it before breakfast tomorrow!
Okay! Let's all redouble our efforts starting tomorrow!
Yukimitsu?
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
A Solitary Death March!
How can this be...
What kind of torture is this?
That's right... I have to start zig-zagging today.
Now I can't slow down AND I have to turn back and forth.
This is putting an unbelievable strain on my knees.
But...
He's running like that while kicking a stone, and I'm already collapsing?
That's impossible! How can that be?!
Yo, check me out, Sena!
This is kinda fun!
It feels like water skiing!
No offense guys,
but I need to handicap myself to make simple training like this worthwhile!
He could be as good as he is dumb.
Oh, I was having so much fun I didn't even notice myself get out front!
Confident to the max!
Nothing like an afternoon snack!
Yes, I'm feeling quite confident myself!
I think I'll run while doing standing splits!
M-Monta...
Bro...
We've got a whole quarry of diamonds here.
They might just have the faintest hope of making it to the Christmas Bowl.
But the most grueling part is yet to come!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I just got a little tripped up.
Tomorrow's gonna be rough, too.
Get yourselves ready!
Guys...
Seconds!
If it's gonna be that bad, we'll need to eat extra!
Another helping please, mon chere.
Y-Yeah, give me two helpings!
Please to the max!
O-Okay, line up! And make sure you eat it all!
Aren't you hungry?
N-No, but don't worry.
We're all exhausted, right?
If I get a good night's sleep,
I'll be ready and raring to go!
Move out!
You're sure you're okay, Yukimitsu?
Y-Yes, absolutely.
Go on ahead, don't mind me.
I'll be sure to catch up.
But...
You have your own task to focus on, Sena.
Right...
I have to get it together.
I don't want to hamper everyone else.
I can't quit now!
Even the slightest incline is murder!
Stop pushing with just your arms!
Tuck in your butts...
...and thrust 'em forward!
Holy smokes, it moved!
Amazing!
The hill's about to drop, you boys can hop back on!
Yahoo!
Now let's catch up to the others!
Are you okay, Yukimitsu? Want to ride in the truck?
No, I'm fine... Go on ahead.
Fight on, Yukimitsu!
Fight!
That dude's wiped out.
He's walking more than running.
He might have to hang it up.
I wonder if Yukimitsu is really all right...
Dunno.
Even the truck passed me...
I have to try harder.
Well, we're out of gas again.
We'll have to siphon some from a passerby.
I'll stop a car that's fit for hitchhiking.
Y-You can't stop people with something that dangerous!
A car!
That was WAY more dangerous!
Time for me to shine.
Please, pull over for me.
How can this be?
Umm, excuse me, could you maybe stop, please?
Stop!
This is no good.
Just leave this part to the ladies.
The...
...ladies?
Aww yeah.
You catch more flies with honey!
Time to hit the road again!
What's wrong?
Sena?
Yukimitsu!
Yukimitsu?!
Football Clinic!
What does a cornerback do?
Stop the opponent's wide receivers from catching!
Hinder your enemy's movement so he can't get near any passes! Ya-ha!
Umm... About Yukimitsu...
I don't intend to slow down our pace.
But...
Forget about him.
You guys either keep up or get left in the dust.
What?!
Hiruma, aren't we all supposed to be teammates
who've made it this far together?
I don't need you reminding me of anything!
You're too soft, Sena.
Coach Doburoku?
I'll tell you right know, that boy is finished.
I never expected the whole lot of you to last until the end.
Right, Hiruma?
But...
I see you think you're good enough to merit worrying about others.
Ow!
See? Your knees must be screaming.
There you have it.
Because of him, we only got half as far as we should have today.
At that rate, we wouldn't make it home in time for the Christmas Bowl.
I'm gonna hit the hay.
We get up early again tomorrow.
Yukimitsu?
Yukimitsu, wait!
No, I don't want to quit!
I want to stay with everyone, all the way till the end!
I'll run without any breaks if that's what it takes!
Guys...
Sena?
What do you think you're doing, Yukimitsu?
It's my fault we're behind schedule,
if I don't make the difference up now...
You can't possibly think you can run without ever stopping!
That's crazy!
But...
I don't...
want to have to quit!
I was so shocked when I learned YOU were Eyeshield, Sena.
Yeah... Sorry for keeping it a secret.
Eyeshield's speed was so incredible...
You must have been born to play football.
Oh, no, I'm really not that great...
And you're so fearless, like when you stood up to Zokugaku.
That actually wasn't me...
On the other hand, I...
I've done nothing but study since I was a kid.
Never really played outside.
In elementary school...
This is a very important time for you.
In middle school...
Even in high school...
This is a very important time for you.
I wondered if I'd chosen the wrong path...
A path with no memories...
Wondering, "Will I regret going through high school like this?"
But being introduced to football, seeing Eyeshield in action,
made me want to DO something for the first time ever!
I still don't know why I try...
I don't have your talent or tenacity,
so what could all this effort possibly give me?
But...
But I made my choice.
No matter what happens, I'm going to stick with football.
Yukimitsu...
I haven't played in any games,
but staying on the team to the end is my own personal battle.
If I bow out of the death march, it'll mean I've lost.
I absolutely will not give up!
I'd better get going...
Good luck!
Good luck, Yukimitsu...
The rain's getting worse and worse...
The water'll make their feet feel heavier...
Someone's going down, I can feel it.
Don't stop moving your feet, even for a second!
I think... I'm hitting my limit...
There's so much rain I can barely see the rock...
I can't build up any speed.
I wonder how far Yukimitsu's gone...
Is he doing all right in the rain?
Yukimitsu!
How are you doing?
You really should rest...
Hop on the truck bed and ride for a while...
I'm fine...
I don't want to quit!
I'm staying... with you all...
...all the way...
...to the Christmas Bowl.
Yukimitsu!
You okay?!
Leave him!
I told you, if you can't keep up, you get tossed aside!
But-
We're out of time!
If we waste any more time,
we won't make it to Vegas OR the fall tournament!
Come on.
If I bow out of the death march, it'll mean I've lost.
I absolutely will not give up!
You're slowing down.
You must've put on a few pounds, Suzuna!
I didn't gain an ounce!
Besides, I'm on roller blades, I can't be that heavy!
You don't get it, Suzuna.
I'm the only one here pulling someone else's weight.
The rest of them are alone!
Yeah, I guess, but-
No braking... and zig-zag!
We'll go to the Christmas Bowl together.
All of us...
The pain won't beat me!
Thank you, Sena.
Yukimitsu?
I'm fine now, thanks to you.
But...
Yukimitsu, that's the wrong way!
I know...
I want to rerun it...
...from where I collapsed.
I don't want to lose my battle.
Yukimitsu, win, for all of us,
your own battle, and the Christmas Bowl!
Who said you could stop?!
Why is it only me?!
You're all blessed to be such close friends.
I've gotta admit I'm jealous.
Death March - Day 11
1406km to Las Vegas
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima blaze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
1000 kilometers to the end!
The death march is reaching its climax!
Everyone's so amazing!
We all have to stay focused until the very end!
Shooting for the goal's all well and good, but do I sense trouble?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Final Trial! Ya-ha!
You're slowing down again, bro.
Okay, then I'll carry you on my shoulders!
I can handle even the fattest Suzuna!
Hiyah!
- OH, MY SISTER!
- Shut up already, I didn't get fat!