Ojo White Knights vs. Deimon Devil Bats
- Ya-ha!
- Oh!
Then we won't let them score a single touchdown.
We'll stay in the lead until the final whistle blows,
and counter Yoichi Hiruma's tricks by not giving them a chance to rest.
For my part, I will take out...
...Eyeshield 21!
Set,
hut hut!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Superman!
Nice try.
Yes!
He dodged it!
With this strike,
I will destroy Deimon's pass!
Hiruma is skewered by the Trident Tackle!
Miraculously, he manages to at least protect the ball from Shin!
But...
Wow, he didn't drop it? Not bad!
Our shotgun got completely shut down...
Something's different from before...
What do you mean, Mamo?
Ojo's defense has always been solid, but they used to play very conservatively.
But today they're so aggressive!
Your moves are too plain, Shin!
A player of my caliber would've known you were blitzing from your stance.
Of course, Hiruma couldn't tell.
Well if YOU think so, Onihei...
I could tell right away!
I knew it!
That freak...
His blitzing stance was so obvious even a blind man could tell.
He didn't bother hiding it because he's trying to taunt us!
I see, now that Ojo's increased their offensive power,
they're able to take more risks on the defensive side!
So a stronger offense gave them a stronger defense?
How does that work? Ojo's defense was already the best!
Well, it's even stronger now.
Shoot, we gotta start scoring or we're gonna fall too far behind.
This is another effect of the Ballista...
Deimon can no longer complete passes against Ojo's defense.
Play your strongest run card, Yoichi Hiruma!
Don't strain yourself trying to play head games with me.
I already know that's our only option.
Our...
...strongest run card...
Eyeshield 21! You're up!
Blow a hole in Ojo's defense!
Right!
Eyeshield 21...
No, Sena Kobayakawa.
You showed me your light speed run six months ago in the spring tournament...
That day, you proved to me...
...that no amount of strength is enough...
...against speed that cannot be touched!
So I trained.
I trained non-stop...
To defeat you!
So did I!
That day, every time your incredible strength knocked me back...
I was hurt, I was scared...
But I knew that someday, we'd stand on the field again.
So I fought my way past one strong opponent after another!
All to make it here!
Then let's settle this for real.
With everything we've gained since that day!
Yes!
With Shin's blitz, Deimon's pass has been completely negated!
It seems they really have no choice but to have Eyeshield run!
Set, hut, hut, hut...
The first time...
I didn't realize exactly how much faster Shin had gotten and messed up the timing.
But this time...!
Hut!
No tricks, just as he promised.
How effective will Eyeshield 21's speed be against today's Shin?
What a fascinating jam session.
I'm not letting you butt in, you chained-up nutjob!
Sena!
Yes!
Shin...
Aah, THIS is it!
One-on-one, Seijuro Shin vs. Eyeshield 21!
This is nothing less than a clash of the two strongest runners!
No one else is able to interfere.
Don't blink folks-
Go, Sena!
-this field's about to explode!
Shin has me beat in power, technique, and all-around athleticism.
There's only one...
...just one area I can match him in!
Do it, Sena!
SPEED is our weapon!
This may settle everything.
Will it be the perfect player, Seijuro Shin?
Or the master of the world of light speed, Sena?
This time...
I'll break through!
There it is!
Can the Devil Bat Ghost pass through the Trident Tackle?!
Now!
He sped up when he turned to use...
- The Trident Tackle!
What?!
Sena!
A trident has THREE blades.
Moving left or right isn't enough to avoid it!
Well folks, Seijuro Shin wins again!
Man, is this... really happening?
The Devil Bat Ghost...
Sena's light speed legs...
I can't...
I can't win...
We're not done.
This isn't over!
Your speed hasn't truly reached light speed yet.
Get serious, Eyeshield 21!
My speed's not really at light speed?!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How does someone become a better football player?
Today we're talking about running backs!
A running back should keep his head as low as possible while running to better protect the ball.
Don't fumble it! Ya-ha!
Your speed hasn't truly reached light speed yet.
That can't be...
I'm sure I ran that last Devil Bat Ghost at top speed...
...and he still...
What're you doing, Sena? We're still on offense.
No time to stand around.
Monta... I'm sorry.
What're you apologizing for? Don't tell me you lost your drive already.
No... No, I haven't.
Shin was talking about true light speed...
But how am I supposed to...?
You sure you're all right?
If we're gonna run it, you're gonna have to face Shin again.
Are we really gonna keep running it, Hiruma?
Do we change plans? What do we do?
We don't do anything except give the ball to the Peewee!
Shin obliterated you a million times,
he pounded you halfway to the Earth's core,
and you beat him last time, didn't you?!
Hiruma...
We filled your thinking box BEFORE the game started.
Thinking box...?
You figure it out.
Right.
I'll figure out a way to beat Shin with what skills I've got.
Leave the rest to us, Sena.
That's right.
We're all part of the team!
We'll do everything we can so you don't have to bear the whole burden!
Yeah!
Kurita, Monta...
Everyone...
Shin, you think they're going to run Eyeshield again?
They might try to surprise us with a pass...
He'll come.
We haven't settled anything.
Shin...
And I won't let anyone interfere with your fight!
What the-?!
Whoa! Who's the doughball?
I really didn't wanna play...
It's too hard... I'm only human...
Omosadake?!
An amateur with nothing but weight...
He's using HIM in a game this important?!
So they're mustering all their power in the center?
A charge straight up the middle, perhaps?
No, ignore him.
It's gonna take a lot more to stop us this time!
Is Jumonji going to shield Sena as a lead blocker this time?
Set!
Hut, hut, hut...
I don't wanna...
Omo!
We've got a year's supply of mango pudding waiting if you push Ojo back!
Come!
Hut!
Mango...
Pudding!
Holy cow, Kurita and Omosadake make a heck of a heavyweight tag team!
He's just forcing his way through!
I don't care how heavy you are, you ain't stopping me!
I can't keep this up... I'm only human!
You're still fighting ME!
Yeah!
Deimon heavies Kurita and Omosadake opened up a hole in Ojo's defense,
and Jumonji just blew it wide open!
Eyeshield 21 is charging straight through Ojo's iron defense!
It's only started.
If I can't get through this time, it'll all be for nothing!
Light speed... TRUE light speed!
But how?
What a strong wind!
Wind...?
Yes! I got past Hiruma!
You're not there yet, Peewee.
Hiruma, how'd you know I was going right?
Look.
If the wind's slow, it's easy to tell which way you're going.
But if it's too fast, even I wouldn't be able to see.
That's it!
If the wind picks up, he won't be able to tell which way I'm spinning!
The "Thinking box..."
Knowing everything I need to win the game before it starts.
The "Playing box..."
Actually doing it!
Shin...
Another one-on-one battle!
It seems there's just no avoiding this MVP showdown!
Shin has already come out on top twice... What will Sena try here?
Will the third time be the charm?!
I WILL get through!
Come on, Eyeshield 21!
I'll use my arm, make the ghost a feint,
and use the recoil!
Don't tell me...!
Finally realized it, huh?
A demonic storm of light speed wind!
The Devil Light Hurricane! Ya-ha!
Yes! Sena made it!
Sena!
He's dodged the Trident Tackle!
The perfect player vs. a one-dimensional wonder...
The third round goes to...
Has the speed demon's technique come out on top?!
That's impossible...
You... How...
This can't be...
The world of light speed... No one's ever caught me once I hit it!
Eyeshield 21, the light speed running back...
to beat you, I had no other way, no other choice but to enter the world of light speed myself!
He is... the perfect player!
He's down...
The light speed Devil Light Hurricane...
...is stopped by a light speed Trident Tackle!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
Shin's caught up to Sena's light speed!
Shin can hit light speed too?!
He really is the perfect player! How do you beat that?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: #21, Defeated!
Ya-ha!
N-No way...
Where's my mango pudding?
Omo, you LOST!
Your pudding's over there.
I wanted it so bad...
I'm only human...