Finals
Deimon, Shinryuji, Ojo, Sado
We won...
We beat Shinryuji!
THE Shinryuji!
All right!
Let's kick butt in the next game, too!
Ouch!
My muscles are so sore!
Oww...
Hey!
Sena, I came to pick you up!
What's with the cart?!
It hurts to walk, right?
So you can ride in this!
Wh-What's with that?
Suzuna came by my place during breakfast
and used my sore muscles as an excuse to do this to me!
Only because you're too sore to walk!
Yeah...
Yesterday's game was so fierce...
Yep! Sure was.
Wow, Suzuna!
I can't believe you did that...
Hey! Mamo, help me out!
We're going to miss the game!
Right...
Let's hurry! It's the Taiyo Sphinx verses Hakushu Dinosaurs.
Ow ow!
This hurts to the max!
Ow, ow, ouch, owie! That HURTS!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Dreadnought Team - The Dinosaurs
Good morning...
All-Japan High School Football Tournament Kanto Tournament
Hakushu Dinosaurs vs. Taiyo Sphinx
There's nothin' "good" about it!
We've gotta hurry before all the good seats are gone.
C'mon! Let's go!
Just a sec!
We should go say hi to Banba and everyone first.
Say hi?
Taiyo Sphinx rivals!
We've still got a score to settle with them.
Sure do.
H-Hello!
Everyone came to cheer for you today.
How nice of you to drop by.
Nice going for little chick-a-dees.
What was that?!
Here, now...
...we'll flatten you!
I dare you to!
Then I can attack you!
- Bring it on!
Enough already, Kasamatsu!
Crap!
Banba...
I saw the game against Shinryuji.
You've grown powerful, Deimon.
We don't plan on losing, either.
We'll see you at the finals.
That's max exciting!
My, my. What a party.
Isn't he...?
My, what an honor.
Huh?
After crushing the invincible Shinryuji, Deimon's come to watch our game.
But I bet you came to watch the Taiyo Sphinx, not us.
Sorry, but who are you?
Wow, how shocking!
You don't remember me!
No, I remember... You're from the Hakushu Dinosaurs.
You're...
Maruko.
It's written with the characters "coin" from "10 yen coin" and "child."
It's written kinda weird, huh?
Yeah.
Well, we may play against you in the future, so see you then!
P-Play against us?
I can't let that slide.
Do you think you can defeat us?
I won't be looked down on!
No, no. I'm not mocking you at all!
Why are we going to this dumb football game anyway?
Mura, you're the one who wanted to flirt with the cheerleaders!
This stinks! Football's so boring!
Look out!
N-No way!
Sena!
The truck...
He stopped it with one hand!
Who the heck is he?
He'll be playing in this game.
He's Rikiya Gao.
Ga-Gao...?!
Rikiya...
He's so... powerful!
He's overpowering... No...
...he's threatening!
What is he?
What's with that monster?!
Gao's a freshman like me?!
There should be rules against high schoolers like that!
Calm down.
Football's about more than just brute strength.
We should know that by now.
R-Right.
That giant's nothing but a big ol' pushover!
Got that right!
We'll give 'em a thorough lashing!
- Yeah!
Hakushu'll be a cakewalk!
Yeah!
What's wrong, Harao?
I've been doing this with everyone for three years.
This is my last crack at the tournament.
Harao?
Whenever we come to the Kanto Tournament, I think...
...that the nationals are filled with monsters.
The Taiyo Sphinx's super-heavy line is first-rate
and can stand on par with any other team at nationals.
But deep down I know!
I know that I, the quarterback, is the only second-rate player here!
I'm no fool! Did you think I hadn't noticed?
I'm not a fool, either.
I know that ever since our humiliating tie with Deimon last spring,
you've kept up a good front,
but have been training like mad in secret.
Just relax and throw the ball.
Kasamatsu and I will protect you!
Exactly!
Harao, I swear that I'll protect you!
We won't let them mess up your passes!
No matter who are foes may be,
we will not let them stop us from going...
...to the Christmas Bowl!
I know!
It's not like I needed any reminding!
Well, the game's about to start!
The Hakushu Dinosaurs from the SIC District
will be going up against the Taiyo Sphinx from the Kanagawa District.
This is one of the bigger games.
It's truly a game where two powerhouses collide!
Riko...?
Sorry! I'm really excited about this game...
Let's go!
- Yeah!
Everyone at Taiyo's pretty worked up.
Battle-hungry!
Hakushu time!
Hakushu Dinosaurs vs. Taiyo Sphinx
Ra!
Set!
Their formation-!
The linemen are...
...bunched up super close!
There's no room between them!
It's called a split.
It's a play where they pack themselves tightly together
so that no one can break through the line.
It's a human wall meant to protect their passes.
Only the Taiyo Sphinx could pull this off!
The heavy-weight army forms an impenetrable wall
around its QB pharaoh so he can throw his passes!
W-What gives?! They aren't budging!
They've been flattened!
The Taiyo line quickly obliterated the entire Hakushu line!
Harao!
Right!
The Taiyo Sphinx have already gotten their first down!
You rock, Banba!
- Kasamatsu!
- Harao!
A-Amazing!
Banba!
They're way more powerful than when we played against them!
Yeah!
See that?
This is our secret weapon,
the indestructible golden shield,
King Tut's Mask!
Man, those Taiyo guys are strong...
But it's still not time...
...to put him on the field.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How many people do you need to have on a team?
Here's your hint! It's the same number in soccer.
You need eleven people to play a game.
It's OK to swap out players as often as you like during the game.
Teamwork's important! Ya-ha!
We will protect our Pharaoh!
Just relax and throw your passes, Harao!
I know!
They did it! Touchdown!
Taiyo gained seven points.
Hakushu Dinosaurs 0 - Taiyo Sphinx 7
They're absolutely perfect!
Their perfect line has given birth to a perfect offense!
This is how an ideal offense should be played!
Does that mean that the Taiyo Sphinx have turned into an offensive team?
No!
Really?
Just look!
Chariot Bump!
He tackled the other player so quickly!
Right! This is what makes King Tut's Mask so scary!
It's scary?!
Well, if they change the formation of their iron wall just a little,
they can transform into a tank capable of toppling any offense!
A-Amazing!
Banba!
Cool!
They're easily countering the enemy's offense...
...and blowing past their opponent's defense.
I was afraid we'd be no match for them...
This certainly is problematic.
Set, hut!
Stay alert!
I know!
Touchdown!
It's time.
We'll never make it to the Christmas Bowl
if we don't let our teammates pack on some more in-game experience...
But they're not getting past Banba.
We're outta options...
Yeah!
Now, now... You really shouldn't spit here!
It looks like a regular mouthpiece isn't good enough...
I figured you'd need a titanium alloy one.
Yeah, that's better.
Hakushu Dinosaurs 0 - Taiyo Sphinx 21
The Taiyo Sphinx are overpowering them!
With a 21 point lead, it's clear who'll win!
Okay, let's go.
Just remember to hold back some.
Don't break Banba or that Harao guy's bones.
Or would that be asking too much from you?
You bet it is.
Isn't he that guy?
R-Rikiya Gao is entering the field!
N-No way!
What's wrong, Mamori?
In all of the Hakushu Dinosaurs' previous games...
...their opposing teams have had to forfeit in the middle of the game!
And it always happens after they send Gao onto the field.
What's with that?!
All of the other teams' quarterbacks...
...left the game with broken bones!
No way!
Broken bones...?
Is he... a monster?
This is bad. Everyone's afraid of him.
Do they think that they can overcome our super heavy line by swapping out a single player?
Harao...
Where's your pride?!
We are the Taiyo Sphinx! Our battle chariots are invincible!
- Yeah!
Nice going, Harao!
Yeah. If he hadn't said that, his team would have lost their team spirit.
Set, hut, hut!
He's not moving!
I told you not to use your full power right off the bat...
I told you, Marco. It's not happening.
W-What-?!
S-Such strength...
He's blowing off all my attempts to stop him!
He's inhumanly strong!
Can a person... really be this strong?!
B-Banba!
I won't... I won't let you through!
I WILL protect Harao!
Banba!
Hakushu Dinosaurs 28 - Taiyo Sphinx 21
I-I can't believe it...
Now he's done it.
He didn't use any special moves or strategies.
And he did it... all on his own!
Can you really play like that?
The Taiyo Sphinx...
...don't have any linemen left!
B-Banba!
So? Is the game still on?
There's no way we could keep playing.
We forfeit.
The Taiyo Sphinx are the first ones who've walked away
with their QB still in one piece.
He protected his Pharaoh even after passing out.
Banba's quite the player.
Just relax and throw the ball.
Kasamatsu and I will protect you!
Banba... I have no regrets!
I'm proud that I got to fight with everyone.
Rikiya... Gao...
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
What's with that speed?!
That's Taiga Kamiya from the Seibu Wild Gunmen's opposing team, the Misaki Wolves?!
This is the Kanto Tournament!
Everyone here really is amazing!
Seibu's in trouble if they don't keep their guard up.
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Wolves' Battlefield!
Ya-ha!
There aren't any cheerleaders...
There are some cheerleaders!
Hey, cuties!
Wanna go have some ice cream with me?
Caught ya!
No way.
What's he doing with the chicks?!
Mura, so you like to flirt with dogs?
Not in your dreams!