Eyeshield 21!
Please watch it! Please watch! Please watch!
Good day to all you football fans!
The big game between Deimon Devil Bats and Ojo White Knights
that everyone's been eagerly looking forward to is tomorrow!
I'm really excited!
Will the winners will be...
...the ones who beat the Shinryuji Nagas...
...that everyone's talking about...
...the Deimon Devil Bats?
Or will it be the grand king that prides itself
on its iron wall defense and unparalleled offense, the Ojo White Knights?
I've asked both teams here as special guests today.
Let's hear how the players feel about the upcoming game!
I'm already so excited!
I'm max excited, too!
I'm going to give an upbeat interview unlike any before, so stay tuned!
I'm MAX looking forward to it!
Ashi wa bou no you ude wa agaranai,
My legs are like sticks, my arms are hanging limp,
ore no subete ga tsuujinai.
I just can't give it my all.
Teki wa dekkakute sugee chikara da,
My opponent's huge, and really really strong,
naketekuru hodo ka kanawanai.
he's so much better it makes me wanna cry.
Demo mae wo mukeba nando demo
But when I look back up,
butsukatteiku nakama
I see my teammates
boroboro na no ni akiramechanain da.
tired and beaten up, but ready to keep going.
Ima mimi sumaseba tomodachi no todaeru koto no nai eeru
And now that I listen, I hear them cheering nonstop
garagara koe de sakenderun da!
screaming at the top of their lungs!
Ore nanka wo shinjiten da!
They still believe in me.
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Iki wo kirashite kakedashite,
Breathe deep, plant your feet,
tsumazuite kizu tsuite,
trip and fall, hurt and sore,
Wararete akireraretemo,
laughing or exhausted,
nando datte sou tachiagatte!
stand up one more time!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
Saigo made saigo made
Don't ever, don't ever,
Akiramenai honoo no RUNNING BACK!
don't ever give up, blazing running back!
The Demon vs. The Light Speed Man!
S-So then, let's get started.
I can already feel tremendous tension coming from both teams.
First off, would you please tell me how you feel about the game tomorrow?
Well, I'll be max catching like nuts!
I'm gonna super max catch big time!
R-Really? And what does Ojo's receiver, Sakuraba, have to say?
Will you two be duking it out as two of the Top Four receivers in Kanto?
There's no way I'll lose!
I'll prove that I'm the number one catcher out there!
I-I was asking Sakuraba...
We've been training so hard everyday, we've been sweating blood!
Right, Sena?
Oh. Is that true, Sena?
S-Sena?! You turned to stone!
I-I'm nervous.
Oh...
Sena, get a grip!
My voice recorder for the interview!
Sorry, he's horrible with electronics.
S-So then, please give me your thoughts, Sakuraba!
To say the least, I'm different than I used to be.
I'd like to prove to everyone that I'm the best receiver in Kanto.
I-I see. It feels like the competition between you two's already started.
Now then, the battle between Sena and Shin is what this game really comes down to.
How do you feel about that, Sena?
U-Um...
N-No good...
So how about you, Shin?
There's but one thing for me to do.
I'm going to use all of my strength to crush Eyeshield out on the field.
Shin...
This man has always stood before me, always improving.
How many times have I dared to try catching up to him only to fail?
Shin...
Do you remember when we first joined the team?
You were already on a higher plane than everyone else.
Next, #60!
Huh? Me?
Next, #51!
It's the bashing ring!
Players surround one person and slam into him from different directions.
It's a training style that got its name from them bashing up the player.
But he just joined the team...
That shows just how much we're expecting from him.
Next is the 40-yard dash!
Shin, 4.62 seconds!
Amazing...
He's a seventh grader, and already Ojo's fastest...
You're lazy!
My apologies.
You could have done it in 4.5 seconds.
Did the bashing ring exhaust you?
But that's nothing compared to a real game when going up against all those opponents.
No amount of power will work against a foe you can't touch.
Right.
Thank you very much!
Amazing!
I'd like to become as great as Shin someday!
Shogun's summer camp has always been tough...
But it's been crazy...
...ever since Shin joined.
You're lazy!
New menu! Give me 10 more laps!
- Okay!
That's strange.
The other 20 players are late.
You go back to your dorms.
I'll wait here.
Coach...
What was that?!
Hey, w-wait!
The guys... all of them left!
Nakamura and Kawano left!
What?! So did Otawara and Sakuraba!
Shogun had been counting on Otawara, and now he's gone...
He must be shocked.
Thirty years ago, when Doburoku and I were still players...
...our dream came to an early demise.
I worked them hard so they wouldn't go through that, too.
Was I... wrong?
Hey, one of them's coming back!
What?!
He's coming back?
Sakuraba!
Coach... I'm sorry... I'm so late....
I finished... the extra ten laps.
Sakuraba...
Hey, sorry!
I got lost!
I asked a dog for directions, but I couldn't understand him!
Why'd you ask a dog for directions?!
Don't worry about the small stuff!
Geez, Otawara.
Coach...
You aren't mistaken.
Please give us as much rigorous training as it takes for us to win.
I'll prove to you that you've been right these past thirty years.
Shin, I used to be jealous of your innate ability.
But not anymore.
I'm proud that I can play football together on the same team as you.
Just kidding!
Sakuraba...
You may not have noticed,
but you've improved more than anyone this past year.
Shin...
Deimon is formidable.
We need your strength in order to win.
Let's reach the top together!
Yeah!
But man, those two were intense!
We can't lose to them! Right, Sena?
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong, Sena? You don't look well.
No, I'm fine.
Really? That's good to hear.
See ya tomorrow!
Let's do our best!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
In football a kick is worth three points. So how many is a touchdown worth?
You get a bunch of points!
When you enter the enemy's end zone and score a touchdown, you get six points.
Then there's the extra point conversions!
Get even more points! Ya-ha!
That was you 500th ball!
Your accuracy was 96%!
I'm not done yet.
A scrimmage?!
Right before the Spring Tournament?!
With the Deimon Devil Bats?
I've never even heard of them.
Of course not. We just started!
I can't believe he's challenging Ojo after just making a new team at our new school!
It's okay. Let him handle this.
Don't be stupid. Go on home, go on!
Oh, so the invincible Ojo is scared.
What?!
Not that it matters to me.
Since you're that scared of a newly formed team, I should go ask some other team.
Jerk! Are you lookin' for a fight?! Huh?!
Let's do it.
Shin?!
If it isn't the ace himself.
We won't hold back against anyone.
Interesting...
We didn't even get a first down!
You're making a mockery of football by challenging us with this lame make-shift team!
No we're not! We're not...
We're definitely gonna go to Christmas Bowl!
Think you'll make it to the Christmas Bowl with this lame team?
Don't make me laugh, stupid!
What?!
Let's go.
You jerk. You didn't hold back at all.
If you underestimate an opponent, they will take take you down someday.
I'd love to hear what type of weakness a monster like you has.
If a man appeared who runs as fast as the speed of light,
my power would be rendered meaningless.
Why'd you tell me that?
I want to fight a strong opponent. That's all.
Next time I'll bring just what you're looking for.
He'll be an untouchable,
light speed running back.
When you do, I'll use all of my strength to crush him out on the field.
It's taken two years.
Even though he told us to go home early today so we can prepare for tomorrow,
that'll just make our bodies stiffen up.
There's no way we can just rest up!
Right now we're...
...pretty cool-looking.
Especially me.
I just stepped on something...
There's but one thing for me to do.
I'm going to use all of my strength to crush Eyeshield out on the field.
- Run for it!
What?! Why me?!
Huh? Didn't this happen...
...when I first entered high school?!
Hiruma?
Wasn't that a nostalgic little show?
So I was wondering why...
Unlike me, Shin is strong and full of confidence...
Getting scared before the game with Ojo?
No, that's not really... what I meant.
It's just...
I'm really nervous about it.
Peewee,
try to get past me.
Hiruma?
I just challenged you!
Uh, okay...
I can't believe I'm up against Hiruma before our big game.
But this is my first time ever going up against Hiruma.
This is Hiruma, the one who got me into the world of football.
Here I go!
His right hand moved!
A feint?!
I did it! I got past Hiruma!
Ouch!
Rope?
H-Hiruma?
You've still got a lot to learn, Peewee!
When did you-?
You may not have noticed, but your speed drops a little when you make that spin.
Your plays are always too stupidly obvious.
Seijuro Shin's a monster.
There's no telling how he'll come at you.
But the game's tomorrow...
I'll never beat Shin like this.
Peewee!
Just remember this:
You were chosen to crush Ojo...
...by me.
I was chosen?
I was chosen by Hiruma to crush Ojo...
So you better crush Seijuro Shin!
Okay!
Hiruma, I swear I'll win! I'll beat Ojo and Shin!
Houkago no koutei ni yohou hazure no ame,
Schools out, and it started raining out of nowhere,
ima nara namida nagashitemo barenai to omottetandaro.
You think, "If I start crying now, no one will know."
Umai koto ikanakute tsukareteru toki mo
You're all by yourself, fighting to keep a smile on your face
sore demo egao wo tsukutte hitori tatakattendaro
even when you're tired, or things aren't going your way.
Yokei na kotoba hitokoto ookute,
One annoying word too many,
daiji na kotoba hitokoto tarinakute.
one kind word too short.
Baka de yabo de shou mo nai ore da kedo
I may be dumb and clumsy with words, but believe me when I say
omae wa hitori ja nai ze.
you're not all alone.
Utau ze...
I'll sing...
Tokoderu ze...
until you can listen...
Utau ze!
Sing it!
Tomenai de!
Don't stop!
It's finally time to settle the score with Ojo!
I get to fight against Shin!
Please win, Sena!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Challenge for Sovereignty!
Ya-ha!
Hey, we've been...
...running way too much!
But he'll eat us if we stop!
Right now we're...
...pretty lame-looking.
Especially me!
- He got eaten!