Whoo!
What's all that?
Fan mail for the team.
Fan mail?!
From all the people who watched the Amino game.
They're wishing us luck.
It's tough being so popular.
You didn't even PLAY.
Who's this for?
Eyeshield 21, go get 'em!
Eyeshield 21...
Eyeshield 21, Eyeshield 21, Eyeshield 21...
For God's sake, are these ALL for Eyeshield 21?!
Here's one for Komusubi!
It says, "Watching you fight so hard, even though you're so small,
makes me feel like being brave!"
That's so nice!
This one says, "Keep crushing the competition, Kurita!"
This one's for Hiruma...
"To Jumonji and his brothers, stick together and hold the line!"
We're NOT EVEN RELATED!
W-W-Why am I the only one with no fans?!
I-I-I didn't get to play against Amino!
Ooh, here's one for-
"Plain ol' Ishimaru."
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Ghost is Off Limits?!
Go long!
Max Catch!
Keep it up, everyone!
Does it seem like we've got more spectators since we beat Amino?
I guess so, now that you mention it.
Some of them are even taping us.
The Amino game...
It feels like we could take on anyone now, doesn't it?
We are invincible!
Huh?
The Devil Bat Ghost...
...is off limits?
Yup.
We've got some spies mixed in with the crowd up there.
Spies?
The Devil Bat Ghost is our secret weapon.
We can't afford to start showing it off.
You're not allowed to use it outside of actual games.
Is that clear?
Y-Yes.
He's right...
Now that we've gotten better,
our opponents are sure to start researching our abilities.
We have to be careful.
Man, I wanna get back on the field.
We gotta keep it up!
Eyeshield 21.
Shin...
Don't you dare fall before the finals.
I will face your new technique and beat it.
I'll see you at the finals,
and beat YOU!
Yikes, I'm shaking.
He's overwhelming.
Excellent rushing, Shin.
He's been really fired up since he watched the Amino game.
Eyeshield!
Whoa!
Nice!
His execution gets sharper and faster every time.
It gives me goosebumps.
Okay! I need to go another round!
Those three aren't really cut out to train with Otawara.
Shin... Otawara...
I suppose they need higher-caliber training partners.
A corporate team?
Yes, the Shuei Elephants.
Several of their members are Ojo alumni.
You two are to practice with them tomorrow morning!
Yes, sir.
Adult players are faster than high schoolers and have more stamina.
It will be a very good learning experience.
Sir.
Listen up!
Go down onto the field we're playing on in round 2.
Go ONTO the field?
What for?
R-Right, well, it's important to get used to the new setting,
and it'll help if you get familiar with the unique aspects of the turf.
An adult team called the Shuei Elephants is practicing there,
and we might learn something from watching them!
Unique aspects? Whatev.
Stop your mumbling and get down there!
W-We're going!
The bus to the Shuei Arena...
This one!
- Bro!
- Taki!
Guys! This is the bus for the Shuei Arena!
Oh, it's that one?
That is NOT the Shuei Arena bus.
Taki, that's not the right b-
Nagano Hot Springs Tour
They're gone...
Ugh, that moron!
So are we really going?
You guys hungry?
- Yeah.
- Me, too.
Hey, Sena!
We're gonna grab a quick bite.
We're not kids!
We'll catch up with you later.
Later!
Welcome!
Hey, wait-
We're finally here!
They're already at it!
That's a pro team for ya.
They pack a REAL punch!
They're all so big, but they're fast, too!
H-Huh?
What's wrong?
Those are...
Ojo uniforms?
Huh?!
Next!
One of the high school kids.
Shin...
Football Clinic!
What is Arena Football?
An indoor football game played with eight people.
It's popular enough in America that it has its own league! Ya-ha!
Set, hut!
Wow.
I'm shocked...
They're only in high school?
They earned their status as Ojo's two superstars, Shin and Otawara!
Even against pro players, no one can slow them down.
Hey!
Mr. Kumabukuro!
You...
Oh, Suzuna! Haven't seen you in a while!
And you two... You're from Deimon...
What're you doing here?
Checking out where our next game's gonna be.
Yourself?
Well, uh...
So Shin and Otawara are...
Shin is amazing.
He's really worked on his speed and agility.
Pretty scary, isn't it?
Hey, we survived that horrible death march!
We won't lose!
How would we do...
I want to see if how I stand up against a corporate team, too...
Okay, great job!
You two can hit the showers.
- Right!
- Okay.
Over already?
Too bad Eyeshield wasn't here, that'd have been REALLY fun to watch.
Well, Eyeshield's-
Suzuna!
-location is a secret.
Did something happen to Eyeshield?
N-No, of course not!
Right, right, nothing at all.
Say what?
You won't make it in time?
Why not?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
They're supposed to be playing the Samurai Warriors today.
Looks like he's mad about something.
It's almost kickoff time!
Where the heck are you?
Huh?!
Everyone, welcome to the Nagano Hot Springs Tour-
How can this be?
How can this be?!
We can't have a game NOW.
This was a big one that we had a lot riding on, too.
Arima!
Mr. Kumabukuro?
If you're short a few players, why don't you ask them?
We play on Deimon High School's football team!
You kids know pass routes?
Of course!
Really? Can you give us a hand?
Yes!
A corporate team! My arms are itching for action!
That's right...
I can't play without my Eyeshield gear...
Set!
Hut hut, hut!
Go go!
The Warriors are mostly a passing team.
The QB Arima stays in the center,
and he makes most of his passes to the same three receivers,
but how will he handle playing without his usual teammates?
He's got Monta- I mean, Raimon.
True, but that's still only one option.
If Eyeshield were out there,
THAT would spice things up.
Is this a joke?
Are we playing a midget team?
I can't play, I'm too worried I'm gonna trample this kid!
I'm open!
Monta broke free!
Go!
That's the high school kid.
If gets injured, it'll be on my head.
He threw it to the other receiver.
Not on my watch!
Get him!
The Big Bang Bros...
...Sandwich Press!
That was the Big Bang Bros. Sandwich Press!
Why the heck didn't he pass it to Mon-Mon?!
Hey, they're already playing!
Crap crap crap crap crap crap!
Those two're from Deimon, aren't they?
Deimon...
Eyeshield...
Set, hut!
Big Bang Bros...
...Sandwich Press!
Monta was open again...
Set, hut!
Let's try a scramble!
I'll run it myself!
Big Bang Bros.!
Pass it to me!
Pass it, pass it!
The scramble didn't work, either.
They're not gaining any ground.
Set, hut, hut!
Fine... If you don't want to pass to me...
Oh, no! He's going to intercept it!
C'mere!
Max Catch!
If the pass won't come to me, I'll go to the pass!
Huh?
Yay, Mon-Mon!
He made it from all the way over there?
Monta!
That little runt!
Have a bite of the Sandwich Press!
Master's "HNNRABA" block!
Sweet!
First down!
Yay!
He did it!
Good one!
You two are really good!
I apologize for not trusting you earlier.
It's cool!
I could do this, too...
...with the strength I gained on the death march!
That's...
Shin...
Shin's watching...
If I only had an eye shield...
Sena?
Set...
Those pipsqueaks duped us before...
But the kid gloves are off!
I'll just squash you from above, kid!
Max Catch-
I guess there's just too much of a gap, eh?
They're really going after them now.
Why are you standing on the sidelines, Eyeshield?
My senses tell me there should be one in here.
Set, hut!
The emergency running back's not cutting it.
Shin...
Eyeshield 21...
Your running has evolved.
You've mastered such a diabolical running style, why are you sitting this out?
I WANT to play, I really do, but...
Show me! Show me your running!
Shin...
Suzuna?
Here ya go.
Suzuna!
You can play as long as you've got this on, right?
Right?
Yeah!
Oh ho! It's Eyeshield 21!
I called him over. You can thank me later!
We've been waiting for you!
Waiting!
Sorry it took so long.
I'm glad to be on your team for today.
R-Right...
Go, go, Deimon!
Fight, fight, shorties!
Let's go, let's go!
Yay!
Set, hut!
Give me the ball!
A runt rush? Gimme a break!
Big Bang Bros...
...Sandwich Press!
W-What did he do?
Charge!
Touchdown!
Whoa...
Yes!
Wh-Who's the kid with the eye shield?
I've never seen anyone run like that.
That's the famous "Devil Hero"
who appeared on the high school football scene out of nowhere...
Eyeshield 21!
Huh? High school?!
He's an outstanding player who is, in some ways, on par with Shin.
He's awesome.
There's more.
Your running is better than that.
Show me your true abilities...
Eyeshield 21!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
It's time for the Devil Bat Ghost!
Watch out, because Shin and Otawara are getting in the game, too!
I want to face Shin again!
Are Shin and Sena about to clash again?
Who's gonna win?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Ghost vs. The Spear! Ya-ha!
Nagano's Shiromomo Hot Spring Resort
This hot spring is great...
We're making nice animal friends, too...
How can this be?!
HOW CAN THIS BE?!