ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The tournament starts today. My debut game as manager!
Sena!
Who's that?!
He's so fast!
High schoolers don't run that fast!
What I Hold In My Hands!
Is the game over, Ishimaru?
Not until this play ends...
Either he goes down, and we lose...
...or we come from behind.
Smash him!
Oh no, if he runs that way-
Go!
Wow, he got through!
Ya-ha!
The Devil Bats' first win!
That's just amazing!
He's as small as Sena, but he's such a skilled athlete!
If Sena just worked as hard as him-
Where's Sena?!
Ishimaru, where's Sena?
He screwed up his managerial duties, so Hiruma dragged him back behind that shed.
He did what?!
Sena!
S-Sena!
What happened?!
It's my fault... I'm so sorry!
If I hadn't told you to join a club...
I'm sure you did your best, Sena, I'm sorry!
Mamori... you're killing me.
Oh thank goodness, you're conscious, Sena!
Hey manaJERK, what're you doing?
Get your butt up and collect the equipment.
Hold it, Hiruma...
Yeah? What?
M-Mamori, I actually-
After a year of your ignoring their reprimands and continuing your savagery,
even the school disciplinary committee has given up on trying to stop you.
But what you've done today...
But what I've done today?
But what you've done today is unforgivable!
Oh? So what happens when you don't forgive someone?
It means...
You'll use your authority as a member of the committee to shut down the club as punishment?
I wouldn't do that.
It's the middle of a tournament, the team would be disqualified, right?
Instead, I'll never let you near Sena again!
I'll make him quit the football club!
M-Mamori, I-
I'll find a nicer club for you, Sena, okay?
B-But-
You don't have to ever worry, Sena.
I'll always be here for you.
Always.
He needs a girl to protect him!
What a wiener!
You jerks!
I won't let you get away with bullying Sena anymore!
You don't have to cry, Sena.
They're just mean to you because you're such a nice person.
But it's okay now.
I'll be there to protect you from now on, Sena!
'Kay?
Let's go.
Sena?
Mamori.
I... want to keep trying...
For a little longer.
But if you hang around them, they'll eat you alive!
I-I'll be fine!
I AM a man, after all!
Sena...
Our first win, our first win!
The Devil Bats' first victory!
We might actually get pretty far this season!
So long as we don't have to play the Ojo White Knights!
The Ojo White Knights?
Yup.
Hiruma, who're our next opponents?
The Ojo White Knights.
What, that's it?
The Devil Bats made their comeback a moment later.
You missed the one important part.
Sakuraba, Shin!
Why didn't you record until the very end?!
Especially you, Sakuraba. You were in charge of taping the game!
Well, Coach, they just came-
No, it's all my fault. I abandoned our post.
You're getting lazy!
Shin, you won't be starting in the game against the Devil Bats.
I understand.
In fact, all of you have been slacking off lately.
Lack of mental focus is a breeding ground for defeat!
Remember, if the opponent can't score, it only takes one point to beat them.
The most important aspect of football is an impenetrable defense!
This will be the finest year ever for the White Knights' defense.
We'll return with the pennant held high above our heads! Got it?!
Sir!
I'm not starting.
It's because I had a mental lapse.
I'm taking it too easy on myself.
Pampered hands such as mine aren't capable of grasping anything!
Oh yeah! Who is Eyeshield?
Hiruma, you have to bring him to the track team!
Yeah, who could he be?
In football, if the opponent scores 99 points, you just need to score 100.
The most important aspect of football is an unstoppable offense!
All we need to do is block, secure a clear path, and let Eyeshield 21 do the rest.
His hands...
...hold the key to 100 points!
Football clinic!
How does playing offense work?
The offense has four chances to advance the ball 10 yards!
If they can advance it 10 yards in four tries or less, they get another four tries! Ya-ha!
Our second game is against the Ojo White Knights... Wonder if we'll do well...
Sena!
Mamori?
I've decided I'm going to stay with you for as long as you're in the football club.
I need to make sure he doesn't bully you.
What IS this?!
You'll catch some kind of disease if you hang around here!
I'll clean this mess up!
Oh wow, what is this?!
Holy smokes!
Whoa!
It's to celebrate the Devil Bats' first win!
Yum!
The cake tastes even better now that the clubhouse is cleaned up!
You can't beat Kariya's bakery by the station for cream puffs!
Their two-layered outer shells are to die for!
All moist and flaky-
They don't use any water to make them, only milk!
And the filling's so good!
The texture's so smooth and creamy, there aren't even words to-
Yo!
The gang's all here, huh?
Time to plan for the White Knights game.
Hiruma, you could've let us clean up the cake first!
Why are you so inconsiderate?!
What do you think you're doing here, exactly?
You're not a member.
I, um...
If you're not here on club business, beat it.
I'm Sena's bodyguard. I'm here to make sure you don't pick on him!
Bodyguard, huh...? Whatever you say.
Well, that's what I say.
You two line those figures up on the field.
These are really well-made.
The modeling club was generous enough to stay up all night sculpting them.
Generous... Right.
Right! Lemme explain the plan.
This guy zooms right on through.
That is all.
You made all those for that?
So... he's playing again...
But, maybe doing everything would be too scary, right?
Something wrong, Sena?
Oh, no, nothing...
I doubt that Eyeshield boy would be frightened.
I wonder...
Well, he stood up to those big scary guys even though he's so small.
You should follow his example, Sena!
M-Maybe you're right.
Umm... I think it's safe to tell Mamori...
Yeah, true...
No way. She'll be all, "No, it's too dangerous! You have to quit!"
What are you trying to pull over here?!
Still, you want to run the whole game, with no passing at all?
Even if it's 3rd and 9?
It's not like anyone can catch.
Umm, what's 3rd down?
The offense starts out with four "plays."
If they can advance 10 yards within those four plays,
they get another set of four plays.
"3rd down" is what you call the third play in that set.
Mamori?
Very good!
I read a rule book yesterday and memorized everything!
Bah.
Doing a bunch of last-minute cramming ain't gonna help anybody.
I learned everything.
Oh? What if ask something you don't know?
I know EVERYTHING.
All right, I'll give you three advanced questions.
If you get a single one wrong, you can never oppose me again.
Fine. And if I get them all right, you have to promise you'll never hurt or bully Sena!
Ya-ha!
Don't pick on Sena!
Get ready!
Question number one: How many meters is 10 yards?
That's easy. About nine meters.
WRONG! You have to be specific to at least a few decimal points.
That has nothing to do with the rules of football!
Answer it!
9.1440183 meters.
Name all the ways the ball can change possession!
When the ball isn't advanced 10 yards in four downs,
after a punt, after a field goal,
after a blocked kick, at the half, and when the defense steals the ball!
Sounds like things are getting wild in there.
Last question.
Hey, Man-Pig, Peewee, time for weight training.
Wait, no fair!
What about the last question?!
Hiruma!
You're up first, Peewee.
Why does Sena have to train?
Our managers need to have stamina, too.
We'll start with something light.
Yeah, 20kg should do it.
Uh huh.
Give 20kg a try, okay, Sena?
Oh, yeah.
Five kilos...
...10 kilos.
Sena-Sena's!
Okay, so 20kg is too much!
I thought I was gonna die...
This, I can just about handle.
Bench Press, Sena Kobayakawa. New high school record - Lowest ever.
Well, the bar by itself is 10kg...
Is it that heavy?
Ooh, that was 20kg!
Bench Press, Mamori Anezaki. 20kg.
Bench Press, Yoichi Hiruma. 75kg.
Bench Press, Ryokan Kurita. 160kg.
1-160kg?!
Ojo White Knights Bench Press, Haruto Sakuraba. 50kg.
Great job.
As always.
Ojo White Knights Bench Press, Seijuro Shin. 140kg.
140kg, huh?
Ojo White Knights Bench Press, Makoto Otawara. 135kg.
You finally beat me.
But I ain't finished yet!
Numbers mean nothing.
It takes more than power to succeed in this world.
You aren't just another powerhouse.
You're also the fastest high schooler in the country.
No one can stand up to your tackle, Shin.
They call it the "Spear!"
For you, a regular tackle's a super move!
I'm such a weakling.
Even Mamori's stronger than me.
It's okay, you're the manager, Sena.
You don't need strength.
Mamori Anezaki of the disciplinary committee!
You are urgently needed in the broadcasting room!
Please come as quickly as possible! Like right now! Please!
What could they want?
Our meeting's not until tomorrow...
I've got to go for a bit, Sena, will you be okay?
Don't start picking on him just because I'm leaving!
Shouldn't you get going? They said it was urgent.
Finally, no more obstacles.
C'mon, Peewee, it's time to run.
The 40-yard dash!
Y-Yes!
He's so fast.
I realize this sounds arrogant,
but I have yet to find a single person faster than myself.
Well, duh!
However, if such a man DOES exist...
If a man so fast as to seem untouchable appeared before me...
A man with such speed that I couldn't lay a finger on him...
No amount of power would be enough.
What was that all about?
Let's go, one more round!
Get moving!
W-What?! Sena!
Why are you so mean to him?!
Sena, Sena!
Sena...
You just aren't cut out for this club.
Just quit, okay? You've tried hard enough!
Mamori...
I've always had to rely on you to save me.
In kindergarten, elementary school...
But someday, I want to let go of your hand...
...and use my own...
I'm okay. I'll get up on my own.
I'm sticking with the football team.
I want to keep going!
Sena...
You sure you can hack it, Sena?
I think I may have piled too much work on you.
He was bound to make mistakes, having so many managerial duties on his list...
Huh?
If we just had a co-manager, Sena's job would be considerably easier...
A manager?
What to do...?
Can girls do it? Can anyone join?
But of course.
Then I'm joining. I'll be a manager!
Hooray! Now there's four of us!
I'll work hard too, Sena!
More slave labor!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
It's time to face the strongest team out there, the Ojo White Knights!
But their ironclad defense won't let a single run through!
I-I just have to believe in everyone and try my best!
Get over it, scaredy-cat!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Half-Second Bodyguards!
Ya-ha!
Why does Hiruma always disappear when it's time to clean up?
Geez!
No, not that one-
What the heck?!