We shall hereby commence the scrimmage between Ojo University Silver Knights
and Ojo White Knights.
Without us, Ojo's golden generation,
you're like a bunch of helpless babies!
You're losers!
Just thinking about it ticks me off!
They're dead once the game starts!
You're on the bench since you'll attack them.
Not again!
Let go! This stinks! Hey!
Listen up, everyone.
This is our Ballista's debut game.
Let's show the golden generation the new and improved White Knights!
Leave it to us!
We aren't going to take it easy on you just because you're high school students!
That's just fine.
Just wait till you see...
...the new Ojo!
Now let's give them a taste of our Ballista!
- Yeah!
- O...
- ...jo!
Silver Knights vs. White Knights
Set, hut, hut!
Let's go!
W-What?!
Th-That's-!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Ojo High's School Festival!
We're sneaking into Ojo's school festival so we can find out about their Ballista?
21st Ojo High School Festival
Wow! Sounds fun!
Sounds fun?
I see. That just might work.
Yeah.
Since it's a school festival, we can walk right on in without making a scene.
But what if the students there notice us?
It's not like we're going to pick a fight.
We're just going to enjoy the school festival, right?
It shouldn't be an issue.
So why're you carrying a bat?
So are you going or not? Which is it?
- We're going!
Then it's settled. Let's get going.
- Yeah!
What gives?
It's too much!
It's too impressive!
I fit in here perfectly!
Wow! Awesome!
There's a red carpet!
It's max fancy!
This looks like it'll be a lot of fun!
I'm hungry...
Please come see class 1-3's "History of Ojo" booth.
Class 1-3
"History of Ojo Booth"
But the events aren't anything special.
Well, it IS just a school festival.
I wonder what the football team's doing?
Wouldn't it be cool if they were holding on open practice for the public?
A Chocolate-covered banana?!
The game's just around the corner, ya know?
Fried noodles?!
First we've...
...gotta scout out Ojo's...
...school festival.
A gun game?!
Boo-yah!
Since we're here and all.
Want some?
Crepe?! Fried octopus?!
Thank you all for coming!
Please gather 'round the central stage!
Opening Quiz Game Show
The traditional Ojo Festival opening quiz is about to start!
Sounds fun!
Who will be our true hero
that answers the questions and wins the legendary sword, Excalibur?!
We're currently looking for contestants!
By the way, I, Sanada, will be the game show host!
I, Riko Kumabukuro, am the special guest host!
I can't believe you set up a stage for me!
I knew my stupid brother would do that.
So,
why am I up here?
Because you need at least two players per team, Sena!
That trophy...
Who cares about winning it anyway?
That's so stupid.
Naturally, there are plenty of extravagant supplementary prizes!
First there's the yakiniku restaurant by the station!
Fried Meat
Minotauros
You'll get get a one month all-you-can-eat coupon at Minotauros!
Hey, guys, this isn't the time to be doing this!
Hey, Mamo, you should pair up with me!
But we-
There's also...
...a year supply of Kariya's cream puffs!
Kariya Cream Puffs
1 Year Supply
Let's go, Suzuna!
Yay!
A-A switch just flipped in Mamori.
And finally...
I, Miracle Ito, president of Jari Productions, will give away a
Sakuraba duffel bag!
A Sakuraba baseball cap!
And a Sakuraba stadium jumper jacket!
You'll get a bunch of sweet prizes!
Cool!
Sakuraba!
P-President!
When did you make all that?
I-Isn't that...
...Sena Kobayakawa and the Deimon Devil Bats?
It's them! This is great!
Let's have a practice game before the finals!
Why are cracking your knuckles? It's a quiz.
All of the contestants are up on stage!
First there's Team Sena and Taki!
Next up is Team Otawara and Sakuraba!
We're gonna win!
I've got a really bad feeling about this...
Our only ladies group is Team Suzuna and Mamori!
Hey!
Concentrate... Concentrate!
Representing the White Knights is Team Shin and Takami!
Even if this is just a quiz, we can't lose to Deimon!
There's also the Three Ha-Ha Brothers!
We're not related!
Here's Team Komusubi and Piggyberus and Cerberus!
Team Yukimitsu and Monta!
Let's do our best.
We'll max win!
Finally, there's Team Torakichi and Onihei!
When did I pick up this character image?
These are the eight teams!
The game will have 16 people and two animals!
Oopsie, I forgot to mention this earlier,
but there's a penalty for whoever comes in last.
You'll have to dress up as a maid and help out at the maid cafe after the game!
So if Mamori comes in last...
Welcome home, Master.
M-M-Mamori... in a maid outfit...
Monta!
Maid! Maid! Maid!
Uh-oh! Everyone who had been cheering for the beautiful ladies now wants them to lose!
I can feel their desire for them to lose!
No way, nope. We'll be fine, right, Mamo?
Yeah, I think so.
Huh? Come to think of it, where's Hiruma?
He was with everyone up until just a minute ago.
You're right. I wonder where Yocchie went...
Ojo White Knights
Ojo U. Silver Knights
I've got a pretty good idea of what exactly the Ballista is now.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
In football, offense includes pass plays and what else?
It's Sena's specialty!
Offense plays in football include pass plays, where you quickly gain ground
and run plays, where you run into enemy territory.
Win through utilizing your passes and runs! Ya-ha!
Now, let the game begin!
Question one!
See that, Sakuraba?!
Between my power and your buzzer catching ability, we're invincible!
There's so many things wrong with what you just said...
Team Otawara loses a point for a false start.
They're fast. They're really good.
No, they're not. Taki, don't you know how to play a quiz?
You bet!
Really?
I'll start over!
He doesn't get it!
Now it begins.
The greatest battle in history between two idiots...
...has just begun.
You're embarrassing me! Stop it!
Let's hit the button after we hear the question, okay, Taki?
Okay, Mademoiselle Mamori.
Finally, first question!
The ingredients for Kariya's famous cream puffs-
M-Mamo, you didn't listen to the question either!
Organic vanilla beans from Madagascar,
collagen peptide, flour from eastern Kurume,
eggs from Hamamatsu, corn, margarine,
butter from Torapisuchinu in Hokkaido, brown sugar from Okinawa,
fresh cream from Onuma, corn starch, melon oil,
- and baking soda from Holland.
- I-I get it!
You named at least five raw materials correctly!
A-Amazing!
Next question!
I can't rely on Otawara.
Let's go, Shin!
Got it!
What are the two philosophies behind Ojo's teaching style.
Always get a receipt!
Eat as much meat as you want!
Be proud and courageous!
Correct!
Just what I'd expect from the White Knights' strategist!
Takami even has the nickname the Walking Databook!
Any Ojo student could have answered that, right, Shin?
You didn't know?!
Let's keep going!
Next question!
How much does the football team's idol, Koharu Wakana, currently weigh?!
43 kilograms!
N-No way!
She lost 0.5 kilos during summer camp, so she's 42.5 kilograms!
Correct!
Sh-She lost weight?
How do you two know about that?!
Never mess with the Devil Bats running computer, Yukimitsu!
Who knew that he'd be such a maniac about collecting data?
Y-You even have data on their manager...
I've got a bunch of information on our next opponents right here.
Next question!
What was the White Knights' coach,
Gunpei Shoji, called when he was a student at Sengoku University?
Old Fart Gunpei!
The Wrinkly University Student!
Twin Blades!
Correct!
Great!
Let's keep on going!
He's evolving from a lousy receiver to a true hero!
What is the name of Sakuraba's production studio?!
Jari Productions!
He beat me to it!
Shin, why didn't you push the buzzer?
Y-You didn't know that either?
This thing's gotta be broken, Sakuraba!
That's not the problem...
We've gotta answer something...
Here comes the next question!
How much does the highly unpopular Liver and Chives Natto Lunch cost
at Dumpling Ojo located in front of the train station across from Ojo High?!
How're we supposed to know that?!
All of these questions have been about Ojo!
That's playing dirty!
Even I don't have information on that!
Let's see, 500 and... 500 and... 80...
530 yen!
Absolutely correct!
- How'd you know that?!
Like it!
Looks like everyone's getting really into this!
So then, let's start the true-or-false questions for everyone!
Here I go!
Wow, this one's a toughie!
It's about the White Knights' coach, who I introduced earlier.
Was Shogun or Coach Shoji actually popular with the ladies when he was young?!
Annoyed
This is why I teamed up with Onihei!
What do you think?
I don't think Coach Shoji was the type to waste his time on romance.
And while it may sound rude,
I don't think he was hot enough for the girls to flock after him.
It's false.
Then it's true!
Correct!
What's with that?!
Yay!
That's one more point for Team Suzuna and Mamori!
They're currently in the lead!
Yay!
Now we're finally at the last question.
Who knows who will come out the winner?!
It's kinda obvious...
We're doomed!
Will victory turn-
Don't do that!
Hiruma!
H-Hey!
What's he...
- ...doing?
Well everyone, this last question is part of the true-or-false quiz.
Hiruma?
Question! The Ojo White Knights' new strategy, the Ballista,
has Seijuro Shin playing on both defense and offense.
Calm down, Sakuraba, Otawara!
Hiruma's watching how we react to figure out the answer.
Sorry, Hiruma,
but we can't answer that question.
Shin, why'd you answer that?!
Shin, why?
Whoo boy!
I answered because I thought that was the right thing to do.
W-What?
Yoichi Hiruma came here to find out about the Ballista instead of focusing on training.
That means that Deimon Devil Bats used all of their cards in their game against Shinryuji.
Well, I still have a few little tricks.
But I don't have any biggies like Yukimitsu anymore.
I don't think it's fair for Ojo to be the only ones with some cards up our sleeves.
That's why I answered.
Yeah, you're exactly right.
Sorry, but you've got the wrong idea.
What?
We don't think of the Ballista as some trick play.
That's because the Ballista...
...isn't some petty strategy that falls apart once the rival team finds out about it.
That's true.
It doesn't matter if you know about it!
There's no stopping them.
It's just as he says, Hiruma.
Shin will be on offense in the Ballista.
You'll also be facing mine and Sakuraba's Everest Pass,
along with Otawara's speed and power.
Then there's Shin's Trident Tackle.
Ojo is no longer a team that focuses on just defense!
We're the strongest Ojo White Knights since the team name was first formed!
So that's why your game against Ojo University ended as it did.
Shin's going to be on offense, too.
That's the secret behind the Ballista.
That means that Shin's going to be running!
Yeah, sure does.
Who's gonna stop him?
Eyeshield 21, now we're even.
Both of us are on offense and defense.
We will burn through the same amount of strength and energy.
This game shall be the stage for my final battle against you!
I'll see you at the game, Eyeshield 21.
Shin...
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
Ojo's new strategy is the Ballista!
Shin's even going to be playing on offense!
I wonder how they'll attack us.
Watch Ojo's public practice closely!
They might have something other than just the Ballista!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Oath to Become an Ace!
Ya-ha!
See ya at the game!
By the way, Team Otawara and Sakuraba will be working at the maid cafe since they lost.
Oops! I totally forgot!
Anything but that!
It looks like they've finished changing! Open the curtain!
Yay!
Sakuraba's cute!
You're super cute!
Sakuraba!
They love you, Sakuraba!
This stinks...
Otawara, you're gross!
Sakuraba!
They aren't erotic.
Erotic
You know some strange words there, Shogun!