Thanks for the lift.
Geez, Hiruma,
did you have to get such an extravagant car?
Every once in a while, yes, Manajerk.
Again! Stop calling me that horrible name!
Would you rather we switch to "Mamo?"
Are you making fun of me too, Musashi?
Yay!
So they're first, huh?
Mamo!
Suzuna, Sena, Monta!
That's for picking us up!
Welcome back!
We made it, Mamori.
I assume you both cleared your Death Climbs?
- Yup!
- Yes!
So did all of them.
Everyone's looking good.
Yeah, like they've all toughened up.
Okay, now that you babies finally crawled your way home,
it's time to take on the Survivors!
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
Ya-ha!
We'll win!
We'll do it together, as the Devil Bats!
Hey!
Don't forget about me-
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
A Shout of Friendship!
Our Japanese team's finally up!
The Deimon Devil Bats vs.
the Savanna Survivors is about to begin!
Riko, as our analyst,
can you tell us a little about the Survivors?
The Savanna Survivors...
The African representative team are all over two meters tall,
making them a predominantly heavyweight team,
and a very athletically gifted one to boot!
Their players' impressive size has garnered them a lot of attention!
In other words, an opponent that the Devil Bats can't look past!
Sorry about yesterday.
He's huge.
But I think you guys will understand soon.
To us, this game's nothing more than a warm up.
Of course, if you guys don't at least try,
the audience will get bored,
and we won't get much practice, so work hard!
You know what to do!
Oh yeah, we're ready!
We'll murdalize him!
No violence!
We'll get him on the field.
We're footballers!
- Yeah!
Okay, we can't fail either!
Yeah, let's win this!
Things are looking good!
I'm looking forward to this.
Survivors vs. Devil Bats
Deimon kicks off!
Go, everyone!
Jomo makes the catch,
and it's already a showdown between Jomo and Sena!
He's fast!
What incredible athleticism...
Jomo, the Survivors' ace, could go all the way!
He's nicknamed the cheetah,
after the world's fastest land animal!
- Get him!
- Take him down, teach!
- Go, Deimon!
Remember your training!
- Let's go!
First...
Speed!
What else you got?
Now me!
Power!
Pests!
What?!
And finally...
Technique!
What?
W-Whoa...
Yes! The Ha-Ha Triple Team!
The cheetah has been caged!
The Three Ha-Ha Brothers
and their new Delinquent Deathblow,
The Ha-Ha Triple Team!
Speed, power, and technique!
A classic combo play by the brothers!
The Ha-Ha Triple Team...
What a frightening play...
You Ha-Ha Brothers are incredible!
Lemme make one thing clear.
WE'RE NOT BROTHERS!
Great!
Yeah.
- Yeah!
The bros are kicking butt.
Yup.
Whatever their Death Climb was, they did it.
Even the Russian Roulette couldn't beat that!
Go, Butt-Monkey!
Catch!
The Catching Monkey takes off!
Raimon intercepts the pass!
- Yes!
All right, he timed that perfectly!
The Survivors fail to score.
Now it's Deimon's turn!
Set...
Hut hut!
Okay...
My turn!
Hut!
The ball goes to Deimon's ace, Eyeshield 21!
Run, Peewee!
- You're going down!
What?
I'll get you!
Repeated Devil Bat Ghosts!
Un... unbelievable...
Touchdown!
Eyeshield 21 scores easily!
- Woohoo!
Was he there?
He left about an hour ago...
We owe all our success to coach Apollo...
Without him...
We're all with you.
The Shuttles won't be a team without the coach.
Let's find him!
We've gotta get the coach back on board no matter what!
Right!
The Deimon Devil Bats will not be stopped!
Game over!
The Deimon Devil Bats destroy the Savanna Survivors 28-0
and advance to the finals!
Yes...
- All right!
Don't get cocky!
The Blizzards are next.
That's right.
If we don't beat the Blizzards,
this win is meaningless.
We have to win!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what's important in a wide receiver like Mon-Mon!
The key is "routes?"
A wide receiver needs memorize lots of routes
so he knows exactly where the quarterback
will throw the ball.
You gotta read ahead!
Ya-ha!
There you are, coach!
What do you want?
Please... please come back to the team!
I no longer have the drive...
Now what?
If he doesn't want to come back...
Yeah, at this rate, we'll have to give it up...
No... no...
Everyone wants to keep going...
Don't give up for a second!
The Devil Bats...
Get the lead out, Peewee!
I don't wanna see your legs stop!
We can take the Blizzards!
- Snuff the Blizzards!
Speed!
Power!
Technique!
What're you doing, Peewee?!
If you stop moving for even one second,
the Blizzards will flatten you!
Right!
Quit slacking-
Hiruma!
This is crazy, let him rest a little.
Come on, Yocchie, Sena's the only one-
I'm fine.
Mamori, Suzuna...
I'm not even halfway to where I could be.
I've gotta keep practicing.
Over and over and over!
Sena...
Very good, that's the spirit!
There's no getting around the need for practice.
Let's blow past the Blizzards and go on to the Christmas Bowl!
Yeah.
Let's keep going, Hiruma!
Okay then...
Keep up the pace, ladies!
- Right!
None of THEM are giving up...
Only focusing on their goal...
...the Christmas Bowl.
And they're still having fun.
They love football.
I can't take it anymore!
Come on, guys!
Sena, you think we could help you guys practice?
The Shuttles...
What're you-
Your enthusiasm rubbed off on us.
We just couldn't sit still.
We're game.
Set, hut!
Get ready, Monkey!
Here's my fake Soyuz Pass!
It's Monta, not Monkey!
And I'll intercept whatever you throw!
Not if I have anything to say about it!
Go, Mon-Mon!
You can do it, Monta!
Watch this, Mamori!
This is what I trained for!
Max Catch!
You let your guard down.
There's a Japanese proverb that says,
"He that is too sucky is not safe."
It's not "sucky..."
It's "secure."
Is that even a real proverb?
That was pretty good.
But Nikolai's Soyuz Pass is much better.
Faster, tighter spiral, everything.
Gotcha to the max.
Here I come, Sena.
Here I come, Panther!
Well, Sena?
If that had been Ivan's Mammoth Attack...
Let's go again, Panther!
I thought he had it...
When you're TOO focused on your opponents movement,
you tend to stiffen up.
I can't just try to dodge...
I need to watch the opponent's knees and charge in first,
like I did at the pro wrestling gym!
There!
Good! Just like that, Sena!
Right!
He figured it out without any advice.
He's made big strides.
Don't stop running!
You're slowing down!
- I know you're not tired already!
- I'm not done yet!
Thanks for everything, Sena.
Hmm?
We learned something by watching you guys.
You can't ever give up, no matter how tough things get.
Nah, I didn't...
I just want to keep pursuing my dream, without ever stopping.
Dream?
To face Shin from Ojo again.
I see...
Well, my dream is to get coach Apollo
back on board and reform the Shuttles.
I'm sure it'll come true.
Yup. I'll MAKE it happen no matter what.
I won't quit.
And when you do, we'll play each other again.
We have a deal?
Okay, it's a deal.
The Blizzards are tough,
but you guys can do it!
Yeah.
A gift for you.
Who's it from?
You're invited. You're invited. You're invited.
Invited?
Today, today, TODAY!
Today is the Cream Puff Cup championship game!
Riko steals my big moment.
Machine Gun Sanada makes the biggest mistake of his career-
-But regains his composure.
Now, the two teams competing today!
Representing the Asian region, the demons amongst demons,
the devil kings themselves, the Deimon Devil Bats!
And representing Europe and Russia, the pulsating Aurora Borealis,
The Northern Light Blizzards!
The cup's as good as ours.
As I always say,
talent is everything in this game!
You rag-tag kids are about to learn what talent is,
like it or not.
Whoever amasses the most talented parts
builds the best machine.
That's life.
You're forgetting something, Afro-Man.
Talent can take you so far.
Hard work can take you ANYWHERE.
Hiruma...
And they're about to prove it.
You need to learn your place.
Don't worry, we'll teach you.
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
We beat the Survivors,
now it's on to the Blizzards!
Overcome the Mammoth Attack!
We aren't trash!
We'll prove it to everyone out there!
Morgan'll be so shocked his gold teeth will fall out!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Silver Snow's Secret Weapon! Ya-ha!
How will this game play out?
Let's turn to our analyst, Riko-
What's going on here?
Riko has suddenly become the spitting image of her father.
If I get too into my work, I end up looking just like him.
A-Another mystery of youth.