ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
The Pierce of the Spear Tackle!
Go get 'em!
Show them the power of Ojo's offense!
Glory on the Kingdom!
Us scoring first got them all riled up.
What happens now?
The offense and defense switch.
Ojo has been on defense so far. Now it's their turn to try and score.
Wait, that means-
Sakuraba!
The wait is over.
Jari Productions' model and Ojo's ace, Haruto Sakuraba takes the field!
Ace Sakuraba! Ace Sakuraba!
Since when has he been Ojo's star player?
I don't think we're gonna get them to calm down.
Doesn't look like it.
I-I'm sorry...
Referee timeout!
Umm...
Why does it seem like the White Knights all have different players now?
Usually in football, the players are different for offense and defense.
But we're almost always out here...
We don't have enough people!
Oh, I see!
But...
Hmm? Otawara plays offense AND defense, huh?
He has to.
He's the only one with the power and weight to hold off Kurita.
Kurita...
Thanks.
Sorry about that.
Our famous "football sandwich" set
is now only 380 yen!
To a gourmet's heart, it's a touchdown!
American Burger!
Okay, commercial's over!
The wait is over.
Ace player Sakuraba is finally on the field!
Sakuraba!
Hey, where should we focus on?
Who's the thrower person?
The quarterback.
The one in the middle who gets the ball first.
Ichiro Takami.
He focuses on the fundamentals and makes very few mistakes.
He's also 190cm tall and uses that height to make accurate passes.
Set!
What?
That's...
A goal line defense?
What are they thinking?
G-Goal line defense?
What is that, Mamori?
What's a goal line defense?
This is our usual setup.
4-3 Formation
But we change it depending on the situation.
Like in front of the end zone, teams usually run more often,
we use what's called a "goal line" defense formation.
Goal line defense
But it's a formation you never use unless you're right at the goal line.
Wide open
It leaves the backfield open and our team unable to defend against passes.
I see.
They're going to focus on stopping the run
and banking on Kurita sacking me before I can pass.
Huh...?
That...
Won't work!
Hut!
H-He's tough!
It's no good,
just stopping him takes everything I've got!
Nice pass!
10 yard gain!
That was close...
1st down!
Why'd he go down?
He could've easily ran another 20 yards there.
He actually catches a pass and then nothing... Some ace.
Don't say that.
Everyone around him calls him that on their own... It must be hard for him.
Hut!
18 yard gain!
Why are they letting him make all those passes?
Why...?
This is odd.
Why don't they counter?
It's as if they're TRYING to get us to pass.
All right, listen up losers!
We're gonna pretend to give up on defending the pass,
and let them throw as many as they want!
There's too much of a difference between us. If they tried to force their way downfield with runs,
an amateur-packed line like ours would never stop them.
But we've got one chance. Eyeshield 21...
Intercept their pass!
Hut!
Okay, their QB, Takami, is gonna have accounted for your legs when he passes.
No matter how fast you are, at that distance, he'll be convinced you can't cut in time.
He'll send a pass through that narrow space.
That's your chance!
I can make it!
He couldn't have...
That was his plan!
What'd I tell you?
There're no coincidences in football.
If you wanna land a lucky punch, you gotta work for it.
Shoot-!
Oof!
Ow ow ow...
Your hands, spread out your hands!
When you try to catch, you move your hands too late.
You gotta have your hands ready from the get-go.
For low passes, bring your pinkies together.
For high ones, bring your thumbs together.
Bring my thumbs together...!
Hup!
For high passes, reach your hands out and put your thumbs together!
I can catch it!
Football clinic!
How many minutes per game?
One game is 60 minutes long.
One quarter is 15 minutes, and there are four quarters! Ya-ha!
Leave Sakuraba alone!
I'm okay.
I'm so much taller, I won't miss it!
Remember, just knocking the ball away won't bring it back to us.
You've gotta catch it, before it hits the ground!
What-
The- I can't see!
I did it!
That's right... I only practiced a little...
Life is never this easy!
Nice job,
Peewee!
Come back, it's a turnover!
Ya-ha!
Eyeshield's the only one with any speed!
Smash him!
Go, Eyeshield 21!
Stop him!
Knock him out of bounds!
Woohoo!
That was almost another touchdown!
But now we're only 13 yards from the end zone!
Just a little further!
Set!
Don't be fooled! Eyeshield's the only one to be concerned about!
Hut!
Again!
Eyeshield's running it to the right!
One down! Two down!
Three...
The ball's not there!
Deimon, five yard gain!
Just eight yards to the goal.
We just might pull it off!
I can't believe we're in this situation against Deimon.
It's all because of him, the one x-factor we couldn't plan for.
However...
We can't afford to show any more weakness while Shinryuji's watching.
Shin.
Sir?
Put a stop to this.
It's Shin.
Who's he?
He's...
Professional coaches have been saying this about him:
"There is a monster among the high school players,
a man we want on our team no matter what it takes."
The greatest linebacker in Japan,
Seijuro Shin.
Here he comes.
He's...
Yo, your rival's heading over here.
Go get inside his head!
Japan's best vs. the star of the famous Notre Dame!
This'll be a blast!
Eyeshield went to Notre Dame?!
That's awesome!
You wuss!
It's fine, he doesn't need to taunt him!
Yeah he does.
It doesn't take any energy to run your mouth.
But it's worth it if you mess them up, even a little!
Pass! We're passing!  We're going for a long pass!
No one's dumb enough to fall for that...
Wha?!
They're passing?!
He was...
Shin, I think they're gonna pass it.
Or maybe they just want us to think that.
Huh? Or do they want us-
Speculation is meaningless.
We must trust only what our eyes see.
If we use our standard formations, and play like we always do...
The White Knights' defense will not fail.
Yup, the mood sure changes when you're out here!
Deimon Devil Bats, 2nd and goal.
Starting on the 8 yard line.
The air feels different!
Their expressions look completely different.
Ojo's just back to being its old self.
Which spells game over for Deimon.
Now let's see what the Spear Tackle's all about.
Hut!
I made it last time...
I can do it again!
He's going to the right for real this time!
Three blockers in the middle.
He's cutting!
All right!
No way!
Round 1, fight!
It's a battle of the aces!
Gotta go for it!
He made it!
Nope. Shin wins.
There's the Spear Tackle.
That move... He really extended his arm for that.
Eyeshield...
That was the first time I've seen him get tackled!
So that's a tackle...
I can't believe he stretched out his arm from back there...
Oh yeah... Now I remember...
This is what pain feels like.
With Shin in there, we'll never break through the center.
Our only chance is to slip by on the right.
Maybe, but we can't stop Otawara.
Even double-teaming him isn't enough.
Fine, whatever.
Man-Pig! You gotta stop Shin AND Otawara.
Th-That's too much!
Hey.
Are you listening?!
Hut, hut, hut!
Here he comes again!
As I thought, with those thin arms...
And the way he uses them...
He's definitely an amateur.
In which case-
He caught me...
Huh?
H-He's not down, Shin's holding him up!
Ouch!
Shin!
Go!
Get him, track team!
He can't...
So fast!
With his power... and speed...
Deimon can't handle an opponent like him!
He is, unarguably,
the greatest linebacker in history!
Touchdown!
Yeah, a REAL ace is something to behold.
Ow!
It hurts... That's it... I can't handle this!
Me mo kuramu you na hard days
When the hard days leave my head spinning
First down mo ubaezu ni time out
and we can't even get a first down, I call a time out.
Sherbert-jou ni tokedashita taiyou
The blazing sun looks like melted sherbert,
Nomihosu no sa I am a loser
and I'm a loser who's gonna drink it up.
Dare no shizu mo ukenai to
I don't take orders from anyone,
Hashiritsuzukeru like a rolling stone
I just keep running like a rolling stone.
Dare mo ga ikiru tame no reason
The more you think about your reason for living,
kangaeru hodo ni meikyuu no sa so blue
the more it seems like you're trapped in a maze so blue.
Moteamashiteru passion
So much passion, I can't keep it in.
Nuritsubusareta question
I've whited out all the questions.
Shinjitsu wa maru de ficion
The truth is total fiction.
Jidai to iu mei no machine ni matagatte
Balancing on those machines we call "generations."
Inochigakete no bakageta game to ikigatte
I live to risk my life playing this stupid game.
YAY! The real thing sure is different!
The Devil Bats have no way to stop an ace like Seijuro Shin!
I can't... get past him!
Are you okay with running away and crying again?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Fighting to Win! Ya-ha!
Go get him!
Silent and Sissy!
And Chicken's Best Friend!
Pass! We're going for a long pass!
Plays dirty!
Wha?!
They're passing?!
Huh? Horse-Deer?
"Idiot!"