Distance to Las Vegas: 221 km.
DEATH MARCH - DAY 35
It broke!
Um, what should I do now...?
It was originally one stone.
You'll have to redo the whole 2000
kilometers if you lose a single piece.
No way!
Ack! Oops.
If you're gonna kick two stones, then I'll run with one leg!
I'm overflowing with energy, after all!
Honestly, I wonder why everyone's so full of energy now?
Guys, you're super exhausted!
The blisters on my feet hurt, but my legs are killing me!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'll survive.
Why?
Why what?
You didn't have to come all this way to America for this harsh training.
There are plenty of other ways to strengthen up your body.
That may be true,
but all of us want to reach our goal now that we're here.
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Final Trial!
Your all going to get a taste of real hell now.
You'll have to fight against your body screaming out in protest from here on.
"Why do I have to suffer like this?"
"I've worked hard, isn't it enough already?"
The death march I did back in college was also 2,000 kilometers long,
but everyone gave up in the last killer 200 kilometers.
Are the last 200 kilometers really that harsh?
Have you ever heard the saying,
"One who travels a hundred miles thinks of ninety-nine miles as half?"
What's that mean?
Like I'd know!
It means that the very end of a trial is the hardest part.
Here's a picture from then.
You've got one?!
How on earth did you get that?
Don't tell me this guy holding the sake bottle is...
It's me.
How young!
Well duh!
Oh my. I feel like I've seen the guy standing next to you somewhere...
He's Shogun.
The couch for the Ojo White Knights?!
At Sengoku University the two of us were called the "Swords of Japan."
Let's go!
And win!
Why are you resting?!
We've only got 200 kilometers left!
The backs are outta the game!
Doburoku, who's left in the line?
Why are you alone?
Where is everyone else?!
They all quit.
But...
I know that they'll come after me if I continue on my own.
They'll all say, "We can't lose to the likes of you!"
No one else is left.
It looks like everyone dropped out.
My leg!
Darn it! It's because you over did it!
Hey, hang in there, Doburoku!
Sounds painful...
Let me say this again.
Anyone who doesn't want to go through what I did should give up now.
What is it?
If you're not careful, you'll never be able to use your legs the same way again.
Doesn't anyone want to retire?
That's not funny!
We've already come so far!
I try hard!
We're almost there!
I could do this round trip three more times!
We're gonna reach the goal!
Why?
This is nothing but a group of idiots.
So get to sleep already!
We're setting out as soon as it's dawn!
Ow!
Sena...
Why is everyone trying so hard?
Why do they care about reaching the goal so much?
Well, I can't really answer that...
This really ticks me off!
I'm asking you because I'm worried about everyone!
And I'm thankful for that, but...
Everyone is determined...to give it their all till the very end.
Good night!
This road's a mess.
Ouch!
You okay?!
I'm fine!
The goal's right in front of us!
I won't allow anyone to run in front of me!
Yeah! I won't lose!
Keep it up just a bit longer!
I wanna eat some shaved ice!
Sounds good. I'd like strawberry ice.
Strawberry ice?
If you're gonna eat shaved ice, it's gotta be melon flavored!
You two are such kids.
Adults like green tea flavored ice!
Ya old fart!
What'd you say?! HUH?!
Wanna fight?! HUH?!
I like all three flavors!
What's wrong?
We aren't moving forward any.
I told you not to push with just your arms. Give it some UMPH!
I know that!
Tuck your butt in...
And PUSH!
PUSH! PUSH!
What?!
Stupid truck!
What should we do?!
We're almost at the goal!
We've gotta push it out!
Yeah, we just need to push it!
Okay!
C'mon!
No way!
"One who travels a hundred miles thinks of ninety-nine miles as half," huh?
They're so slow...
They'll catch up anytime now!
It's horrible, absolutely horrible!
Come with me!
Football Clinic!
Who are the people that offer support to their team?
There's managers like Sena, head coaches who set up game plays,
and trainers who help train your body. Ya-ha!
Drat! It's sliding backwards!
I can't push forward!
Don't give up!
But this might be for the best.
Huh?
I bet God is telling them to stop already.
Stop it!
Why are you trying so hard?
You've made it this far!
Isn't that enough?
I'll help!
Don't get in the way!
Just us in the line are gonna push it!
I'll kick your butt if you help!
I told you to back off!
I'm not pushing it for you, Jumonji.
I'm doing it because I want everyone to reach the goal.
Shut up! I said that you're in the way!
Hey!
This isn't the time to fight!
Everyone, run for it!
- Stupid little...!
- It's going to sink!
It's not working. It's gonna sink!
Help to the max!
Monta!
You punks!
We're telling you that you're in the line's way!
Don't you get it?!
Stop them!
All their work will be meaningless if they ruin their bodies after coming this far.
Hiruma!
It's dangerous here, so get away!
Yukimitsu! Taki!
They helped me when I thought that I was finished, after all.
I'm strong enough to handle this on my own!
Okay! If we all work together!
Go to the max!
Why... Why are they trying so hard?
It stopped!
Okay!
Now let's give it our all!
Push it!
It moved!
We can do it!
We're doing it!
Why? I don't get it!
Hey, Mamori, why don't you stop them?!
How can you just sit and watch them?!
You can do it!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Thank you.
Start pushing already!
Let's eat some shaved ice in  Las Vegas!
To the power of strawberry ice!
Fight for melon ice!
You idiots!
Keep at it a bit more!
Smash 'em!
Take 'em out!
They're amazing!
Smash 'em! Take 'em out!
Now that they're almost to the finish line, they're finally acting like a team!
Smash 'em!
Take 'em out!
We've worked hard together for 2,000 kilometers.
We're going to reach the goal together....
...because we're a team!
Take 'em out!
Smash 'em!
You can do it, guys! Go for it!
Take 'em out!
Smash 'em!
- Smash 'em!
- Take 'em out!
Take 'em out!
Smash 'em!
It's out!
We did it!
Yay!
Smash 'em! Take 'em out!
Okay!
Let's keep at it!
We can do it!
Okay! We'll reach Las Vegas once we go over that hill.
Everyone can hitch a ride on the truck now!
You kidding?!
Like we'll ride to the goal after we've worked so hard!
We're going to keep pushing till the very end!
Great! Everyone, you're great!
Smash 'em!
Take 'em out!
Hey, look!
It's Las Vegas!
Distance to Las Vegas: 0 km.
DEATH MARCH - COMPLETED
Everyone completed the 2,000 kilometer death march!
We did it!
Wow, that's cold!
What's a fountain doing out here?
We did it!
Isn't it great?!
We did it! We did it...
...all together!
I underestimated you.
I never even imagined you'd finish without any dropouts.
You've got power and stamina.
You're nothing like you were just a month ago.
Really?
The truck seems...
...lighter than it was at first.
Idiots!
You still can't defeat all 100% of the powerhouses in Kanto!
The fact that you were able to stick with this torture until the very end...
Experience and determination helped you discover your true abilities.
But football is also a game of will power.
That's what I'm betting my money on.
But for now, let's have a drink to celebrate your victory!
You did great running those 2,000 kilometers!
You're the greatest!
That was a great speech, but...
...no one's listening.
Time to say farewell.
I'd love to go back to Japan with you and continue to be your trainer, but...
I can't go back to Japan.
But, why can't you?
I'll take a look at you before we part ways.
At what?
At your devil running, the Devil Bat Ghost!
I think you've mastered it!
I'm going to go at you for real.
So try to get past me.
Can I beat Coach Doburoku...?
Can I really...?
But I gave it my all throughout the entire 2,000 kilometer death march,
so just maybe...
I've been practicing the whole time!
I can zig-zag and break without losing any speed!
I got through?
Doesn't he know?
Just now, he looked so terrifying...
I did it!
This isn't the goal, you sissies!
The start of the fall season is the starting line!
You got that?!
That's enough for now! Really!
He's REALLY tough!
I wonder why he's the only one who's so full of energy.
Yeah, I wonder...
Ah, I forgot to ask if bro made the team!
Not now, Suzuna-chan.
Why not?
Ask him tomorrow.
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Oh, it's beautiful Mt. Fuji!
We're back, Japan!
Shin and Sakuraba from Ojo are supposed to be undergoing
harsh training on Mt. Fuji for the fall tournament.
And Sakuraba ran away from training camp?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Distant Peak. Ya-ha!
What's with all that money?
It's our loot from battle!
Our loot?
Hey, why did you sell my truck?!
How the heck am I supposed to survive in America now?! You idiot!
You're the Devil Bats' trainer, aren't you?
You'll repay your debts and return to Japan with us.
With this puny amount of money?
You stupid old fart!
Did you forget what kinda place Las Vegas is?
Use roulette no. 21.
Bet everything on 21 Red.
I'm finished. And all because of that jerk.
I'm absolutely finished!
Ah, I'm through!
Impossible!
Hiruma, how did you...?
Ya-ha!