Misaki Wolves vs. Seibu Wild Gunmen
Zoom!
- Stop him!
Wow! Kaitani's catching up!
I WILL stop you!
Wolf Fang!
The Misaki Wolves ace player Taiga Kamiya has scored another touchdown!
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Rodeo Drive Stampede!
Misaki Wolves 14 - Seibu Wild Gunmen 0
Just after the Wolves-Gunmen game began,
ace running back Taiga Kamiya used his Wolf Fang technique!
Kamiya's running style
takes advantage of his long stride
as he crunches down and dives forward!
Wolf Fang truly is a technique that can be used for both defense and offense.
R-Riko...
Anyway, Wolf Fang is super strong!
Riko, your eyebrows are still off...
He crunches down to increase his speed...
Shin, what do you think?
He'll get around anyone trying to tackle him.
Once he's spotted his prey, he runs straight for it.
It won't be easy to catch him.
But more importantly than that...
Riku Kaitani has lost his cool.
Kamiya, you jerk!
Riku, let's keep our cool.
It's okay. The game just started.
Right!
There's no way Kid and Tetsuma could lose to them!
Hiruma?
I wonder...
Huh? What's that mean, Yocchie?
There's a certain flow leading to victory.
This next play is vital.
Can Seibu score something during their offense?
If they don't, the game'll turn in favor of Misaki.
We might get to see Seibu go home crying today.
That's our Yocchie. You're overflowing with evil.
He's having a blast.
But there's no way Riku's gonna lose!
Set!
How will Seibu attack now that they've lost the lead?
Seibu could be called the number one best offensive team in the Kanto Tournament.
They'll probably attack with their Shotgun Formation like always.
I'm not afraid of that! I can stop it!
I won't lose. I can't lose to that jerk.
Go all out! You're stampeding cattle!
Hut!
Let's go!
Twin Horns!
Ushijima sent the Misaki Wolves' line flying!
Nice going, Ushijima!
Will Kid use his Quick-Draw Shotgun?!
Quick-and-Fire!
Kid!
- Crush Kid!
Kid's pass to Hata flew like an arrow!
But Hata got tackled!
If only he'd given the ball to me!
This isn't good!
Why didn't he give it to Riku-Riku?
Because Kamiya's sticking to Riku like glue.
Misaki's planning on keeping someone on Rikky throughout the game.
Tsk-tsk-tsk!
Seibu has one of the max ace catchers, Tetsuma!
But Tetsuma isn't feeling very well...
Huh?
He caught a cold.
He has a 104-degree fever.
Tetsuma caught a cold?!
Goodness... I forgot how literally Tetsuma takes things.
I shouldn't have said that yesterday...
Back in my younger days,
I'd take a cold bath before a big game to clear both my body and mind.
You should go all-out and do that, too!
But then, Tetsuma went and stayed in the cold bath for twelve hours...
He doesn't know the word "moderation."
You okay, Tetsuma?
I... am... fine...
Good grief...
Kid!
I'll make up for Tetsuma with my run!
So give the ball to me this time!
I can't lose to that jerk!
Tetsuma has a cold and Riku has Kamiya...
Both of them are burning up...
Set, hut!
Seibu was just one yard away from stealing their first down!
Offense is going back to the Misaki Wolves!
Darn! Darn it! I can't let him make a fool of me!
Looks like Seibu's in trouble...
No! They're not done!
If Riku just used his Rodeo Drive...
There's no way he could close!
Stop their offense, my raging Seibu cattle!
Set!
If we're raging cattle then it's my turn as Buffalo Ushijima!
Dang it!
I'll stop him this time!
Hut!
Kamiya's making a run for it!
You're mine!
Twin Horns!
Ushijima's gonna try to stop Kamiya!
Riku?!
Look out!
What?!
What are you doing, Kaitani?
Well, I'm gonna go grab another touchdown.
Someone stop him!
That's not happening!
Seibu's defense is going after Kamiya!
Sheer numbers can't stop me!
Here I go! Wolf Fang!
Touchdown!
I'm number one!
Kamiya is unbelievably fast!
He scored another touchdown!
The Misaki Wolves were nobodies before the Tournament...
Yeah, they're more powerful than I had predicted.
What are you doing?! Get those points back!
Thanks, thanks!
We're going to breeze through the Kanto Tournament and go to the Christmas Bowl.
Am I too much?
That jerk!
My, my...
They just won't give us an easy victory.
You're getting too fired up, Riku...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Does everyone know what do the letters on the field mean?
Your hint's "50 yards."
You can stay on offense if you move forward ten yards during your first four shots at offense.
Keep doing that and go for the goal!
Remember that! Ya-ha!
What the heck were you doing?!
And why'd you get in my way?!
You should have left him to me!
What was that, Riku?!
I could have stopped him!
If you hadn't gotten in the way, I could have-!
Cut the crap!
Besides, you could never catch him!
It's gotta be me!
Brat! Is that how talk to your upper upperclassmen?!
Internal conflict?
Losers sure are ugly when blaming each other for losing.
What?!
Uh-oh! How scary!
Don't, Riku! Calm down!
That stinkin' Kamiya!
Hey, Tetsuma! What are you-?!
Ouch! What gives?!
Calm... down.
Cool off some, Riku.
Kid?
Kamiya's not the only wolf here, right?
However...
...we can't have you acting like a lone wolf.
I...
Just a second ago I heard you say that the Misaki Wolves are pushovers.
Isn't that a tad harsh?
I was just stating a fact.
I kept losing to a guy that had made fun of me before the game...
I got nervous and kept failing...
I... was repeating... the same mistake I made at the Tokyo Tournament.
I get it, Kid.
I'm sorry, Ushijima.
I was...
It's okay. It's just like Kid said.
A lone wolf can't play football.
The Seibu Wild Gunmen have to act like a full herd!
Right!
What are you guys doing?!
Give an all-out counter-attack! Go all-out!
Well, no worries there.
We're all nice and warmed up now...
Misaki Wolves 21 - Seibu Wild Gunmen 0
How will Seibu attack the overpowering Misaki now that they're 21 points behind?!
It's about time we started.
Yeah, I'm ready whenever!
All-out!
I won't...
...let him have the last laugh!
Well, let's begin the counter-attack.
- Yeah!
Seibu looks different...
I don't get to see them all upset after all...
Set, hut!
Let's go!
Double Twin Horns!
Tetsuma, slant!
Tetsuma's on fire!
Tetsuma!
Max awesome!
He's a  burning locomotive that's outta control!
Quick-and-Fire worked!
Seibu's long pass was a success!
Sweet!
Yay, Tetsu-Man!
I-Is Tetsu-Man Tetsuma?
This is the real Seibu Wild Gunmen!
The cool and clever Kid together with the burning Iron Horse Tetsuma make the perfect golden pair!
They got their first down!
Buffalo Ushijima's Double Twin Horns are super strong!
Great! Now it's my turn!
I wanted to keep this a secret until we fought Deimon, but..
Watch me carefully, Sena!
It's my Kanto Tournament version of Rodeo Drive,
the Rodeo Drive Stampede!
Riku...
Wow! Go all-out, Riku-Riku!
Suzuna's acting like Seibu's coach...
Set, hut!
Go get 'em.
Okay!
Kaitani's got the ball!
I'll stop you easily enough!
Kamiya's going after Kaitani!
Go, Rikky!
My prey never escapes me!
Here I go! Wolf Fang!
Riku!
Heads up, Kaitani!
I've already seen through your Rodeo Drive.
Then let me show you my more advanced Rodeo Drive...
Rodeo Drive Stampede!
Rodeo Drive Stampede?!
What?!
What's this?!
It looks like there's a bunch of Kaitanis out there!
Which one's the real one?!
It's a super fast change of pace!
Stampede has him quickly moving in all directions.
He's like a stampeding horse!
He's running! He's running!
No one can stop his mad dash!
Amazing. You're so amazing, Riku...!
Touchdown!
Great! Zoom, zoom!
Most impressive. I'm amazed he's improved so quickly.
I'm the one who will fight Eyeshield to be number one, not you.
Y-You've only beaten me once.
Your brief victory will be the best memory you get from the Kanto Tournament.
Set, hut!
Go all-out!
The Seibu Wild Gunmen are on all-out offense!
Their offense knows no bounds!
Sena, power means nothing if you're so fast that no one can touch you.
Sena, speed is our only weapon!
Rodeo Drive Stampede!
Sena, with this run, I'll make it to the semi-finals!
Game over!
Scoring in at 48-21, the Seibu Wild Gunmen have stolen victory!
Yay!
Seibu's strong!
Yep!
Seibu might have the strongest offense in all of Japan right now.
I'm glad we got to see Seibu's true offense.
Yeah.
Tetsuma wasn't even feeling well and they still scored a bunch of points.
Riku... Kaitani...
- Congratulations on making the semi-finals!
Yeah, it was kinda rough.
I bet you were getting pretty nervous, huh, Riku-Riku?
I saw your Rodeo Drive Stampede...
It was great!
You really are amazing, Riku.
Sena, we'll win the next game and go to the finals!
So you've gotta defeat Ojo so we can fight in the finals together!
Yeah!
I'll make sure we win!
Then I'll make this pose!
Hey, check out my pose!
No, no, you're not pointing your finger right.
Mon-Mon's actually a perfectionist!
That was a pretty interesting game.
Gee, thanks.
Next up is Deimon versus Ojo.
We'll face Hakushu.
What a pain, huh?
Both of us will be facing monsters in the semi-finals.
I just want to make sure no one gets hurt.
How unexpected considering how badly you want to win.
That goes for you, too.
I'd love it if you could share some good ideas with me, Mr. number one QB in Tokyo.
Who're you calling No.1?
I can't stand that punk.
I wonder what he's got up his sleeves this time...
Kimi to deaeta no wa kitto guuzen ja nai,
Lately I've been thinking
Itsu no ma ni ka sonna fuu ni omoeteta.
that it was no coincidence we met.
Doko made tsuzuku, bokura no tabiji?
How far will our journey take us?
Futo kizukeba saitetan da na,
It's just now dawned on me that the flowers between us
bokura no aida ichirin no hana
are in full bloom.
Makimodosu clock & play back (Every day)
Rewind the clock & play it back (every day)
Dai kirai datte sakende mitatte, kage oikakeru
I wanna scream "I hate it" at the top of my lungs, but it won't come out.
Arigatoutte sunao ni ienakute
I just can't say "thank you" to your face,
sonna jibun ga dai kirai de
and I hate myself for it.
tatta hitokoto nanoni kuchi ni dasezu ni
It's just one word, but it always remains unsaid.
mune no oku de deguchi wo sagashiteru
It's stuck in my heart, searching for a way out.
Nanimo kamo ga barabara ni natte
Even if everything around me falls apart,
Kowaresou de kiesou de
and looks like it's gonna disappear forever,
Sore demo bokura sugoshita hibi wo shinjiteru
as long as I keep my trust in the days we spent together,
Kawaranai mono zettai arukara
some things will never change.
Rodeo Drive Stampede!
Riku's grown even faster, hasn't he?!
All I've got is my speed.
And Shin's got speed, too.
So what if Shin gotten even faster?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Knight with no Blind Spots!
Ya-ha!
Toga, you sure can pump out great pictures.
Unlike our manager there.
Here!
Wow! Cool!
She's ten times hotter than the real her.
Toga, you're drawing your own manga, right?
What's it about?
It's a hot-blooded ballet manga called "The White Rose Angel."
You're drawing a volley manga when you're playing football?
It's not volleyball.
It's a ballet dance.
- That's so not your style!