- Fire!
- Ya-ha!
Seibu's Kaitani scores on a beautiful touchdown run!
The extra point is good, and the score is now 35-26!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 26
They now have a nine point difference!
It really seems like neither team is playing conservatively anymore.
Both teams' offenses are on fire!
As time ticks down, will lady luck favor Seibu or Deimon?
We'll soon have our answer!
Riku beat me again...
95 straight losses...
But if we can just get the momentum back...
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Lightspeed Pride!
Only nine minutes to go...
And nine points...
There's a huge difference between nine points and eight.
One touchdown can only be eight points max.
But nine points means they need two touchdowns to catch up.
And they're playing against Seibu.
Even we'd be hard pressed to score twice in nine minutes.
Deimon is back on offense.
We'll pay 'em back two times over!
Time for a comeback!
Yeah!
We've got plenty of time.
If we can score a touchdown here,
the momentum will be back on our side!
We're counting on you, ace!
There's only one way to turn the tide...
I have to get through Riku!
Set, hut!
Yeah! At that speed...
- Go, Eyeshield!
Eyeshield is blazing down the field!
He's fast fast fast!
Will this be another one-play touchdown?!
Perhaps not!
Seibu's Kaitani is coming to meet him!
Come on, Sena!
I'll beat you, Riku!
With the Devil Bat Ghost!
I refuse to let you beat me, Sena!
He's so fast.
I need to start the Devil Bat Ghost steps...
He's been stopped! He's been stopped!
Riku Kaitani's Rodeo Drive shuts Eyeshield down!
Deimon's strategy fails!
What a Rodeo Drive!
Stop 'em dead in their tracks!
He was so close!
Just a little further...
I can't believe he was tackled before he could use the Devil Bat Ghost...
He's incredibly fast!
He stopped Eyeshield again...
I guess Kaitani's faster after all?
No, their speed is more or less even.
I need to start the Devil Bat Ghost sooner
or I'll never get past Riku.
Okay, THIS time...
Set, hut, hut!
And once again,
it comes down to Deimon's Eyeshield and Seibu's Riku Kaitani!
I'll move before Riku!
No way... Already?
He's down!
Eyeshield 21 just can't get through Riku Kaitani!
With just five minutes to go, Deimon's chances are slipping away!
Five minutes...
There's no time left...
Faster...
I have to start the Devil Bat Ghost faster!
We're running out of time!
Faster... Faster!
Stuffed again!
The Rodeo Drive trumps the Devil Bat Ghost!
The Devil Bat Ghost doesn't work...
Four minutes and it's 4th down for Deimon!
Deimon is all but finished if they don't score in this play.
Four minutes...
No time...
Calm down, just calm down!
If the Devil Bat Ghost won't work...
Set, hut, hut!
I'll use the Devil Bat Hurricane!
Keep trying, Sena.
I'll stop you no matter what move you try!
This time!
It's him!
Turn!
I did it!
He's stopped again!
Eyeshield 21's Devil Bat Ghost AND Devil Bat Hurricane have failed!
The Devil Bat Hurricane didn't work either...
Deimon fails to score on this drive.
Will the Seibu Wild Gunmen finally put the Deimon Devil Bats down for good?
What do I do?
There's no time left!
Sena.
That was my 99th straight win.
Riku...
Get up, Sena.
Be a man. Stand back up.
Riku...
What makes you so strong?
Because I refuse lose, no matter what.
But I don't want to lose, either...
I don't want to lose.
But why...
What am I lacking?
What does Riku have that I don't?
The game is entering its final stage!
There's only
three minutes to go!
Three minutes?
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
How do you protect the ball after catching it?
The hint is "stomach?"
After catching a pass,
quickly tuck the ball into your stomach and start running.
Keep it protected!
Ya-ha!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 26
They're up by nine!
There's only three minutes left in this showdown of Tokyo's top offenses!
A time crunch like this would make any team desperate.
Deimon's really been driven into a corner.
With Eyeshield completely neutralized,
they have no other options.
Okay, Hiruma, what do we do now?
Our last chance... and I blew it.
We'll hold them off and score on the next drive!
Quit standing around posing!
You're sucking up all our comeback time!
They're just trying to run down the clock!
Don't make me smack you!
No fair! Get back out on the field!
Suzie.
They're not breaking any rules, we can't do anything about it.
It's a legitimate tactic.
Three minutes to go!
You boys are toast!
We'll use the full 25 seconds each time and run away like a bucking bronco!
It's not over till it's over!
Stomp Seibu into the ground!
It only makes sense to use the full 25 seconds available.
I expect Seibu will stick to conservative, risk-free plays.
My guess would be they'll rely heavily on Kid's quickdraw
to make very short passes.
I see. That's how I'd play it.
However...
Deimon's usual method of winning remains...
The unquenchable thirst to rise to the top,
that only those who crawl up from nothing possess.
The thirst... to rise to the top...?
Am I doomed to lose to Riku no matter what?
Come on, Hiruma, say something...
Something's wrong.
Someone as crafty as Yoichi Hiruma is never paralyzed like this.
And why would he use such a slow offense
when killing time benefits us more?
Kid...
Yep...
Like I always say,
when things go too well,
it spells trouble later... You know?
Based on how Seibu's played,
the most reliable play they have is a slant pass to Tetsuma!
Huddle up, shrimps!
Let's go with our most reliable play.
A slant to you, Tetsuma.
Kid's a true genius.
He'll know exactly what pass play
has the highest chance of success.
That's what makes him easy to read.
With so little time,
someone as dedicated to victory as Kid
will narrow down the possibilities for us.
I see, so killing time actually improves our chance of winning!
That's why we used a slow-paced strategy like my Blast!
So you're saying...
It was all...
So you could predict his passes?
And we'd have one final shot at scoring off an interception!
This strategy's the only shot we ever had!
Let's go!
- Yeah!
Yo, Sena!
How long're you gonna hug your knees?
We've gotta get deadly serious!
But I...
But you what?
I can't beat Riku-
It doesn't matter how many times in a row you lose,
you might still win the next round!
There are no winners or losers until it's all over!
But there's only...
...two and a half minutes left.
Still!
Still?
Not "only," there's STILL two and a half minutes left!
Still two and a half minutes...?
We're going to the Christmas Bowl, remember?
Look.
No one else is giving up.
You can't give up, no matter what happens.
The most important lesson I've learned, and I almost forgot it.
Thanks, Monta!
A scant two and a half minutes remain.
Deimon's fate is sealed if they don't make something happen here!
Have you finally snapped out of it?
Defense, defense, defense!
Be a man. Stand back up.
No more wavering.
I have to do it.
I have to get through Riku!
I have to win!
I'll won't lose the 100th round, either!
Set! Hut, hut!
There! He's going to pass to Tetsuma!
Get it, Butt-Monkey!
They saw through...
...the pass route!
Yes!
He can intercept it!
Oh, I already KNEW you had me all figured out.
What?!
He threw an underhanded super quickdraw?!
We got the route right, but he still-
That was out last chance for Monta to intercept the ball!
He can't...
A low pass at that speed... He can't catch it!
Ignore Tetsuma, follow Kid!
His eyes, the way he moves the ball...
The very things that make them the ultimate team
are how you can catch those bullets!
They'll be there...
Kid's timing and aim are too perfect!
Tetsuma's hands...
The one moment the invincible Tetsuma has no power!
The instant he closes his hands to catch the ball!
Tetsuma, my target wasn't the ball to begin with!
What?!
I was going for the fingers on your "invincible" right hand!
No one beats me when it comes to catching!
Holy cow! Raimon slaps the ball from the Iron Horse's hand!
No way!
I actually beat Tetsuma!
That's all I've got, Sena...
The rest is up to you.
And there's Eyeshield 21!
Kid and Tetsuma's "Quick-and-Fire" has been intercepted!
Monta...
They've stolen the ball, now they counterattack!
Open up a path!
It's clear!
He made it...
Just when it seemed Seibu had a foolproof plan,
Eyeshield breaks through with no one in his way!
Can he run it in for a touchdown?!
Sena!
Riku?!
Wait, Kaitani's headed right for him!
Eyeshield and Kaitani are about to butt heads again!
If I try to dodge when he's doing the Rodeo Drive it'll be too late.
I have to move first!
If I can just get past Riku, it'll be a touchdown!
I'm ready, Sena.
Prepare for a lightspeed Rodeo Drive!
And our 100th showdown!
I'll win!
I'll beat Riku! The one who taught me how to run!
Eyeshield and Kaitani are too fast!
We're about to see two forces collide at the speed of light!
Riku's taught me so much...
Back then, and today!
He's got me!
I want to win. I have to win!
It's all for the ball!
I don't need to dodge.
My body's just here to carry the ball.
I'll smash through him at top speed!
I'll turn my body into a lever,
and use the Devil Bat Hurricane...
...to push through!
Sena...
Our 100th match...
...goes to you.
Eyeshield 21 wins!
Touchdown!
Devil Bats! Devil Bats!
Here, at the very end,
Eyeshield 21 triumphs over Kaitani's Rodeo Drive!
His touchdown pulls Deimon back from the brink!
One minute left!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 32
Only three points separate them!
Eyeshield! Eyeshield!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
The Peewee actually beat Riku!
We've got one minute left to win.
If we don't, then I haven't beaten Riku at all!
We're going to the Christmas Bowl!
Save that energy for trashing the Gunmen!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Fateful Kick! Ya-ha!
We're all right, we're still winning!
Bang-bang that clock to zero!
Come on, you losers! We've still got time!
It ain't over till it's over! Ya-ha!
Suzuna...
I think a certain someone's rubbed off on her.
Ya-ha!