Pops, more milk please.
Okay!
Man, the oden there is so good and cheap!
They have fresh milk, too.
Yep!
We'll defeat Shinryuji with oden power!
Right, Musashi?
That's...
Agon... Kongo.
S-See you... in this next game!
I recognize you.
And I'll never forget you!
U-Um...
Huh?!
Well...
Who're you?
No way...
Huh?
That's weird.
I wonder if I've got a fever...
I caught a cold!
What's wrong, Ryokan?
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Shinryuji is the Enemy!
All done!
T-They're great, Mamo.
Mamori, you've never been good at art.
Go at 'em!
Don't hold back, Jumonji!
Bring it on already!
- Ready!
H-Here I used to be one of the Twin Swords of Japan
and they're already surpassing me!
Mamori, what's my time?
40 yards in 4.2 seconds!
That's become your average speed, hasn't it?
Result of work!
Well, my legs are still shaky from the run.
I thought they'd be upset at having to fight Shinryuji,
but they're all excited.
Most impressive.
You know it!
I AM going to become one of the three great receivers!
So first we've gotta crush Shinryuji!
Yep! Let's win!
- We can do it!
- Boo-yah!
Master?
Yeah, I haven't seen him yet today.
There's no way you could just over look someone that big...
Actually, Kurita's sick at home today with a cold.
A cold?
No way!
With a body like his, he'd just eat the bacteria!
I can't believe he got sick at a time like this.
Quit yacking and start practicing! Practice!
- Okay!
Darn Fatty!
He got a fever from worrying about Shinryuji too much.
Shinryuji's special to Kurita, after all.
Shinryuji's important to him?
Excuse me, Musashi.
What happened between Kurita and Shinryuji?
Kurita...
He was originally supposed to be part of the Shinryuji Nagas.
Are you serious about that?
So what happened?!
It's not for me to say.
You should ask him if you're so curious.
I can't believe I caught a cold...
Shinryuji Nagas
Shinryuji Nagas...
Who're you?
Agon... Kongo...
He didn't recognize me at all.
That shows how little he thinks of me
as a football player, doesn't it?
Tokyo Stadium
Winner of the Kanto Tournament
is the powerful dragon that summons tempests!
The Shinryuji Nagas!
Amazing! Football's amazing!
Huh? That uniform...
He's a student from Mao Junior High.
And he's got a great physique!
Someday I'm going to be a member of the Shinryuji Nagas
and go to the Christmas Bowl!
But...
Most middle schools don't have a football team...
And the school won't let me start a team if I'm the only member
and I can't afford to buy the practice equipment.
It may look worn-out, but it's sturdy.
It oughta be good enough to practice with.
A-Aren't you Mr. Doburoku Sakaki?
I used to play football back in the day.
F-Football?!
Give it a try!
With your build, you should be a lineman.
S-Sorry! I-I broke it...
This kid... just maybe...
he'll make a great lineman someday!
And then Hiruma came by one day with uniforms and equipment.
A football! A football helmet!
How'd you get all of this?
Shortly after that...
Amazing!
Gen Takekura... AKA Musashi!
Hey, hey, Hiruma!
Let's get him to join the football team!
Once Musashi joined,
the Mao Devil Bats were formed
and our dream was set in stone.
All three of us should go to Shinryuji!
Then the Christmas Bowl!
I had a lot of fun back then.
But...
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
Ryokan, some guests are here to see you.
Huh?
Kurita...
How're you feeling?
M-Master!
Guys!
I see. So Musashi told you...
Is it true?
You were supposed to go to Shinryuji High?
Not just me.
Hiruma and Musashi were going to join the Shinryuji Nagas, too.
Shocking news, part two!
It's all my fault... that we couldn't.
Huh?
What?! There's an entrance exam?
You bet!
Here, these are the questions from Shinryuji High's exam last year.
No way. I don't know the answers!
They aren't that hard...
I can't do it! What should I do, Musashi?
Here!
Huh?
S-Shinryuji's uniform?
The Shinryuji Nagas have two athletic openings.
One of them's going to Ikkyu, some genius receiver.
That leaves one other spot still open.
Student ID Shinryuji High School Ryokan Kurita
Huh? My Shinryuji ID?
Whaa-?!
S-So that means...?
We'll take the entrance exam to get in.
The sports spot is yours since you're a stupid fatty.
I don't know how you did it, but I'm impressed.
Hiruma!
Quit rejoicing and start practicing, Fatty!
I'm drenched!
Who's he?
Agon.
Agon Kongo...
So you two had issues in the past...
Some guy calling himself Agon Kongo popped up
and said he wants the sports spot.
What a surprise!
But we've already made our decision.
What should I do? Send him away?
Hmm... It wouldn't hurt to see what he's got.
Hmm. So this is a football.
Is this your first time playing football?
No biggie. This'll be a cinch!
- Crush him!
Amazing!
He's the genius of the decade, no, the century!
They're revoking... my acceptance?
N-N-No way...
Did he do this, Hiruma?
Yeah...
The jerk!
Huh?
Who're you?
I'm looking for Agon Kongo.
Agon, huh?
Know where he is?
If you do,
please tell me where he is.
Like we'd know!
Now scram, you loser!
Tell me where Agon is!
- He was so fat!
- You for real?!
What a gross fatso!
You're terrible!
Why?
Huh?
You could have passed the exam to get it.
Then Kurita, Musashi and I along with you and Ikkyu...
We coulda turned Shinryuji into an invincible team.
Idiot! I don't need you guys!
Why'd you do it?
Why did you do this to us?
Man, I just felt like it.
I did it for kicks.
Watching a loser cry about how he's a talentless freak,
now that's real entertainment!
I just had to crush that worthless, fat chump!
They're scary!
Are you friends with these guys?
Nope, never even met 'em before!
Then let's go!
Yeah, let's!
Hey, I wanna have some crepe!
Me, too!
Totally!
Hiruma, someday... we'll make him pay for this...
...in a game.
Yeah.
Musashi, Hiruma...
Really, if they'd wanted to,
Hiruma and Musashi could have left me behind
and gone to Shinryuji anyway.
Kurita...
Hey!
Kurita!
- We came to check on you!
Wow, everyone's here now!
Kuriton!
Are you sure you should be getting up?
I'm all better!
My fever's even gone now!
All better!
The Devil Bats just aren't the same without you.
Even practice doesn't feel the same!
The field feels too big.
It's like a giant wall's gone missing.
That's right.
Hiruma and Musashi could have gone to Shinryuji.
But they came to Deimon with me
and we formed the Devil Bats together.
I'm not afraid!
I've got Hiruma, Musashi and all my friends with me!
I'm not afraid of Shinryuji or Agon!
Kurita, we brought this for you.
Huh?
It's from that one stall.
Everyone pitched in to help pay for it, so eat as much as you like!
I love their oden over there!
It smells great!
Okay! I'm going to eat up and then defeat Shinryuji!
Well said!
Being sick hasn't hurt your appetite at all!
I'm stuffed!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
As a bit of fun before the tournament,
let's go all-out on a luxurious dinner cruise!
But accidents keep happening one after another!
We need a detective to handle these mysterious accidents!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Sena's a Famous Detective?!
Ya-ha!
Thanks for the feast!
Holy cow!
It just vanished!
I'm not even full yet!
Good thing!
'Cause there's still...
...plenty more!
Yay!
Thanks for the foo-!
Cerberus ate it all!
How 'bout this?
And this one?!
I was so hungry. I'm only human, after all.