Slay Shinryuji!
Wow, everyone's kicking butt!
They're really fired up.
But Shinryuji's not your everyday team.
And there's no denying Deimon's still lacking...
All right, 100 laps to the river and back!
Whoever falls behind has to answer to Cerberus.
Yukimitsu.
Yes?
Come with me, we need to talk.
Hey, Sena, we're gonna get caught
if we try to carry these things the whole way.
Let's put 'em back first.
Yeah.
Gotta hurry...
Now then.
Our first game in the Kanto Tournament
is against the undefeated Shinryuji Nagas.
And it's also going to be your debut on the field.
Yuki's...
Debut?
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
The Devil Bats Move Out!
I'll... be playing...
Yes, you hold the key to the one slim chance
we have to beat Shinryuji.
You and only you, Yukimitsu!
But how?
Me, against the invincible Shinryuji?
Yukimitsu, have you realized why we kept you on the bench to analyze
even during the games we had no chance of losing?
Football is as much a game of strategy
as it is a game of muscle.
That was your job.
You're the only man for the job,
BECAUSE the enemy is so strong!
Now what the job is, is...
What's this?
Smells like barbecue sauce...
Carnivore!
Isn't anyone going to comment on how well he runs on two legs?
Why don't you tell them?
Because that butt-monkey will try to do it, too.
He doesn't need to learn techniques that aren't for him.
These are moves only you can do, Baldini.
Actually...
We haven't heard your thoughts on this.
Do you think you're ready to step onto the field
against a powerhouse like Shinryuji?
I do.
Please send me out!
Yuki's... really going to play.
Until ALL the Deimon Devil Bats are on the field together...
We won't lose!
It's finally happening.
Every Deimon Devil Bat...
We just lost one.
"Shishi Hakuto."
The wise lion will exert its full strength
even when hunting the smallest of rabbits.
I don't think I need to tell you,
no matter how weak Deimon may seem,
the Shinryuji Nagas cannot show either laziness nor mercy
during tomorrow's game.
Ikkyu. Project our montage of Deimon's players
onto the waterfall.
Sir.
Yay!
What the heck?!
Way to go, Ikkyu!
I mean, what were you thinking?!
That-uber-hurts!
I'm sorry, wrong tape, wrong tape!
They calmed down so quickly.
Renouncing ones worldly desires is never easy...
Ryokan Kurita, the heart and soul of Deimon's line.
He's uber-awesome.
All that bulk gives him incredible pushing power.
Taking him head-on is almost suicidal.
But he has no speed at all.
He shouldn't give you any trouble, Yamabushi.
Leave him to me.
He hasn't matured at all.
We were right to admit Agon into our athletics program instead of him.
Coach, coach,
please don't say that in front of Unsui.
Remember how he had to get in through the normal exams,
even though they're twins.
There's no need to concern yourself
with my personal issues, Yamabushi.
I'm fully aware of the differences between myself and Agon,
and I chose my path.
Well, if you say so...
- Max Catch!
- Whoa, he scared me!
Banana...
Moron...
No, monkey!
Monkey or not, his skill is undeniable.
A catching expert...
Or rather, a midair warrior.
What do you think, Ikkyu?
No problem.
When it comes to midair battles, I'm number one.
Even Agon can't beat me in the air.
Then our monkey friend is yours, Ikkyu.
You are to cover him man-to-man and completely shut him down.
Yes, sir.
Daikichi Komusubi.
Use your arms to keep him
from tunneling his way through the line.
Togano, Jumonji and Kuroki.
Freshmen and newcomers to the game.
They're no match for you.
A fool.
How can this be?!
The video synced up perfectly...
This one has yet to appear in a game.
We know very little about him.
But just look at him, he's no athlete.
He's probably just a third-stringer.
Perhaps.
Seriously, there's a huge waterfall.
Really?
Sounds cool!
You can even watch movies on it with a projector.
- I wanna see!
And Yoichi Hiruma.
A vicious fellow, this one.
He makes up for his average athleticism
with cunning trick plays and tactics.
In other words, he stands in defiance of his limitations...
Not entirely unlike yourself, Unsui.
I won't let him get away with anything.
"Shishi Hakuto."
We'll use full arsenal as well!
You always say stuff like a wimp.
That's what makes you bald, bro!
Agon!
You're uber-late!
Ahh, relax.
I'll take out the trash tomorrow.
Especially that stinking pile Hiruma.
Wha- Agon, what're-
Him, too.
What's up, Sena? Got a cold?
No, but I felt a chill go down my spine...
Are you okay? This is no time to be sick!
Holy smokes.
Where'd you keep all those?
I'm fine, Mamori.
Tomorrow's the day.
We'll win!
Yeah. We'll get even with them.
Without fail.
I've done everything I can.
Now I just have to give 100% tomorrow.
Tomorrow's the day.
I can't sleep!
A text, now?
It's Suzuna.
Beep-beep!
You scared to play Shinryuji tomorrow?
I'm not scared.
It just... feels weird.
Six months ago, there were three people on the team.
And tomorrow we start facing Kanto's best teams.
I'm just amazed at how far we come in such a short time...
Are you satisfied?
Nope.
Our goal is still the Christmas Bowl.
That's why we'll win tomorrow!
Even against Shinryuji!
Good luck. I'll be cheering for you, Sena.
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
The weather today is nothing short of perfect!
The heavens have smiled upon the opening game
of the Kanto Tournament!
Hey, Agon's not even late!
Is he actually starting today?
Wow, that's rare.
Don't let him drag you in.
You all right, Sena?
Yes.
If we're going to beat Shinryuji,
we'll have to take down Agon!
The Kanto Tournament is about to begin!
Will the Shinryuji Nagas win their 10th tournament in a row?
Or will Deimon cause a miraculous upset?
As always, I'm the man with the full-auto mouth,
Machine Gun Sanada,
and with me on color commentary
replacing the still-in-America Mr. Kumabukuro,
The high school journalist
who's always available on short notice, Riko Kumabukuro!
To start things off, Riko,
what should we look for in today's game?
Right! Take a look at this chart.
At first glance,
Deimon seems like a dark horse
that's enjoyed an incredible rise from obscurity to the top.
However, they lost badly to the powerful Ojo,
tied Taiyo, and lost to Seibu.
All of their victories have actually been against
teams of equal or lesser ability.
I see.
There haven't been any miracles.
They've simply trained hard,
and won with blood, sweat and tears.
But against superior opponents, they've always lost.
And this time they're up against a wall.
Indeed. Their opponents are the Shinryuji Nagas.
There are no losers brackets or 3rd-place tiebreakers
in the Kanto Tournament.
One loss seals your fate.
Deimon's only chance today seems to be a real miracle!
Lemme show you boys something funny.
Here are the odds for today's game.
They're giving us a 0.7% chance of victory.
- 0.7%?
Not even 1%?
Once again, everyone sells us short.
Although I'll admit it sounds about right.
True.
Now, I'm putting something on the line too.
If you lose today,
I'll never drink another drop of sake.
I want to carry some kind of burden along with you all...
Because once the game starts,
I'm just a trainer who can't do anything more.
Win a decisive win so I have an excuse to drink something expensive.
You old coot.
Gotta hurry...
Argh...
I dropped them all.
I-I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
Uhh, I'm fine, don't sweat it...
Oh man, I just came to sneak a peek, she is UBER-cute.
He's so excited, yet he acts aloof and says only a few words.
He can't look her in the eyes.
A by-product of going to an all-boys school.
Are you okay, Mamori?
Is something wr- Ikkyu!
Don't get excited, everything's fine, Monta.
I see.
Ikkyu.
I swear, I'll snatch the ball away from you today.
You really think you can beat me?
I sure do!
I swore to Honjo that I wouldn't let anyone out-catch me!
At your level?
Yeah.
At my level.
H-H-Hey!
S-S-Sorry about that!
What're you doing, Ikkyu?!
Going to flirt before the game, I'm jealous-
I mean, disappointed in you!
Mamori.
I may not have grown up yet,
but I promise you this:
Today, before your eyes,
I will become a real man!
Good luck, Monta.
Agon, we're here!
I'm afraid he can't hear you.
the moment he puts on his uniform, he enters his zone.
He sees what he wants...
And every fiber of his being is honed and focused only on getting it.
The only thing he feels now
is lust for eradicating his overconfident, mediocre enemy.
Nothing more.
I'm not afraid.
I'll charge in at full speed!
Will the undefeated, invincible Nagas win again?
Or will the demons who wield miracles, the Deimon Devil Bats prevail?
The crowd is at a fever pitch!
Let's go, men.
We ain't here to defeat our enemies.
We're here to murder 'em!
Rip their heads off!
Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
With the the power of the dragon gods,
we strike down the enemies of enlightenment!
We are the Shinryuji Nagas!
Shinryuji Nagas vs. Deimon Devil Bats
Ya-ha!
Stay calm. Your turn will come later.
Right.
Deimon will receive.
Shinryuji kicks off...
...and the game has begun!
Our lives are on the line.
Here we go!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Late night texts from Suzuna...
Is Sena finally growing up?
W-Where'd that come from?
This is no time to brag!
You're up against Shinryuji!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Devils vs. Dragons!
Ya-ha!
This is Riko Kumabukuro reporting live!
I'm here at the Deimon Devil Bats' bench.
Have you completed your preparations for today's game?
Yes!
Is your side prepared in case anyone is unlucky enough to be injured?
You've worked out your signs and signals with Hiruma as well?
Yes!
This must be a result of the deep love you and Hiruma share!
Absolutely not!
I am the MANAGER and ONLY the manager.
This concludes my report from Deimon's bench...