Our game against Shinryuji's just around the corner.
You've done everything you can to prepare.
So check this out.
Luxury Cruise: One-Night in Tokyo Bay
Welcome to our dinner cruise!
A luxury cruise?
It's a one nighter in Tokyo Bay...
- A dinner cruise?!
It's just a little present for everyone.
Sweet!
He must have lost big time at the races.
Yeah, probably.
Hiruma, should we be doing this before the game?
Yeah, why not?
It will be a chance for us to relax both our hearts
and bodies before the tournament.
That's was I was thinking.
- Yay!
Thanks, Coach Doburoku!
Maybe I'll put on a dinner show for everyone!
No one'll watch it.
Oh, my sister...
You're in charge of getting everything ready...
...you little Peewee!
Oh!
You're team manager again!
Good luck with everything.
T-Thanks...
A dinner cruise, huh?
Umaku tobidasenai
When it seems like
sonna toki wa
I can't rush forward
kanjiru mama ni hane wo hiroge
I just spread my wings and go.
Togiresou na
I project all my
omoi wo kono sora ni utsushite
disjointed thoughts onto the sky.
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Kyouteki wo gekiha!
Clash & dash! Clash & dash! Smash & bash your opponent!
Mabataki shiteru mae ni in your area!
And in the blink of an eye I'm up in your area!
Watch out, watch out! I'm about a touch down!
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Donna toki demo
No matter what happens,
Sasaete kureru kimi ga iru kara
with you standing behind me,
Nando datte tachiagatte
I'll get back up every time
ano hikari ga michibiku
and follow that light
basho e ikou!
wherever it goes.
Sena's a Famous Detective?!
I wonder where everyone is...
It's time to board...
We'll just leave 'em behind!
N-No way!
I'm going to go look for everyone.
What are you doing?!
There! There! Don't you dare lose!
- E-Excuse me...
- Back off!
I don't let anyone throw me around!
It's time to board the ship now...
Once more! One more time!
Sorry, but it's time to go now.
Lookie! This should fit Sena perfectly!
You're right!
But this would look better on him!
Look!
How CUTE!
How's this?
Wow! It's so unique!
Sorry, but it's time to go now...
There's two hours until dinner,
so we need to eat a quick snack.
Sorry, but it's time to go now...
The sea is calling for me.
The gulls are calling to me.
Oh, Sena!
Sorry, but could you take some pictures?
How's this?
Nah, I like this pose.
Wait, no.
How about a shot of my back?
Yep, that's it!
Back shots make you look masculine!
Okay, so everyone's here now.
Let's go ahead and board!
Guys, what're you doing?
The boat's gonna leave without us if you don't hurry!
Don't, Taki! That ship's going to Africa!
Africa Bound: Next Departure 19:00
That was intentional.
Definitely intentional.
It had to be intentional.
It's so pretty!
It's awesome!
It's just about time for dinner.
Yeah, let's go.
Japanese Desert
Japanese Dinner
Looks good!
I'm starving!
Dinner!
Sweet! There's spare ribs and cow tongue stew!
It's not THAT amazing...
Wow! There's cakes and cream puffs!
Cream puffs!
Mamori's eyes just changed!
So then, everyone...
- Let's dig in!
Hey, manager, what's going on here?!
Someone ate our dinner!
Hey! Don't ask me!
Who was it?! Who ate our dinner?!
Show yourself! I'll beat you up!
Sena!
I wanna have dinner!
- Dinner! Dinner!
- K-Kurita, calm down!
- There's no way we can stay calm!
Sena, you've gotta do something!
We've been had!
Huh?!
A mysterious robbery's happened here!
As a result, no one got to eat anything!
No one got to eat anything!
- Sena!
- Huh?
It's time to show off your skills as team manager!
You've got to find the dinner thief!
Me? Find the culprit?
We had half an hour of free time before dinner.
I bet the crime happened then!
And the culprit is still in this room!
Really?
You have to ask for everyone's alibi in order to find the culprit.
Your pride as team manager's on the line!
N-No way!
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
Ta-da!
Let's go, my dear Kobayakawa.
My dear Kobayakawa?
It sets the right mood, ya know?
There's no way I can find the culprit.
That's not true, my dear Kobayakawa!
First let's go hear everyone's alibis, Kobayakawa!
S-Sure...
Master Ryokan Kurita
Master Daikichi Komusubi
We'll start here!
Okay...
Huh? Suzuna!
What are you doing, Suzuna?
I'm not Suzuna.
My nickname is Detect, the famous detective.
I'm going to keep a look out.
You burst in, Kobayakawa!
This whole detective-police thing's a mess!
Sena, I want my dinner!
It hurts! Help me!
I can't believe they'd still be that hungry
if they'd just finished eating everyone's dinner...
So they're innocent.
Yours is two grams heavier!
I'm the one who brought this cup ramen on board,
so don't complain!
Then I get the fish cake!
Punk! I haven't had anything to eat since breakfast!
I told you that this is MY cup ramen!
That doesn't matter!
Eat it!
That's mine!
Stop it!
Hey, guys!
What is it?!
Gotta problem with us?
Ouch! Ow-ow-ow!
Why me?
I think they're probably innocent...
What's wrong with him?
He's dizzy from hunger and can't stop spinning.
How can this be?!
Oh, sorry!
He's definitely innocent.
Let's give up already.
No, not yet!
There's still those two!
Oh, don't tell me...
Need something?
No, it's nothing.
Well, enjoy yourselves...
- See you later!
What's with them?
Dunno. Just ignore 'em.
So we still don't know who the culprit is...
Huh? A black-out?
That was Mamori!
I hope the culprit didn't attack her!
Let's hurry!
Help me!
Mamori!
What happened?!
The light's back.
Huh? Oh, well,
I was just so shocked when the lights suddenly went out.
Oh, thank goodness...
Sorry for screaming like that.
What's wrong?
It's gone. My luggage is all gone!
This time somebody's luggage got taken?!
Yep!
Hey, this for real?
It looks like someone from the outside's the culprit.
Man! Who'd do this?!
Hey, Monta, we're gathering together.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
The boat's so big I got lost.
Where on earth am I?
Monta! Monta!
What is it?! What happened?!
I don't know.
He hung up on me.
First our dinner,
then the lights go out and our luggage gets stolen.
And now Mon-Mon's missing.
I-I'm scared!
Hey, we aren't getting mixed up
in something really bad, are we?
Sena! I'm scared!
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Amazing! I can't even see his face.
Who's that?!
After him, my dear Kobayakawa!
Huh? Me?!
Hurry! It might be the culprit!
Okay!
We'll help!
Hold it right there!
Miss Mamori Anezaki
Miss Suzuna Taki
Isn't this...?
Jerk! I said to freeze!
Sena, let's trap him!
We'll swing around from the other direction.
All right!
Okay, we caught him!
We won't let you escape!
We're gonna let you have it!
That's-!
Look out! He's got a weapon!
What are you doing here?
Shin!
What? So that was his Spear Tackle?
What are you doing here, Shin?
I can't believe you're here.
Just running.
Running?
Oh, what're you doing?
Huh?
If it isn't Deimon!
Oh, it's everyone from Ojo!
What are you doing here?
Well, Mr. Ito from Jari Productions invited us on board.
Oh, really?
So Otawara ate our food?!
What? It wasn't a buffet?
No way...
That was our dinner!
Really? Well, don't let it bother you too much!
- You little...! You're so toast!
- C-Calm down, Kuroki.
A-Also, our luggage went missing after the lights went out.
Do you know where it went?
Oh! You mean that blackout?
Sorry, I did that.
The exit door's shut.
That'll open it.
Why'd you do that, huh?!
- Huh, Shin?!
- Calm down, Kuroki!
Well, he probably thought that he was trapped...
Even so, why'd he do that?
Dunno...
But I don't know about your luggage.
U-Um, Sena..
About my luggage...
I just realized this, but during that blackout...
I was so upset that
I entered the wrong room.
My room was the next door!
I'm so sorry!
Huh?
What a relief.
But there's more!
Huh?
The case isn't closed yet!
Oh, that's right! Monta's still missing.
Yamashita Circus
The crew thought he was a monkey
from the circus and caught him.
Hurry up and let me out!
You'll be just fine now, Monta.
Mamori, that's...
...a real monkey.
M-Mamori, you're cruel!
Uh, well, you see...
I kinda feel...
...sorry for him.
How pathetic.
- Let's dig in!
Mamori, your eyes!
Wow!
I can't believe they cooked up another meal for us!
It's great! Great!
He just ate and he's still hungry...
This is really good.
Which one?
But man, what a relief.
Sometimes it's nice to relax like this.
Huh? Shin's not here.
That's kinda shocking!
The tournament's coming up soon...
But I still can't believe you were training here.
I don't think I'm skilled enough
to be picky over when or where I train.
I'm getting really nervous now,
since Shinryuji's really powerful.
Not confident about winning?
No, that's not it...
There's something special about you
that only those you've fought can recognize.
You must win!
Right!
We're gonna defeat Shinryuji!
We've gotta!
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
Today you're going to take it easy
and watch a baseball game?
It's the OB game
and master catcher Honjo is going to be there!
You can't call yourself a fan if you don't go!
Hey, isn't that Ikkyu from Shinryuji?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: His Talent at Catching!
Ya-ha!
Man, that was heavenly!
We should all thank Coach Doburoku.
It's so cool how he let us go and stayed behind.
Sure is!
Did I keep you waiting?
I hope you aren't planning on boarding dressed like that.
You're supposed to enjoy the salty sea air
while getting drunk on the beauty of the night sky
when on a dinner cruise.
Night cruises are oasises for adults.
Viva night cruises!
I guess you're a bit young to understand...
I guess he goofed up the time.
Poor idiot.
Manager, tell him...
Tell him that the cruise is already over.
I can't...
What are you doing dressed like that?
The cruise is already over.
He said it!
He turned to stone!
Coach Doburoku!