Sorry I'm late, Mamo!
Huh? Where's Sena?
He's late! And he's not picking up!
I bet Sena overslept!
Yesterday's game against the Poseidons
was pretty hard on him.
It wasn't hard for him at all!
Just before the game,
when we were getting all set up...
Oh, shoot! We're out of batteries again!
I'll go buy some!
It's okay, Sena.
I already bought some since this always happens.
Ah, but, it looks like I forgot a video tape, too.
A tape, too?
Yeah! I'll go buy one!
You just can't count on him!
And you know what?
I saw a tape in his bag when I looked in it!
Keeping Eyeshield 21's identity a secret from Mamo's
pretty hard for poor Sena.
Sena!
When'd you get here?
About when you said "You just can't count on him!"
Today I'm going to make sure you do your job
as a team manager during Ojo's game!
The batteries are all okay
and we've got three hours worth of video tape!
"The pirates that summon storms:
The Karibu Pirates are challenging the Ojo White Knights!"
"The Pirates summer training included
swimming an entire lap around Japan."
"So they're a super offensive team."
That means Ojo can't let their guard down, huh?
They've sure gathered quite the crowd!
There won't be any seats left if we don't hurry!
Suzuna's always so energetic!
My bag!
W-What should I do?!
He's fast!
Darn it!
Thank you very much.
Man, that was pretty lame!
Hey!
Ri-Riku!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Appearance of a Lightspeed Man?!
Rikky?!
He'll never change, Mamo!
He's always been a space case!
Riku, what are you doing here?
Sena, it's supposed to be your job to protect Mamo!
Well, it's easier to say than do...
Hey, who's he? Who? You know him?
I'm Sena's big brother.
Oh, his brother.
HUH?! Sena has a brother?!
No, I'm an only child.
Back in elementary school
Riku and I were in the same class for a while.
So how's that make him your brother?
It means I'm LIKE his brother.
Riku... is my master.
Your master?
Yep.
There's no way I can carry so many backpacks!
Make sure to drop them off at our homes!
It's impossible!
You guys are all pathetic.
It's the new transfer student, Riku Kaitani!
I bet you think you're all that
just because your smart and good at tag!
Huh? What's that?
Dummy!
- We won't forget this!
HEY!
Don't tease Sena!
Mamori, you've got it wrong!
Oh, I see. I'm sorry!
'Kay...
I'm Mamori Anezaki, a fourth grader.
I'm Riku Kaitani and I just moved in last week.
Rikky, huh?
Come on, Sena, be good and thank him!
T-Thank you...
You're a third grader,
so you need to be more responsible!
- Okay, Sena!
- Huh?
I'm going to become your brother
and teach you the ultimate move for how to win fights.
I don't really want to fight...
It's not really fighting, but speed!
Speed?
Speed's important for dodging your enemy's attacks.
Got that?
Kinda...
But I'm not going to simply teach you how to be fast,
but how to do an explosive dash.
So, first run a little.
Sure...
No, no! You're doing it all wrong!
When you were running you only moved your foot
at the ankle and had it slap the ground.
That's awful!
Really?
You want your ankle to form a right angle
and then push off the ground with all your might.
Right angle? Pushing?
Well, learning it'll take some time,
so lets practice every day from now on!
E-Every day?!
Sena! Rikky!
Here's some madeleines!
I made them in home economics.
Thank you!
They're GOOD!
What are you two doing together everyday?
It's a secret, right, Sena?
Y-Yeah....
Really! Leaving me out like that...
Listen carefully, Sena.
Use the muscles in your inner leg
and push forward with a BOOM!
Amazing!
Push forward with a boom...
That's right!
That's it!
You'll cream those guys if you keep
that image in your head while running!
Just after that, Riku moved away...
- It's been six years...
- Yep!
Rikky hasn't changed at all!
Mamo, quit calling me "Rikky!"
I'm not a kid anymore.
Nope, Rikky is Rikky!
Man!
So, Sena, what have you been up to lately?
Well, not much...
Rikky, Sena here's joined Deimon's football team.
Football? Wow, that's cool!
I'm just the team manager.
I see! Team manager, huh?
Oh yeah, Sena,
you've been collecting a lot of data
if you're the team manager, right?
Who do you think the strongest player in Tokyo
is right now with the remaining teams?
The strongest player...?
I guess Ojo's linebacker, Shin.
Ojo's Shin, huh?
Why do you think it's him?
He's got some good techniques
along with amazing power and speed.
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us how to throw a spiral ball!
The key point is your pinky finger?
When you want to throw a spiral ball,
make sure to place your pinky finger
in the middle of the fourth stitch along the seam.
Your pinky goes on the fourth stitch! Ya-ha!
- Oh!
- We rule!
Pirates! Pirates! Pirates!
White Knights! White Knights!
It's Shin!
Hey, look! It's Shin!
Awesome! It's Shin's Spear Tackle!
Somebody stop Shin!
It's no use, Coach!
He's completely untouchable!
Thanks to Seijuro Shin, Ojo won 27-0!
Karibu Pirates 0 - Ojo White Knights 27
They're going to the semi-finals!
Amazing! Shin is truly amazing!
Sena, why do you like Ojo so much?
Because it's true that they're great!
Come on!
Where to?
Let's go see Shin!
We can't go see him now!
Hey!
If it isn't Kurita's team manager!
Ah, Onihei!
Spying on Ojo, huh?
No, I'm not spying...
Deimon's only got one game left before they face Ojo.
But our team will have to defeat Seibu before we can fight Ojo.
Seibu, huh?
They're certainly a tough adversary.
But Deimon's pretty good, too.
Sena!
Who's the old fart?!
Riku, that's rude!
This is Onihei Yamamoto from the Hashiratani Deer.
His technique as a lineman is incredible.
Everyone really respects him!
But didn't Hashiratani lose pathetically
to the Poseidons in their very first game?
Riku!
Well, it's to be expected.
I shouldn't have underestimated the Poseidons.
Seriously!
The line didn't even do anything impressive in that game!
What would an amateur know?
Wanna find out?
Are you wanting to fight for real, boy?
Yeah, bring it on anytime!
Here I go, boy!
He just...!
You really are a good lineman!
Sena, let's go.
Sorry, Onihei! Goodbye!
That cocky brat's no pushover...
Riku, are you...
What?
Are you playing football, too?
Oh!
It's Ojo's locker room.
Ojo High School Locker Room
- Excuse me!
- Riku!
Shin!
I-I'm sorry,
but m-my friend said that he wanted to meet you...
Yesterday's game against the Poseidons was impressive.
Y-You were watching?
Deimon has become even more powerful.
If they win again, we'll fight each other in the finals.
Shin!
Hey, hey!
Sorry to butt in, but I don't think Ojo's gonna play Deimon.
After all, Seibu's gonna defeat Deimon
before they ever get to fight Ojo.
Who're you?
I'm the Seibu Wild Gunmen's running back, Riku Kaitani!
Seibu's running back?
Deimon was just a hodge-podge team
that always lost in real games up until last year.
Their only real player is that
Eyeshield something-or-other.
Riku...
And what do you know about him?
That he's just a little fast.
You don't realize how strong he is until you fight him.
That's how he is!
Is he really that strong?
Then let's find out who's better,
me or Eyeshield, right now!
Stop it already!
Shin, Seibu's game's about to start!
If it isn't the shrimp from Deimon!
And are you... one of Shin's fans?
He'll give you his autograph later!
He got in the way!
Shin, I wonder how well your Spear
would do against my Rodeo Drive.
Rodeo Drive?
Well, I'll be waiting for you!
Shin, I'm sorry.
Riku!
Riku, are you really in Seibu's...
Just watch the next game!
Pay attention 'cause I'm the greatest!
Riku's part of Seibu's team...
And we'll be up against Seibu
in the semi-finals if they win this game.
All right, let's go crazy today!
My, my. What a pain.
Well, let's just finish this up right quick.
Let's go, Tetsuma!
Riku's on the bench!
There's no need to show them all the cards in our hand!
You're our secret weapon in our game against Deimon.
Now, don't start sulking!
Hey, stop right there!
Skewer 'em!
On the one side there's Seibu Wild Gunmen!
They're up against the anti-Seibu tactics using Edomae Fishers!
Will they manage to catch the big fish, Seibu?!
Set, hut, hut!
Wow! Edomae burst through Seibu's line and are going after the Kid!
Kid's in danger!
Sadly, we're doing TOO good today.
Tetsuma, slant!
Look out! Kid just shot a Quick-and-Fire!
No one can stand up to the Human Locomotive, Tetsuma!
Touchdown!
Seibu's just too much!
The Kid's super fast passes take advantage
of Tetsuma's absolutely perfect routes.
Seibu's offense is really great!
I wonder what type of team it would be like if you added Riku to it?
We're doing WONDERFULLY! Go crazy!
Man, nothing good ever happens when we're doing too good.
What is it, Riku?
I want to play!
Don't be stupid!
There's no need to keep me a secret from Deimon.
H-Hey, wait a sec!
Sena!
Riku!
Seibu's swapping players!
It's #29! Who's that?
- I've never seen him before!
- There it is!
#29 is the running back, Riku Kaitani.
Kid, please give the ball to me!
Man, you're as heated up as ever.
Wow! Kaitani, who just entered the game,
is running with the ball!
I dare you to stop me when I'm running!
You cocky brat!
Everyone, get him!
Here's my Rodeo Drive!
What just happened?!
When did Kaitani get past all of the Edomae players?!
He burst through 11 people and got a touchdown!
Game over! It's just too much! Seibu's victorious!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 49 - Edomae Fishers 0
They're going to the semi-finals!
That's Riku's running style...
That idiot! He even used his Rodeo Drive!
Shoulda expected it when he went out on the field.
I won't lose to anyone!
He hasn't changed at all!
Riku really is great!
Did you see that, Sena?
I'm the greatest, fastest running back in the world!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Yay! Deimon's going to have field day today!
But I have a bad feeling about this!
The losers have to play in a penalty game!
Mamori, I don't get what's going on, but I know I CAN'T lose!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Field Day at Deimon High School! Ya-ha!
Riku's on Seibu's team.
I wonder if I can beat Riku...
Huh?
I feel like I'm forgetting something.
Sheesh, Sena!
And here I was going to make you do your job today!
Where on earth did you go?