Huh? No way...
Why aren't I moving?!
I've gotta keep going...
I've... I've gotta keep moving forward!
Sena, we'll have to forfeit the Kanto Tournament
if we give up here.
Try hard!
Sena, you're our only hope!
I know!
Everyone's counting on me!
I... have to... keep going!
That was a weird dream.
Sena, good morning!
Oh, Mamori! Good morning.
What's wrong?
You look kinda tired.
I haven't been sleeping well lately...
I see...
Well, make sure you don't push yourself too hard.
But I've gotta push myself!
This isn't the time to take it easy!
Guys, stop Sena!
He's surrounded!
Go around!
Don't be rash. Just go around them...
I'll bulldoze in head on! I can do it!
He's pushing through?!
That's nuts!
- Belly Tackle!
- Sena!
That outright stunk.
We need to keep the ball,
even if it means breaking into the sidelines.
Are you okay, Sena?
Yeah...
Is it just me or has he lost his edge?
Normally, that tackle wouldn't have worked on him.
He's exhausted...
And it seems...
...it's more than just physical fatigue...
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Invisible Shackle!
Good morning, everyone!
I'm tired from morning practice.
Class time is a great time...
...to recharge.
That was quick!
I think I'll have one of you translate this sentence into English for me.
"For the sake of my family waiting for me at home, I can't give up!"
"I can't give up!" He's exactly right!
We can't win if I don't score some points.
I... I...!
There's a strange pain in my chest.
I wonder why.
Why do I feel so nervous and out of it?
Y-You sure, Musashi?
Yeah,
I want everyone to focus on just taking it easy
and relaxing until tomorrow.
Which means...
We can do whatever...
...the heck we want?
B-But we don't have time to take it easy!
Practice may be important,
but so is giving your muscles a break every now and then.
Fatigue isn't good for both your mind and your body.
Yay, we get a break!
But is it really okay to just take off?
I feel like... I just can't calm down any.
Riku!
Hey, Sena!
I thought I'd drop by!
The Kanto Tournament Lottery's coming up pretty soon.
Yeah.
Both of us have worked hard to make it this far.
And I hope...
...that I can fight you in the finals.
The finals...
Hm? What's wrong?
Nah, it's nothing.
In fact, I was just wondering why you came all the way out here to see me.
Yeah well, I thought it would be best
to talk to you in person instead of on the phone.
Shin and everyone from Ojo...
...are undergoing training camp on Mt. Fuji?
Yep.
So, Sena,
how 'bout going and checking it out tomorrow?
I might not feel so blue if I can just talk to Shin.
Sure, I'll go, Riku!
Shin's higher up the mountain with Sakuraba
doing some high-altitude training.
He's with Sakuraba?
Yeah.
It's his dream to become like Shin someday.
I wonder why they're undergoing coach training
"Coach" and "High-altitude" are said the same way in Japanese.
when they don't have the coach up there with them.
Sorry, Otawara, but you're thinking of the wrong word.
So, Sena, let's go check it out!
Up the mountain?
I wouldn't if I were you!
A bear might come out and attack you!
A-A bear?!
W-What... should we do, Ri-Riku?!
Let's go.
We can outrun a bear with our good ol' legs anytime!
Come on already, Sena!
Hey, wait up!
Riku!
If a bear shows up, either play dead
or make it eat a bamboo leaf.
You give bamboo leaves to pandas, Otawara.
Don't pandas eat pastries?
This's great!
It's been ages since we had some free time!
I feel like we've been set free!
We've been doing nothing but American football lately.
So today...
...we're going to...
...spread our wings and fly!
Master!
Komusubi, did you come over to hang out?
My beloved old Deimon baseball team's playing a game?
I guess I should go cheer for 'em!
Hey, what are you up to?
Oh, my sister,
I'm splicing together all of the game footage
covering me helping the team!
Helping them? When'd you do that?
Where'd Riku wander off to?
A-A bear?!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What's an important trait for running backs like Eyeshield 21?
You need the courage to give your all protecting the ball
as you run through enemy territory.
Don't chicken out! Ya-ha!
A-A bear!
Huh? S-Shin?
Sakuraba...
Man! Let's go after them, Sena!
Wait up, Riku.
I swear... my calves feel like they're ready to explode.
What's wrong? A bit much?
I can handle it!
I'll follow you to the ends of the earth!
This average-Joe is going to turn into a hard-working genius!
My determination... is unparalleled by anyone!
You lose!
Darn it!
Man! I just can't concentrate!
What gives?
I thought you were practically a pro gamer!
I just can't get a hold of my self.
Say, why don't we drop by there right quick?
THERE, huh? Sounds good.
Yeah, let's go THERE.
Where?! Where'd he go?
They're way over there? Shoot!
Lookie here, my sister!
What gives?
All you're doing is spinning around or getting whacked.
All of my shots are of me swirling around...
How can this be?!
Then rip there!
Right! Perfect! That's the rip!
And when we do it together...
Stop it, Ryokan!
Curse you!
Sorry...
Sweet! This is your max chance!
I hope you get one in, dude!
Look out!
Good going!
You rock!
That was a piece of cake!
That was cool!
What's with this weird feeling...?
I feel strange to the max...
I shouldn't be here!
A-Aren't you from Seibu?
You're amazing!
I can't believe this is how you train!
I'm impressed you were able to keep up with us.
Oh yeah, Sena...
Where'd he wander off to?
I wonder where everyone went...
Riku!
Shin!
Sakuraba!
What should I do?
I think I'm lost!
I've just gotta practice.
Kurita! Komusubi!
Monta?!
What wrong?
I just couldn't sit still...
Same with us. Check it out.
Musashi!
Hey!
It's been so long since I played regularly, you see.
Now I've gotta practice extra hard.
Huh?
Everyone came here to practice even though they're off today.
Really, a genius like me doesn't need to practice...
Whatever! Just go get changed!
What, so we're the last ones here?
Looks like everyone's...
...thinkin' the same thing!
Hey!
You betcha to the max!
It looks like Sena's the only one
actually obeying orders and resting up.
I'm totally lost!
And it's getting dark!
Calm down...
I've gotta meet up with Shin and the others.
S-Shin?
It's a bear this time!
I promise you I don't taste good!
I've just gotta keep running from it until it gives up!
A dead end?
Shin...
Shin was training with all those weights on...
And he's still faster than everyone else...
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Shin, you really are amazing.
I can't believe this is how you train.
I could never do that...
Not right away.
You're right.
You and I are so different in both our physique and mentality...
I just... haven't been able to focus.
I feel like I'm in a daze all the time...
But I can't stand just sitting around doing nothing.
It's the stress of wanting to win.
Stress?
Oh, I get it.
I'm feeling pressured.
You're telling yourself that you can't lose.
It's the pain of knowing that you and you alone
can pull it off and you can't run away from that fact.
So um... Have you ever felt pressured before?
It's not like I've never felt stressed before.
So even you've felt pressured?
But how did you overcome it?
With practice.
In order to develop a strong mentality that can withstand the stress,
you must hone your confidence and strength
through undergoing extremely difficult training.
That's the only way.
Honing strength and confidence through tough training...
I see. That makes sense!
Thank you very much!
I think I'm on to something thanks to you!
Oh, and come to think of it,
where's Riku and Sakuraba?
We were together until just a minute ago...
By the way, where are we?
Which way leads up?
So you're lost, too!
Well, there's no need to worry.
We've got plenty of food to live off of.
The bear!
Sena!
Shin!
That's Riku and Sakuraba!
Thank goodness!
What's up, Sena?
You look pretty happy.
Anything good happen?
I'm going to train harder and win the Kanto Tournament!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Ya-ha!
It's time for the Kanto Tournament Lottery at last!
Sena, good luck at the lotto!
Is it really okay for me to do it?
What if I draw a bad number?
It doesn't matter what number we get!
We just have to win!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Ultimate Evil! Ya-ha!
We can't lose to Shin and Sakuraba!
Let's show Japan just how strong the new Ojo White Knights are!
Let's show off our manly determination!
Before we do that, Otawara...
Quit showing THAT off and put on some pants!
Quit worrying about small stuff!