The Deimon Devil Bats
went to America and returned home to Japan
as the first champions of the "Cream Puff Cup"
international high school football tournament.
Today, they're taking a well-earned rest.
Everyone's at home recuperating from the trip.
They'll need their strength for all the tough teams
waiting in the Kanto Tournament.
Seriously, Hiruma!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
It's Time! Prepare for the Kanto Tournament!
The Death March and Death Climb made for extreme training,
but without them, we'd not have all these Tokyo Tournament memories.
I can still see all those close games in my mind's eye.
Back then, you couldn't count on Sena for anything.
It's almost impossible to think that he turned out to be Eyeshield...
Our first game in the Tokyo Tournament
was against the Amino Cyborgs,
a school that specializes in sports medicine
and uses their knowledge to build strong sports teams.
Ya-ha!
He disappeared...
Yuhi Guts!
After them came the always-passionate Yuhi Guts!
Atsumi...
Let's go, Eyeshield 21!
I've waited three years for my chance!
That was REAL running...
The Dokubari Scorpions and Kanagushi specialized in dirty tactics.
With Hiruma missing, we weren't sure what was going to happen,
Ya-ha!
Sorry I'm late.
Touchdown!
THIS is the only place that's allowed to get worked up.
Keep your heart fired up and your head clear and cool.
That's how you play football!
Our victory that day put Deimon in the Best Eight!
Sena got better and better with each game he played.
Freeze!
In order to make it to the Final Four,
we had to go through a team full of tall, strong players.
The gods of the sea, the Kyoshin Poseidons!
It was a back-and-forth battle that stayed close the whole time!
I won't lose!
Give it up!
Moby Dick Anchor!
I can get through!
You're not going anywhere!
Now I've got him!
There!
I made it, I'll get the touchdown!
We're going to the semi-finals!
The semi-fi-
I won't let you!
Stop the clock!
Time out!
An obsessed Mizumachi
just barely managed to stop Sena's touchdown.
We've got three centimeters to go.
Just three centimeters to the goal.
Our win was sealed...
He jumped over us!
No way...
We win!
Komu...subi...
The Deimon Devil Bats came from behind
with just two seconds to spare!
- Ya-ha!
As with every game, there's a winner, and a loser.
And a true winner will always remember
the losing team's dedication and passion.
I think Sena understood that very well.
But then, out of nowhere,
Riku, a childhood friend of Sena's and mine
appeared out of nowhere!
He played for our semi-final opponents, the Seibu Wild Gunmen!
Eyeshield 21 takes off!
He's fast, fast, fast!
Can he score a touchdown!
Come on, Sena!
I'll even beat Riku!
I can't lose to Sena, I can't!
He's shut down!
Sena faced the person who taught him how to run
over and over again.
But...
This time...
There, now dodge!
I made it!
The Devil Bat Hurricane didn't work either...
Man up and get on your feet.
Riku...
Seibu had a commanding lead,
and Riku had completely shut Sena down.
Yo!
Why so serious, Mamo?
S-Suzuna?
That an album?
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what you need to be a lineman like Kuriton!
The key is "power!"
You need explosive strength to push away your opponent on every play!
You heard him, explode!
Ya-ha!
Hey, it's Kiddo!
Man, those Seibu guys were something else.
Kid...
What do I always say?
It's a bad sign when things go too well.
And here were are.
Kid's a true genius.
He'll know exactly what pass play has the highest chance of success.
That's what makes him easy to read.
With so little time,
someone as dedicated to victory as Kid
will narrow down the possibilities for us.
This strategy's the only shot we ever had!
Let's go!
- Yeah!
Get it, Butt-Monkey!
Oh, I already KNEW you had me all figured out.
What?!
He threw an underhanded super quickdraw?!
Tetsuma, my target wasn't the ball to begin with!
What?!
I was going for the fingers on your "invincible" right hand!
And there's Eyeshield 21!
Kid and Tetsuma's "Quick and Fire" has been intercepted!
Can he run it in for a touchdown?!
Sena!
Riku?!
I'm ready, Sena.
Prepare for a lightspeed Rodeo Drive!
And our 100th showdown!
I'll win!
I'll beat Riku! The one who taught me how to run!
Eyeshield and Kaitani are too fast!
He's got me!
I want to win. I have to win!
I don't need to dodge.
My body's just here to carry the ball.
I'll smash through him at top speed!
I'll turn my body into a lever,
and use the Devil Bat Hurricane...
...to push through!
Sena...
Our 100th match...
...goes to you.
Touchdown!
Eyeshield! Eyeshield!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 32
Sena's touchdown brought us to within three points,
but there was only a minute left to play.
We'll do an onside kick.
The fateful kick...
...goes flying!
Riku!
You'll have to kill me to take it away!
Monta!
Huh?
Dead ball! Seibu's ball!
Game over!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 35 - Deimon Devil Bats 32
Advancing to the finals of the Tokyo conference
with a score of 35-32, it's the Seibu Wild Gunmen!
Our chance at the Christmas Bowl...
...is gone...
For that one moment,
we all gave up on the Christmas Bowl...
No one knew there was a 3rd-place tiebreaker!
And our opponents...
Yup, the Bando Spiders!
Where could Sena be?
This morning when I said "today's the day" to him,
he looked like he was ready to play himself!
It reminded me of what you said yesterday,
and I thought, he really is like a 12th player.
Mamori...
Hmm?
Sena...
What... are you doing, Sena?
Football's... too dangerous for y-
I'm sorry I could never bring myself to tell you, Mamori...
But I have to go...
...because I'm...
And finally,
the man behind the mysterious mask known as "Eyeshield 21,"
"The Lightspeed Running Back,"
Eyesh- no!
Sena...
Kobayakawa!
Sena... Oh, Sena...
When did you grow up?
Prepare yourself for the strongest,
smartest kick team's first strike!
The Bando Spiders specialize in kicking and special teams.
It was another harsh game,
with the Spiders using their skills
to steal the ball and widen their lead.
Gotta stop him!
But our kicker, Musashi, finally came back,
and we suddenly had a chance again!
The kick is good!
The game came down to a final face-off between Sena and Akaba.
I'll get past Akaba!
No matter...
No matter what! I'm going to the Christmas Bowl!
Sena Kobayakawa scores a touchdown!
We did it, we did it!
The Deimon Devil Bats won their way into the Kanto Tournament.
Everyone really is incredible.
Sena... and everyone is ready for the Christmas Bowl...
We've got a new battle waiting for us.
Keep working, everyone!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Huh? "Death Game?"
One loss and we lose our spot in the Kanto Tournament?
A-And our first opponents are Onihei and the Hashiratani Deer!
This is no time to be excited, you have to win!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Farewell, Onihei! Ya-ha!
I'd better put this album back where I found it.
What's this?
"Ya-ha! As thanks for your support of the Deimon Devil Bats,"
"here's a rare souvenir photo
of Mamori Anezaki in a cheerleader outfit!"
Darn it, Hiruma!