- Drown!
- Ya-ha!
All you midgets think alike!
Komusubi!
W-Win!
He fumbles!
Max Catch!
Just moments away from a touchdown,
the Deimon shorties combine power, speed and catching
and steal the ball back!
All right!
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
The Secret MVP!
Deimon's definitely tough.
I see what you meant now, Kakei.
It might actually be 50-50.
S-So, what we should do is, uh...
All of Hiruma's strategies are focused on offense.
Even when they seem wide open, they come at you with surprising force.
Their previous opponents beat themselves by letting that force intimidate them.
The Kyoshin Poseidons are different.
We'll call their bet and win with a superior offensive.
R-Right, that's exactly what I was about to say!
We'll fight fire with fire and win on offense!
Yeah!
- Yeah!
- Right!
Deimon goes back on offense!
But they need to be careful here.
They may have recovered the fumble, but it happened right in front of their own goal line.
If they fail to advance...
They'll give up two points on the safety, plus the Poseidons get the ball again.
Yikes! Fight hard, everyone!
He's gonna try the Swim again.
Beat Mizumachi no matter what it takes!
Daikichi!
Use your arms! Your arms!
You figured out the secret all on your own!
That's right, Daikichi!
You're the son of a moving man,
so deliver your teammates straight to their destination!
Couldn't have said it better.
Should I run him through your spot?
Can you take down Mizumachi again and open a path for Eyeshield?
We can count on Komusubi!
Komusubi...
I know you can beat Mizumachi again,
so I'll be running like he isn't even there!
- The shorties will break the wall down!
The quarterback, Hiruma, is the key to this game.
Not the line?
Can Deimon manage a first down?
I'm not going down this time, Komusu-baby.
Okay... Here goes!
Set, hut hut!
- Here it comes!
- The Swim!
He'll win... Komusubi has the strength to beat the Swim!
A-Arm...
That's right! When you use the Swim, there's a brief moment
where your chest is wide open, just begging to be shoved!
What?!
Another amazing display of speed and power!
Komusubi sends Mizumachi flying!
I'm clear... Time for top speed!
Yes!
Eyeshield 21 breaks thr-
Kakei is awesome!
O-Oh no!
It's Kakei!
Eyeshield charged directly at the hole where Mizumachi was standing,
but was sent to the ground the second he broke through!
Did you think you were home free, Fakeshield?
Please, I'll stop anyone who makes it past the line!
Master Kakei's not alone.
We're back here, too!
Go ahead and try to get past us!
We're the High Wave!
They really are like a sweeping tidal wave.
Yes... Not a single move I tried on them worked.
They give new meaning to the phrase "high-level defense."
How will you counter, Hiruma?
Just inches from their own goal line,
the Deimon Devil Bats are on their fourth down!
This is their last chance - will the punt to try and make some distance?
Or will they go for broke and try to get a first down?
Go, Yocchie!
Hiruma makes a big gamble and decides to try for a first down!
Pass, pass! Pass to the max!
They've blocked his pass route!
Ohira- I mean, Onishi Hiroshi rushes in quickly!
He's headed straight for Hiruma!
Watch out!
He passed to me?
That was sweet!
He changed targets...
...and threw a lateral to Eyeshield!
It's Kakei and Ohira!
Guys, make a path for him!
We're on it!
Time to show off my blocking!
If Ishimaru and Taki can each block one of them...
Their arms are so long I can't even touch them!
How can this be?!
The High Wave pulls Eyeshield under!
How'd you like that, small fry?
That hand technique was passed down directly from Master Kakei to me!
Master Kakei's perfect moves far beyond your wild flailing.
You're still much too unpolished.
What?!
They used their incredible wing span to hold those two blockers out of reach.
Graceful, efficient use of the arms... That's Shun Kakei's true ability.
As long as I'm blocking, you won't score a single touchdown.
If you really think you can get through,
you'd better start trying harder.
Even Hiruma can't counter them...
Poseidons! Poseidons!
Hiruma...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to kick the ball!
You need a "kick tee?"
You use one of two kinds of kick tees when you kick the ball.
Don't forget the tee!
Ya-ha!
Deimon fails to get a first down,
and the Kyoshin Poseidons take possession!
Set...
Time to show them what real cheering is!
Go, go, Devils!
Go, go, Bats!
Hut!
Kobanzame!
That way, that way!
You can get through on my left.
Whoa, for real?
N-Need help!
Whoa, you're not going anywhere.
You're stuck with me, Komusu-baby!
I'm not going down again.
I'll stop you with everything I've got.
We're going all the way to the end!
Kobanzame makes a frantic dash for the end zone!
- Stop him!
- Argh!
Touchdown!
The Kyoshin Poseidons score first!
Oh, no!
Yeah, brah!
Crap!
The extra point is good, and the Poseidons lead by seven!
Kyoshin Poseidons 7 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
Poseidons! Poseidons! Poseidons!
We'll get it back! Score on the next drive!
Set, hut, hut!
Kakei crushes Eyeshield 21 once again!
Deimon's offense fails!
Kyoshin takes possession again.
I guess Kyoshin's height does give them the advantage...
Set, hut!
Touchdown!
They scored again...
Geez!
The extra point is good, and the Poseidons lead 14-0.
Kyoshin Poseidons 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 0
At least block them for a second, you worthless line-girls!
Argh!
If we could just grapple them, we could at least put up a fight like Grunty down there!
They're using their height and long arms to hold us, we can't even touch them!
We don't even get a chance!
Small fish will always be swept away by powerful waves.
Together, mine and Master Kakei's High Wave is impenetrable.
Hey, don't leave me out, jerk!
Is this really all you were capable of, Fakeshield?
What do I do? At this rate-
Fakeshield 21.
Today I'll show you why you have no right to use his name.
Yo, Sena.
Forget about what he said.
It doesn't matter if Kakei called you a phony.
Ack!
All you have to do is show that telephone pole, Kakei, that short guys can still hang, right?
We'll figure out some way to deal with Ohira and Onishi.
Just take care of Kakei!
Monta...
Interesting.
How about we try a Peewee-Monkey combo play?
- Peewee?
- Monkey?
It'll be a revolutionary, brand-new style of Deimon offense.
If you fly like a bird, the waves can't pull you under.
A bird?
The Wishbone.
Ya-ha!
- Wishbone?
Like in a turkey?
Yup, the formation looks just like the wishbone you pull from a turkey.
Can Deimon turn things around with this drive?
What an odd formation!
He's got three running backs behind him?
Takami, what is this formation?
Wakana!
Y-Yes?
Zoom in on this play and record every single move Deimon makes, please.
Right.
This play will likely show us the true depth of his skill as a playmaker...
One of Yoichi Hiruma's secret weapons.
We've never practiced any combo plays....
Let's just try to stay in sync!
Mizumachi, take care of the end!
Okay! I'm on it, brah!
Eat this.
The Devil Bat Wishbone!
Set, hut!
Deimon goes for a run!
Ishimaru rushes in!
Get 'em!
No, he didn't hand it off!
Hiruma's the one with the ball!
Stop him!
They both appeared to be running the ball at one point,
but now Ishimaru is blocking Mizumachi,
and Hiruma is blocking Ohira!
Let's go, Sena!
Denied!
Eyeshield and Raimon are running it together!
Block!
Wow!
They're totally synchronized!
20 yard gain, first down!
All right!
The first time and they've already perfected it.
Amazing! You guys are the best!
All right, let's keep the Wishbone momentum up.
Set,
hut!
Here it comes again!
The Wishbone!
Deimon's totally gonna go with Eyeshield!
Gotta stop him quick!
That makes this easy.
If they're gonna leave Ishimaru alone, he gets the ball.
Mizumachi somehow manages to change course.
But Deimon gains another six yards!
Ishimaru makes a perfectly ordinary run!
Amazing! He's amazingly ordinary!
I can't believe Hiruma's mastered the Wishbone in just two years!
When the opponent comes for Ishimaru, Hiruma runs away with the ball.
If they come after Hiruma, he hands it off to the golden boys, Eyeshield and Raimon!
This's nuts...
There's no way to defend against three different run patterns at the same time.
In one instant, Hiruma looks at where Kyoshin is focusing its defense,
sees who he can hand the ball off too,
and makes his decision.
Set, hut, hut!
This time it's Raimon!
Shoot, who do I target?
It's like I said, Hiruma holds the key to this game!
Yoichi Hiruma... He's...
The Deimon Devil Bats' secret MVP!
Ya-ha!
Touchdown!
Kyoshin Poseidons 14 - Deimon Devil Bats 6
It's 14-6! Is Deimon mounting a comeback?
- That was great, Hiruma!
- Yay, Yocchie!
Now it's my turn.
I need to beat him this time!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Yay! The Wishbone snaps the competition!
I'm really pumped now!
It's 14-6... We can win this!
I just have to beat Kakei...
Take him down!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Promise Made on the Field! Ya-ha!
Hiruma's brilliant strategy brings Deimon back to life!
Ow!
Kicking me without saying anything...
It's a compliment!
At times like this...
...a kick in the butt says it best!
Ah, you're following Hiruma's lead...
Ya-ha!