I won't lose!
Good job, guys!
Let's take a quick break.
Hey, I brought some lemons!
Wow, that's sour!
Everyone's working so hard.
Yeah!
Our next match is against the Kyoshin Poseidons
and it'll be our third death game.
We're almost half done!
We've just gotta win all five of those games!
And defeat Shinryuji!
Tsk-tsk-tsk!
Don't worry!
Since we've got Eyeshield 21,
the ace running back,
and me, the master catcher,
this'll be a piece of cake!
We are number one!
You seem rather enthusiastic.
Kakei!
What're you doing here?
Deimon may have grown stronger,
but your competitors in the Kanto Tournament are no pushovers.
Especially Shinryuji, they're incredible.
What gives?
Did you come here to insult us?
Monta!
Besides, with me as Deimon's master catcher,
we're awesome to the max!
Small dogs bark the loudest.
What?!
It's said...
the Kanto Tournament's three greatest receivers in history
will be competing this year.
Three greatest?
There's Tokyo's best receiver,
the perfectly precise invincible locomotive,
Jo Tetsuma from the Seibu Wild Gunmen.
Another of Tokyo's best receivers
is the master of the Everest Pass,
Haruto Sakuraba from the Ojo White Knights.
Finally, there's the backwards running master,
a guy with great sense and athletic ability,
Ikkyu Hosokawa from the Shinryuji Nagas.
Are you telling me that you're on par with them?
You bet I am!
Don't lecture me about great football players
unless you include me!
Monta, that's taking it a bit far...
Who's side are you on?
Amusing.
Let's see if you can walk the walk.
Show me how great you are in our next game!
You bet! Just you wait and see!
I did just as you instructed.
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Invincible Double-Blocker!
Geez, I wonder what type of handicap we're gonna get stuck with?
In our game against the Hashiratani Deers,
the majority of our offense was stuck warming the bench.
And only the freshmen got to play
in the game against the Zokugaku Chameleons.
Isn't Kyoshin's main lineman,
Mizumachi, out of the game?
How'll they play?
I'll still help the team 150% even if I'm not playing!
Is the food ready yet?
- HE'S our handicap.
It doesn't matter what type of handicap Hiruma gives us.
I'm tellin' ya Deimon's powerful!
We'll defeat Kyoshin AND Shinryuji with max ease!
Oopsy, oopsy!
But I'll catch every darn ball during the game!
Monta...
It's said...
the Kanto Tournament's three greatest receivers in history
will be competing this year.
Are you telling me that you're on par with them?
Who cares about that?!
Deimon is number one!
I'm number one!
- Shut up!
- Who's yelling?!
Do you know what time it is?!
Crap! I'm sorry!
Welcome to Kyoshin High!
It's time for our big game!
Mizumachi!
Is your shoulder all better?
Yeah, it's doing okay!
Looks like it's not all healed up yet.
Try not to push yourself too hard...
Way smart!
Akaba?
And Kotaro?
Long time no see, Deimon.
It's been a while.
What're you doing here?
Hey, don't tell me!
It was inevitable that we'd have a rematch.
This is your handicap for the game.
Deimon will be going up against the two of us...
Kyoshin and Bando will be playing as a tag team.
For real?! Kakei, that's cool!
I can't believe you're doing that when I can't play!
I'm so happy that I get to go up against you two again.
I'm looking forward to the game today!
Your attempt at befriending me won't work.
Live performances that amaze the audience
are what give birth to new melodies.
- Music has nothing to do with football!
Wow! They're going at it again!
To be blunt,
we're here to fight you fair and square!
We're gonna look so smart when we beat you!
We're going to have a tough time against Kyoshin
now that they've got a Tokyo MVP
and the greatest kicker out there.
Bando Spiders-Kyoshin Poseidons vs. Deimon Devils Bats
- Splash!
- C'mon!
Ya-ha!
Folks, it's time for the third death game!
Deimon'll be up against the Kyoshin Poseidons
and the Bando Spiders!
It's a mixed team containing Kyoshin's giants,
the Super-Kicker Kotaro and the Almighty Akaba.
I wonder what type of gameplay they've come up with!
I think we're in for some grand surprises!
Ready or not, it's gonna be a blast!
Set, hut!
I won't let you through!
We'll stop you here and now!
It's the High Wave!
The fist tsunami of the game's hitting Eyeshield 21!
How will Eyeshield 21 break through?!
It's an invincible barrier,
but I bet there's a way through!
There!
Max coolness!
It was a run force?!
Spider Illusion!
Sena's down!
That was a double-blocker!
Akaba!
All of the phrases are perfect.
Now we just need the right beat to make Sena sweat.
They're like great football-playing illusionists!
That was a fearsome double-blocker!
Even if he gets through Kakei's High Wave,
there's still Akaba's run force!
C'mon! Go, Sena!
Set, hut!
Go for it, Sena!
I can do it!
Spider Illusion!
Sweet!
- Die, small fry!
Moby Dick Anchor!
You go, Kakei!
Oh no!
Now it's Kakei?!
Just as I thought.
They're no longer a one-trick puppy.
Now there's no telling how they'll come at us.
No way!
They're a patchwork team,
so why're their combos synced together so perfectly?
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
Run away? Never!
We've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
What's brought you all the way out here...
...to Bando High, Kakei?
I'd like you, a former Eyeshield,
to give the current Eyeshield a little gift.
It's for Sena?
Yeah. Let's use a double-blocker on Deimon.
Deimon must be able to overcome that
if they're to defeat Shinryuji in the Kanto Tournament.
Sounds smart!
It's a pretty smart idea, actually.
I'm okay with it!
Since he bears the name of greatest high school football player,
we can't allow Sena to lose.
Let's go fight 'em all smart-like!
It's show time.
Deimon's going for a 40-yard field goal!
They did it!
- Yay! Go, Musashan!
- Yes!
Bando Spiders-Kyoshin Poseidons 0 - Deimon Devil Bats 3
We're three points in the lead!
- Boo-yah! We did it!
- Good going, Musashi!
- Sweet! Now we're cookin'!
Deimon, I won't let you win!
He made a score!
I'm too smart!
Good goin', Kotaro!
Bando Spiders-Kyoshin Poseidons 3 - Deimon Devil Bats 3
The Bando-Kyoshin Team's kicking prowess is amazing!
Plus, Akaba and Kakei's Double-Blocker
is holding Deimon's primary point-getter, Sena, at bay!
Talk about a tough game!
Geez!
What should we do?!
Hiruma!
Huh?
Please throw the ball to me.
I'm begging you!
We might be able to break through them
if we can complete a good pass.
- Yeah!
- Yep!
You're our only hope!
You're our master catcher, after all!
Then we'll try a pass or two, Butt-monkey!
Okay!
I'm everyone's last hope!
If I fumble the ball,
Deimon will lose and we won't be able to compete in the Kanto Tournament.
I'll definitely catch it!
Now!
W-What?!
Amazing!
Akaba, who was just in the front line,
is now back in the goal area!
Riko, you got too excited again and turned into your dad.
Oh, sorry about that!
But how...
...did Akaba get that far back?
I hope you haven't forgotten about the
ever rhythm-changing kaleidoscopic syncopation.
Darn it!
Are you okay, Monta?
No way...!
Deimon's offense has been rendered completely useless.
So your being a "master catcher" was nothing but talk.
Monta...
Darn it!
DARN IT!
Monta...
Monta, you're always telling everyone that you're a master catcher.
Huh?
And you're always telling me that I may be our ace runner,
but you're Deimon's ace catcher, Monta!
Ace... catcher?
That's right.
I made an oath...
...to Honjo!
I'm definitely going to become a master catcher!
You're right, Sena.
I've gotta give this game my all!
Now I'm really gonna let them have it!
I won't stop until Kakei and Akaba
tremble in fear before me!
Now you've got the idea, Butt-monkey!
Hiruma...?
There's no way we'll win
if you aren't the absolute best out there.
Yep!
Let's go, ladies!
Rip their heads off!
Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
Set, hut, hut!
We won't let you through!
I swear we'll stop you!
Got that right!
- Sena!
Nice try!
What?! You don't have the ball!
Ya-ha!
Akaba!
That won't work, Monta!
Kakei and Akaba may be impressive,
but I can't let them get in the way of my catching!
I'm the best catcher out there!
I'm a master catcher!
Monta!
- Catch it!
A tie?!
- Yay! Monta caught it!
Max Catch!
Monta!
Thanks, Sena.
You reminded me that the team's counting on me to lead the way.
W-What is it?
Not just you!
Don't forget...
...that we're helping...
...the team big time, too!
Yep!
Your max-right!
Max Catch!
Touchdown!
They won.
That was perfect.
Kakei!
You're such a jerk!
Monta!
At least, that's what I used to think.
But thanks to you, I've got a new dream!
I'm going to change that title from three best receivers in Kanto to four!
Yeah!
I hope you never forget how beautiful Deimon's melody is.
Right!
So they set it up so that we'd have to limit our offense to Monta.
They've helped him grow stronger.
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
The next death match is against the Taiyo Sphinx!
Hey, aren't we missing someone?
Yeah, you see-
Relax! He'll make it in time!
Of course he will!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: One Lineman Short!
Ya-ha!
I wanna hurry up and get better
so I can turn the Poseidons into an invincible team!
You sure ACT well enough.
I'm not gonna lose to you!
I, Ohira, am Kakei's number one pupil, after all!
What was that?! I'm his best pupil!
- Those three are idiots...
And I'll spin around better than anyone else!
I'm so smart-looking!
- Those five are idiots...