Hurry!
We're dead meat if we're late!
This is your fault for sleeping in!
Max apologies!
National High School Football Lottery
It's the National Championship Tournament Lottery!
How wonderful!
We're in the Kanto Tournament!
But Sena and Monta sure are late.
We shoulda given them a wake up call.
They've got until three, two, one...
...zero!
You'll pay for being late!
Ya-ha!
Our quarterback's nuts!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
The Ultimate Evil!
National High School Football Lottery
All of the super max powerful players are gathered here...
Sure are.
Everyone here won the regionals for their area.
Wow!
I'm amazed so many people are here
since this is just for the lottery!
That just shows how enthusiastic
everyone is over this tournament.
I-Isn't that...
...Banba from the T-Taiyo Sphinx?!
He's all banged up!
H-H-How'd he get so banged up?!
He went all-out with his training.
It's the High School Football Kanto Tournament!
We're about to begin the lottery
that will determine who plays against who!
First up is the Seibu Wild Gunmen!
Come, it's your moment of destiny!
At last!
Yep!
Number Two.
The Seibu Wild Gunmen will be Number Two on Block A!
Wild, Wild, Gunmen!
- They're so flashy.
And next up is the Ojo White Knights!
Ojo's up next!
Right!
The Kanto Tournament...
I'm finally going to play against Shin!
L!
It's not an "L."
It's "7!" Seven!
Quit making a fool of yourself!
Ojo's on the opposite block as Seibu,
placing in at No. 7, Block B!
Hmm...
Ojo and Seibu are on different blocks.
So we're up against one of them
no matter where we end up.
Sena, get on Block B so we'll be on opposite sides.
Riku?
Then Deimon and Seibu can face off in the finals!
I see.
I'll be going up against Riku and Shin
in the finals!
Sorry, but that's impossible.
Next up is Deimon Devil Bats, who won third place!
I-It's our turn!
Y-Yeah...
Well, go on, Sena!
Huh? You want me to?
But shouldn't someone else go...
We made it here thanks to you.
Hurry up and get going!
I'll do it! I'll do it! I'll do it!
Let's see... number Five...
Yay!
We're on opposite sides as Seibu
and we won't have to fight Ojo right off!
Yay!
Good going, Sena! You're sure lucky!
Yay! Yay!
Oh, stop!
So he showed up.
Coming in late is...
...last year's winners, the Shinryuji Nagas!
So those are Shinryuji's Kongo brothers...
They've won this tournament nine times straight!
So they're the Shinryuji Nagas,
the only team that's ever defeated Ojo.
Hey, Agon, that's him.
That's the Deimon Devil Bats player everyone's talking about.
Huh?
Oh, really?
So he's that annoying Eye-snot or whatever!
That shot should have hit him smack in the bull's eye...
He just barely dodged it...
...by moving an inch.
That punk! He's toast!
What was that noise?
What's going on?
The lottery ball slipped out of Yamabushi's hands
right after he drew it.
Right, buddy?
Uh, sure...
No way!
There's no way it just slipped!
He threw it at me!
You better watch yourselves.
It's time to announce the brackets!
In Block A of the All-Japan
High School Football Tournament we have
the invincible quick-draw,
shotgun-wielding Seibu Wild Gunmen
versus the ravenous claws and fierce teeth
of Hokkaido's speedy Misaki Wolves.
The biggest heavyweights in Kanto,
no, all of Japan, The Taiyo Sphinx
versus the ferocious and carnivorous
Hakushu Dinosaurs!
Next is Block B!
The infamous masters of defense
have returned with a fully restored fortress!
It's the Ojo White Knights
versus the ever-reckless, running-fanatics
of the Sado Strong Golems!
And last but not least,
it's the totally unpredictable
and aggressive Deimon Devil Bats
versus the invincible gods,
that may wind up champions for ten years in a row,
the Shinryuji Nagas!
What?!
But that means Deimon's very first opponent...
...is the team most likely to win the tournament.
The Shinryuji Nagas!
What's this feeling I have...?
My stomach's all tied up in knots!
This is the first time I've ever felt this way before...
We're definitely going to the Christmas Bowl!
Eyeshield 21!
I can do it!
C'mon, we've gotta win!
Eyeshield 21!
Wow, it's huge!
Y-Yeah...
It's more like a temple than a school.
According to Football Monthly...
Shinryuji is considered the best
at every kind of sport out there, not just football.
And they say that they've taken football
to a whole new level.
They may think of themselves as gods,
but they're nothing special.
It just means that they practice daily
on this ridiculously huge campus.
The chanting is part of a Buddhist Sutra.
Kanjizai bosatsu, gyojin hannya haramitsu taji...
It's freezing!
I swear a person could get hypothermia in this!
So Agon's late again?
He hasn't shown up yet, I think!
A pity since the Kyoshin Poseidons
are going to scrimmage with us today...
Agon? What are you doing?
Idiot! Get over here!
Don't yell in my ear, you punk.
I hear ya just fine!
I'm on my way!
Did you sleep in again?
What?! Agon, how dare you?!
You don't need me there
to sweep the floor with Kyoshin.
In fact, you're dead you if you beat them before I get there.
Lighten up! It was a joke, a joke!
Well, I'll be there as soon as I can.
Curse that wretch!
I'm sorry.
It's jammed pack even though this is just a practice game!
Y-Yeah...
Sorry, Sena, but...
Riku?
Everyone thinks that your gonna lose.
So we came to see what our future competition
is going to be like.
Don't worry.
They're just wasting their time watching these guys.
Yeah! WE'RE gonna win!
After we win I'll fight Shin in the finals.
And I'll fight Riku, too!
No, you can't!
W-What're they doing?!
The Shinryuji linemen are doing their
traditional pre-game meditation.
Try to startle them.
Yes, sir!
Hah!
Not bad.
Scary! He's so loud...
Yeah, he's really pumped up.
Hey, Sena!
Mizumachi!
Did you come to watch us?
Well, watch us closely,
'cause we're gonna defeat them in no time!
Poseidon!
- Go, splash, go!
With our great power,
we shall destroy our honorable foes.
We are the Shinryuji Nagas!
- Yeah!
- Splash!
- Roar!
Shinryuji Nagas vs. Kyoshin Poseidons
Who cares if you won nine tournaments?!
We're no pushovers!
Splash!
That's the Swim!
He's really impressive!
The Nagas' line's nothing!
Hah!
Mizumachi was knocked down so effortlessly!
He's really powerful!
He's the amazing man of steal,
the lineman Gondayu Yamabushi!
Back when we played against them,
he used that technique to send Otawara flying.
Otawara, flying?!
Hah!
K-Kobanzame, hurry and pass the ball!
R-Right!
That cornerback's fast!
Yeah, he's quick.
He can run 40 yards in 4.9 seconds.
So he's as fast as Ishimaru.
Oh, okay. So he isn't anything great.
I wasn't done talkin', twerps!
He runs 40 yards BACKWARDS in 4.9 seconds.
Cornerbacks are supposed to be able to run backwards.
They watch their opponents while going after the ball.
How can he run faster than us while going backwards?!
Ikkyu Hosokawa is considered the best receiver in Kanto
because of his backwards running.
Shinryuji sure is strong!
We need to change our plan of attack!
We're gonna have to do a blitz.
I-I was just about to suggest that, too!
Set!
I swear on behalf of the Poseidons,
we will not let them crush us!
Yep! Got that right!
Hut!
They're blitzing!
Sweet! They'll crush them!
I'll stop you!
Tranquil Reflections!
Tranquil Reflections
It's such a sharp throw
that it can slice the reflection of the moon right in half.
That right there is the ultimate pass
that gave Unsui his title as master QB.
It's Tranquil Reflections.
Tranquil Reflections...
They're too strong.
Now you've seen the Shinryuji Nagas.
But I don't see Mop Head around anywhere...
Man, we lost to the Shinryuji when Agon wasn't around, too...
So they're the Shinryuji...
Looks like I don't get to kill you after all.
Agon!
What are you doing?! You're late!
Shut up and quit yelling in my ears.
He's the other Kongo brother, Agon Kongo...
What are you doing?!
Go apologize to Coach Sendoda and everyone!
Just for the record,
if anyone else tries to pull this stunt,
I'll toss them under the waterfalls.
But I'll let Agon off the hook.
That's how things work when you're great.
You understand that, don't you, Unsui?
I do.
Well, it's not like I'm needed in a game against such a lame team.
Lame?!
Sounds interesting.
Let's just see which team's really lame!
I wouldn't.
Sure, whatever.
Hey, he said okay!
Training time! Training time!
Hurry up and get changed already!
I don't need to put on pads to fight a bunch of losers!
We can do that?
Then I don't need pads, either!
They're so heavy they slow me down.
Splash!
Wait, Agon!
Oh, shut up.
Quit yer whining, it's not broken.
I just dislocated it.
- Mizumachi!
What a big baby.
Tatoeba soba ni iru kimi ga
If it ever looks like
nanika de kuzuresou ni nattara
something's going to overwhelm you,
nanimo iwazu ni boku ga
I'll give my hand for you to hold
sotto te wo sashinoberu darou.
without saying a word.
Kono sora no shita de okoru kiseki wo
I want to see the miracles that unfold
zutto mitsumeteitai
beneath the starry sky.
mata chotto zure gimi no pinto
makes everything look just a little out of focus.
Mata sukoshi yume mitetai kara
'Cuz I've still got more dreams to dream
I even though I really love this moment ore ni totte
I, even though I really love this moment, to me
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid yubi saki made
you seem to be a sleepin' mermaid, from head to toe
stay with me tere warai ukabe
stay with me, smile and laugh for me,
tada soba ni itai dake
I just want to be with you.
Arifureta kotoba de shika
All I can manage to say right now
ima ienai kedo
are regular, everyday things
Ari no mama no sono subete ga
But even still, they represent everything
boku no kokoro wo tsutsumu
I feel in my heart.
Nagare yuku toki no naka de
As time marches ever onward,
donna mirai ga mieru?
what will the future hold?
Itsu datte bokutachi wa
Someday, we'll just have to trust
kibou de egaku ashita wo shinjite
that our hope will build a better tomorrow.
He defeated Mizumachi?!
I guess Agon's no push over after all!
We're up against the Kyoshin Poseidons
in our next death game!
I wonder if Mizumachi'll be okay?
He might be really bummed out!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Overcome Your "Fear!" Ya-ha!
Hah!
Everyone's in deep meditation!
It's way cool!
Hey, guys, they're freaking out!
Their team manager sure is hot when she's scared!
That other girl's kinda cute, too.
Goodness gracious.
I should have made this a co-ed high school.
Ikkyu, curse you!
Reflect on what you've done!
Huh? What'd I do?!