Distance to Las Vegas: 2000 km.
DEATH MARCH - DAY 1
~TEXAS~
We all kinda got into a ticket-ripping frenzy there...
So how do we get back to Japan in time for the fall tournament?
We walk to Japan.
Walk?
What about the Pacific?
We can earn all the money we'll need over on the west coast.
Oh, thank goodness.
We'll earn the money on the west coast?
You can't mean...
Las Vegas.
You don't EARN money there!
Okay, let's roll!
We've got 40 days to walk 2000 kilometers from Texas to Las Vegas.
Our ultimate training regimen is a trek across America!
THAT'S the death march?
It really is torture.
Dream on. That's not the half of it.
Remember, we're cramming a full year of training into 40 days.
This is a marathon combined with position-specific training.
Position-specific?
Ya-ha!
Square-in!
2000 kilometers of THAT?
Thank God we're linemen.
We don't have nearly enough gas to get all the way to the west coast.
You intending to leave the Devil Bat Rig behind?
Come on, push! We haven't moved an inch!
Sena, put this over your head.
We can't have you getting heatstroke!
Now, I've got to go buy some water.
Here's your training, Sena.
This?
I have to kick this stone?
Yes. You're going to run while kicking the stone.
If you can kick that stone all the way to the end without losing it,
not only will you conquer the fatal flaw in your running,
but your cuts will become so vicious,
even Shin won't be able to stop them.
So this is the death march?
So hot... So difficult...
But...
...everyone else will be getting stronger, too!
ONE toki wo koete
ONE passing through time
tokihanatta mihatenu yumetachi
freed from unfinished dreams
LOVE poketto no naka
LOVE inside my pocket.
marumeta chizu ima, hirogeyukou
I'm ready to unfurl my rolled-up map.
Kidou ni noseta kodou kimi ni todoketai
The beat drums on perfectly, and I want to show you
togireru koto no nai ai de sasaeatte
my unflinching, unwavering dedication.
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH ashita e mukai
I FIND BREAKTHROUGH, running towards tomorrow
yami wo kakete asayake wo ukete
racing against the darkness, bathing in the rising sun!
I'M JUST DREAMER komayoi nagara
I'M JUST DREAMER hanging out, goofing around.
mitsuketanda mamoru beki mono wo
I finally realized what I'm here to protect.
arata na hikari motome...
Searching for that new light,
Minds made up!
Woohoo!
These hot springs rule!
Mt. Fuji's so beautiful!
We've got new passports, we have time to relax... We've got it made!
Hey Panther, I've got some insider info.
Shin and the White Knights are doing their training camp up on Mt. Fuji right now!
Shin? The one they say is the greatest linebacker in Japanese history?
Yup.
Shin's out there...
You're really staying behind?
I've faced Eyeshield. Now I face Shin.
How can I leave when he's so close?
Besides... I can't be part of the Aliens anymore.
You gave me your word. You can never call yourself an Alien again.
Yes, sir.
That reminds me...
Before the game, he wagered that if we didn't win by ten points,
the NASA Aliens could never return to America... You think we'll be okay?
I'm changing our name!
From now on, we're the NASA Shuttles!
There, now we can go back to America without any problems.
NASA Aliens X / NASA Shuttles O
That's like... a little kid's trick.
Panther!
The NASA Shuttles need a running back...
I'll save the new #20 uniform for you if you want it.
M-Me?
NASA Shuttles #20? The running back?
I wanna join Leonard Apollo's team! I have to!
I'm gonna be a lot harder on you from now on...
You'd better be ready!
I will!
Get ready, Shin!
Shin, I've developed a special program tailored to you.
You're to remain on Mt. Fuji for the 40 days we have left until the fall tournament.
Yes.
Training in the summit's thin air will improve your cardiovascular health and lung capacity,
but reduce the effects of other exercise...
Therefore, you'll spend the daylight hours down here practicing with the rest of us.
In other words...
You'll be climbing up and down Mt. Fuji every day.
You can handle it.
Yes, sir.
Take this.
It's a GPS. Push that button.
It communicates with satellites to calculate your location.
The forest here is so dense that normal compasses won't work.
If you got lost, we'd never see you again.
Understood.
As long as you have that, you'll be fine.
I think...
I feel like I forgot something...
Something's wrong with the map.
Five minutes into his climb,
disaster befalls Seijuro Shin!
Ya-ha?
Deep post!
Running in this heat is brutal!
Fade to the corner!
What's the point of this?
I understand practicing pass routes...
Oops!
Don't get distracted!
I'm warning you...
You lose that stone and I'll make you start over.
Where'd it go?
Ah ha!
I don't know why I'm doing this but I only got 40 days to figure it out.
I can't quit!
If I can see Eyeshield's fatal flaw...
...then a real defense will mop the floor with him.
A flaw...
I WILL fix it!
A boar...
Hey, maybe...
Don't forget your GPS units!
And no one is to go off on their own!
Shouldn't we call the police?
If Shin's lost...
Let's search for him ourselves first.
I'm sure Shin is fine.
There are bears and wild boars up there, though.
Please don't talk about the scary parts!
BEAR!
What? A bear?
I'll clobber it!
It whooshed past us up in the treetops!
Wait...
Whooshed?
You must've seen something else.
Bah, even if it was a bear, we don't need to worry about Shin!
I bet he hasn't even noticed he's lost! He's probably working out!
You're not worried enough...
Wait a second...
Oh, no... I'm...
...throwing off my nutrient balance by only eating meat!
Shin!
Shin, I've been looking all over for you.
I'm here to take you on!
Football Clinic!
What do linebackers do?
They stop opponents from running up the middle!
And they fend off any and all tacklers who try to charge in! Ya-ha!
I-I-
Shoot, I'm so excited I can't speak!
Oh man, come on, hurry!
Um... Um...
I...
Wanna take you on...
Shin!
Ah, I understand.
I am hungry.
Please let me have.
Some of that boar.
Very well.
Shin!
Dunno why, but he gave me some, too.
Wow, so now you're the NASA Shuttles?
Yes. And I don't want to have any regrets once I put on the uniform.
So...
Shin, please, accept my challenge!
I've gone against Eyeshield. Now the only thing left for me to do...
...is face you, Shin!
I'm still training.
Shin?
I'll use this as a ball.
He's fast!
So that's the famous Zero-G running?
No...!
He got him with the Spear Tackle!
Game, set, match!
Are you okay?
He got the wind knocked out of him.
You can't get past me at your current level.
Why... Why not?
Your running is far too efficient.
Inefficient is better?
I see!
Shin can tell what the easiest route past him is.
Meaning he immediately knew which way Panther's highly efficient running style would take him.
I lost... You got me.
I assume you haven't played in any real games for a long time.
He could tell? Just from that? He's amazing!
I give up!
Giving up, eh?
What're YOU so proud about, Otawara?
Tell me one thing.
Can Eyeshield 21 beat you?
Its so hot! Are they going to be okay?
They'll start dropping like flies any minute now.
Place your bets before they open the paddock!
Who's gonna give out first?
Tough call.
Hmm... How about you?
There are so many cracks and bumps, I can't pick up any speed.
I'm barely making any progress...
Who's better, you or Eyeshield 21?
Shin is! Duh!
I agree.
I want to know what Shin thinks, too.
The moment you close in on him, he makes a completely unpredictable move.
But in order to make those superhuman cuts,
he's forced to come to a halt right in front of his opponent.
I always have to slow down to kick... My stride never seems to match up.
They're already that far ahead?!
I can't do this without losing speed!
But if he could somehow put on the brakes without losing any speed...
I have to catch up!
Another crack!
If he could do that, he'd become an unstoppable monster!
This feeling...
I didn't brake at all.
No, I must have, or I wouldn't have been able to kick the stone.
I stepped on the brake... without slowing down.
An unstoppable monster?
Kicking this rock's just like turning on the field.
I lose speed because I have to stop when I get to the critical point.
All right...
If I rush at full speed until the very last second...
And then...
Shorten my stride on the final step
and blast through on the next one!
Ouch...
It kills your knees... You need strong legs for this.
You're leaving?
Yup. Now that I know what's wrong with my running,
I wanna get home and start working on it right away.
Because now...
I've got the best coach in the world.
I'll save the new #20 uniform for you.
Goodbye!
Shin!
Eyeshield 21, Shin... The next time we meet,
neither of you will be able to figure me out so easily!
Higher... as high as I can go!
I'm fine.
If I train hard, I'll be fine.
That's what the death march is for!
I'll be waiting for you at the finals.
I WILL get stronger!
Death March - Day 1
Distance remaining to the west coast 1980 km
Naze jibun dake ga kizu tsuku to nageku
Why are you upset? Do you think you're the only one who hurts?
tada hito wa dare mo fuzoroina kakera
Because each and every one of us is just a single, splintered fragment.
Mirai wa kimatta basho bakari ja nai
Our future isn't a single place that all roads lead to...
Hikari ga sasu michi ga aru kara
The light will always illuminate new paths.
Blaze away ima blaze away sugu
Blaze away Go blaze away towards
Blaze away tobira no mukou e
Blaze away what lies beyond the door.
Saa toki wa umarekawaru
Our time will be born anew.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away dekiru koto ga aru
Blaze away you have a unique purpose.
Tatoe hitotsu shikanakutemo
Even if it's just one thing.
Blaze away ima blaze away ima
Blaze away right blaze away now
Blaze away kakenukete yukou
Blaze away dash straight through!
Kagi wa tokareteru sono te ni ima
You've opened the lock with your own hands.
The death march!
I figured it someone would break down soon, and look!
I've had more than enough of this!
We're going back to Japan!
Uh-oh, are the brothers gonna split up?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: Quitters? Ya-ha!
We should be getting back, too.
Hey, where are our GPS units?
They're broke!
Now we're all lost!
Someone help us!