Time to swap out a few parts!
It looks like the Blizzards have changed their lineup
for the second half!
Ivan's twin brother, Owain Ivanov!
Eyeshield 21 is running again!
Will they manage to stop Sena this time?
Screw Attack!
Sena!
Stretcher!
We need a stretcher!
Sena... It'll be all right!
Come on, Sena, can't you hear me?
Answer me!
Sena...
Wake up, Sena!
He's got a concussion...
He won't come to for a while.
B-But...
Without Sena...
What'd you think of Owain's Screw Attack?
Do you have a replacement part?
Looks like this is the end of the line.
What will you do without Eyeshield, Devil Bats?
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
Break Through the Blizzard!
With the loss of Eyeshield,
Deimon is in deep trouble!
What does this mean for the rest of the game!
Deimon can't get a first down.
Touchdown!
The Blizzards strike back with a touchdown!
The extra point is good,
and the Devil Bats' lead is cut to ten!
Sena...
Come on, Devil Bats!
The Blizzards score again!
Touchdown!
The Blizzards have turned this game around!
Oh no, it's only five minutes into the second half...
What's wrong with them?
Asia's team, the Deimon Devil Bats...
Are losing their grip on the championship!
This is ridiculous!
Get in there and rip the Blizzards apart, you bums!
And our analyst Riko has snapped
and reverted to an everyday fan!
Argh...
It took us the whole first half to get 17 points,
and they got 21 in no time at all!
And 14 of our points came from Eyeshield...
Without Eyeshield... I mean, Sena...
We're dead in the water, huh...?
We can't give up, guys!
We've still got lots of time.
Right, Hiruma?
Hiruma...
You all make me sick.
I thought winning your way into the Kanto Tournament
would've changed things,
but none of you have made any progress at all!
W-What're you saying?
Yeah, we cleared our Death Climb and everything!
We destroyed the Survivors!
Yeah, by putting the burden on Peewee's legs again.
There's no telling how the Tokyo Tournament will go down.
Our top guy might go down with an injury, just like now!
Are you just gonna make excuses?
"We only lost because he couldn't play."
R-Right!
If Sena... If Eyeshield can't play,
we need pick up the slack!
Fight together!
Yeah...
We're gonna win the Kanto Tournament
and play in the Christmas Bowl!
We can't let anyone throw us around!
We came here to win!
Y-Yeah, I kinda feel relaxed for the first time in a while...
Ah ha, his favorite phrase.
Everyone can just rely on my genius inst-
Just do your job.
- All right!
Everyone, listen up!
Show everyone what you learned on your Death Climbs!
- Ya-ha!
There... that's more like it.
I'm... I'm actually rooting for them...
Ah, the passion of youth.
They've become a good team.
Sena...
Here I come!
Belly Buck Tackle!
Both teams show excellent defense!
Neither side gives up any ground!
I've never seen such an amazing game!
A game and a martial art all rolled into one,
this is American Football!
Riko, you're turning into your father again.
- Eek!
- Such a mystery...
Sena...
You're so small...
But you've accomplished so much.
Don't worry.
Everyone's working hard in your place.
They're still playing their hearts out.
- Sena!
Mamori... Suzuna...
Oh yeah...
Is the game...?
We're losing...
Sena!
It's too soon!
She's right, Sena!
But... if I don't play...
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Tell us what's important in a wide receiver like Mon-Mon!
The key is "courage?"
A wide receiver needs the courage
to charge into enemy territory to catch the pass.
Put it all on the line and make the catch!
Ya-ha!
Speed!
Power!
Technique!
- Triple Team!
Refuse to lose!
Max Catch!
The brothers, Monta and Sena weren't the only ones!
We did the Death Climb, too!
Belly Buck Sandwich!
Everyone's really...
They're... fighting as one.
Individually, none of them
are a match for any of the Blizzards...
But... they're not going down!
We've got each other to rely on.
We fight as one!
That's right...
They aren't just parts in a machine...
The Devil Bats are a team,
with one mind, and one heart!
So don't just turn your back!
What... What have...
Ya...
Ha!
Go, Devil Bats!
- Go, Devil Bats!
This one's for you guys!
First down Deimon!
Everyone's...
Can you play?
Yes.
Sena!
Don't force yourself... you're still-
I'm okay, Suzuna, Mamori.
They've given me my strength back.
I can do it!
Get out there and cinch this one.
Sena...
Mamo.
Yeah.
- Go get 'em, Eyeshield!
Eyeshield, Eyeshield!
It's about time, Sena!
Eyeshield 21-
Is resurrected!
Look, the trademark pointless bowing.
Even clearing the Death Climb couldn't fix that, huh?
Finally awake, Peewee?
Yes.
Nothing to worry about...
We'll just knock him out with the Screw Attack again.
Put him down for the count this time!
We're low on time.
Break through the Screw Attack and get a touchdown!
- Yeah!
It's 21-17 with 1:21 to go!
Will Eyeshield's return turn the tide?
This will be the Devil Bats' last chance.
If they turn the ball over,
the Blizzards will run out the clock.
Set, hut...
- You can do it!
Hut...
Rush in... and run through!
Destroy them.
Hut...
Faster than any blizzard.
Hut!
Here we go!
Open up a path!
There!
Go! Don't stop for a second!
Just... focus on the goal!
Eyeshield 21 is flying!
Can he make it to the goal?!
Get him!
Owain and Ivan bear down on Eyeshield!
And once again, Owain disappears behind Ivan!
Can Eyeshield dodge them both this time?
I'll beat you!
Screw Attack!
Peewee! Smash the Screw Attack!
Dig in...
Yeah!
Sena!
Go, Eyeshield!
Touchdown!
A revived Eyeshield scores a comeback touchdown!
He did it... He did it!
The Deimon Devil Bats win 24-21!
- Yeah!
Yahoo!
You did it!
- All right!
He really did it!
That was awesome, Sena!
Coach...
You win.
I'll come back to the team.
However...
we'll no longer be the NASA Shuttles.
From now on, we're...
The NASA Aliens!
- You're going with the old name?
All right!
The NASA Aliens are back again!
Sena.
I owe you, again.
Homer...
We'll play each other again someday!
The Deimon Devil Bats vs. the NASA Aliens!
I can't wait!
You let that rag-tag team beat you?
Hey, it's me, Morgan.
I think I'll take that new coaching job you offered the other day.
An elite team needs an elite coach, right?
Wow, he sure knows how to recover from a setback.
You've changed my opinion of you... a bit.
What...
...do you mean?
He paid me a visit in my hotel...
"I'm invited?"
You really plan on beating the Blizzards?
What if I do?
Not in a million years.
Oh? Wanna bet?
He goaded me into coming so I'd reform the Shuttles.
- Hiruma!
There's more.
I believe there was another condition?
Do what you want.
So in the end,
Hiruma was the one who showed me the way...
The first-ever champions of the
international high school football tournament,
the Cream Puff Cup, are the Deimon Devil Bats!
Don't think you've earned a vacation.
The Kanto Tournament starts as soon as we get back!
Stay sharp!
- Yeah!
- Yeah
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Yay! We won the Cream Puff Cup!
Of course, there's no rest for the weary!
Time to start practicing for the Kanto Tournament!
Still, we've really been through a lot, haven't we?
Next time on Eyeshield 21: It's here! The Kanto Tournament! Ya-ha!
The grand prize is so awesome!
What...?
What is it?
Taa-daa!
A year's supply of cream puffs!
A year's supply?!
Well, that's what they named it after...
This might last ME a week, though...
M-Mamori...
She gets that look
whenever anyone mentions cream puffs...
By the way,
how'd we get first-class seats for the trip home?
Hmm...
Well...
If we win, you've gotta pay for Deimon's return flight.
First-class for everyone.
Now you know.
So scary...
He's the devil himself.