We might've gotten here a little too early.
Well, we have to play the winner of this game after the Scorpions,
so we have to grab the best seats!
They're freshmen too, but they're so tall!
Y-Yeah...
It's Habashira's team.
Ooh, arriving on bikes! Flashy.
Don't get too overconfident just because you beat Hashiratani,
or you'll get burned, kid.
Man, this dude's all fired up.
Cut it out, Mizumachi.
We'll settle this on the field.
Yep, it's almost time.
Let's go, Mizumachi.
B-Boy, you could cut the tension with a knife...
Yeah...
Kireigoto de katameta boku no
My defense is so full of holes,
suki darake no defense
nothing I do can cover it up.
Nani wo mamotteta no?
How was I supposed to protect anything?
Ukabarenai hibi wa
Let's just say these long boring days
yosou no hanninai to shiyou
are about what I expected.
Demo yume wa bokura no
But our dreams
souzou ijou no chikara de jimen wo keru
will kick up off the ground much harder than we imagined.
Tsugi no shunkan
And as the dirt gusts up
ano kaze wo hikitsukete fuwari to ukabun da
the wind will take me and carry me into the sky.
Kinou no kusari wa chigireteku
I'll break free from the chains of yesterday
Boku ga tonde misetara tsuzuitekureru ka na
If I keep trying to fly, will I eventually take flight?
Nigitta bukiyou na kono te mo
And pretend these clumsy hands of mine
tsubasa to shinjite
are really wings.
Clash! The Chameleons vs. the Poseidons!
Let's go, Rui Habashira!
Show 'em that the Zokugaku Chameleons are number one!
Knock 'em out!
Rui! Don't forget you're the great Tokage Habashira's brother!
Show 'em what that means!
What do you think of the Kyoshin Poseidons?
They're a completely different team from last year.
Agreed. They've become a team of big men.
But contrary to what you'd expect, they didn't sacrifice speed to do it.
No, they're even faster.
And their speed and power must seem staggering to their opponents.
Go, Zokugaku!
Yeah, if I had to root for someone, I'd pick Zokugaku.
Yeah.
They've helped us out of more than a few jams.
Yup!
Plus... this is Habashira's last shot at the Christmas Bowl, too.
I know you haven't forgotten that only ONE team here
will make it to the Christmas Bowl.
Right...
Listen up, men!
This is the last tournament for all the Zokugaku second years!
We don't get another chance!
If we beat Kyoshin, we get another shot at Deimon!
We'll get revenge! We'll tear them apart!
Yeah!
Remember how we tortured ourselves training this summer!
Remember how we worked until we puked up blood!
Yeah!
We WILL win!
Even if it kills us!
You got that, everyone?!
Yeah!
The Poseidons are awesome!
They really are giants!
Let's make this quick.
Don't get sloppy.
Remember, this is a tournament.
I know, I know.
You worry too much.
Anyway, as far as Zokugaku goes, Rui Habashira's the only one to worry about.
They can't handle our height.
They're huge!
Did Zokugaku's line...
- Were they always there?
- They're big.
The Chameleons change their colors to match their opponents.
Make 'em feel your power, Heavy.
Yikes, they switched to a big line...
Now we're talking.
They're trying to negate our height with strength.
What's the plan?
We've still got plenty of tournament left.
There's no need to play all our cards yet.
Yes!
Set, hut, hut!
Not too shabby!
There!
Go!
You cream puff!
Get it together!
That was close.
I'm getting pumped!
That linebacker is Shun Kakei... He's fast.
I told you not to get sloppy.
My bad, brah.
You're all right?
I told you, don't worry.
They're all brawn.
Wow... Check the nose steam.
Set, hut, hut!
I'm telling you, power alone's not gonna cut it!
Pass incomplete!
Again... He almost had it.
Yeah, but regardless, this is a good game!
Either one could win it!
Yeah!
I wonder.
To me, it seems to me like Zokugaku is desperately struggling
to stay competitive, while Kyoshin
still has confidence to spare.
Their chances aren't at zero yet, though.
What're you doing out there?
Put some effort into it!
If we get in trouble, we'll just beat 'em with our patented dirty moves!
Yeah!
C'mon, defense!
Huh?
Now Zokugaku's using its normal team!
What'd I say?
We change to match our opponents and the situation.
That's how the Chameleons play.
They gave up on power and switched to speed, I guess?
You guys don't look too speedy, though.
Say what?
You punk!
We'll have you barfing blood, beanpole!
Ooh, scary!
That does it-
Get in position, now.
R-Right...
That's why you're the boss.
You're intense, brah!
Set, hut!
Gotcha!
Zokugaku didn't spend its summer vacation goofing off!
Nice, he got him!
Yeah!
Zokugaku's back on track!
What'd you say, punk?
I said, everyone but your boss is a loser.
Who're you calling a loser?!
Penalty on Zokugaku!
A penalty flag?
He broke the rules...
10 yard penalty.
Shaddap, you old fart!
W-What?!
Knock it off, you boneheads!!
What's your problem?!
Get back.
Get back now!
Uh oh... Dissension in the ranks?
Forget them.
Cool and collected, as always.
All right, guys!
Don't drop the ball even if they tear your arms off!
Yeah!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
What do you wear under your uniform? Tell us!
The hint is "protector!"
You wear a full upper-body protector underneath your uniform.
Everyone get that? Ya-ha!
Set, hut hut!
Close.
That would've been a first down.
But Kyoshin is beginning to stifle them.
Why are we the only ones getting penalized?!
They're starting it!
Yeah! Why do you let them get away with it?!
Settle down, you three!
What was that?!
You're the worst excuse for a ref I've ever seen!
The deck's totally stacked against us!
For God's sake, will you three knock it off?!
But why?!
Why are you so...
I told you... We have to win this game, no matter what.
I won't let anyone mess this up, not even you three!
Y-You can't...
You think... we're messing this up?
Habashira...
Get out.
Get off the field!
What're they doing?!
This isn't the time for infighting!
Habashira...
Zokugaku's digging their own grave.
Mizumachi, we're going back to our original plan.
Aww, but I was really getting under their skin!
Scum like them, who don't take football seriously,
don't deserve to play even one second more than necessary!
We'll take our standard formation and obliterate them!
Geez, they made you mad, huh?
Well, that WAS our original plan.
Let's get this over with!
What kinda stance is that?
Is he nuts?
That's right!
I just remembered something the swim team told me.
Two years ago during a middle school swimming tournament,
a peerless swimmer exploded onto the scene
and disappeared just as quickly.
Kengo Mizumachi!
Set, hut, hut!
That's a super heavyweight block!
Take him down, Heavy!
In the 3rd lane, Mizumachi.
For the 50 meter freestyle...
The crawl!
Oh man! Heavy, his arm!
He's off!
Kyoshin's ball!
What did he...
For that move...
He used a crawl-like motion to work his arm past the opponent's head
while pushing his other hand on the armpit to knock him aside.
It's less about pushing with the arms,
and more about the height. It's a tall lineman's secret move...
The Swim!
Even Heavy couldn't stop him?!
Put a sock in it, the game's just started!
If we stop this drive we'll still be even!
C'mon, defense!
Yeah!
Set, hut hut!
If size doesn't work, we'll use speed!
Habashira's so fast!
His speed wasn't anywhere near that when we played!
I'll get you!
Get who?
What?!
Touchdown!
What happened?
What're you doing?!
The Poseidon's giant line isn't bulky like the Taiyo Sphinx,
but they've actually got speed.
The gap... is just too wide...
No, it doesn't matter!
Forget about the gap...
We can't lose this one!
Everyone, stay focused and...
Uh-uh-oh.
They look like they've had enough.
W-What're you doing?
Get back... Get into positions!
I-It's no use... Seriously...
Their skills... and their builds...
It feels like no matter what we try, we won't win...
What'd you say, you idiot?!
You don't know that unless you play to the end!
Remember what I said before the game?
This is our last shot at the Christmas Bowl!
Why did we spend a whole summer toiling away at training?!
We still have a chance!
Don't give up on Zokugaku!
Zokugaku can still do it!
Y-You guys, say something!
Say I'm right!
You wanna just let them destroy us?!
Habashira's team lost...
Forget them, our game's tomorrow!
Yeah.
Only one team can go to the Christmas Bowl...
Well, my dream of going to the Christmas Bowl is over.
You still had a chance...
The rest of your team gave up too early.
Where're you hiding?!
Why did you cream puffs give up before the end?!
Get out here!
My brother's class...
they're a bunch of fossils who still do nothing but scream about guts and might.
But...
The guys in my class are different.
If I had to pick two words to describe them,
they'd be "stupid" and "lazy."
The only thing guys like them understand...
...is force!
I had to control them with fear!
You did the same thing...
That's how you formed YOUR team...
But us... Ugh...
In the end, we fell apart.
I thought if we grew by playing football together,
and made it to the Christmas Bowl,
everyone around us would have to look at us in a new light.
But I couldn't bring them together.
You've been struggling by yourself all this time...
Rui, you idiot!
You... You should've had more faith in us!
Does this mean... I did something wrong?
Why? Why aren't your guys only playing because they're scared of you?
Why are you all striving for the Christmas Bowl together?!
What did you...
...do...
What did you do that I didn't?!
Goal mezashi
Zero in on your goal
eranda michi hashirinukou.
and charge down the path you've chosen.
Yowai jibun wo semeru yori
Instead of berating yourself for being weak
naritai jibun wo egaitemiru.
figure out what kind of person you want to be.
Hajime no ippo fumidasu yuuki
Work up the courage to take that first step
ashita no bokura kaeteyuku.
and we can change who we'll be tomorrow.
Nandomo tsumazuite wa
Constantly getting tripped up
ashiato furikaeru.
just ends up making you retrace your steps.
Okubyou na kono kimochi
Take that nervous, sick feeling
bane ni shite
and use it as your springboard
habatakou.
to take flight.
GOAL ni mukatte SPEED agetara
If you all turn towards the goal and start speeding up
kokoro wo hitotsu ni kake dasou.
your wills and spirits will unite as one.
Tomo ni tatakau nakama tachi to
And you and your friends, all together,
tsugi no tobira hirakou.
will open the next door.
Our next opponents are the Dokubari Scorpions!
Careful, they look like they play dirty!
And Hiruma's gone missing, too!
Those Dokubari punks... Have they managed to get to Hiruma?!
Next time on Eyeshield 21: The Fearsome, Venomous Scorpions!
Ya-ha.
Habashira, we...
We never even tried... to understand how you felt...
Habashira!
H-Habashira...?
We're...
...supposed to take over?