- Fire!
- Ya-ha!
I'll show you my pride!
I won't let anyone defeat me!
The Devil Bat Dive!
Deimon closes the gap to nine points!
Sanzan sora wo nottotte
Show no mercy and hijack the sky!
Gangan hoshi ni nokkatte
Ride those stars into the stratosphere!
Kaidan kette agattekou!
Stomp your way up the stairs!
"Dame nara dame da" sore de honmou?
"If we can't, we can't." You really mean that?
Nanka MY PACE sou ne MY NAME
You go at your own pace, you worry about your name,
Maji kattarii toki ni kattari
but you gotta keep winning even when you're wiped out.
Mada shimijimi sun na iki iki
So stop your sulking and move it!
Kibibiki ike misero iji
Psych yourself up and show 'em what you got!
Naitemo warattemo
Cry or laugh,
Toki wa tomattekunnai daro
time keeps ticking on.
Nakushite te ni irete
Win or lose,
Naa motomoto zero da ze icchou dou dai?
you started at zero. What's it matter?
Dandan harewataru
The sky will clear,
Asu ga aru akiramenantenai ze
and there's still tomorrow, so never quit!
Dondon susumeba ii
Just keep moving forward,
Utaeba ii sunao ni egao de
and sing whatever song's in your heart.
Dandan ashioto ga
The sound of your feet will ring out
Aoi sora hibike kaze ni nore
and the wind will carry it into that blue sky.
Dondon noboreba ii
So keep on climbing,
Kono semai sekai wo tobidase
and break past that narrow, little world!
Ah! Ah! Yume ni mukatte
Ah ah, reach for your dreams.
Ah! Ah! Koe dashiatte
Ah ah, sing out as one.
Ah! Ah! Kurushikanai ze!
Ah ah, nothing can hurt you!
NUMBER ONE mezashi hashitte
Aim to be number one!
A Demonic Counterattack.
Seibu Wild Gunmen 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
I did it, Riku.
Just like you told me!
What're you telling me for?
Well, I mean, you said...
Don't get excited from one little success.
Riku...
You think that was enough to put you on my level?
Deimon kicks off, and now it's Seibu on offense.
Kaitani speeds off!
He was already in a full sprint when he caught the ball!
Will he score another touchdown?
Attaboy, Riku! Bang-bang your way through!
Sena, I'll show you that you're still just a kid trying to catch me!
Wow, look at Kaitani change course!
W-What in tarnation is he doing?
He's headed straight for Eyeshield 21!
He's trying to get through me and score a touchdown!
Sena!
You little-! Stay outta my way!
Riku...?
Whoa there, ain't you getting a little too worked up there?
I'm fine.
Calm and collected.
Please, give me the ball.
I won't let Eyeshield 21 take me down.
Set, hut, hut!
Riku!
Sena! Stop me if you can!
He fumbled it?!
Oh no!
Holy cow, Kaitani fumbles and Eyeshield 21 recovers!
A huge turnover!
Touchdown!
Incredible! Eyeshield 21's famous legs propel him past the Gunmen!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 12
Seibu Wild Gunmen 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 18
Deimon shaves the lead to three points!
Argh...
What the heck was that?!
You didn't have your eye on the ball.
All you've been doing the last few plays is going after Eyeshield.
Start scoring some touchdowns!
Beating Eyeshield is the key to victory for Seibu.
That's a load of horse hockey!
Are you one to talk, Ushijima?
Those three are tossing you all over the place.
I'd say YOU need to focus more.
W-Wha-
Easy, easy, that's enough.
Kid...
Are you gonna tell me I'm wrong, too?
Hey, are they fighting?
Riku...
If you want to square off against Eyeshield, that's one thing,
but it's causing you to lose sight of everything else.
Go cool your heels on the bench for a bit.
You're not serious, are you, Kid?
Oh, I'm serious.
Me? On the bench?
Kid, do you even WANT to win?
Hey! Tetsuma?
Tetsuma...
What are you doing? Let me go, Tetsuma!
"Do I even want to win?"
He really told me, eh, Tetsuma?
What a quickdraw!
He's got this year's laser pistol tournament in the bag.
Well, he is Mushanokoji's son.
Someday soon you'll be competing at the Olympics like your father,
winning the rapid fire pistol competition.
Won't you, Shien?
Yes, dad.
Everyone expects a lot of you.
Nothing less than the gold will do your heritage justice.
Man, this is tough, huh?
But at least we get to play a little, Tetsuma.
This is way more fun than target practice!
I was just a kid who let his dad dictate his every move.
The first thing I ever did for myself was start playing football.
Practicing outside with Tetsuma...
...was the highlight of my life.
And it still is...
...even now.
It's 4th down for Seibu, and three yards to a 1st down!
It makes sense to go for the field goal at this point.
If it means we can keep playing football together,
even if it's just for one more game,
I'll keep winning.
Tetsuma, slant!
Up the middle, Peewees!
Oh, he drops back for a pass! It's a fake field goal!
Hiruma, Raimon, and Eyeshield rush to surround Tetsuma!
All right! Hiruma reacted just quickly enough!
He saw right through it, Kid...
Tetsuma's the ultimate receiver.
Yet Kid passes to the triple-teamed Tetsuma anyway!
Tetsuma knocks off his three defenders and scores a touchdown!
Yeah! Attaboy, Tetsuma!
Man, we totally saw it coming, too!
I can't believe he passed to him even though all three of us were there...
It just shows how confident he was...
This stinks.
Seibu Wild Gunmen 21 - Deimon Devil Bats 18
Seibu's kick is good, they extend their lead by seven!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 28 - Deimon Devil Bats 18
10 points... and we were just within three!
Hayato Arima's Football Clinic!
Teach us how to catch a low ball!
The hint is "pinkies!"
To catch a low pass,
put your pinky fingers together and clamp down on the ball.
Don't drop it!
Ya-ha!
I guarantee you they'll come at us with another Blast.
We can't let 'em open any holes!
If we close them down, we win!
Let's stomp 'em flat!
We're pioneers on the unsettled field!
Wild and tough!
Wonder if it'll be that easy....
Our Blast is the only card we can play right now.
Peewee, Fattycakes, you know what to do!
Yes!
Leave it to us, Hiruma!
A 10 point lead's nothing more than two touchdowns to us.
We ain't here to defeat our enemies.
We're here to murder 'em!
Rip their heads off! Ya-ha!
- Ya-ha!
We can do it...
We WILL do it!
Sena...
Set, hut!
Deimon sets off another Blast!
Can anyone out there stop Kurita?
Here they come!
Concentrate on the center!
They're tossed aside again!
Stop laying down!
Even Ushijima goes down!
What is this guy, some kinda mutant?
Deimon, eight yard gain!
Yay! Kuriton blew them up!
Deimon is close to a first down!
They could practically guarantee themselves a first down
if they do with a Devil Bat Dive...
But in football, even "practically guaranteed" plans can backfire.
What will Deimon do?
Set, hut!
Gimme a break,
the same move ain't gonna work forever!
Midair Dual Horn!
Ushijima leaps to knock Eyeshield out of the sky with a jumping lariat!
What?!
He doesn't have the ball!
Hiruma's got it!
Ya-ha!
I'll catch it this time!
Touchdown Deimon!
Hiruma's incredible pass finds its mark!
Wow, that pass was like a laser beam!
That's Hiruma's trademark.
The Devil Laser Bullet!
I don't believe it...
They were so close to a first down and they still went for broke...
Sena was a decoy?
He'll even use Eyeshield 21's trump card,
the Devil Bat Dive as bait if it gives him a shot at winning.
That's the kinda guy Hiruma is.
Good one!
Thanks!
28-24! Deimon closes in again!
Seibu... Deimon...
And Sena...
You're not getting through!
Everyone's trying to win for their team...
But I'm...
Why am I wasting time on the bench?!
The Devil Bat Ghost succeeds!
Deimon scores on the two-point conversion and pulls within two points!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 28 - Deimon Devil Bats 26
Devil Bats, Devil Bats!
Yep, you ARE Eyeshield 21!
Nice work.
Staying motivated enough
to crawl your way back from a 15 point deficit's no walk in the park.
- Ah, well...
Hey, I'm not some monkey that gets excited
when his opponent compliments him during a game!
No point gap ever gets to me!
You guys really wanna get... there, huh?
The Christmas Bowl?
What, you can't say it?
You're always playing the humble nice-guy act.
Hey, when you don't get your hopes up,
you don't get disappointed.
I knew it...
The first half went too well.
The way Deimon's staying in the fight is making the guys feel the pressure...
Two points...
How can the score be this close?
H-Huh?
I-I can't snap my helmet strap...
Ushijima, I'm sorry for acting like that.
R-Right...
I won't lose.
So please, give me the ball, Kid.
Sure, if you're ready.
Looks like we're gonna cap this thing off by running up the scores, huh?
It's was bound to happen sooner or later,
with these two powerhouse offenses.
Seibu's offense...
We have to stop it...
This drive!
9:30 left to play...
If we can't stop Seibu's shotgun,
Deimon has no chance!
Defense! Defense! Defense!
C-Copy.
Wow.
Set, hut, hut!
Yeah! That's Komusubi's super move, the Rip!
Kid!
Get him, Peewee!
Riku!
Sena!
I will stop you!
Come on and do it, if you can!
Let's go, Sena!
Touchdown!
Just as the gap closed,
the Seibu Wild Gunmen open the game up again!
Even Eyeshield 21 is shut down by Riku Kaitani's Rodeo Drive!
I couldn't see him...
I knew he was coming, but I couldn't block him.
By the time I noticed, it was too late!
Seibu Wild Gunmen 28 - Deimon Devil Bats 26
Seibu Wild Gunmen 34 - Deimon Devil Bats 26
Seibu is up by eight again!
That makes me 95 for 95.
You know, Sena...
Just beating you by myself isn't enough anymore.
I'm here to help my team beat yours!
I won't let you win, not even once!
Donna toki mo minna ga
I kept walking forward
sasaete kureta kara
without ever giving up
akiramezu ni aruite
and I stand here now
ima koko ni iru yo
because my friends supported me.
Ganbaroutte iinagara
Sometimes it's tough to say
honto wa kuyashii no mo
"let's all do our best."
onaji yume wo miteiru nara
But we understand one another
wakariaeru.
because we share the same dream.
Yorokobi ya kanashimi ga
When we share each others joys and pain
tsuujiaeru kokoro wa
our hearts create a power
hitori de wa tsukurenai
much greater than anything
kasaneta chikara.
we could ever achieve alone.
Hikari yori hayaku hashire
Run faster than the speed of light!
Zenryoku de yume wo tsukame
Grab hold of your dream with everything you've got!
Mirai e tsunagu kono shunkan
This is the moment that can change all of our futures,
Jibun dake no tame ja naku
not just yours alone!
Kaze yori tooku habatake
So fly farther than the wind,
Daichi yori tsuyoku mamore
defend harder than the land itself.
Shinjiaeru nakama ga ireba
If you have friends you can rely on,
mou nandatte kowakunai
there's nothing to fear!
Mayowazu fumidasu dake
Just plant your foot and push forward!
Whatever Riku did to cool off on the bench, it worked!
He's not messing around now!
Nine minutes to score nine points...
If I'm going to turn the tide,
I need to get past Riku!
Oh ho, Sena's serious too!
Next Time on Eyeshield 21: Lightspeed Pride! Ya-ha!
Way to go! That was incredible, Komusubi!
Actually...
What's incredible is Kuriton's face!
What's happening?
He's at his peak "fired up" level,
and proud of his pupil at the same time.
He needs to pick one.