You idiot!!!
You believed the enemy's words and lost the will to fight?!
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
Don't lose your composure!
Do not simply accept death.
If you are truly my aide, then keep your head.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to continue to rely on you to watch my back. Be prepared.
You have no right to talk, Colonel.
What kind of commander wanders out in a mission like that?
Shut up!
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow...
Besides, why am I in the same room as you?!
Aren't hospital rooms supposed to be singles with beautiful nurses?
You'll have to deal with it.
It's much easier for me to guard you two if you're recovering in the same room.
That's what's worrying me.
Why haven't they come to kill us?
Why?!
Why did you let the flame guy leave alive?!
He burned Lust to death!
Lust... died...
It's not too late! Go kill him!
Roy Mustang. We can use him.
Use? Don't tell me you're going to make him open the...
Worry not.
Father put me in charge of him.
Drawn by a landscape as white as snow,
真っ白な景色にいま誘われて
Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
I'm headed toward an unseen world.
僕は行くよ　まだ見ぬ世界へ
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
I've been traveling while lost
迷子のまま旅していた
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
Under this gray sky.
鼠色の空の下
Nezumiiro no sora no shita
Every day with new maps, stained with my many dreams.
日替わりの地図 いくつもの夢が滲んでいた
Higawari no chizu ikutsumo no yume ga nijindeita
I wonder if someday,
いつかはさ
Itsuka wa sa
Even with these tiny steps of mine,
ちっぽけな僕のこの歩幅でも
Chippoke na boku no kono hohaba demo
I'll be able to travel beyond those clouds.
あの雲の向こうまで行けるかな
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
I put on a bold front.
強がって
Tsuyogatte
End up hurting myself.
キズついた
Kizutsuita
I feel empty inside.
心透かしたように
Kokoro sukashita youni
It's started to rain,
降り出した
Furidashita
And the raindrops
雨粒たちが
Amatsubu tachi ga
Began to repeat their scattered reflections.
乱反射繰り返す
Ranhansha kurikaesu
These straight rays of light
真っ直ぐな光が
Massugu na hikari ga
Start to cross one another.
交差して
Kousa shite
And without telling anyone where they're headed,
行き先も告げぬまま
Yakusaki mo tsugenumama
Across the endless distances,
どこまでも
Doko made mo
They pass through all matter.
突き抜ける
Tsukinukeru
I burn these faint afterimages onto my eyes.
淡い残像　両目に焼きつけて
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakitsukete
Under this sky,
この空の下
Kono sora no shita
Wherever I am,
どんなとこにいても
Donna toko ni itemo
I should be able to reach
届くはずなんだ
Todoku hazu nanda
The unseen world.
まだ見ぬ世界へ
Mada minu sekai e
What if it's decomposed?
What?
My body on the other side of the gate hasn't taken in any nutrition!
Even if I was able to return to a body like that...
Brother! Winry!
Really, Ed?!
This is only hypothetical, but when we tried to transmute Mom,
we used our blood in the formula as information for her soul, right?
Yeah.
Then, we were both taken to
the other side and were decomposed.
I wonder if there's a possibility our minds were entangled during that process?
What do you mean?
I'm wondering if it's possible your body and I are connected in some way.
You know, for my age, I'm sh-
Sh...
Short...
He said it.
He was able to face reality.
So you're saying your growth is connected to how Al would have grown?
Sounds crazy to me.
It's not crazy!
You're short because you never drink milk.
This again?!
Of course!
Now that I think about it, Brother is always sleeping.
Could it be he's making up for my sleep, too?
Drink it!
I said, no!
Do it!
No!
It would be nice if that's the case.
Drink it!
No!
Paying the Colonel a visit?
Mr. Havoc is injured, too,
so we wanted to pay them a proper visit.
I'm not sure I would be here today
if the Colonel hadn't come to our rescue.
Is that why you're here, too, Sergeant Fuery?
Running some errands for the Lieutenant.
I've calculated the approximate distance to that large door...
...by counting the steps I took since entering Research Laboratory 3's basement.
The exact direction is unclear, so I drew a circle with the laboratory at the center, and...
Central headquarters?
And to top it off, this building is...
The Führer President's residence.
The Homunculi reside under there?
So there's a chance the Führer President has connections to them... eh?
If he does, then I wonder why he killed Greed and his crew?
He's still suspicious, even if he doesn't have ties to them.
He killed them all without even trying to extract information from them.
Führer President... He's mysterious.
Either way, the enemy has infiltrated pretty high up in the military command.
We ought to approach him with caution from now on.
Fullmetal. Take care of yourself.
Homunculus and the Führer President...
We were able to fish out something larger than expected.
I also have a feeling it's a bit too large...
It wouldn't be worthwhile otherwise.
Well, I have a lot of work for all of you.
Oh yeah, about that.
I won't be able to participate.
I can't... feel my legs.
I'm sorry.
Looks like an early retirement for me.
Yo.
Hey. Are you not feeling well?
Backache.
Coroners are always standing,
so it's a tough job for old guys like me.
I knew right away when I heard you were the one who killed her.
What are you up to?
So you declared that thing was Second Lieutenant Ross when you knew I was up to something?
War buddies are wonderful to have.
We're not war buddies; more like accomplices in crime.
You burned them up; I dissected them.
Ishbal was a giant experimental site.
If you keep taking risks like that, you'll get tit for tat.
Already done.
Did something happen?
My comrade...
...is paralyzed from the waist down due to a spinal injury.
And I just got permission to have one smoke a day, too...
Geez, isn't that just hilarious?
Getting stabbed by a woman and having to retire.
What are you going to do after you retire?
My family runs a general store.
I can at least help out by answering the phone.
Can't you get an automail?
They said it's not possible since the neural network for the entire lower half of my body is disconnected.
Retirement doesn't suit you one bit.
Colonel.
About Havoc's legs...
...here's some information I got from the Fullmetal boss.
Dr. Marcoh.
An alchemist well-versed in medicine.
The Philosopher's Stone?!
Would it be possible to have my vacation extended?
I permit it.
Go.
Ah, Major!
Are you back from your vacation, sir?
How was your trip to the east?
You can't tell anyone.
It was a nice place with lots of beauties.
I see...
Oh, right, Major.
This is from military police headquarters.
They want all the State Alchemists to know first.
This is...
How was it?
They let me in without objection when I told them I was a State Alchemist.
What about the entrance to the basement?
Wasn't there.
But there were traces of it being covered up with alchemy.
They're not so stupid as to leaving the entrance wide open.
I see.
I guess it's not possible for us to go
and meet the Homunculi from here.
They said something about not wanting me killed because I'm an important sacrifice.
They said that to me, too.
That I could become a sacrifice because I'd opened the gate.
My guess is that these sacrifices...
...are alchemists who are capable of opening the gate and returning.
What are they planning on doing by making us sacrifices?
I'll beat it out of them!
Edward!
Huh? Sergeant Brosh?
Good thing I found you!
Hey, what happened?
You ought to go back to the hotel immediately!
If you wish, I'll call for escorts!
A notification to the entire city from military police headquarters.
It seems Scar has appeared in Central once again.
Three casualties, all of whom are State Alchemists.
Several others wounded.
According to witnesses, he has a large cross-shaped scar on his forehead.
An Ishbalan with tattoos all over his right arm.
Tattoos... on his right arm!
Scar killed the Rockbells?!
It's not certain yet.
No way...
Brother, you can't tell Winry about this.
Like I could even if I wanted to.
I don't ever want to see her cry again.
Me neither.
I guess we'll have to face Scar again.
You're going to try to find out the truth?
That, too, but I have something else in mind.
We'll use him to lure out the Homunculi.
Huh?
They want to keep me alive.
So if I'm attacked by Scar and in danger...
They'll show themselves?
I don't think that's very likely...
But it's better than sitting around and doing nothing.
But we were defeated by him in an instant last time!
I'm sure we've... gotten a bit stronger-
And even if the Homunculi do show themselves, how do we catch them?!
Not only are they strong,
but they're pretty much invincible!
Invincible?!
Which means...
Immortality, correct?!
From the window again...
We'll lend you a hand with that mission.
What?
We're not interested in all the military troubles,
but if it's about Homunculi or immortality, we can talk.
Huh? Are you doubting us?
We're grateful you rescued Second Lieutenant Ross, but-
The more people by your side, the better, right?
We're serious, too.
The fate of an entire clan rests on me.
Fine.
You'd better not run off with the Homunculi.
We'll keep our promise! We owe you for a meal, after all.
A meal?
Room service?
This place has great food!
"A meal" my ass!
Shut up!!!
I need to get up early tomorrow,
but I can't sleep with all this noise!
Oh, that's right. So you're going back to Rush Valley tomo-
Wait, cancel the trip and stay in Central for a little longer.
What?
Well, you know. How should I put this?
My arm may break again, or more accurately... it's definitely going to break again...
You're planning to break it now?!
Oh no! Brother's soul!
Geez...
Don't do anything too dangerous, okay?
Doctor! Doctor!
Are you not in?
Dammit!
I see... Nice try, nonetheless.
A deadlock, huh...
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Who were they?
My mother and someone from the Department of Veteran Affairs.
I've completed the retirement procedures.
It hasn't been determined if you'll be able to recover, yet...
I'm not so stupid as to not understand I'm useless now.
But...
You don't need a chess piece that can't move, right?
You have no idea how pathetic of a look you have right now...
Leave me behind! Throw me away!
Do you have time to be worrying about an underling like me?!
Don't you have a promise to keep with Brigadier General Hughes?!
I don't need your sympathy!
Second Lieutenant Havoc!
Let me give it up.
I'm begging you...
All right.
I'll leave you behind.
I'll leave you behind, so you'd better catch up to me.
I'm going on ahead.
I'll be waiting for you at the top.
He didn't even abandon me;
someone who tried to accept death.
He told me he'd rely on me to watch his back.
He can't throw his men away.
He's an idiot...
There's no way he can reach the top of this country with a soft attitude like that...
I think it's better for everyone
if an idiot like that exists among us.
Bring my uniform.
You're in no condition to be discharged from the hospital...
Don't make me repeat myself.
Yes, sir.
Look at what you've done!
I-I'm sorry!
I guess we have to close down for today!
Looks like you guys are in trouble!
State Alchemist, Edward Elric, to the rescue!
That was amazing, kid!
Thank you so much! How much should I pay you?
Pay?
There's absolutely no need for that!
I broke a precious jar. Could I ask you to fix it?
No problem at all!
Edward Elric!
I'm Edward Elric, your city's State Alchemist!
This, too!
Please fix it!
The whole city is talking about me.
With that flashiness, it's no surprise.
I wouldn't have expected things like this from you, Fullmetal.
Colonel?!
You're well enough to leave the hospital already?
I guess.
I heard about Second Lieutenant Havoc.
If you ask Dr. Marcoh, he can probably...
Hold that thought.
We're in public.
Get in.
On second thought, get out...
Dr. Marcoh is missing?!
He was probably abducted by them.
By the way, Fullmetal.
You've heard about Scar, right?
Why are you doing things that will just catch his eye?
I want him to find me.
I need to fight him again.
Don't be stupid!
Did you forget what happened to you in East City?!
Oh my! Afraid of Scar now, are we?
You were pretty much useless
last time, if I remember correctly!
Don't underestimate me! The weather's fine today!
On top of that, you're exhausted!
You really are useless, aren't you?!
Shut up!
Now look! He's here!
What's wrong? It's not even raining, but you look pretty drenched.
Hang on, Lieutenant!
Don't shoot.
What are you saying?!
I just thought I'd try fishing like the Colonel likes to.
We're going to drag out the Homunculi, using Brother as bait!
Since Brother is an important sacrifice and they want him alive!
This is reckless...
We don't want any more casualties!
So either me or Brother have to be the bait!
What if Scar gets shot to death by the
military police before the Homunculi come out?
You can take care of that, right, Colonel?
Ordering me about now, are we?
You've got some guts.
If you do capture the Homunculi, give me a crack at them!
Roger!
Sergeant Fuery's second home is nearby.
Let's go!
Roger.
It's begun.
You two! Please back away!
Don't shoot! You'll hit Brother!
Dammit... if Scar gets shot, it's all over!
Not being too close or too far is a pain!
When are you going to get here, Homunculus?!
The channel for the military police headquarters is...
Got it.
Nothing less to be expected from Fuery.
3rd District Military police unit reporting.
We are currently fighting Scar.
Requesting reinforcements immediately!
Y-You! What... are you doing?!
All right, the 17th district next.
This is getting kind of fun.
This is-
What the hell is going on?!
Scar is in the 17th district, too?!
Then what was with the 3rd district?!
Colonel Douglas! He's shown himself in 8th district, as well!
What?!
This is the Central military police headquarters, reporting to the 8th district.
Scar and a boy are engaged in combat!
The boy is a State Alchemist.
Do not shoot.
There are false reports all over the place!
A fourth Scar?! What the hell?!
This is the 3rd district! Everything is in order!
This is the 8th district! We've found Scar! Requesting reinforcements immediately!
Gluttony.
I can smell it. I can smell him!
The scent of that Ishbalan!
I sense something... Did you, Ran Fan?
Yes.
All right, let's go!
Which is he after?!
Human destruction or my automail?!
Brother!
I got lucky...
He canceled out the decomposition energy?!
So reckless...
Tattoos on his right arm!
Bastard...
So it was you!
I can smell it. I can smell him!
Hey, how's it going?
You have a strange interior.
How many people do you have inside you?
Who?
There's no point in trying to run.
I can sense your distinct aura from a mile away!
Enemy? Enemy?
Can I eat you?
As I thought!
A Homunculus!
Oh? You can sense us?
A troublesome ability.
I'll eliminate you!
Ran Fan!
Run!
Ran Fan!!!
Let it all out, Let it all out
I don't have to act tough, right?
強がらなくていいんだね
Tsuyogaranakute iindane
The scribbling someone made...
誰かが描いてった
Dareka ga kaitetta
On the wall, of a flower is swaying.
壁の落書きの花が　揺れる
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
No one knows their true selves.
自分らしさなんて, 誰もわからないよ
Jibunrashisa nante dermo wakaranaiyo
Even though we both lose and gain
長い長い道の途中で
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu de
By embarking on this long, long path,
失くしたり, 拾ったり,
Nakushitari hirottari
And though there may be days loneliness strikes and makes us weep...
急に寂しくなって, 泣いちゃう日もあるけど
Kyuu ni samishikunatte naichau hi mo arukedo
Let's transform our tears and pains to stars.
涙も　痛みも　星に変えよう
Namida mo itami mo hoshi ni kaeyou
Let's light a candle to illuminate our tomorrow.
明日を照らす　灯りをともそう
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
And we'll hold our small hands over the fire to create stardust,
小さな手かざして　ふたりで作ろう
Chiisana te kazashite futari de tsukurou
And an eternity that shines so brilliantly.
星屑を　強く光る永遠を探そう
Hoshikuzu wo tsuyoku hikaru eien wo
Farewells may be unavoidable,
さよなら　いつかは来るかもしれない
Sayonara itsuka wa kurukamoshirenai
Yet the seasons continue to change obliviously.
季節はそれでも巡り巡ってく
Kisetsu wa soredemo meguri megutteku
Even if I lose myself, I'll continue to walk...
小さく迷っても　歩いてく
Chiisaku mayottemo aruiteku
Walk by your side.
君と歩いてく
Kimi to aruiteku
That's the only thing I'd like to never change.
それだけは変わらないでいようね
Sore dake wa kawaranaideiyoune
The shriek of the hurt girl echoes throughout Central.
When the trampling force meets his past again,
memories of violence are awakened.
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Episode 22, Backs in the Distance.
"I want to protect her."
That was the thought in the boy's mind.