Drawn by a landscape as white as snow,
真っ白な景色にいま誘われて
Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
I'm headed toward an unseen world.
僕は行くよ　まだ見ぬ世界へ
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
I've been traveling while lost
迷子のまま旅していた
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
Under this gray sky.
鼠色の空の下
Nezumiiro no sora no shita
Every day with new maps, stained with my many dreams.
日替わりの地図 いくつもの夢が滲んでいた
Higawari no chizu ikutsumo no yume ga nijindeita
I wonder if someday,
いつかはさ
Itsuka wa sa
Even with these tiny steps of mine,
ちっぽけな僕のこの歩幅でも
Chippoke na boku no kono hohaba demo
I'll be able to travel beyond those clouds.
あの雲の向こうまで行けるかな
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
I put on a bold front.
強がって
Tsuyogatte
End up hurting myself.
キズついた
Kizutsuita
I feel empty inside.
心透かしたように
Kokoro sukashita youni
It's started to rain,
降り出した
Furidashita
And the raindrops
雨粒たちが
Amatsubu tachi ga
Began to repeat their scattered reflections.
乱反射繰り返す
Ranhansha kurikaesu
These straight rays of light
真っ直ぐな光が
Massugu na hikari ga
Start to cross one another.
交差して
Kousa shite
And without telling anyone where they're headed,
行き先も告げぬまま
Yakusaki mo tsugenumama
Across the endless distances,
どこまでも
Doko made mo
They pass through all matter.
突き抜ける
Tsukinukeru
I burn these faint afterimages onto my eyes.
淡い残像　両目に焼きつけて
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakitsukete
Under this sky,
この空の下
Kono sora no shita
Wherever I am,
どんなとこにいても
Donna toko ni itemo
I should be able to reach
届くはずなんだ
Todoku hazu nanda
The unseen world.
まだ見ぬ世界へ
Mada minu sekai e
Geez, you still haven't had a bite?
You're an important human sacrifice candidate.
We need you to stay healthy.
Are you listening, Doctor Marcoh?
I've been thinking for some time...
...as to what you mean by "human sacrifice"...
...and about what you are trying to make me do...
What you are trying to do right now...
...is to create a giant transmutation circle, using this country and its people.
And the purpose of that...
...is to create a philosopher's stone. Am I right?
You're close. On the right track, at least.
On the right track?
So, what are you going to do?
If you're not going to help us out, we'll destroy that village.
I heard from Lust.
You'll lend us a hand as long as we promise to leave that village alone, right?
What are you going to do?
Will you help us out and kill everyone in this country?
Or will you refuse and let everyone in that village die?
Such a fool.
By sacrificing something minor,
you'd be able to save something major.
It's a simple concept if you just think about it.
Well, I guess that's what makes you guys human.
Emotion always gets in the way of logic.
It was the same way with that guy I killed.
When I transformed into his wife, he couldn't fight back and lost his chance to get me.
It's really helpful to us that you humans are so vulnerable.
Seems to me you're really struggling against these humans,
Wrath.
To let Scar get away and even have Gluttony captured is unlike you.
Yes, you're right.
You look happy.
I won't deny that.
I'm having fun.
I've lived for sixty years, and now, I stand at the top of this country.
All according to Father's plan.
However...
Colonel Mustang, the Elric brothers,
and the ones who come from a foreign land.
We, the wise ones, are being thrown into complete disarray.
It may just be it's almost time for the young ones to take over the generation, Pride.
Wrath, you've interacted with humans for far too long.
That may be true.
I want you to remember what exactly we are.
I won't report to Father that earlier statement, which could be interpreted as treachery.
More importantly, we need to rescue Gluttony.
There's no need to worry about that.
I have a vague idea of their location based on information I received from the military police.
What is this...
Colonel! Where are you?!
Stop! Lieutenant!
Colonel!
Lieutenant...
Don't provoke him!
He's only after me!
Mustang!!!
Lan Fan! We're getting out of here!
What... happened?
The monster was keeping another monster inside its belly!
It swallowed everything around him!
So even something like this is created...
...by alchemy...
There's no other choice. I'll have to kill him.
W-Wait, we were finally able to capture a Homunculus!
Staying alive is more important.
Also, he knows our names and our appearances.
There's no reason to let him go alive!
He swallowed...
...the fire?
You really are useless, aren't you?!
Then why don't you try to do something about it?!
More like, stop following us! He's only after you, Colonel!
Run into the bushes! Spread out!
Dammit... talk about bad timing...
Hurry up, kid!
Hurry! There's no reason to stay here any longer!
But Ed and the others are still...
Not my problem!
I'm just a civilian.
Getting dragged into some ridiculous battle like this and dying doesn't sound too great to me!
Dammit!
What's taking them so long?!
Roy Mustang!!!
No!!!
Sounds like he fell for the dummy.
He doesn't seem too happy about it either.
Come on, hurry up and go home,
Mr. Useless.
Lieutenant, you're on this side.
Please take care of Lan Fan.
Are you telling me to shamelessly run away in this situation?!
You'll just get in the way!
Please, just leave!
You're really not helping at all, Colonel.
Seriously, this stupid Colonel...
Just do your own job.
The fact that the highest ranked man in this country is a Homunculus isn't exactly a problem you can brush aside.
The highest ranked man...
You don't mean, Führer President Bradley?!
We can talk about this later.
Hop in!
Looks like there aren't any more empty seats.
Just go ahead without us.
You idiot!
There's no way we can just abandon you kids on the battlefield!
Your opponent is the upper echelon of the army, right?
We have to beat some information out of that Gluttony guy.
We're going to stay here and fight him.
It doesn't matter that we're kids.
We're the ones who came up with this, anyway.
Thanks for lending us a hand up until now.
Edward.
Take this with you.
You know how to use it, right?
That's something used for killing people.
It's something to protect your lives with.
Your hands aren't meant for killing people.
Please don't die.
I'll be borrowing this.
Please, take care of Lan Fan.
Young master...
Young master!
Let's go.
Go!
Damn those brats!
Those are the types that end up dying early!
Mustang...
Where is Roy Mustang?!
How dare you kill Lust...
I won't forgive you!!!
I said we'd fight him, but he's kind of scary.
He's like a whole new person now...
How are we supposed to capture him?
What's wrong?
A dog?
Stop, Gluttony.
I-It talked?!
Hey, it's been a while.
Fullmetal runt.
Who are you calling a flea-sized runt?!
Calm down! I just came to pick up Gluttony!
I have no intentions of fighting mister runt--
Seventh time!
What are you talking about?!
Twice just now, and fives times back at Research Laboratory 5.
All told, you've called me a runt seven times!
Don't tell me you forgot!
You've got such a good memory...
Wait!
Giving me so much trouble...
I saw Mustang!
The one who killed Lust!
I'm going to swallow him! Swallow him all up!
You can't do that to the Colonel.
Not to the Elric brothers, either.
No!
I felt it earlier, but...
How many people do you have inside of you, Homunculus?!
So you're the kid who crossed swords with Wrath.
What do you mean by "kid"?!
I'm the 12th Prince of the Xing Dynasty.
My name is...
You can swallow him, though.
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
I see...
Looks like you can't do anything to us.
In that case...
Lin, we'll leave him to you!
Fine.
Show it to me, then.
Your skills that were enough to challenge Wrath.
Oh, really now?
He got the highest grade in his class.
On the essay he wrote about you.
Umm... do you mind if I read it here?
Not at the dinner table, dear.
Come on, what's wrong?
Let's hear it.
Okay!
My father is the Führer President of Amestris.
He works hard every day for this country.
He's always thinking about his people.
He's constantly trying to find solutions to problems so that everyone can live in peace.
But no matter how busy he is,
he has never forgotten that he has a family.
He loves me and my mother.
My father always listens to me.
He always respects my wishes.
I love my father and everything about him.
Thank you, Selim.
Not bad.
Thank you for the compliment!
You fell for it!
What do you think?
It's something you humans can't do, isn't it?
Now... do you want to be strangled to death?
Or bitten to death...
Or cut to death?
Actually...
You're cheap, kicking dirt into my eyes...
There have been many assassination attempts on me, ever since I was little.
I've had to learn a few cheap tricks of my own.
What do you say? Can't you just give up and turn yourself in?
I just want information about immortality.
You don't want to get hurt, do you?
You little shit!
You're just a human! Don't be looking down on me!
Don't underestimate humans, Homunculus!
Okay! Got him!
That was dangerous, geez...
Dammit, you...
I'm not allowed to eat you guys!
I want to eat that guy with the thin eyes!
Got him!
Hey now, don't be interfering with--
You're a human, after all.
Now, Gluttony!
Lin!
What?!
Dammit! I can't let him swallow human sacrifices!
Brother!
I swallowed them.
Brother! Lin!
Hey, spit him out! Spit out my brother!
I can't. I swallowed them.
No way...
You're fine, right, Brother?
I've got the rooms my wife and kids used to live in, but if I have too many lights on, the neighbors will get suspicious.
You're going to have to sleep in my bed.
I... I have to go to the young master...
Moron!
What can you do in that state?!
He still hasn't returned yet?
Got it.
Then I'll be on my way to Headquarters.
Yes. Thank you.
We're going.
Roger.
To where?
I need to find out who's on our side and who's not.
Geez, the whole lot of you...
You're still going to push yourself,
even though your wound hasn't healed yet?
The Führer President might be a Homunculus.
I can't just sit around.
Also...
We just left some kids on the battlefield.
I'll be setting a bad example as
an adult if I don't take action now!
What's so funny?
Nothing.
I was just thinking about how mad Edward would be if he knew you were treating him like a child.
I was just repeating your words, you know.
But still, I'm amazed.
I would have never expected you to take such a bold step.
It isn't bold at all.
I'm just trying to clear the field.
Also...
Have a lot of people who understand and are willing to support you.
It's a little late, but I'm going to take his advice.
This could either be the gates of glory or an entrance to a den of evil...
You wait here, Lieutenant.
If something happens to me, I want you to get out of here.
I refuse.
This is an order.
I cannot comply.
You're quite the stubborn one...
You should know that by now.
Fine.
I'll definitely come back, so wait for me here.
Yes, sir! Good luck!
So you're Roy Mustang, eh?
I got a call from my wife earlier.
Lieutenant General Raven! I deeply apologize for not coming to introduce myself to you due to duties.
Also, I'm terribly sorry for visiting you at this hour!
I don't mind.
How's the old geezer Grumman doing these days?
He's doing fine.
Check.
I'm beat.
That's eleven losses in a row.
Make that twelve.
Well, I guess you put up a good fight this round.
You started to lose your touch right after you started to think you had a chance.
So you're saying I let up?
That's right. You're not able to become heartless.
Just like Raven.
General Raven...
From Central?
He's exceptional, but very soft-hearted.
There was a case where he ran in to rescue one of his men, who was injured, and ended up disrupting his formation.
If he's like that, he'll need a lot of men on his side.
W-What an insult!
I was employed at Central because of the way I treat my men!
A geezer out on the frontier has no right to say that about me!
M-My apologies...
Please don't let it get to you.
Also, seeing how you got angry at this,
you must be a man of justice.
Lieutenant General Grumman told me I should go to you in times of trouble.
So that sly dog one-upped me again, huh...
Oh, it's almost time for the meeting.
I'll accompany you.
Have you gotten used to Central?
Not quite. I'm trying to bring myself to talk with the people more, but...
They've got rumors flying around all over the place, don't they?
But most of those rumors are nonsensical.
Something about Scar feeding a cat, immortal beings, and...
...something about the Führer President being a Homunculus.
You don't have a great sense of humor, do you?
Did you really work under Grumman?
I guess I didn't pick that up from him.
Well, even gossip like that may end up entertaining everyone.
Huh? Am I really allowed to...
So, about that earlier joke...
About the Führer President being a Homunculus...
I'd like you to continue.
What's the matter, Colonel Mustang?
What about me being a Homunculus?
Is there a problem?
Oh, now I get it, Hughes...
When you said that the army was in danger...
...you didn't mean a crisis was approaching the army...
You meant that the army itself was in a crisis.
Fullmetal.
Looks like I've arrived at the depths of hell.
Where am I...
Blood?
What?
What is this place?
Al!
Hey, isn't anyone here?!
Where the hell am I?!
Let it all out, Let it all out
I don't have to act tough, right?
強がらなくていいんだね
Tsuyogaranakute iindane
The scribbling someone made...
誰かが描いてった
Dareka ga kaitetta
On the wall, of a flower is swaying.
壁の落書きの花が　揺れる
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
No one knows their true selves.
自分らしさなんて, 誰もわからないよ
Jibunrashisa nante dermo wakaranaiyo
Even though we both lose and gain
長い長い道の途中で
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu de
By embarking on this long, long path,
失くしたり, 拾ったり,
Nakushitari hirottari
And though there may be days loneliness strikes and makes us weep...
急に寂しくなって, 泣いちゃう日もあるけど
Kyuu ni samishikunatte naichau hi mo arukedo
Let's transform our tears and pains to stars.
涙も　痛みも　星に変えよう
Namida mo itami mo hoshi ni kaeyou
Let's light a candle to illuminate our tomorrow.
明日を照らす　灯りをともそう
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
And we'll hold our small hands over the fire to create stardust,
小さな手かざして　ふたりで作ろう
Chiisana te kazashite futari de tsukurou
And an eternity that shines so brilliantly.
星屑を　強く光る永遠を探そう
Hoshikuzu wo tsuyoku hikaru eien wo
Farewells may be unavoidable,
さよなら　いつかは来るかもしれない
Sayonara itsuka wa kurukamoshirenai
Yet the seasons continue to change obliviously.
季節はそれでも巡り巡ってく
Kisetsu wa soredemo meguri megutteku
Even if I lose myself, I'll continue to walk...
小さく迷っても　歩いてく
Chiisaku mayottemo aruiteku
Walk by your side.
君と歩いてく
Kimi to aruiteku
That's the only thing I'd like to never change.
それだけは変わらないでいようね
Sore dake wa kawaranaideiyoune
Do people search for the lost because they fear being alone?
But even if he can't see them, he won't give up.
Because he believes.
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Episode 25, Doorway of Darkness.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at this figure.