I'm back, Gramps!
Is the bath water hot?
I have to hurry or I'll be late!
Is it so serious that she
can't have visitors?
That voice...
Yes... Kagome is laid
up in bed.
I see.
Err... This is a hot compress
for Kagome...
Oh, you're so thoughtful!
My... I mean, her neuralgia
will get much better with this.
I'll be going then.
Okay, take care.
Who has neuralgia?
Oh, Kagome!
Be happy!
You're supposed to be disposed today,
so you can miss school.
What are you saying?!
I WANT to go to school desperately!
You're a strange one.
Only my family knows of my
jaunts through the hidden well...
into the Feudal States Era.
Besides, I doubt that anyone else
would believe me if I told them.
Huh? You're going to take the
math supplement course, too?
Teacher told me to.
We're used to it, but it's a shock
to hear that you need it, too.
The high school Hojo is applying to
is very difficult to get into.
What? Don't tell me you're
seeing Hojo, Kagome?!
Stop it! Who has time to
go out with boys?!
That's not something
you want to brag about.
Err... Well...
Gee, I don't even know if
I'll be able to get into high school!
Not with a life like this!
Oh, look!
Fireworks!
So pretty!
It looks like fun!
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha! Serves them right!
That girl!
Hold it!
What did you do that for?!
You... You can see me?
Who is this girl?
Where're her shoes?
And a down jacket...
when it's almost summer?
Let's go apologize.
I'll go with you.
None of your business!
What's the matter, Kagome?
Who were you talking to?
Huh?!
Gone... Who was she?
Myoga, isn't it finished?
Not yet.
Master Inuyasha, if you go out now,
you'll be stung to death.
That sheathe was cracked
battling the Thunder Brothers.
Let the steel wasps repair it
with their special wax.
Dang it... It's boring!
Shut up!
I came along because I thought
Kagome would be here!
Why must I be stuck
alone with you?!
That's my line!
Arghh... Why am I alone
with you?!
Hah!
Don't I count at all?
Huh?
That's...
A goblin!
Shippo... So are you!
That's the Soul Piper.
It was born from the souls
of departed children.
When a child dies, the Soul Piper
plays with that child...
until the soul is able to
rest in peace.
As long as its eyes are closed,
it's a peaceful demon.
What?! Not when I've come
back to this world!
Jeepers! Why do I have to
accompany you...
to visit YOUR friend
in the hospital?!
Because the hospital's in
the next town...
and Mom's too busy to
take me today.
Cripes! Everyone's interfering
with my studies!
Sis...
What?
Is there such a thing
as an evil spirit?
Huh?
Sota, thank you for coming
so often.
Aunty, how is Satoru?
Physically, he's healed.
But he's still unconscious.
Here...
Thank you so much for
worrying about Satoru.
Burn scars?
Oh these...
I got them from the fire
six months ago.
Oh, I'm sorry!
That's how Satoru...
Huh?!
The girl at the park...!
She disappeared!
Again... Why must this happen?
Who is she anyway?
I can't ignore this.
Darn, foiled again!
You mentioned an evil spirit.
What did you mean, Sota?
I thought maybe an evil spirit
was after Satoru...
Satoru has been in a coma
since the fire six months ago.
At first, all my classmates went
to visit him at the hospital.
But...
weird things happened
on their way home...
like falling down the stairs...
or barely missing getting hit
by a car...
After these things kept happening,
the kids stayed away.
In that fire six months ago,
she died...
Satoru's older sister.
Her name was Mayu.
- Is that the place?
- Uh-huh...
Whenever they tried to
clean up after the fire...
an accident would happen.
So it's been like that
for six months now.
Watch out!
I knew it!
There is an evil spirit!?
Sota!
Huh?!
Watch out!
Stupid!
I'm already dead.
You're Mayu, aren't you?
Why do you do
these things?
Aren't you Satoru's sister?
Satoru, hah! I'll kill him!
Mom hated me!
That's why she abandoned me!
She never wanted me!
Mayu... She seems so nice.
Don't make her unhappy anymore.
Be quiet!
If you keep interfering,
I'll kill you, too!
Huh?!
Huh?
Until my eyes...
are open?
"Until my eyes are open"?
What does that mean?
So that demon is called
the Soul Piper?
Uh-huh... So you have it
in your world, too?
It's supposed to console the
souls of dead children.
It plays its flute
until the souls find peace.
And if the soul cannot
find peace?
If the soul has regrets
or harbors a grudge...
Then that spirit becomes
an evil spirit.
Evil spirit?!
When regrets turn to rage
and hatred in a spirit...
it becomes evil.
Upon becoming an evil spirit...
the Soul Piper hurls it
into the depths of hell.
When the Soul Piper's eyes
are fully open, it's too late.
I won't allow that!
Mayu must find peace!
Forget it, Kagome!
Ghosts are different
from demons.
You can't just slay them.
One misstep and you'll regret it.
But I can't ignore it!
I come from a shrine family!
There must be something
I can do!
Hah! Well, count me out of this one!
There's nothing in it for me...
Kagome is already gone.
Fool!
I can't ignore her.
That girl has so much
sadness in her.
Mom, I want a cotton kimono
with goldfish on it.
When the summer comes,
I'll go to the fairs...
and catch lots and lots
of his goldfish friends.
I want to wear my
cotton kimono then.
Mayu, summer's a long
ways off.
That's okay.
Promise?
All right!
When Mom leaves the
hospital tonight...
I'm going to kill her
dear, little Satoru.
You're going home now?
Yes. I'll see you again tomorrow.
Take care.
Excuse me...
Oh, you're Sota's sister?
Umm... About Satoru's
late sister...
We've been waiting for you!
Please go around!
That day...
Stupid Mommy!
Why didn't you come
to the Open House?!
It couldn't be helped.
Satoru's temperature
shot up.
All you care about
is Satoru!
Mayu!
I hate you and Satoru!
Mayu, just a minute!
Mayu!
We always had arguments
like that.
On that day, when Mayu ran off...
I thought,
"Oh, there she goes again."
But...
If I had known that
Mayu was inside the apartment...
A child!
Poor thing!
If I had known, I would
have gone back...
If I had only known!
She wasn't aware that Mayu
was inside during the fire.
That's Satoru's room!
Mayu!
Mayu, stop!
M-Mayu!
Why?!
Quiet!
Mayu, think hard!
Did your mother really
abandon you?
Maybe she didn't know you were
inside the apartment during that fire?
Brrr... It was cold!
Sis... You're not supposed to
hang things above the heater...
when Mom is not at home.
Oh, be quiet!
Don't you dare tell Mom that
I'm hiding here.
I want to make her worry!
That muffler caught on fire!
It's all my fault.
Mom's not to blame.
Even Satoru...
Mayu...
I... I... I know that!!
Satoru!
Huh?!
He fell!
Cripes! I can't stand
to watch you!
Inuyasha!
You came!
Didn't I tell you
not to get involved?
It's too late for that
little kid.
Making her realize the truth
doesn't mean she'll find peace.
It ain't that simple!
Huh?! The eyes!
Aghh! What's this?!
No! No!
Remember this! I don't know
anything about ghosts!
So you work it out!
I must help Mayu find peace
before she falls into hell.
This is what Myoga said...
the Soul Piper takes the spirit
to the spot where the death occurred...
then drags it down into hell!
Look over there!
Seems pretty dangerous to me!
Inuyasha, let me off here.
Fool! Did you really think
you can manage alone?
No wonder they say that...
there's nothing scarier
than an ignoramus!
Oh that's right... This is where
humans get sucked into hell.
Only humans like Kagome can
proceed any further.
Damn! This is one time
I'm totally helpless!
It's pitch black.
Where am I?
A light?
Huh?!
You're conscious!
Umm... What happened?
Never mind... Look at Satoru!
Huh?!
Satoru!
Mom...
Mom... Umm...
Sis is inside the closet.
Please hurry and get her!
This is how I died.
I couldn't be saved...
Mayu!
Who is that?! Mom?!
Where are you?!
Answer!
Mayu!
Hurry! Let's get out of here!
Are you crazy?!
I'm already dead!
I don't have a home anymore!
Mayu!
You're going home, Mayu.
You're going home and
make peace with your mother.
Your mother loves you so
very much!
Is it okay if you never
see her again?
She's not angry?
Mom's not angry at me?
Don't you worry.
She's your mother!
Try to remember...
about your mother...
Mom!
I want to see you one more time,
so I can say I'm sorry!
I wanted to make up with you!
Mayu...
Mommy!
Mayu!
I'm sorry...
Mayu...
I have to go now.
I hope it worked.
Cripes! You get into
such scrapes!
One wrong move and you'd
have been dragged into hell...
with that impish evil spirit!
Evil spirit...
One week later, Satoru was
released from the hospital.
Kagome!
Mayu!
I wanted to thank you
before I left.
Such a pretty cotton kimono!
Mom sewed it for me.
Thanks for everything.
Bye-bye!
Mayu, you weren't meant
to be an evil spirit.
You were just a little girl
who loved her mother very much.
Inuyasha... Half-demon and
half-human.
Inuyasha's goal is to gather
the fragments of the Sacred Jewel...
to become a full-fledged demon.
During our search for the fragments...
we come to the rescue of a
girl named Nazuna.
She takes us to spend the night
at an old temple.
The Spider Lord lurks in
the shadows... Is it a trap?
But on this moonless night,
a secret weakness is revealed!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Mystery of the New Moon and
the Black-haired Inuyasha!"
Don't miss it!