Between catching a cold and trying
to help Sota with his first girlfriend,
I used up a lot of time.
But at last, I've returned
to the Feudal Era with Inuyasha.
So long, Sota.
Awright, let's go Kagome!
Now we can get back to
tracking Naraku's whereabouts.
Though we sure wasted a lot of
time on stupid things.
Well, excuse me!
My illness certainly was stupid!
Such a fool... He's digging his
own grave again.
Yeah, he's so dumb.
It can't be helped.
So Naraku disappeared in
the direction of the Ox-Tiger.
The way I see it,
it's in that direction.
Yeah! No time to dally!
Let's go!
Naraku! Just you wait!
Hey! Wait Inuyasha!
Hearme, all!
The divine oracle
has been received!
The feline invites calamity!
Feline?!
It is said that when a cat's
tail becomes two,
it possesses supernatural powers.
You mustexpel the feline
from the village,
orthere is sure to be
misfortune!
Never come around here again!
Cursed twin-tail!
Kuroro!
Where are you going, Kirara?
Kirara!
Man! Where did she go?
Hey, Kirara!
Hah!
Huh?
Ahhh! This is so refreshing!
Kuroro?
Oh... such a cute girl.
Kirara... Were you following
the sound of hervoice?
Kuroro... Here you are!
I was so worried.
Now come. Come.
Here... Good girl!
I'm so glad, Kuroro!
That's not Kuroro.
Hername's Kirara.
Let's put this on.
She's Sango's beloved pet.
Huh?
There, all set.
Now let's go home, Kuroro.
I told you that's not Kuroro!
Hername's Kirara!
They're coming.
Run away, Kuroro!
Kuroro! Don'tget caught!
I said that's Kirara!
She's cute, but strange.
What's the matter, Kirara?
H-Hey look! That cat again!
I'm sure we chased it far away
from the village.
Why, you...!
Get outta here!
Hey! Stop!
What're you doing?!
Owwee!
Hey!
Wait Kirara!
You mustn't bare yourfangs
against humans.
Hey Shippo!
What's going on?
Shippo?
E-Everyone!
You guys! Are you in league
with that demon cat?!
Who you calling a demon cat?!
Come come, Inuyasha!
W-What?
Let me handle this...
Villagers, violence is notgood.
We can talk it out...
Why, you...!
- Come come...
- Miroku, calm down.
Wait, everyone!
Stop!
Don't do anything rough!
Cats are vengeful creatures and will
curse you for seven generations.
Besides, that cat is not Kuroro!
Oh, dear... The villagers have
been awfully rude to you!
Nevermind that.
But why're you all frantic
over one cat?
Well...
I wonderwho that girl was?
Kirara seemed to take
to herso well.
She must be a girl with
a kind heart.
Avery smart cat named Kuroro
lived in this village.
It used to play often
with the children of the village.
But several days ago,
a very important faith healer
passed through the village.
And he read an oracle that said
that a two-tailed cat was bad forthe village
and to expel it.
I see... That's why the village girl
mistook Kirara forKuroro.
I feel badly forthe children
of the village,
but we cannot afford any calamity
to hit ourvillage.
It's pretty harsh to expel
one poor cat from the village.
Something's fishy about
this faith healer.
I think we should meet
Yeah, you're right.
What's the matter, Shippo?
Maybe he's got
an aching belly
from eating a feast
he's not used to.
Where can I find that
girl I saw?
Huh? That sound.
Oh, thatgirl's the one...
Kuroro!
Kuroro...
Hey!
This is yours, huh?
My name's Shippo.
The one you put the bell on
wasn't Kuroro.
But Kirara.
Kirara?
You're looking for a cat
named Kuroro, right?
Uh-huh.
I'll help you.
'Kay.
My name's Koume.
Koume?
Nice name.
On-kiri-kiri-kyabara-furanku-kyapura
Damn that Shippo!
Where'd he go?
He was acting strange.
Everyone, look!
What IS that?
An ominous cloud!
This faith healer...
He's no ordinary man.
Let's hurry!
According to the headman,
the faith healeris in the shrine
on the village outskirts.
'Kay!
Kuroro!
Shippo!
I don't think she's here.
Huh?
You really cared forthis cat, huh?
Uh-huh...
And...
Hmm?
Kuroro is going to have babies.
Really?
She'll be okay!
I promise to find her!
Uh-huh!
Let's go furtherin.
Huh?
What's this demonic aura?
W-Wha...?!
Fox Magic!
Smashing Top!
Hang onto me!
We'll have to go higherup!
What's that?
Rats! Ahuge army of rats!
Huh?!
Huh? What's that?
Huh?
W-What's...
...going on?!
Ourprecious sutra scroll!!!
Foolish villagers!
Not a sign of the frightful cat
in the village.
While the cat's away...
the rats will play and devour
everything in sight!
Oww!!
I can't go any further!
Huh?!
Kirara!
Kuroro!
That's Kuroro!
She has two tails, too!
Kuroro, you came!
What's that?
From the looks of it...
the demonic aura has created
a barrier.
Which means...
The faith healer
is a demon in disguise.
Well, I ain't standing forthat!
I'll break through that
stinkin' barrier!
Tetsusaiga!
How's that?!
So, you show yourself...
rat demon!
Hmm... I see that you're
actually a half-demon.
How dare you, a half-demon,
defy the Great Tesso!
What was that?
C-Cat!
Hmm... he may be large,
but he still fears cats.
No wonderyou didn't want the
cat that the children loved around!
Well, I ain't wasting any more time
to get rid of you!
Wind Scar!
Hah! This one's only talk.
Hah! Is that the limit of
yourpower, half-demon?
The Wind Scardidn't work on him?
What's wrong?
Scared stiff?
What?!
Hold it!
That is not the demon's
true appearance.
What?!
He's probably a demon created
by the demonic aura of the rats.
Asword will go right through it.
Then what'll we do?
Leave it to me.
My Wind Tunnel...
should take care of
that rat in an instant!
What?!
He disappeared.
He escaped!
Kuroro, where are you taking us?
Kuroro, yourkittens are safe!
That's wonderful!
Yes, now let's go back
to the village.
We'll neverbe apart again.
I can smell it! I can smell it!
The scent of a human child!
By devouring the child,
I'll double my spiritual rat power!
Ademonic aura!
Kuroro!
Don'tgo!
It's too dangerous
to go out now!
But...
Let Kuroro handle the outside;
we'll protect these kittens.
I found her!
Why, you...! How many times
must you interfere?!
Koume!
You stay right here!
Shippo!
Kuroro!
Persistent creature!
Now you die!
Aghhh!
Release me!
Good work, Kuroro!
Damn!
Feel the magic ofTesso!
Oh, no!
Are you all right, Koume?
The exit has been sealed.
Don't worry.
I'll save us all.
Hmm...
The exit is overhere.
Shippo!
Are you all right?
Does it hurt?
Don't worry.
I'm immortal.
That damn rat!
He probably got scared of us
and fled the village.
No...
I don't think he'll abandon
the village
aftergoing through the trouble
of getting rid of the cat.
Then he's still close by?
Probably.
It's Kuroro!
It's that cat again!
Let's go!
Yeah!
What's that?
That's the bell that
Shippo had in his possession.
Could this be Kuroro?
It's pretty badly injured.
That cat is trying to
take us somewhere.
Huh?
It's getting... hard to breathe.
Just a while longer and
I'll be through to the other side.
Hang in there, Koume!
Uh-huh... I'm all right.
Just a bit more!
Hang in there, Koume!
Hang in there!
I did it!
Koume! We're through!
Alittle kid demon, huh?
Move away from there!
There should be
a human child in there.
Move, so that I can eat her!
As if I'd allow that?!
Move, you little punk!
The wound Kuroro inflicted
is gone!
Inuyasha!
Eating a human child
to increase yourpower!
That's a sickening thing to do!
Why, you...!
Have you forgotten that
you can't harm me?!
He's a fake!
He doesn't have the wound
that Kuroro inflicted upon him!
I see...
That's it!
Well then!
Inuyasha! Behind him!
Aim forthat rock!
What?!
So that's where you've
hidden yourtrue self!
Wind Scar!
He did it!
Kuroro...
Kuroro!
Kuroro ignored the injuries
that she sustained
and led us to you two.
Kuroro...
Thank you, Kuroro!
Koume...
Thank you very much.
You saved us!
Koume... take care.
Everyone, it's time to eat.
We'll be togetherforever
and ever, Kuroro...
Hey, Shippo!
Looks like you did
pretty good.
Koume told us.
If you're a man, it's yourjob
to protect a woman.
It's admirable that you had
no ulteriormotives.
I wish someone else
would heed those very words.
Huh?
Hey, Shippo...
I'll bet you were
in love with her!
No way!
I'll bet you had
the hots forher!
No way! No way! No way!
See? You protest too much!
No way!
Inuyasha's teasing me!
Stupid!
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Sit!
W-Why?
Such fine weather.
No mistake!
This is the scent of the
herbs that Urasue was using!
Urasue? You mean the demon woman
who reincarnated Kikyo?
Kikyo's smell still lingers!
No way... Kikyo can't be
manipulating Urasue's soldiers!
No!
Don't tell me there are still puppets
in this world that possess human souls!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Plot of the Walking Dead"
Urasue was supposed to have died!