Naraku!
What's this?
By the time we got to
Naraku's Castle...
the Wolf-Demons
had been slaughtered.
W-what?!
Why that!
Koga!
Naraku's trap!
Koga went after Inuyasha...
believing that his comrades
had been killed by him.
The glow in his right arm was not
from a Sacred Jewel fragment.
With greater ferocity,
Koga attacked Inuyasha!
He says this should keep you busy.
As usual, the ape likes to make
things complicated.
While those hotheads
fight it out their way...
we get to take on a demon puppet.
He takes us lightly.
Don't let your guard down.
We're inside Naraku's castle.
Who knows what traps have been laid.
Damn these traps.
I've had just about enough!
Shall we teach them?
A measly demon puppet...
is no match against us!
Damn! Where's he getting
that brute strength?!
Ooh! The roof's been blown off!
The power of that right arm
isn't normal!
What'll we do?
We have to stop them quickly!
It's not Inuyasha who killed
Koga's friends... It was Naraku!
Damn mutt!
I'll never forgive you!
Kirara!
Kirara, good work!
Thank you, Kirara!
Kagome!
Damn you!
Jumping around, trying to escape!
If Kagome is ever hurt,
it'd be your fault!
Naraku wants us to fight...
until one of us dies.
I don't intend
to fall into Naraku's trap, but!
You've pushed me this far...
I'm not holding back!
Prepare to die!
I'm avenging my comrades!
He's fast!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer...!
What?! Did I claw you just now?
This is bad...
He smashed my arm bone.
This is... the end for you!
Inuyasha!
He's dead...
Who are you?!
Mr. Wolf Man...
now you have no regrets, huh?
Just who are you?
I'm Kagura.
Now I'll let you have your last dance.
W-what?!
What's happening?! Aren't they dead?
They may be dead,
but they want to dance.
They're so happy
they can dance with you.
You!
You're the one
who killed my friends!
Well... I forget.
I'll kill you!
I can't move...
What's happened to my body?
The poison in the fragment in your arm
is starting to work.
Well, I guess it's time to start.
Can't move, can you?
The fragment you have
imbedded in your arm...
It's a fake Sacred Jewel made
from crystallized poison and miasma.
You jumped around so much...
it sped up
the spread of the poison.
Damn!
Now then, I'll have the real
fragments you have.
So that's the sacred arrow?
It's coming!
Kagome, are you all right?!
l-I think so.
Not impressive at all.
But I won't let you get in my way.
Huh?!
Don't you dare
lay a finger on Kagome...
I'll take you on!
So you're still alive?
Mr. Wolf Man,
you didn't complete your job.
Inuyasha...
Hah! As if I'd die
from a blow from that puny wolf cub!
You want to fight me...
in that condition?
Lemme tell you this...
I'll show you no mercy!
Bathing me in the blood
of the Wolf-Demons...
and setting that fool on to me
wasn't nice at all...
but what I can't stand more...
is the scent of Naraku
that reeks from you!
Naraku?
Just the thought of Naraku enables me
to move my wounded body!
She thwarted the Tetsusaiga
with such little wind power.
With just one arm,
I can draw only half its power!
I am the Wind Sorceress.
The wind in this castle
is under my control.
Dance of the Wind Sword!
This...is her ghostly wind.
The point where the winds collide...
the Wind Scar!
Where Tetsusaiga can attain
its greatest power!
If I cut it through...
I can destroy her!
What's happening?!
What's wrong?
I can't see the Wind Scar
anywhere around Kagura!
I am the Wind Sorceress.
The wind in this castle
is under my control!
That means...
my wind is also under her control!
Something's wrong with Inuyasha!
It's like he can't move his right arm!
This time... Hit the target!
Where is she aiming?
Huh?!
Kagome's sacred arrow!
Kagura's ghostly wind
is being blown away!
All right!
There is a way
to create the Wind Scar!
Stop dallying!
Hurry and shoot!
What are you thinking?!
Inuyasha, if this arrow hits you...
even you could die!
But... I must have faith in Inuyasha!
This arrow...
is purifying my ghostly wind.
I knew it!
The ghostly wind has disappeared!
Fool! Wind is easily created!
When the two ghostly winds
appear once more...
the Wind Scar...
will be created!
Take that!
The Wind Scar...!
What's that?!
That scar?!
The castle is disappearing!
This castle was an illusion, too!
Inuyasha! Are you all right?!
Where's that woman!
I let her get away...
I couldn't use my broken right arm...
so I couldn't deliver the finishing blow.
Koga! Are you all right?!
The color in the skin is different.
The poison
from the fake fragment is spreading!
What'll we do?!
We can't let him die!
It's no use. The barrier is too strong.
It deflected your hands, Kagome.
But we must do something quickly!
Are you sure, Kagome?
I tried to kill Inuyasha...
What are you saying?!
You were just tricked by Naraku!
Even Inuyasha has no desire
to settle it like this.
Inuyasha?
Since we both fell
right into Naraku's trap...
if you only want to save his life,
there's a way.
Hold out your arm!
I'll chop it off with the fake jewel!
No! Just wait, Inuyasha!
There must be another way!
That's right!
We can't touch the barrier...
but Kagome, the sacred arrow
can dissolve the barrier!
Kagura who killed my comrades
and Naraku...
with my own hands...
Someday...
I will kill them...
I wonder if Koga will be okay?
He looks like a very proud man.
Better to let him be.
It's a funny way to put it...
but we're used to being tricked
by Naraku.
Now then... let's see how strong
the other proud one is.
He's... fast asleep.
He fought so hard.
Even Inuyasha must be exhausted.
We should let him sleep.
She had the same spider-shaped
burn scar on her back... like Naraku.
I wonder what that means?
A woman who has the same scent
as Naraku.
Naraku!
Naraku, where are you?!
Naraku...
Fifty years ago,
in order to steal the Sacred Jewel...
Naraku tricked Inuyasha
and Kikyo to battle each other.
Die, Inuyasha!
He is gathering
the Sacred Jewel fragments...
and his evil power is growing steadily.
Miroku has been cursed by Naraku...
with a Wind Tunnel in his right hand.
One day, the Wind Tunnel
will devour Miroku himself.
He must destroy Naraku
before that happens.
Sango's father
and fellow demon slayers...
were killed before her very eyes.
Naraku had resorted to the dirty trick...
- of using her brother Kohaku.
- Kohaku!
It was also Naraku who gave the
deadly poison wasps to Sesshomaru...
and deceived Sango
into fighting Inuyasha!
He never dirties his hands...
a despicable coward!
Someday, we'll get him!
Naraku!
Kagura... so you came out of this alive.
Shut up!
You tricked me, didn't you?
You never told me about the power
of that Inuyasha's sword!
The sword that cuts through
the Wind Scar.
I wondered just how powerful it was...
but if you can make it back alive...
I guess it wasn't much of a sword.
So you did trick me?
How dare you!
T-that's!
Don't forget, Kagura.
Your heart is in my hands!
Damn!
It's simple to turn you back
into what you were.
So Kagura... do not forget.
In essence...
you were created from a part of me.
We met up with a girl named Koharu
who is an acquaintance of Miroku.
What?! You asked her to bear your
child when she was just eleven?!
Miroku is definitely a pervert!
We must leave this village quickly,
for Koharu's sake!
But something's wrong.
The villagers are attacking us!
I'll bet that female demon
is behind this!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kagura's Dance and Kanna's Mirror!"
Don't miss it!