What is it?! A fire?
Slaying of demons.
- Smells awful!
- What's all this smoke?
Got that?
Send them this way!
Like we're getting
rid of insects.
Sango, are you about ready?
Is this one of
the demons?
Inuyasha's nose is
awfully sensitive.
How beautiful!
Hey Miroku!
Where're you goin'?
It's coming!
Get back!
Kagome!
It's all right now.
Inuyasha, do you still
feel sick?
Huh?
Where's Miroku?
He went after
some strange woman.
W-what?! While we
were working?
She was awfully pretty.
He probably went and asked her
to have his baby.
Huh?!
A b-baby?!
I see... so you are the princess
of a very prominent clan.
But my clan was ruined
by war.
And I am the last survivor
of my House.
In order to restore my family...
I wish to bear the child
of a strong lord.
And you sought me out?
Such fine taste.
Will you heed my request?
I thought it was too good
to be true.
Giant mantis...
disguised as a woman!
I devoured the insides
of the real one!
You picked the wrong victim!
Wind Tunnel!
Damn! My Wind Tunnel
got nicked!
I don't know if
I'm imagining it...
but the girls have been
looking at me quite coldly.
Didn't you just go to
pick up a woman?
That's why they think
you're a lecher.
I'm so misunderstood.
You may not believe me...
- We don't.
- You're lying.
I wish you'd hear me out
at least.
Shucks... It still hurts.
That praying mantis made
my Wind Tunnel bigger.
Father!
Do not go! Miroku!
Father! Father!
Let me go, Master Priest!
You will be sucked into your
father's Wind Tunnel, too!
Father!
He went out before dawn?!
Yes, the monk said that
he was going on a journey...
and to wish you well.
That Miroku! Always acting
on his own!
My father got sucked into
his own Wind Tunnel...
and disappeared without
leaving a trace.
In time, I probably will
end up dying like that.
Miroku, I can see it!
W-what's this giant hole?
This?
This is my father's grave.
Master Mushin, are you there?
It's Miroku!
Cripes... drunk as usual.
Wake up!
You drunken monk!
Oh, it's you, Miroku.
So you're still alive?
Master Mushin, if you keep
drinking to excess...
you won't live long.
Did you come here
to lecture me?!
Well... A demon nicked
my Wind Tunnel.
Will you repair it?
Let me see...
Huh?!
You will die tonight!
Not! Just joking!
Do you want to be
sucked in?!
Now, now...
Calm down.
I'll stitch it up, but
I must warn you.
Until the wound is
completely healed...
you cannot expose
your Wind Tunnel.
And if I do?
The Wind Tunnel will spread
from the nicks...
and hasten your death.
I will no longer be able
to help you.
Now then...
I will get my medicinal herbs.
Go and thoroughly purify
your dirty self.
Hmm... So that Master Mushin is
the one who raised you?
Yeah... Everything bad,
I learned from him.
He acts gruff, but he seems
very kind.
I guess.
That Miroku... Going timid
over little nicks like that.
Well, I can't blame him.
He's had such a tragic life.
Why did Miroku leave us
like that?
Isn't it 'cuz you treated him
so coldly yesterday?
Huh?!
Hah! As if he's so sensitive!
Err... Master Inuyasha...
Old Myoga? You're here?
Yes.
Actually, I returned last night.
And the monk was
acting strangely.
Whaddya mean?
He kept staring at his right hand
and seemed deep in thought.
I'm not sure what he
was thinking about...
Inuyasha, let's find Miroku.
Huh? Did something happen?
Yes... but we're not
sure what.
Find him? But how!
Well...
Leave 'im alone!
Finding the Sacred Jewel
fragments is more important!
Miroku...what happened?
It's still day, but unusually dark.
W-who are you?!
Did you take your medicine?
Yeah.
I feel quite groggy.
Sleep.
It'll be over soon.
I'm counting on you.
Frankly, I don't want to die...
Difficult you're not.
I'll put you at ease soon.
What is this?
I don't like it.
Inuyasha!
Naraku's toxic insects!
Hiraikotsu!
This time, it's dead!
Wait!
If he's keeping us
under surveillance...
something must've happened
to Miroku!
I'm following it!
- Okay!
- Hey wait!
Oh... are you still awake?
W-who... are you?!
In exchange for a fragment of
the Sacred Jewel...
I promised Naraku to kill you...
I'm the Demon Worm Charmer.
Naraku?
You can't move anymore.
The medicine has numbed
your body.
Go in peace!
Miroku!
My staff!
Err... Umm...
I won't let you get away!
Hurry and save yourself!
I... I can't!
Look well... the demons
are gathering.
Huh?!
If you stay with me,
you'll die.
Master Miroku!
Just go!
I can ward them off until
the medicine wears off.
B-but!
Just do as I say!
Alright!
He talked big, bu
no way he can handle it alone!
Inuyasha must be close by!
This is our only clue.
Don't lose it!
Hah! More insects!
What?!
Help!
You're!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
I fool around with a woman
and have to pay with my life...
Such is my fate.
So this is it.
Miroku is in danger,
after all!
He can't use his
Wind Tunnel right now!
Can't use it?
His Wind Tunnel got nicked.
Before the monk became weird
he was saying...
if Miroku used his Wind Tunnel...
the nicks would allow
the hole to spread wider...
shortening his life,
which is already short.
There's the temple!
Go right through 'em all, Tanuki!
I... ain't... gonna...
waste my time here!
If you want to eat me,
go ahead.
Unlike someone else,
I accept death with grace.
I won't go fighting,
like Inuyasha.
Miroku!
So this is where you've
been hiding!
Inuyasha... you've come for me!
Miroku, you are!
Miroku!
Idiot! Why did you disappear
without a word?!
How could you?!
We worried so much!
So you're okay, Monk?
I see...they are all here.
Inuyasha, say something!
Huh?
Never mind!
You said everything
I meant to say.
Who goes there?!
I shall punish anyone who
disturbs the peace of my temple!
Are you the monk called Mushin?
Interesting... fight me if you dare.
Inuyasha... please...
don't kill him!
Good boy! After all, I am the
one who raised Miroku.
Who cares about that?!
Prepare yourself, you old monk!
Tetsusaiga's transformation
was thwarted!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Feisty boy...
Damn! What's going on?!
You are bound by my special magic,
yet you can still move?
But I wonder how long
you can last?
W-what's that... coming out
of the monk's mouth!?
Demon Worms!
Old Myoga!
The monk is controlled by that.
Can't he be saved?
There must be
a Demon Worm Charmer nearby.
Find him and take the pot away
and aim it at the monk.
The Demon Worm will leave him
and return to the pot.
All right.
Let's search, Old Myoga!
What?! Me too?
Kagome! What's going on?!
The demons aren't decreasing.
Inuyasha's in danger too.
Sango, I'm glad you're here!
Old Myoga!
Feel safer over there?
Err... no...
Kagome, look!
There's no mistake!
That's the one!
- He got away!
- Let's go after him!
These sutra beads are draining
my strength...
Damn!
I'm starting to feel weak.
You no longer have the power
to fight back the swarm.
Do you wish to be
devoured alive?
I shall be benevolent and
chop off your head first.
Those are scum demons
that have no taste.
Scum demons devour
only scum!
Don't get your hopes too high,
stinkin' monk!
Die!
Only I can cure him.
I am the only one who can
repair Miroku's Wind Tunnel.
Left as is, he might all be
sucked into it tomorrow.
Resign yourself!
Everyone in this temple
will soon die!
Miroku!
You can move now!
The Wind Tunnel!
Hachi... prepare yourself.
You and I will probably be
sucked in.
Rather than be eaten the
their likes...
this is much better!
Huh?!
Yes sir! I'll follow you,
Master Miroku!
Here goes!
Wind Tunnel!
Hachi! Support me!
Yes sir!
Miroku!
The fool!
He'll suck in the
Sacred Jewel fragment!
He's losing strength!
Go to sleep!
I can't hold my place!
Inu... yasha!
Damn it! If you try to open
your Wind Tunnel again...
I'll break this arm!
You can die if you wanna!
But don't die so easily
when you're with me!
Feeling guilty of
abandoning you...
isn't something I'll enjoy...
...waking up to
in the morning!
W-what?!
The demons have all been...
blown away!
What just happened?!
Huh?
The true power of the Tetsusaiga...
for the first time!
You won't get away!
It's all right now.
He's taking so long.
He has to stitch the wound.
It takes time.
Fool... being so reckless.
Monk! How is Miroku!
He's asleep.
You there... Inuyasha?
Come with me.
Hey Monk...
I hope you did a good job
stitching up the Wind Tunnel.
I did what I could, but the
Wind Tunnel had spread further.
You mean
his life is shortened?!
How much longer
does he have?
I don't know.
Miroku's Wind Tunnel was created...
by a curse placed upon
him by Naraku the demon.
Hence, if Naraku is destroyed...
the curse is lifted
and Miroku's life will be spared.
The sooner you get him, the better.
That is the only way.
He's very strong-willed.
How can he always
be so cheerful?
Hmm...
I'm sure that actually...
he worries about each
and every day.
- Huh? He's awake!
- Miroku!
You'll be all right.
The monk stitched the Wind Tunnel.
Anything wrong with your hand?
Master Miroku...
Committing sexual harrassment
even now?!
He ain't gonna die for a long time.
The Miroku blood
is to be feared!
Sango had a younger brother,
Kohaku.
He passed away
when he was caught in Naraku's plot.
It's so sad to hear that the scar
on her back is a reminder of her brother.
Inuyasha is attacked by a chain scythe!
Sango gets tense!
Could the boy who throws
the chain scythe be?
But... How?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Sango's Suffering and Kohaku's Life".
Look forward to it!