A spider on his back...
Yes. According to Inuyasha...
a spider-shaped burn mark
on his back.
The robber Onigumo had
terrible burns.
Perhaps this is proof that
it is Onigumo.
A spider on his back...
That will also be the
telltale sign of Naraku.
Kikyo didn't even consider using
the power of the Sacred Jewel to live.
Kikyo chose death...
She chose to follow Inuyasha.
What a huge mansion!
Miroku, will we be staying here tonight?
He's probably gonna tell 'em...
that there's an ominous cloud
over the mansion again.
No, I have a legitimate
reason this time.
A demon that steals the
souls of dead princesses?
It's sad enough that my
dear Princess passed away.
To have her soul stolen
on top of this...
Rest assured.
We will protect her soul
without fail.
Huh?
Told ya! It's the same
as usual.
Well, can't wage war on an
empty stomach.
Still, it's awfully quiet.
I don't like it.
Found it!
Priestess Kikyo!
Look! Look!
Isn't this a medicinal herb?
Good for you!
It's called lantern plant
and it relieves swelling.
Priestess Kikyo!
What about this?
What's this, Priestess Kikyo?
Let me see...
Master Seikai...
That priestess is demon?
She looks absolutely human
to me.
You do not have enough training.
Can't you sense it?
The evil that permeates this area?
Master Monk over there...
You've been watching us
for quite some time.
Well, well... You noticed us?
I'm overcome by your beauty.
Such flattery.
I must apply myself
much more diligently.
I am much embarrassed.
Will you pick it up?
This is an anti-evil sutra.
If a demon touches this,
its true self is immediately revealed.
Hmm?
I'm thankful for such a sutra.
Here you are.
She touched the sutra, yet
nothing happened.
Let's go, everyone.
W-what was that?!
Something went through
my body.
W-what is this?
What's the matter, Master Seikai?
Look!
The sutra is gone!
She completely erased it!
Priestess!
I don't know what holds you
back here...
but this world is not
for you.
Return to where you belong!
What's he saying?!
Funny monk!
That woman...
She's no ordinary demon.
She's much, much stronger... and evil.
Oh, it's Priestess Kikyo.
We're lucky to have such a
wonderful priestess.
Yeah... The sick are cured and
the children are healthy.
We must be grateful.
I want the spiritual power of
a priestess.
This body...free of bones...
burned of flesh...
This soul which has
transmigrated into me...
suits me very well.
Why did you betray me, Inuyasha?!
You tell me to die again...
why do you pity me?
Feel the heat in my hands...
The heat of anger...
of vengeance!
Kikyo!
Priestess Kikyo!
Sayo...
Priestess Kikyo, you won't go
anywhere, will you?
Sayo, you like me?
Uh-huh.
Thank you.
You are dear to me, too...
like a little sister.
Really?
Yes.
I will live here.
Here in this village.
I can do that...
However, is it not allowed?
Nothing out of the ordinary outside.
So how's the deceased?
Hmm... nothing unusual.
I see...
Where's Miroku?
There's another princess here.
He was worried about her.
What?!
The younger princess is so terrified.
Please leave it to me.
The younger sister of the late
princess must also be beautiful.
Err... never mind.
Miroku... Am I gonna protect
that princess, too?
She may be nervous at
our first meeting.
So will you transform
or something?
Transform?
So that she'll go something like,
"Oh, cute little fox!"
What's that?!
When you've grown up a little,
you'll understand.
That guy... He's a monk!
And since he acts like a saint,
my hands're tied!
W-what... Kagome?
I'm afraid!
Like this princess...
might suddenly move.
Is that all?
What do you mean?
Were... you... having dirty
thoughts just now?
S-stupid!
That's 'cuz you
came cuddling up to me!
You were having thoughts!
I was not!
You were!
We should go back now.
I'm worried about the late
princess' soul.
Please don't go, Master Monk!
I'm so afraid!
Oh dear!
You are very safe here!
Meany!
So it's appeared!
Die!
The spirit is safe.
But is this it?
How boring.
Wait... There's still something outside.
It wasn't just one.
They're all carrying
human souls!
So many!
What're they going to do
with them?
Let's go after them!
Right now!
Master Monk... Please wait!
What were you doing?!
I suspect that this princess
too is a demon...
Little fox, you're also a meany!
I'm sorry!
Priestess Kikyo seems
a bit depressed.
It must be that
monk's fault...
I don't know what holds you
back here...
but this world is not
for you.
Return to where you belong!
I can't sleep.
Priestess Kikyo...
Where is she going so
late at night?
Because of those words
this afternoon...
maybe she's going someplace
far away...
Souls of tragic women...
Come to me.
Priestess Kikyo is manipulating
the demons...
You cannot cross to the
netherworld, Priestess?
You are one who has died.
Please overlook my presence.
I want to live quietly
in this village.
If you want to live quietly...
why do you gather the
souls of the dead?
Well, that's...
It seems that you cannot
sustain that body...
without those souls.
What are you... going to do?
I will return you to where
you belong!
I do this for your sake!
You cannot escape my
Demon-Binding Spell!
I will extinguish your light!
Save your soul!
Save?
You?! Save my soul?!
If you hadn't interfered,
you wouldn't have died.
Just what... are you trying to do?
The living are carving new
moments in their lives.
But... Time has stopped
for the dead, like you.
It can never mix.
How sad...
Sad, you say?
Me?
Who's there!?
Sayo...
Were you... watching?
I'm sorry.
I frightened you.
Priestess Kikyo...
Good bye...
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
We have to save the souls
of those women.
Huh?
So where?
Well...
The demon who stole the souls
disappeared without leaving a clue.
It's no use returning
to that mansion.
Isn't it that you don't
want to return?
That young princess was
really smitten with you.
Ahem...
Are you tired of this?
Think about it... What's
the point in all this?
It's not like we'll
find a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Not again!
Look, we're helping people.
And that's what I'm tired of!
I'm gonna be a great
demon someday...
so why must I help
petty humans?
Acting like a villain!
When you're actually
quite a saint.
W-what?!
Don't put me down!
I'm flattering you.
Hah!
Anyway, I don't like this,
so I'm out.
Understand?
Are you listening?!
What's that?
An octopus!
It's a person!
That's terrible!
Hurry!
W-what?!
Help someone!
This priest is just
unconscious.
He's moaning.
What?! Don't scare us!
What about Kagome?
A demon?
Yes...
You say that Kagome
looks like that demon.
She was in human form...
but in actuality, a frightening
demon!
That priestess.
A priestess...
who resembles me?
She was able to deflect my
master's spiritual powers.
Oh yes...
Her name... was Kikyo.
If you're lying,
you'll really pay!
I'm not lying.
That woman lured away
Ionely souls of dead women...
Never mind that!
The name! How do you know
her name was Kikyo?!
The village children
addressed her so.
I'm not mistaken...
They called her Kikyo.
The stolen souls...
were being accumulated
by Kikyo?
Kikyo...
Are you still in this world?
Didn't...you die on that day?!
She's still alive!
If she walks this earth...!
I...want...to save you!
Was it wise to let Inuyasha
go alone?
He shot off like a bullet.
Inuyasha still probably
loves Kikyo.
What?!
That's why it's better
if we stay away...
Why?
I think I understand.
Huh?
The woman he once loved
may have changed.
If so...
he would not want others
to see her.
What're you talking about?
She may turn out better
than before.
Then what?
Well, I'd get back with her...
Oh, I see...
She seemed awfully cold
just now.
I don't think you imagined that.
This is so maddening...!
What is Inuyasha up to?!
Err... Kagome.
What is it?
Umm... Shall we go
after Inuyasha?
No way!
Why should I?
An evil wind?
- That's...
- Those demons!
- Let's go after them!
- Yes!
W-what's this?!
It's a barrier.
- We can't pass?
- No.
Kagome? Where's Kagome?
Be careful! It's slippery.
Huh?!
No, I'm alone!
Ouch...
This... is...
Kikyo!
Kikyo is alive!
A demon had tried to steal
her soul...
but only ended up awakening it.
And now, her soul wanders
the real world.
Her body made of clay feels
no warmth.
Her eyes are cold and dark.
Inuyasha, run!
Kikyo is trying to kill you!
Stop, Kikyo!
Your enemy is not Inuyasha!
Next on Inuyasha,
"Kagome's Voice and Kikyo's Kiss"
Don't miss it!