Fifty years earlier, falling right into a trap
laid by Naraku,
Inuyasha and Kikyo ended up hating
and trying to kill each other.
I broke the seal that
bound Inuyasha.
And Kikyo also was resurrected
through Urasue's black magic.
I think it's false that a mortal cannot
understand a demon's feelings.
Afterall, I share a kinship with
Inuyasha and Shippo, and even Kirara.
But I can't fathom the pain of
someone who once died as Kikyo did.
Kikyo... Will the day come when the pain
in yourheart subsides?
That girl...
Soul Collectors?
What are they doing here?
Don't interfere...
I don't want you!
Leave me alone!
So you wanted to die?
Or rather, you wanted to
stay dead?
Who are you?
Huh?!
You are... Kikyo?
You know me?
I thought so!
So Urasue revived her, too.
I didn't realize there were others
who share my fate.
Fight! My lifeless puppet soldiers!
Cover this land with dead bodies!
Just watch me, Mother!
I, Kawaramaru, shall fill this world
with dead humans!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
No mistaking it.
I smell medicinal herbs.
Medicinal herbs?
This smell is from the
same medicinal herbs
used by the witch Urasue
who resurrected Kikyo.
Urasue?
I don't think it's possible....
Anyway, you all wait here.
Huh?!
Inuyasha!
How can he expect us to wait?
It's only natural that
we'd be concerned.
Back then....
when Kikyo was resurrected,
Urasue was supposed to have died.
And yet...
What're you doing here?
What are you doing?!
Leave me alone!
No! I will not go back!
Let me go!
Why you...!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
I knew it!
You're Urasue's soldiers.
Inuyasha!
- Inuyasha!
- Are you okay?
Yeah!
These....
Look, Miroku!
Ohh!
So these are the puppets baked
from human bones and graveyard soil?
But why're they here?
I dunno.... But it seems like they
were afterthatgirl.
Is she alive?
The smell of incense?
Yeah.... The smell of medicinal
herbs used by Urasue.
What does this mean?
This girl is the same as Kikyo....
a dead person revived
by Urasue.
Like Kikyo? One of the dead?
It happened soon afterl began
traveling with Inuyasha.
I was captured by Urasue who
had stolen Kikyo's remains.
I need you!
In orderto completely
resurrect Kikyo!
I was put into a tub filled with hot water
that reeked of medicinal herbs.
It was a terrible experience.
Urasue was a witch who used
bones and soil to revive the dead.
She tried to draw out Kikyo's soul
which had transmigrated into me.
Ultimately, Urasue resurrected Kikyo...
but was destroyed by Kikyo,
the very one she revived.
We've come this far following
the scent of the herbs.
But we've found nothing.
No, you're wrong.
Kikyo's smell still lingers.
Lady Kikyo?
She's not around here anymore though.
Lately, a strange army of soldiers
has destroyed
castles in this area one after another.
Hah! I have no desire to stick my
nose into human wars.
There are rumors that a demon
is behind it.
These soldiers cannot be slain
with swords
and even spears will not
pierce through them.
And you think they're Urasue's
puppet soldiers?
One thing is certain. Someone is
resurrecting the puppet soldiers.
It couldn't be that Kikyo...
is manipulating
Urasue's puppets?!
I don't know.
However, it's a fact that when we
came upon that dead girl,
we all sensed Kikyo.
Damn it!
What's going on anyway?!
Inuyasha! Where are you going?!
Where else!
I'm gonna slay whoever is controlling
those puppet soldiers!
WheneverKikyo comes
into the picture,
the blood goes to his head.
Oh, you're awake.
You sure you can get up?
Don't overdo it.
Go back and rest.
So many meddlers.
Last night, too....those Soul Collectors.
Soul Collectors?
She should've just left me
fordead.
Soul Collectors....
Did you see Kikyo?
So that was Kikyo, after all.
I wondered where she went
after she killed my mother.
Yourmother?
What do you mean?
There are puppet soldiers here.
There must be someone in here
who's manipulating the soldiers.
Next, we'll attack this castle.
It's heavily guarded.
No one can overcome
the power of our army.
It's no longer a dream that
we will reign over the land.
It's all due to you, my lord.
And the puppet soldiers constructed
by Enju and myself.
Where is Kikyo?!
I don't sense herpresence anywhere.
What business do you have
in this castle?
So it wasn't Kikyo.
So you're the one controlling
Urasue's puppet soldiers
and causing war.
This place reeks of dead men.
My name is Kawaramaru.
I am Urasue's son.
What? Urasue's son?
You must be the one who was with
the priestess who killed my mother.
Perfect timing.
I gathered soldiers in order
to conquerthe neighboring lands.
But I shall deal with you first.
Turn him into a pile of bones!
As if I'd let ya!
Take this!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
The chests of those puppets are
infused with miasma!
Your skin and flesh will melt!
I'll use yourbones to
make me a puppet servant!
My vision's blurred....
Why you...!
Wind Scar!
Hmm....so he escaped.
Fragments of puppets
from my kiln.
Puppets that Kawaramaru
ordered me to make.
Kawaramaru?
I am Enju.
Urasue brought Kawaramaru and me
back from the dead to serve her.
She called us her children.
So you can use hermagic?
Kawaramaru was a warriorwho died
because of a vassal's betrayal.
He excelled in commanding soldiers
and after he was reborn,
Urasue gave him the power to
control puppet soldiers.
Before I died, I was a potter.
Kaede said that Urasue brought
the dead back to life
in orderto take advantage of
the powers they had while alive.
Urasue made me help her
create puppet soldiers.
And she intended to make that
priestess help
search forthe shards
of the Sacred Jewel.
But Urasue was killed....
Then Kawaramaru began to
order me to make the puppets.
I didn't want to!
I didn't want to create puppets
who killed people!
But when I became weak and frail
from the lack of souls,
Kawaramaru brought me
souls of the dead.
I didn't want any....
ljust wanted to
find peace and sleep.
And so you ran away?
Huh?
You are beautiful even though
you were once dead.
Miroku!
You say you want peaceful sleep,
but shouldn't you cherish
this second chance at life?
Look at the Buddha smile.
It is because he loves all life.
Miroku...
You are amazing!
No, you're wrong, Sango....Kagome.
I won't be fooled.
Well, he doesn't intend to
let you go.
They've come afterher!
Shippo! Kirara!
Protect Enju!
Leave it to me! I won't let them
lay a finger on her!
Stop or I'll shoot!
It's useless to talk to them.
They're lifeless clay puppets, after all.
He shattered the puppets I made!
Miroku is an unrefined monk
who loves women....
But he does have spiritual powers!
Enju! We'll break up every one
of these puppets!
After all, who wants to be a soldier
even afterdeath!
Return to the soil and
find eternal peace.
It's useless.
Kawaramaru controls
several thousand more.
And....
That's....!
Kawaramaru's army is off
to conquer another castle.
So many!
But we'll do it!
So promise me!
That if we win,
you'll try living.
Why? For someone like me?
Hold it!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Inuyasha!
That man....
The one in the blue armor....
is he the general?
Yeah, so we just have
to stop him!
There are too many of them.
I'll use my Wind Tunnel!
No, Miroku!
The puppets have miasma
in their chests!
If you're not careful,
the toxins will poison you!
Then....sacred sutras!
Why you...! Move!
Blades of Blood!
It's useless!
Inuyasha!
Miroku!
Fool! What're you doing?!
Run Kagome!
Sango, you too!
Yourprotective mask won't
work against this poison!
Kirara!
Take Kagome!
Leave it to me!
Transform!
Damn it! Here I am
fighting with my wits!
- Couldn't you tell?!
- Sorry!
So.... The one with Sango is
thatgirl from earlier?
Yes.
Enju was the one who created
the puppet soldiers.
But she ran away.
She didn't want to make any
more killing machines.
After she made so many!
And only now she's sick of it?
Isn't that convenient?!
Inuyasha!
Kill me. That's what I've wanted
all along.
That's why I ran away from you.
Enju.
We are the reborn dead.
There is no place on earth
forus!
Don't make me laugh!
Then why were we
resurrected?!
Was it just Mother's whim?
Why won't you help me, Enju?!
If we exterminate the living,
you can find peace as
a reborn dead!
Don't you understand why
Enju tried to die all alone?!
She doesn't want you to
kill anymore!
You the living would neverunderstand
what we feel!
Damn! Fools like you are better
off dead!
Don't kid yourself!
We have been reborn!
We'll do as we please!
Arise from the depths of the earth!
Demon of Hell!
Oh, Demon of Hell... Awakened with
the secret magic of my mother!
Destroy them!
Just try it!
Inuyasha!
He'll squeeze the life
out of you!
I'll use my Wind Tunnel!
Get away from there!
Don't meddle, Miroku!
I'll take care of him!
Get back!
- Kagome!
- Right!
Enju!
Unforgivable! How dare you
play around with human souls!
Take this!
W-What...!
The power of the Wind Scar
blasted the miasma and Kawaramaru
into ashes.
Kawaramaru....
You sure this is okay?
Uh-huh....
Even we don't know why
we were born, yet we live.
That's why it's interesting.
No telling what tomorrow
will bring.
Say.... I wonderhow she's doing?
She's probably feeding a fire.
Kikyo bade you to come?
I promised Kagome....
to give life a chance.
Give life a chance, huh?
Why are villagers
coming after Miroku?
Knowing Miroku, he probably
made trouble long ago.
Still, they were awfully angry.
I have no idea what it is.
But there's no sense in
brooding over it.
You were in so many fixes,
you can't remember which is which!
Everyone, I think you misunderstand me.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Mysterious, Lecherous Monk!"
Well then, let's get to the bottom of this!