Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gatherall
the shards of the Sacred Jewel!
And I'll destroy Naraku with
my Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha's older brother, Sesshomaru,
detested humans so much,
yet a young mortal girl
now accompanies him.
His vassal Jaken is caught between them
and they're quite a trio!
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
In pursuit of Naraku
who had disappeared,
we were headed northeast in the
direction of the ox-tiger.
At the same time, Inuyasha's
older brother, Sesshomaru,
was also looking for Naraku.
Lord Sesshomaru!
I'm hungry.
May I go and look
for something to eat?
Quiet, Rin!
Aforest like this will have
nothing foryou to eat.
Just bear it!
But...
No buts!
Be quiet!
- I'll be real quick!
- That girl!
Hey Rin!
Jaken!
Yes?
Let herbe.
I can't believe it!
Why'd you eat it all?!
Shaddup!
This was the last
bag of garlic-flavored chips!
What's one bag ortwo!
I wanted to give it
to Jinenji.
Besides, you nevereat this.
ljust took one piece...
and I couldn't stop.
What'll I do?
Umm...
This Jinenji?
Remember!
When Kirara collapsed from
Naraku's toxic poison.
It was Jinenji who gave
us the antidote.
Oh... I remember!
We're nearhis village,
so I thought we could stop by.
But someone ate his present!
Quitgoing on about that!
Say, isn't Jinenji also
a half-demon?
Yes, but he's so gentle
and nice.
Unlike Inuyasha!
Oh well! There's no present forhim.
So let's just keep on going.
No.
If there's an antidote to the miasma,
we should stop by.
I want to thank him for
saving Kirara, too.
Then let's all go.
Inuyasha can do as he pleases.
She's so heartless!
This is edible.
Brilliant! You are the one and only
Lord Sesshomaru!
You're so dashing, Lord Sesshomaru!
Those are poisonous Saimyosho!
Stand back.
That Naraku...
He left behind
some annoying vermin.
Jaken...
There should be a hive nearby.
Yes! I'll look forit.
Jaken!
Huh?!
MasterJaken!
There! The hive of the poison insects!
Rin, get down!
Okay!
Get a taste of...
the Staff ofTwo Heads!
Persistent pests!
Rin! Keep yourhead down!
I must protect Rin.
Otherwise, who knows what
Lord Sesshomaru will say!
MasterJaken...
What?! Still here?
Jaken!
You saved me, Lord Sesshomaru!
Thank you, Lord Sesshomaru!
MasterJaken?
If I pursue them...
Lord Sesshomaru!
Rin!
Take the stingers out.
Did you get them out?
I'm sorry, Master Jaken!
The toxic poisons have
entered my body!
If I don't do something,
I may die!
I'm sorry, Jaken.
All because of me...
F-Fool!
I'm notgoing to die
foryou!
I'm dying for Lord Sesshomaru!
MasterJaken!
Isn't there some way
to get rid of the poison?
It's okay, Rin...
I have been happy traveling
the land with Lord Sesshomaru.
Even if I should die here,
I have no regrets in my life.
MasterJaken...
Tell Lord Sesshomaru...
that I will be praying for
his well-being...
from my grave.
MasterJaken!
I don't want to see
you die!
I... I'll do anything!
Tell me anything!
Really?
Uh-huh...
Then maybe I'll ask...
MasterJaken... don't die!
To the east of here is an herb farm
known as Jinenji's Garden.
Go there and get the berries
of the sennensou
"thousand-yearflower."
The berries of
the "thousand-yearflower"?
But Rin...
If you truly want to save me,
you must hurry.
Before the sun sets, I must
swallow the berries...
else the toxic poison will have
spread throughout my body
and I shall...
Don't worry, Jaken!
I will return before the sun sets!
I promise!
A-Uun! Go faster!
Hmm... are you sure it's
this way, Kagome?
Hmm...
I think so...
Right, Inuyasha?
It WAS this way, right?
I thought I didn't matter?
Are you still sulking?
Sorry for being rude earlier.
Man! She didn't even mean it!
This smell...
What's the matter, Inuyasha!
I'm sure of it.
Naraku's poisonous insects!
Hah! Couldn't ask for better luck!
Wait, Inuyasha!
Kagome... do you sense
any Sacred Jewel shards nearby?
No... not nearby.
And no demon puppets either.
Then perhaps those insects are
heading back to Naraku.
If we follow them
instead of killing them...
We'll discover Naraku's whereabouts!
- Hey! They're falling!
- What?!
Are they dead?
What's going on?
S-Sesshomaru!
Did you kill them...
the Saimyosho?
Saimyosho?
You mean these poison insects?
So short-sighted.
What?
Now I've lost my lead
to finding Naraku.
Lemme make one thing clear!
These bugs just dropped dead!
I'm becoming quite tired
of yourexcuses!
Who'd make excuses to you!
I'm telling the truth!
Yes, that's the truth!
Stay outta this, Kagome!
He doesn't understand words!
Inuyasha...
I'm not feeling very
magnanimous today.
I won'tgo easy on you
like before.
Cut the crap!
And don't come crying to
me later!
Stop it, both of you!
It's useless.
They're always at
odds with each other.
I'll say.
A-Un, wait here!
An herbal garden...
This is it!
Umm...
Who is it?
Huh?! A witch!
What?
I... I want to see Jinenji.
Jinenji isn't seeing anyone today.
Go on home.
You're here, aren't you, Jinenji?
Please hearme out!
Please give me some
sennensouberries.
There's someone who's been
poisoned and he might die!
That's very regrettable.
However...
I don't have any
sennensouberries here.
Go home.
What's wrong?
Why won't you come out
from underthe covers?
You're just a little girl,
so you won't understand.
But Jinenji is
a half-demon.
Half-demon?
Once in a while, he takes on
the human form.
He's such a coward.
And he doesn't want anyone
to see his human self.
Then please tell me where
I can find the berries!
I'll go get them!
Sennensouberries are used as
an antidote by demons.
Are you trying to save a demon?
Uh-huh...
Are you smitten with this demon?
Smitten?
What's that?
I see!
You're so young!
I underestimated you!
I was like you once!
Never mind that!
I must save MasterJaken!
Ma!
Huh?
This girl resembles Kagome.
Kagome?
Oh, thatgirl...
I think you're right.
The sennensou grows in the ravine
of the mountain out back.
But...
There are lots of demons and beasts.
It's impossible for a human
to go there.
When it's dark,
I'll return to normal.
So can you wait until then?
It'll be too late!
Tell me what kind of plant it is.
I'll go get it!
Really... you're just like Kagome.
Rin...
Lord Sesshomaru!
I... don't... want to die... alone!
A-Un! There!
That's the place!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
What?!
It's my win.
Are you prepared, Inuyasha?
I don't care about my life!
Just do as you please!
I see...
Wait!
You want to know where Naraku is?
Then go in the direction of
the ox-tiger!
We heard that Naraku's aura
went in that direction.
Stu... - ! Kagome!
In the direction of the ox-tiger?
That's all I need to know.
You survived this one, Inuyasha.
Wait, Sesshomaru!
Why do you go after Naraku?
I cannot forgive him!
H-Huh...
Thank you, A-Un!
Sennensouberries...
"Thousand-yearflower" berries...
Oh!
Found it!
That's it!
Sorry, A-Un!
Keep them at bay!
I'm going to get the berries.
Lord Sesshomaru...
I'm scared.
Pa... Ma... Brother...
They all died.
I don't want anyone else
to die...
I don't want to see anyone die!
MasterJaken...
Please don't die.
Don't anyone die... anymore!
Lord Sesshomaru!
The poison is spreading...
Ahh... the sun is setting.
Rin didn't make it, after all.
Ohh... my vision is blurring...
Huh? An illusion?
Huh?
L-Lord Sesshomaru!
Lord Sesshomaru!
MasterJaken, don't die.
Huh? Alittle girl came by?
Yeah. I'm worried if she was able
to get the sennensou berries.
I think she did okay.
She was just like you, Kagome.
Kagome?
Yeah... she's probably much
strongerthan me.
Like Kagome, she warmed your heart...
Just like the sun.
She must have a big, kind heart.
Jinenji... please!
Hey, Jinenji...
I think you misunderstand,
so lemme tell you...
Kagome's heart is pretty small.
Inuyasha...
Sit!
What'd I tell ya, Jinenji!
See how small herheart is?
Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit!
He's so stupid.
I'll say.
Second that.
Oh, you're awake!
Huh? Master Jaken?
You're cured?
Or did I... die again?
Silly fool! Lord Sesshomaru
brought you here.
Lord Sesshomaru?
Yes, Rin!
Stop giving him so much trouble!
Uh-huh... I'm sorry.
Ohhh... But MasterJaken,
I'm so glad foryou!
Ohh... stop, Rin!
Get away!
I won't!
In the direction of the ox-tiger...
Lord Sesshomaru!
Lord Sesshomaru.
We're going.
Lord Sesshomaru...
We're all together again.
What'll I do, Kagome?
Kirara is gone!
Maybe she went for a walk?
Kirara seemed fine.
But this is the first time...
Maybe there's a reason why
she can't return.
I'm getting so worried
the more I think about it!
Could she have run away
because of that?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kirara Come Home!"
Kirara, don't leave like this!