Stay in there and behave.
Hey!
They said they were from
the Panther-Demon Tribe.
We have no business with you.
We want that priestess with
the Sacred Jewel shards.
If you want the shards,
you'll have to go through me!
I know Inuyasha will
come for me.
I just have to hang in there.
What's happening?
Wind Scar!
Humph! I knew it.
It was just a barrier.
Not bad for a mutt.
What?!
Wait, Koga!
C'mon Boss!
Hey!
Hey! Inuyasha!
Huh?
You're late!
This is?
The entrance.
Those cats're somewhere
in here.
Then we'll find Kagome there?
Yeah, let's go!
What is this?
Seems like a village.
A pretty good-sized town...
A castle town.
But why here of all places?
Anyone here?
No one's around.
But it looks like people
inhabit it.
I don't see Koga and his men.
Yeah...
So they've come.
Kagome! Where are you?!
Shippo!
Wind Scar!
Stop acting so hastily!
We still don't know
where Kagome is!
Hold it!
You ain't getting away!
You're so impatient.
Huh?!
Breaking the barrier and
entering like that.
Hey! Where's Kagome?!
She's fine so far.
Answer me!
When the moon
is straight above us,
we'll sacrifice her
to the Master.
Why, you...!
Naturally, you too.
What's that?!
What's this smoke?
It's all right.
It's just a powerful odor.
It's awful!
Damn!
Hang on, Inuyasha!
My power...
Isn't it a potent smell?
If it's awful for us,
I can imagine how bad
it is for dogs.
So it's a trap to stop Inuyasha?
It's not quite according
to our plans, though.
So stay put and be captured!
Sesshomaru!
What's going on, Karan?
I'm the one you have
business with.
So the big brother appears.
Nothing could be better
with the two of you.
Hey, sons of the Great Dog-Demon,
we'll be waiting at the castle!
Sesshomaru, why're you here?
That's my line.
Get out of here, you!
W-What?!
I won't have you getting
involved in this war!
I don't need your permission!
Kagome's been kidnapped
by those cats!
Fool!
W-Why, you!
Whaddya think you're doing?!
Silence, Inuyasha!
Why, you...!
Just remember this...
You lost your heart to a mortal
and ended up under seal...
You have no right to be
part of this battle.
Lord Sesshomaru!
You can't be picky at
a time like this!
How scary!
He really was upset about that.
Did you do something?
How would I know?!
Master!
Huh?!
You're here, Hachi?
Hachi!
I thought you ran off.
I intended to, but...
I caught up with you!
What're you doing here, Old Myoga?
I have a feeling that this has to
do with the great war
that your father waged
many eons past.
Eons past?
I thought Hachiemon said
it happened fifty years ago?
No, no. Way before that.
When your father was still
in the Western Province.
I don't remember a thing
about it.
At that time, the Panther Tribe
of cat-demons attacked the West
and tried to conquer all
other demons.
But your father stepped in.
The enemy leader was a
Great Panther-Demon.
Your father protected his
comrades and battled the demon.
Naturally, it was your father
who was victorious.
The other demons who
escaped domination by the Panther Tribe
were extremely grateful.
However...
The wrath of the cats ran deep.
They cursed your father and his family
for all eternity
and swore vengeance.
Like the saying... that a cat's
wrath lasts seven generations.
Lord Sesshomaru did not
participate in the Great War either.
But I'm sure it's part of the
cat's revenge.
And what were you doing
at that time?
Naturally, I watched over
things in his absence!
I knew it...
But why was Sesshomaru so
adamant about Inuyasha leaving?
Hah! He just doesn't want to
recognize a half-breed like me.
Still...
I think it would be noble
for the two of you
to fight your father's enemy.
Understand this! Neither my old
man nor Sesshomaru are my concern.
l just came to take back the Sacred Jewel
shards and Kagome!
Then... excuse me!
Old Myoga is running away!
Which means...
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Aghh!
Aren't you asking your
brother to help?
Why, you...!
Damn! Not a trace of
Kagome's scent.
Where'd they take her anyway?
Say, Koga...
Huh? What is it?
This is the main base
of those cats, right?
Isn't it dangerous for
us to act alone?
So what would you do?
Why not join up with
Inuyasha and the others.
What did you say?!
You expect me to ask that mutt
for help?!
No, Koga.
We mean you can offer them
your help.
You think I'm that helpless?
No, no!
We just think it'll be easier
to rescue Kagome that way.
Yeah, yeah... it's for her sake.
So you're Koga of
the Wolf-Demon Tribe.
He doesn't smell like
those cats.
You're Royakan?
Huh? You mean Royakan,
the keeper of the forest?
The demon from hell who gobbles
up anyone who gets lost.
So why're you here?
That's what I'd like to
ask of you.
You're not accompanying
Lord Sesshomaru, are you?
Sesshomaru?
Who's that?
You don't know?
Nope.
You ordered me to come.
And you won't let me see
your so-called Master?
Well, we're just not ready
for that yet.
So will my company do?
Leave this to me,
Lord Sesshomaru.
I'll show you the power
of the Staff of Two Heads!
Do not lose!
You sure have a dangerous
weapon there.
Why, you...!
Inuyasha!
Where are you?!
It's Inuyasha!
Kirara!
Brings back memories...
of when we last fought.
It ended up in a draw then.
But not this time.
A draw, you say?
You just retreated.
So many of your men
also died.
Besides, back then, I wasn't
that determined.
We have our master.
It's different now.
Back then...
The Panther Tribe whom
Father battled.
Lord Sesshomaru!
We have come to assist!
A battle! A battle!
We'll teach those cats a lesson!
What do you all want?
We are beholden to your father
from the last war.
This time, we shall assist you,
Lord Sesshomaru.
I can't wait!
It's been so long since
we last fought those cats.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Terrible news!
Jaken...
Whaddya mean "slowed him down"?
And what was a rout?
We failed Lord Sesshomaru.
We told him we'd protect
the battlefront.
Lord Sesshomaru himself
was battling in fine form, but...
Lord Sesshomaru!
Please save us!
Fall back!
Retreat!
Join up with Lord Sesshomaru!
So they lost.
They ran away!
I fought with all my might!
Those cats were cowards!
Shaddup!
Who cares about such
talk from the past?
How deep does this
forest go anyway?
I'll say!
It's like we've been circling the
same area over and over again.
All right!
They'll go and check.
What's that?
Let me handle it!
That's!
She's put a barrier
around us!
Say, you have a couple
of Sacred Jewel shards.
What's happening?!
Hold your breath!
Sorcery!
We're caught inside
this forest!
Damn!
I can only smell flowers!
Miroku! Sango!
Your lives will be offered
to the master!
Huh?
In exchange for the Sacred Jewel
shards and your lives...
our master will be resurrected!
Where did he go?
Lord Sesshomaru?!
Where are you?
Lord Sesshomaru!
Huh?!
Hey! Do not approach!
Don't... come!
Huh?!
Iron Reaver, Soul Stealer!
R-Run!
Hey!
Hey, seen my friends?
No!
And do you know where
Lord Sesshomaru is?
No way!
Besides, why's he here?
It's none of his business!
How could you say that!
You unfilial son!
Say that again!
Your father waged war against
the Panther-Demon Tribe long ago.
Oh that... I heard from Myoga.
But Sesshomaru wasn't part
of that battle.
The Panther-Demon Tribe appeared
again fifty years ago
hell-bent on revenge.
Your father had passed on...
but they came to ravage the
countryside and kill your father's people.
Yet at that time, you!
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru!
Terrible news!
What is it?
I acted on my own and
went to get Inuyasha.
He may be a half-demon,
but he is still
your father's son, after all.
And?
Where is he?
Is he too cowardly to
show himself?
Or did he refuse to come to
the aid of his brother?
That Inuyasha is under
a seal!
What?
Well...
He... lost his heart to
a mortal priestess
and was caught off guard.
Fool!
Yes, a total fool.
But what is that?
Father saved them in
that first battle.
Then they are allies!
How wonderful!
I was concerned,
but now that your father's
allies have come,
you can go to battle with
confidence.
Lord Sesshomaru never
expected your help!
But if we had Tetsusaiga,
the sword forged by your father,
victory would have
been so easy.
Sesshomaru can't wield
Tetsusaiga.
That's not the point,
you ungrateful son!
Can you stop harping
on and on about the past?
What?!
Hey, wait!
Do not leave me!
I see. So this all happened
while I was sealed to that tree.
Huh?
Where is this?
I'm not sure.
I'm so glad!
You're conscious, both of you.
Kagome!
I'm so glad you're all right.
Then this is a prison cell?
There are many more
of us.
Many more?
Look.
These are the villagers?
No wonder there was
no sign of life in town.
This was a secret village.
A gathering of people who
had escaped the wars.
I see... It's the perfect place
to hide and live in peace.
But the Panther-Demon Tribe
discovered it
and made it their
headquarters.
We'll be killed by those cats!
I'm so afraid...
Why did those demons
have to come?
Everyone, don't worry.
We'll be rescued without fail.
Stay confident.
Those cat demons will
interfere for sure.
Someone much, much stronger
than those cats will come to save us.
I'm so scared! So scared!
Namu Amida Butsu...
Someone much stronger?
Inuyasha and Koga...
They'll come. I know it.
So don't worry.
I don't know about
Sesshomaru, though.
Sesshomaru?
He's battling the Panther-Demon Tribe.
W-Why?
It's almost time, Master.
Soon you will be resurrected.
Hmm... It's the older brother.
Go home, wolf!
We have no business with you!
Shut up!
I have business with you!
Jaken is here...
They've come!
Where's Kagome!?
I don't care who this
Master or whatever is.
But I won't let you sacrifice
lives to bring him back!
Move, Inuyasha!
They are my prey!
No way! I'll cut them into pieces
with my Tetsusaiga!
If I had Tetsusaiga back then...
Sesshomaru...
I heard about the battle fifty
years ago when I was under seal.
Exactly what happened?!
Next on Inuyasha: "The Panther Tribe
and the Two Swords of the Fang"
Father, why did you leave
me Tenseiga...