It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
forourdreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
Aftertheirfight with Naraku
was over,
they had promised to marry.
But because of Miroku, their
relationship totally deteriorates.
Are you sure this is what
you want, Sango?
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Miroku is still depressed.
Because a pickpocket stole
his wallet?
How could I have
let this happen?
Miroku, don't take it
too hard.
Sango....
Please don't be so kind
to me.
Miroku....
I can't forgive myself
forbeing so careless.
Hey....
That's being depressed?
What he says and what he does
are complete opposites.
This charm was given to me
by a man of high personage.
Please accept this and
find peace.
- An earthquake?
- And...
Ademonic aura.
Let's go!
P-Please!
Please forgive us! Master!
What is the matter?
You seem to be troubled by
something evil.
Perhaps we can be
of some help....
Huh?!
Monk Miroku!
Huh?
Have you come to fulfill
yourpromise
to marry and become an
adopted son-in-law?
Adopted?
Monk Miroku has returned!
Begin the preparations!
What's going on?
Well....
Don't you remember?
Hah! He probably has
too many things to remember.
Miroku!
I've been waiting for you!
Oh!
O-Oh...
Shima!
How lovely you've become!
I'm so happy!
Huh?!
Stay calm.
It's something from the past?
Yes. And both my wife and I had
given up hope
believing it was
a thing of the past.
Ourdaughter, Shima, was always
sickly and frail.
There was never a day when
she could lift her head
from herpillow.
That's when Monk Miroku
passed through the village.
This was two years ago.
Boil these herbs in
clean water,
then drink the liquid
every day.
And as one would expect from
such a costly medicinal herb,
it worked so well.
It was such an expensive medicine.
What a scam!
And?
You two became fast friends?
No such thing!
He gave us the medicine,
then left.
See? I'm totally clean.
Except....
- Except?
When you are well,
will you bear my child?
Yes!
The medicinal herb and the promise
I made to Miroku sustained me
and I recovered completely.
You were trying to seduce her!
Oh, it's okay.
After all, it's a thing of the past.
Of all the stupid things....!
What's the big deal anyway?
It is a big deal!
Whatever happened to the
evil spirit?
He's right!
The incidentearlier
at the shrine....
A-Anotherearthquake!
I'm so afraid, Miroku!
I'm scared too...
But fora different reason.
Monk Miroku, please help us!
If nothing is done,
ourdaughter will end up
as the wife of a demon!
Ademon's wife?
Y-Yes!
That shrine is dedicated
to the Master!
And Masterhas demanded Shima
to be his wife!
I've told him that I am betrothed,
but he does not believe me.
Err....
Yourbetrothed is....?
You, of course!
But Miroku, you didn't forget
ourpromise and returned.
You don't know how I've
waited for this day!
I understand.
In any case, we cannot hand over
Shima to the demon!
You will help us?
Leave it to me.
Then let us prepare
the ceremony right away!
Huh?
I thought he's gonna
destroy the demon?
That's one thing.
The other is that she intends
to have Miroku's child.
Shima, this is our promised night.
It's so cold.
Why is Miroku the only one inside?
I wonder....
He said he was going
to settle this.
Meaning he's going to turn
down the marriage?
He'd better!
After all, Miroku promised
to marry Sango.
You sure you can trust him?
This is Miroku, y'know.
It's a foolish man who turns down
a woman who offers herself, right?
Inuyasha, sit!
In the first place,
when did you learn such vulgarities?!
In the second place, think about
the people around you!
I'm second place, huh?
I'd like you to marry my daughter
as soon as possible.
But the Masterwho desires Shima
is a demon, right?
Whether she's married ornot,
he will come afterher.
No, that's just it.
The Master of the Lake wants
a virgin bride.
So if a marriage ceremony is held,
we think he will give up on her.
Now that's noble of him.
Before the demon comes,
please make me yourwife.
Shima....
It's a foolish man who turns down
a woman who offers herself to him!
Oh, well....
Monk....
A specter!
Shippo, what are you doing?
I was just trying to express
how you were feeling, Sango.
I'm not upset.
Sorry to interrupt.
Drop dead, you idiot!
Hereyes were shouting to me,
"Drop dead, you idiot."
Monk Miroku....
Who is that woman?
Err....well....
Anotherearthquake!
Something smelly is approaching.
Looks like the Master of the Lake
is about to make an appearance.
W-Wha...?!
Umm...
I am the Master of the Lake.
I have come for Shima
as promised.
You heard him.
He's the one?
He said so himself.
Go on home!
Why do you interfere?!
The girl doesn't want you!
M-Master!
Miroku, I'm frightened!
Are you really scared?
Shima!
No!
See? Give it up!
Why?
She clearly promised to
be my bride!
Promised?
I neverpromised.
P-Please forgive us, Master!
Father?
To be truthful....
in orderto boil
the expensive herbs....
Boil these herbs in
clean water,
then drink the liquid
every day.
I used the water from the lake.
And at the same time, every day,
I prayed at the shrine
by the lake.
Masterof the Lake, please
bring my daughterback to health.
I will do anything in return.
I neverimagined that the Master
was actually listening.
And the Master asked for
Shima in return.
So what did I do wrong?
I feel a bit sorry forhim....
I didn't know....
that my fathermade
such a promise.
Shima, forgive me!
No....
You did it all out of a desire
to save me.
But....
there's nothing we can do now.
Even if you didn't know the Master
was listening,
a promise is still a promise.
Oh, so you'll....
Shima!
You're not serious....
about becoming a demon's bride?
Master....
Huh?
Please forgive me!
I am not fit to become yourwife!
Huh? Why?
I have heard that you desire
a virgin bride.
But two years ago, I....
gave myself to Miroku.
l-Is that true, Shima?!
I'm sorry, Father.
I couldn't bring myself to tell you.
I knew it.
But hearing it confirmed
is still a shock.
Wait now....
It's okay. It's all in the past, after all.
Master.... It's as you just heard, so....
Please forget about this arrangement.
You deceived me....!
Love spurned becomes
intense hatred!
Agiant catfish!
You will feel my wrath!
O-Our house will be crushed!
Miroku, please save us!
All right, we'll tame him.
Let's go, Sango!
Huh?
You can take care of it alone.
Yourpast indiscretion caused this.
l-Is this lady going to transform
from now, too?
She's not a demon.
This is no time to fight!
Ourhome!
Dammit!
I'll take you on!
I'll swallow you whole!
Sango....
Let me explain and you'll understand!
Don't come near me!
I don't think....
things are going to work out.
Not... Not going to work out?
What's going to happen
to the two of them?!
Look, Kagome....
Shouldn't we be paying attention
to Inuyasha and the catfish?
How dare you make a fool out of me!
Why don't you shut up?!
How dare you?!
Why you...!
If you won'tgive up,
I'm gonna get serious!
Shima....
I had faith in you.
He's calmed down.
Has the Master of the Lake....
given up on me?
Thatended quickly.
Well, I couldn't sleep well at night
if I killed a demon like that.
But things have gotten very
serious overthere.
Huh? Are they still fighting?
Sango....
Won't you even listen to me?
I don't know anymore.
Cripes!
Miroku's habit of flirting with women
didn't start yesterday.
Inuyasha!
What?
You don't understand anything!
If the woman of his past appears
before her,
it's not a comfortable feeling!
E-Excuse me....
Please stop fighting.
Shima!
It's all my fault.
Please don't blame Miroku.
Sango!
Don't follow!
Miroku, aren't you going afterher?
Right now, she won't listen,
no matter what I say.
But I'm very saddened....
that she really didn't trust me at all.
My heart is set on one person.
Huh?
You sound as though you've
been falsely accused.
I was!
- S-Shima!
- Help!
I can't forget you, after all!
Blast it!
Please forgive me!
No! We will live together
at the bottom of the lake.
Dammit!
I should've delivered the final blow!
I must save her!
Yeah!
Miroku... isn't coming afterme.
What'll I do from now?
- No!
- You'll marry me...
no matter what!
Wha...!
I told you that I gave myself
to Miroku!
I'll forgive you!
I'll forget about your past!
No!
You were with Miroku....
Sango!
Miroku!
It's not that he's coming afterme!
Kirara, take herto a safe place!
Hiraikotsu!
You fool!
He deflected the Hiraikotsu!
Woman, I'll take you to the bottom
of the lake too
and make you my mistress!
Wha...!
No way!
Say that again!
How dare you take my woman!
Hah! Silence!
We're in the water!
Do you think you can catch me?
Oh yeah....
Then get a taste of this!
Wind Tunnel!
Churn....churn....churn!
The wateris disappearing....
Why you...!
Listen up, catfish!
Don't you dare mess with my girl!
l-Is she one of yours, too?
l-I'm sorry.
Sango, are you all right?
Oh...
Hey, Sango!
Hey!
Sango!
I said, hey!
Hey!
Sango!
Hey Sango!
l-I guess there's nothing for
me to do here....
Miroku....
I guess it was a case of
unrequited love forme.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I lied.
You lied aboutgiving yourself
to Miroku?
Yes.
I didn't want to wed the catfish.
It was the only thing
Shima could think of.
T-Then why didn't you tell me the truth
at least?
Why?
I was too naïve....
I thought you'd understand
even without my saying anything.
Miroku....
It's because I'm always such a cad.
I'm sorry I hurt you, Sango.
Never mind already.
Besides...
When you saved me....
I was very happy....
Will you forgive me, Sango?
That should be my line!
Is this okay?
Sango has such a big heart.
In some ways, it's biggerthan
yours, Kagome.
You make a fine match, Miroku.
But you know....
If he had told her the truth sooner,
all this wouldn't have happened.
Or maybe, Miroku....
it took you a long time
to remember what was what?
Bull's eye!
Is that true? Well, is it?
Well, it happened so long ago....
What's wrong, Jaken?
Rin has been kidnapped by a demon!
Agroup of monks who specialize
in slaying demons went to save her, but....
Those monks don't like demons.
If they come across Sesshomaru,
this could be bad.
Humans can try their half-baked tricks,
but Sesshomaru will tear them apart.
I'm not scared!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Foreverwith Lord Sesshomaru"
Lord Sesshomaru, please don't forget me
even if I die!