Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku with my Tetsusaiga!
Koga is seriously hurt during his
desperate battle with the Band of Seven.
Furthermore, the power of
the sacred barrier around Mt. Hakurei
has the power to even
hinder Sesshomaru.
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time for
a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Here.
Watch out!
Koga is hurt! Can't you be more
gentle with him?
Be gentle?!
By rights, I should take
the Sacred Jewel shards from his legs
and leave him here.
Yeah?
So why didn't you?
Like I would take advantage of
a guy who can't defend himself!
Inuyasha....
D-Dammit!
What's going on?
Why can't I move?
These damned kids...
Hey, Sesshomaru's coming.
Really?
Take care of the kids later.
We need to lure Sesshomaru
into the barrier.
Yeah.... Understood.
I've found them.
They're just beyond this point.
P- Please wait, Lord Sesshomaru!
It's a trap.
They're using Rin as bait to
lure you into the barrier!
If you proceed any further....
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru!
Doesn't Lord Sesshomaru
feel anything?
Am I the only one
feeling weak?
Well then, I must be strong.
If I really set my mind to it,
I can do anything!
I can't do a thing....
Lady Kikyo....
You're all right?
All this....
Did Suikotsu do all this?
Uh-huh.
Dr. Suikotsu had the same
kind face as before, but....
inside, he's....
Mt. Hakurei has no effect
on Suikotsu anymore.
The Sacred Jewel shard has become
more tainted.
That Sesshomaru isn't coming.
I guess the barrier is too strong
for him to come this far.
Don't seem that way...
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru!
You anticipated our moves?
Damn!
You're a demon, yet the barrier's
not affecting you?
Take this!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Thought so!
His moves are dulled.
You must leave this village,
children.
Lady Kikyo....
But where will we go?
Listen well.
If you linger any longer,
other misfortunes may
befall you.
Well, Kikyo...
dead beings like us all end up
with the same fate.
So let's both live as long
as we can.
I don't care about the other world.
I'm gonna do as I please
while I live.
Miroku.
What's the matter, Sango?
We've been on this road before.
Perhaps we're lost.
You think so?
The faster we turn around,
the easier it'll be to get back.
This cave is quite deep and complicated.
D-Don't tell me you don't
know the way back?
Well then, what about you?
All I did was follow you!
There you go again!
Blaming others!
Nothing here.
Huh?
You saw that, too?
Yes.
It seems to be luring us in.
It may be a trap.
I don't sense any demonic aura.
Oh well.... Nothing ventured,
nothing gained.
I can't let those two go
any further.
Please... follow me.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Stay still.
Boy, you're so proud.
You can barely stand, can you?
Because of the barrier!
The bastard...
Acting like he's perfectly fine,
when he's not.
He's steadily trying to move
away from the barrier.
It must be hard on him.
Suikotsu, don't move away
from the mountain.
I don't need to be
told that.
Hurry and take care
of that bastard.
I'm just itching to kill this kid.
I couldn't kill those village kids
because that doctor interfered.
This time I'll do it.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Now do you get it?
Make one wrong move
and this kid is dead.
Although, it's all a matter
of time.
Matter of time, you say?
Why you...!
What's so funny?!
Should you be
laughing like that?!
He threw his sword away!
Lord Sesshomaru!
I'm not letting you go.
Up close, you sure are good-looking.
But you've made a mistake.
We can't be killed like a normal man...
Jakotsu, can I kill her now?
Could be because I've been injured,
but the bastard doctor is too
scared to come out.
Right now, this urge to kill
is overwhelming.
Fool!
It's too late.
Die!
Suikotsu, the light from your Sacred Jewel
shard is tainted black.
You're no longer...
Lord Sesshomaru!
That woman....
She scares me the most!
Lady K-Kikyo....
Dr. Suikotsu.
I was finally able to come back.
A dark light interfered
and I couldn't come out.
Did my sacred arrow
purify the shard?
What am I to do with him?
Must I kill him?
Lady Kikyo....
please remove the shard
from my neck.
Then I will return to bones.
I... wish to be released.
You would choose death?
Yes.
I finally remember....
I died once before.
Pure is impure,
lmpure is pure.
While I lived, I was confused.
About what was right
and what was wrong?
I'll save her!
I promise to save her!
Doctor, she's beyond help.
Let's just leave her
and run!
Don't be ridiculous!
There's hope still!
The samurai will come!
We must flee or they'll kill us!
Then run.
I'm going to save...
Why you...!
How could you?
I put her out of her misery.
You should be grateful.
Our lord's orders...
to kill every single person
in this village.
Stay away!
And I....
I who was sworn to save
people's lives....
killed someone with
my own hands!
Looking back....
I was unable to forgive myself.
I didn't know what to do.
It was then....that I heard the voice.
Why don't you quit
the good-guy act?
The real you isn't interested
in helping people.
Deep inside, you want to kill.
You're itching to kill
and kill and kill.
And I finally realized....
that the one speaking
was myself.
I'm finally free!
I'll kill anyone who
gets in my way!
A totally different evil
lurked in my heart.
And that evil made me
kill again and again.
Not long afterward, I met
Bankotsu and
joined the Band of Seven.
And killing felt like such a
natural thing to do.
The other me has killed
so many, many people.
And the doctor in me was
helpless to do anything.
No matter how many lives
I saved....
No matter how I tried
to make a difference....
my soul cannot be redeemed.
Dr. Suikotsu....
Good and evil coexist in
all men.
You must not give in to
the evil in you.
No, Lady Kikyo....
I would probably do
exactly the same thing.
And I cannot endure that thought.
Please, Lady Kikyo....
remove the shard
and release my soul.
Dr. Suikotsu.
Please Lady Kikyo....
I beg you.
Well, Kikyo...
Dead beings like us all end up
with the same fate.
I'll take it as a memento.
Dr. Suikotsu!
This is fine.
This is as it should be.
See ya!
Suikotsu, may you find peace.
Umm.... Priestess....
Thank you for saving me.
You're not hurt?
You must've been scared.
Uh-huh.
But this person....
Somehow....
Good-bye!
I must leave this place, too.
Before the souls within me fade
and I cannot move.
The priestess who
put Inuyasha under seal.
She is just like those others.
The undead... reeking with the smell
of bone and grave dirt.
Did she get a glimpse
of her own fate?
Lord Sesshomaru?
Rin, let us go.
Okay!
I want them to return.
Kohaku....
We must not let them get away.
I guess we were walking
around all night.
But I don't understand.
Why did that apparition
make us do that?
This....!
This can't be....!
What is it?
A cape made from
glowing moss.
A Demon Slayer uses it
for night raids.
Kohaku was here!
Sango....
Let's go, Miroku!
Koga....
Koga!
Don't die, Koga!
What's Inuyasha thinking?
Beautiful weather....
To avenge Ginkotsu's death,
Renkotsu has his eyes
on Koga's Sacred Jewel shards!
The river is covered with oil.
There's nowhere for you to run!
He has exploding bombs!
He's gonna blow up this place!
You won't live either!
I will not die!
Only you will die!
As if I'd let you!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Vanished in a River of Flames"
Did the mutt get blown to bits?!