Ugh!
Die Inuyasha!
In order to become a
full-fledged demon...
the half-demon Inuyasha required
fragments of the Sacred Jewel.
But someone tricked
Inuyasha and Kikyo...
into hating each other
and fighting.
The demon behind this cruel scheme...
was Naraku.
Why did you betray me, Inuyasha?!
W-wha!
So if you keep gathering these
Sacred Jewel fragments...
you'll come across Naraku?
I'm gonna avenge Kikyo's death...
I'll find him and send him to hell!
We got a good haul today, Chief!
Look at these bales of rice!
For a puny village, they
sure had a hoard.
Let's hurry, Chief.
Demons are supposed to appear
around here after dark.
Can't be a mercenary if
you're 'fraid of demons!
- Chief look!
- Huh?
That's a mere mortal.
Interesting armor he's got.
Kill 'im and strip 'im!
Well done!
You are the one and only
Lord Sesshomaru!
Slaying that blue demon and taking
his arm was a splendid idea!
Are you blind?
This is already useless!
Oh... gone bad again?
Arghhh!
Find a demon with a
more suitable arm.
Or else... I'll kill you!
Arghhh!
Hah... I'm so tired of this life.
And it's all the fault of
that Inuyasha...
for cutting off Lord Sesshomaru's arm.
Die!
No... I don't hate that sword.
Just that half-demon Inuyasha!
The Tetsusaiga belongs with
Lord Sesshomaru!
We will take it back from
Inuyasha without fail!
Even if I find another arm,
it'll be useless after a while.
You seem to be troubled.
Pardon me, but are you Inuyasha's
elder brother, Sesshomaru?
Who are you?
Like you, I despise Inuyasha.
It was rude of me, but
I overheard you talking.
May I suggest that you
use this arm?
Don't jest! That's a human arm!
Precisely.
However, it's not JUST
a human arm.
It's a human arm with a
Sacred Jewel fragment imbedded in it.
A Sacred Jewel fragment?
This arm will empower you...
to wield the Tetsusaiga,
Inuyasha's fabled sword.
The Tetsusaiga is known as the
protector of humans.
Presently, a demon like you cannot
touch the Tetsusaiga.
Humph... You mentioned that
you hate Inuyasha.
Do you intend to use me
to kill Inuyasha?
- Exactly.
- How dare you?!
Interesting. I'll take the arm.
Lord Sesshomaru!
One more thing...
This hive.
I'm sure it'll come in
very handy.
Tell me your name.
It is Naraku.
Naraku?
I shall remember it.
I'm so glad we're not sleeping
in the forest!
We get to eat a hot meal and
sleep under a roof! Heaven!
Well, excuse me for making you
sleep in the wild so often!
Inuyasha, you take offense so
easily these days.
Hate the fact that it was Miroku
who got us shelter here, huh?
Soft, fluffy beddings are
sooo nice!
Hah!
That should do it.
Now the ominous black clouds that
hover over this mansion...
will disappear for good.
Thank you so much, Lord Monk!
My goodness! When you came
suddenly and informed me...
that there were evil clouds
overhead...
I was so afraid of what
might happen!
But now that you have exorcised
this place...
I can put my fears to rest.
It's just part of a monk's duty.
Oh... such bliss! Such bliss!
Thank you for the food!
Finished with the
exorcism?
Now then, I can rest.
Hey Miroku... Something
still bothers me.
Yes?
When we're desperately looking
for a place to sleep...
you suddenly see a black cloud over
the finest mansion in the area.
How did that happen,
I wonder?
Huh? Why bring that up now?
You know the saying,
"A lie is sometimes expedient."
W-what?!
Lie? Was the black cloud a lie?
I figured it was a lie.
W-what a shyster!
Oh yes! He gave me a
gift of dumplings, too.
Yea!
Hey, don't look so happy!
Calm down.
W-what's that?
Aghh! It's coming this way!
Something big is coming.
Let's run!
W-why you! Can't just
eat and run!
But it's big!
We're no match for it.
Impossible! Stupid!
Like committing suicide!
What a guy!
I sense Sacred Jewel fragments.
It's heading this way
with enormous speed!
A Sacred Jewel fragment
coming here?!
What luck!
If it's the Sacred Jewel,
I'm willing to make the sacrifice!
Hold it, Miroku!
What's that sound?
That trembling!
W-what!?
Sesshomaru!
Slow as usual, huh, Inuyasha?
Damn you, Sesshomaru!
Whaddya want?
Don't ask me stupid questions.
I'm here for the Tetsusaiga!
You still haven't given up?!
Are they acquaintances?
That's Inuyasha's older brother.
Brother?
Unlike half-demon Inuyasha,
this one's a full-fledged one.
He's still after the Tetsusaiga.
He couldn't become
one with the sword...
and couldn't even lift it!
That's right! He shouldn't be
able to touch it even now!
Draw your sword, Inuyasha.
Or will you hand it
over quietly?
Shaddup! This time, I'll cut off
more than your arm!
Inuyasha... You still haven't
mastered the use of the Tetsusaiga.
W-what?!
Cut your jokes, damn you!
Such pitiful swordsmanship...
You can't handle that
large sword.
Arghhh!
His arm is rotting!
It's the poison in his nails!
If you don't release the Tetsusaiga,
your arm will rot and fall off.
Damn!
Before that happens!
He's resisting him!
I'll slit you in half!
Damn him...
Damn!
What?!
Sesshomaru has a hold
of the Tetsusaiga!
W-why is Sesshomaru able
to hold the Tetsusaiga?
I shall show you, Inuyasha...
The Tetsusaiga's true power.
Jaken!
Yes, my lord! I shall summon all
the mountain demons!
Come forth!
Watch me well, Inuyasha.
In one stroke...
The power to slay a hundred demons
in one stroke...
W-what?!
The mountain...
Not only the demons, he
destroyed the mountain!
Now that is the true
power of the Tetsusaiga...
the supreme sword forged from
our father's fang!
Unfortunately, it does not have the
power to choose his owner!
Do you realize now that
a half-demon like you...
can never master it?
D-damn!!
Inuyasha!
Hold it, Kagome!
I'll go!
Shippo, stay behind, too!
Then... your right hand!
Become a victim of the Tetsusaiga...
That's a fitting end for you.
As if I'd let someone like him
take the Tetsusaiga!
I can't stay quiet any longer.
Enough of this silly sibling rivalry.
Hey!
Hmmm?
That monk?
Stay back, Miroku!
You can't handle this alone!
Shaddup! Get behind me!
Don't be so stubborn!
W-what?! You!
Is that the monk that
Naraku mentioned?
There should be a young
monk with Inuyasha.
He may prove to be more
troublesome than Inuyasha.
Hah! He looks like a mere mortal.
Aghh!
Sesshomaru, leave this monk to me!
No sense in wasting
your time with him.
That's true. I'll just watch.
Onward! Smash them!
Everyone, get back!
Heaven's wrath!
N-no-o... Stop!
Heavenly power!
It's the Wind Tunnel!
Miroku, you look great!
Inuyasha, you too.
Don't say it like an afterthought.
Please try using this...
It is the hive of the Saimyosho,
the insect of Hell.
You will find this very useful...
in plugging the Wind Tunnel
in that monk's right hand.
Humph... We'll see if he
was right.
W-what's?
Those bugs...
They're not being sucked in,
they're flying at him!
They're!
Inuyasha... Take over!
- Miroku!
- What's wrong, Miroku!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Are you all right, Miroku?
I've been poisoned by
those insects...
Poison?
Foxfire!
Shippo!
I can fight these bugs
at least!
Shippo!
Miroku!
Wait here, I'll look for
an antidote!
Inuyasha! Help Miroku!
Hey, Miroku!
Do your share!
Sorry, Inuyasha...
The poison's weakened me...
I can't believe those petty insects
shut down my Wind Tunnel...
Blades of Blood!!
C'mon, Miroku!
Get your ass over here!
Damn... He said something
about poison...
Is it fatal?!
He's coming!
How hopeless he is.
Damn it! What do I do?!
One swing of the Tetsusaiga,
and we're done for!
This is it.
Die!
You are such a fool!
You can run and hide.
That would totally be expected
of you.
Living in this world only adds
to your disgrace.
Will you shut up?!
Getting a hold of one sword
sure loosened your mouth!
Well, lemme tell you something.
When you kill someone, make
sure you do it right!
Otherwise, you may just end up...
eating your words!!
I've had just about... enough!
He's resisting the Tetsusaiga!
That's the sheathe of the Tetsusaiga!
I was just about to be killed
by Lord Sesshomaru!
Even more than the monk's
heavenly power...
Lord Sesshomaru's disregard
for ally or foe when he kills...
is a hundred-fold more frightening.
Oh dear... I fear for the future.
You!
Something really bothers me.
We have never met, yet it's as though
you had those insects just to trap me.
What's going on?!
Huh?! Well... err...
Miroku!
A weak monk and a
puny fox-child...
I, Jaken, can handle
you alone!
You hope to resist me
with a sheathe, huh?
Well, this is no ordinary sheathe!
You'll soon see... when I
crack open that head of yours!
Stupid things!
Illusory Top!
Fool!
Dang it! My power isn't enough...
Go, Shippo!
Never mind me!
Miroku!
The sheathe, huh?!
What sheathe?!
One swing... Just one more swing.
Huh?!
The Tetsusaiga's transformation
has been cancelled!
Sesshomaru!
The next one is aimed
at your heart!
Kagome!
Inuyasha... Make your escape!
Hurry!
That young woman's arrow reverses
the Tetsusaiga's transformation.
Could Kagome really be
the reincarnation of the priestess?
The Wind Tunnel is shut down.
And the Tetsusaiga has been stolen!
Sesshomaru has Inuyasha
backed into a corner!
The Sacred Jewel burst forth
from my body...
so maybe I can summon the
special powers...
like the priestess, Kikyo!
We combined forces to fight!
So Inuyasha, what's the problem?!
Next on Inuyasha, "Go Home to
Your Own Time, Kagome!"
Don't miss it!