Huh?!
Come out. I've known
you were there for some time now.
Kikyo, Inuyasha is bitter about you.
He's half dead, thanks to the power
I, Naraku, have gained...
since you handed over
your Sacred Jewel to me.
Just a while longer...
Soon, the Jewel will become whole.
Kikyo willingly handed over the
Sacred Jewel to me.
Why Kikyo?!
With the Sacred Jewel
you gave him...
Naraku has increased
his evil powers.
Just what were you thinking?!
Do you still hate me so much...Kikyo?
Kikyo!
Inuyasha! Are you in pain?!
It's to be expected.
The Tetsusaiga protected you...
but you still took the full force
of the Wind Scar.
Even Sango...
She shouldn't be moved
for a while longer.
She acts brave, but she got hit
with the Hiraikotsu.
Where's Kagome?
She and Miroku went in search of
food and more medicinal herbs.
Wait, Kirara.
I'll go and get some cool water.
Inuyasha and Sango
are injured badly.
And Naraku has created two
frightening demons...
out of his own body.
What's going to happen?!
Soul Collectors!
Is Kikyo near?
Leggo!
Inuyasha!
Kikyo!
Don't go! You'll be killed!
Inuyasha! Inuyasha!
Kikyo...
I must see you!
Inuyasha...
Ki... kyo!
You are alive, Inuyasha.
I'm glad.
Kikyo! What're you up to?!
Did you...
really hand over your Sacred Jewel
to Naraku?!
I did. In order to cast Naraku
into oblivion.
Whaddya mean?!
Naraku is increasing his powers now!
He's already created two more
demons out of his own body...
Kagura of the Wind and
Kanna of the Void!
So Inuyasha and that Kikyo
know each other.
Kagura, follow Kikyo and
find out what she's up to.
She can't be trusted.
You wanted to kill me.
Isn't that why you gave Naraku
your Sacred Jewel?!
As if I'd let the likes of Naraku
take your life!
Do not forget this, Inuyasha!
Naraku is our bitterest enemy.
It's no fun just spying on them.
Inuyasha is half-dead.
He hasn't even
picked up on my scent.
I'll kill him and Kikyo both!
K-Kagura!
Next is your head.
She escaped...
Inuyasha, Naraku will only grow
stronger and stronger.
Do not let him kill you!
Until I am able to cast both
Naraku and the Jewel out of this world...
your life is mine.
No one will have you!
Kikyo...
Shippo, are you sure?
Did Kikyo's Soul Collectors
really appear?
Inuyasha was lured out by them!
Inuyasha...
did you go to see Kikyo?!
Kagome...
Inuyasha!
Are you all right?
Ah, yeah...
Say! Oh, sorry.
You did see Kikyo!
It's written all over your face!
You can't even look me in the eye!
You're always like that!
Hey! It wasn't a rendezvous
or anything like that!
So he did see her!
l-I know that, stupid!
Oh dear...
I can understand Inuyasha's
hesitancy...
And what did you find out, Inuyasha?
Did Kikyo really give Naraku
her Sacred Jewel?
Yeah...
In other words, Kikyo has
joined forces with Naraku?
No!
I don't know what Kikyo
intends to do...
but...
Kagome. What's wrong with her?
What're you doing?!
Poor Kagome...
I'll say!
When she's been so worried
about you, Inuyasha! Right?
Inuyasha was hurt so badly...
all because Kikyo gave Naraku
the Sacred Jewel.
Yet he still defends her!
Inuyasha, you fool!
W-what's that?!
Something's going on
in the barn.
Let's go and check!
- A demon!
- It's eating the horse!
Damn...what's this demon?
Some brainless glutton!
Sister. Did you just call me
a brainless glutton?
He's toying with me!
He can read my mind!
Sango, are you able to move now?
I can manage...
Don't push yourself!
Would you like a little
more medicine for the pain?
I'm okay. Besides, isn't it
dangerous to stay here?
Kagura was nearby...
I'm all right.
Kagome, go tend to Inuyasha.
Never mind him!
It seems he can walk.
Apologize to Kagome, Inuyasha!
I'm caught in between and
I don't like it!
I'd much rather stroke
Sango's white skin...
No thanks!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?!
I smell a dead man.
Huh? Dead man?
A demon came!
All the villagers have
been devoured.
Demon?
With a spider scar
on its back!
Spider scar on his back?!
Another one of Naraku's
incarnations!
H-help!
H-he was dead all along!
He was probably being controlled
by Kagura with her fan.
This is a trap.
A lure to meet the three demons.
Will you go?
You can't, Inuyasha!
Your wounds aren't healed yet!
I have no choice!
Sending a dead man here means
they know our whereabouts.
Yes... which means it's useless
to try and escape.
Well then, I'm going!
Sooner or later,
they are gonna attack!
One or two kids, just let them go!
I told Naraku I'd annihilate
the entire village.
So I'll kill every human!
And every horse, dog and fowl!
I'm not interested in keeping
you company. Do as you please.
Don't cry, Yuki.
If we hide under the hay,
it won't find us!
Brother!
So you thought that hiding in
the hay would protect you?
You cried to your ma and pa
to save you, huh?
I ate them up a while ago.
I'm not lying. Look inside my belly!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Run away!
W-what?!
That demon...
Has the spider scar
on its back!
So you're the third incarnation
of Naraku?
So you've drawn the Tetsusaiga.
You thought I was big in body
and small in power, huh?
W- what?!
He can read my mind!
Yes, Inuyasha.
I am able to read my opponent's mind.
My sisters, Kagura and Kanna,
were simply the opening acts...
until I, Goshinki, made my debut!
Hah! You're nothing but
a blabbermouth!
You're nothing!
Didn't I tell you? I can read minds.
You seem to be in pain.
What? Have you reached your limit?
Damn you! I've had just about enough!
Take this!
W-what?!
I can see right through
your swordplay!
Inuyasha!
No! He's not in shape to fight!
- Wind Tunnel!
- No!
Naraku's poison insects!
Monk, thought you could
suck me up into that Wind Tunnel?
Too bad I know
all of your weaknesses.
Kagome...
forget about shooting your
arrow at me.
Before you draw your arrow,
I'll kill you.
Sango, you can't fight.
You still can't move
due to that blow you received...
from your Hiraikotsu!
What about me?!
Hey! Why do you ignore only me?!
Don't worry, Shippo.
He's just playing with you.
You're those kids...
I told you to run!
Why are you still?
Did those...
belong to your ma and pa?
"Unforgivable... I'll kill him..."...
Isn't that what you're thinking,
Inuyasha?
Don't make me laugh.
You're merely a half-demon, Inuyasha.
Demon blood courses through
half of you...
yet you still take pity on humans?
Shaddup!
I'll kill you!
The line which brings out the
ultimate power of the Tetsusaiga...
the Wind Scar!
Inuyasha, you're trying to cut through
the Wind Scar and blast me away.
If you already know...
prepare to die!
He cast away the Wind Scar!
Stupid!
Then I'll just deliver a
direct blow to your head!
The Tetsusaiga is just another
dog's fang!
The Tetsusaiga has been broken!
I guess this proves that a
demon's fangs are stronger.
He bit apart my Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha...
your mind is a total blank now.
Your sword is broken
and so is your spirit, huh?
Or, are you dead?
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Get back, Kagome!
Miroku!
Monk... even if you lost your
life from deadly poison...
you would try to suck me
into your Wind Tunnel?
Miroku!
Monk!
Don't rush to your death...
I'm going to devour you
one by one anyway.
And I'll start with you, Kagome.
Inuyasha...lnuyasha...
Fool!
Inuyasha is already...
What's this?!
Inuyasha's mind...!
What's the matter, Goshinki?
I thought you could read my mind!
l-Inuyasha!
What's happened to Inuyasha?
His face...!
I don't understand...
Inuyasha, why have you
transformed?
Who knows?!
Before you worry about me,
say your prayers, Goshinki.
What's going on?!
Inuyasha's mind is completely
different from just a minute ago.
There's no sadness, no fear,
no confusion...not even anger.
He's delighted
at the thought of killing me!
You half-demon!
I'll rip you apart with my fangs!
The demon blood that flows
through my body...
Silence!
isn't like yours!
This half-demon...
is in a class much
higher than you!
Goshinki! I enjoyed that!
Inuyasha...
Inuyasha, what happened to you?!
I feel the blood
rushing through my body.
What is this?! This feeling... ?
I...haven't had enough killing!
Inuyasha...
Don't get near me!
I don't know what I'll do next!
What's happened to you, Inuyasha?!
The evil side of Inuyasha
is growing stronger.
Yes. He's just like
a full-blooded demon!
Inuyasha...
the enemy is gone.
Don't get near me!
Kagome!
Don't get near him, Miss Kagome!
Inuyasha...
- Kagome!
- Watch out!
Inuyasha, sit!
W-what're you doing?!
- He's back to normal.
- What?
I'm so relieved, Inuyasha!
What's the matter?
W-what? I...
Sesshomaru gets a hold of
the demon's fang...
and has a frightening sword forged.
One swing of this sword
bisects Jaken.
This sword, Tokijin, was forged
by swordsmith Kaijinbo...
who was banished by
his master Totosai...
but why does he come
after Inuyasha?!
Why does the sword exude evil aura?
Inuyasha who has reverted to
a human form is in danger!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kaijinbo's Evil Sword!"
Don't miss it!