Inuyasha at last broke through
Naraku's barrier!
But before he could render
the final blow,
Naraku, who had been seriously
injured, escaped.
That was only because Naraku resorted
to a dastardly trick using Kohaku.
But who would have thought that
Sesshomaru would save Kohaku!
But with Naraku's disappearance...
we were actually grateful
for the brief respite.
Especially Inuyasha.
Our journey's aim is to destroy Naraku
and gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel.
We continue onward!
You'd better back down,
or I'll get serious.
Short-tempered as always.
Huh?
Who are you?!
Sending your wolves at me?
You have a grudge or something
against me?
Isn't that Ayame, the granddaughter
of the Wolf-Demon Tribe elder?
I heard she went north with
the elder a long time ago.
She's back?
Ayame?
I came to give you
Gramps' message.
Message?
You're going to take me
for your wife.
You promised!
W-Wife?!
You have a Sacred Jewel shard
in your possession.
With that, you'll be worthy
of ruling the clan.
So come with me
and let's get married.
D-Don't joke!
Why should I marry you?!
Huh? You don't remember?
Remember what?
You promised to marry me when
I came down from the mountain.
Koga, when'd you make
such a promise?!
What about Kagome?!
W-What're you doing?!
Gramps told me to bring you back,
with force if necessary!
Fool!
We're gonna fall!
Hey, are you all right?!
Let go of my hand!
Hey you!
Don't let him get away!
l-I already have a fiancée
named Kagome who's gonna marry me!
I wouldn't have made any promises
to marry you!
Fiancée?!
Kagome?
Hey wait, Koga!
Has he really forgotten?
He promised....
On the night of the lunar rainbow.
And Naraku's whereabouts?
We checked everywhere.
But there were no rumors
about a demon named Naraku.
I see....
It seems Inuyasha hasn't caught
any scent of Naraku either.
Well....
I can't believe that a demonic aura
that strong could disappear so easily.
Can't be helped if you
can't smell anything.
Kagome, you don't sense
the Sacred Jewel shards either?
Not at all.
No sense getting overly worried.
If we just keep collecting
the Sacred Jewel shards as usual,
I'm sure Naraku will come after
them himself.
Forget it!
We can't just wait around!
But there's no other way.
But I wonder how many
more shards there are....
besides the ones
that Naraku has in his possession.
Well....
I have three shards here.
Then there's the one
imbedded in Kohaku's back.
And Koga has a couple, too.
It was quite a long time ago....
But he DID promise.
Don't overdo it.
And when it gets to
be too hard,
I'll make you my wife, Ayame.
I was still a child....
So if Koga doesn't remember,
I guess it can't be helped.
Maybe I should return
to the mountains.
My territory is being overrun.
Without the Sacred Jewel,
we cannot overcome this.
Find Koga and bring him here
as soon as possible.
I can't! I can't go home!
I have to try one more time!
Damn! What's going on?
This castle reeks with
Naraku's scent.
But there's no miasma or
any sign of him at all.
This mark...
Koga, the castle is
totally empty.
Let's go.
Where?
Where else?
Find the mutt and
question him.
That mutt's smell also
lingers here.
Something happened between
him and Naraku.
I get it!
Inuyasha might know something!
Hey wait!
Don't leave us!
Naraku isn't here.
But if he's nearby...
He's sure to come after me
for the Sacred Jewel shards
in my legs.
I know. Koga was here
without a doubt.
But....
What is this place? It gives
me the creeps.
What is it?
W-What is that?!
What was that demon?!
Ginta!
Hakkaku!
Oh no! It's Ayame!
Why's she here?!
How should I know?!
Hey you two! What were you doing
in that creepy castle?!
Where is Koga?
What's that demon?!
Demon?!
Did it appear from
Naraku's castle?!
Naraku's....castle?
You don't know because you've
been in the mountains with the elder.
Just recently, our comrades in
the north and east were killed.
And the one behind it is
a demon named Naraku!
Koga has been looking for
Naraku to get revenge.
I didn't....
It's coming again!
Huh?
What's the matter, Kagome?
I sense the Sacred Jewel.
Huh?
That whirlwind!
Hah! I thought I smelled
something unpleasant.
He's upset already.
That Koga! Coming here
to flirt with Kagome again!
Inuyasha!
Koga...!
Koga!
Hey Kagome!
How've you been?
Umm...
Hey mutt! Where's Naraku?
'Fess up!
Is that your business here, Wolf?
What else?
Then quit flirting around
with Kagome!
Just answer my question, stupid!
We're still looking for Naraku, too.
That's what I don't understand.
Why did Naraku abandon his castle
and run?
Wanna know, Wolf?
It's 'cuz I busted through
Naraku's barrier!
With my Tetsusaiga!
Hah! Shocked?
Serves you right!
More than shocked! You got that close,
and you let Naraku escape?!
Stupid fool!
What a shame!
If I had been there,
I'd have destroyed Naraku!
Why you...!
If I let you go on....!
Inuyasha! Calm down!
Jumping to dumb conclusions....!
I'll get 'im!
A miasma....
It's Naraku's scent!
Koga!
There's something weird....
coming from Naraku's castle!
Huh?
What the...!
It's huge!
W-What is it?!
Another incarnation of
Naraku?
It's a Hair Demon?!
That's what was in
the castle?
No mistake about it!
Ayame saw it.
Ayame?
She was with you?
Where is she?
I dunno!
We got separated when
we started running.
What's going on?
Why didn't I sense this
demon sooner?
Sacred Jewel shards....
Kagome, stay back!
This pile of hair is after you!
All right!
You're an ugly bastard....
but it looks like you can talk!
Why you...!
Such brute strength!
Answer me!
Where is Naraku?!
Kagome!
Mutt! You can take care
of the demon!
I'll take Kagome to
a safe place!
Hey!
Why you...!
The nerve!
It fell?
Damn it!
It wasn't too strong for
a demon created by Naraku.
No, it went over on purpose.
Its goal is the Sacred Jewel
shards.
Hey Koga!
Where're you taking me?
Where? Someplace where the
demon won't come after us.
Koga!
Ayame!
Ayame?
That's a mortal woman!
Just what are you doing?!
I don't have time to
explain to you!
Kagome, run.
Kagome?!
Kagome....That's the fiancée
you mentioned!
F-Fiancée?
Whose?
My Koga's!
Koga?!
Why'd you say that?!
It's only natural
since I love you!
Don't just decide things
like that!
Koga is my fiancé!
You can drop dead!
As if you can use
your tricks on me!
Keep it up,
and I'll get serious!
Falling in love with
a mortal!
Where's your Wolf-Demon Tribe pride?!
Shut up! I love Kagome!
You have no right
to tell me anything!
Ka-go-me?!
Err... Yes?
I don't like it!
Huh?
It sounds like my name!
Only the final syllable "me."
Even if you want to
marry that girl,
you can't go against
the tribe's code!
A code made up by
the elders!
When did I ever say
I'd marry you?!
You...
promised me....
on the night of
the lunar rainbow....
Don't you remember?
Lunar rainbow?
But the moon appears at night...
Do rainbows come out
at night?
It was when I was
still a child....
During the training Gramps
had instructed me to do...
I got lost near the nest of
the Birds of Paradise demons.
I was about to be devoured.
Hey....
Come with me.
Huh?
The elder is worried.
It must not be easy being
the elder's granddaughter.
Is he going to
the northern mountains, too?
Uh-huh.... He said he
would train me there.
Hmm.... I see.
You're going to use that
flower in training?
Uh-huh.
It has the same name
as me....
so I'm taking it to
the mountains, too.
- Umm...
- Huh?
Thank you for saving me.
Don't overdo it.
If it gets too hard,
I'll make you my wife, Ayame.
Really?
Yeah, when you come down
from the mountains.
Look....
A rainbow.
A lunar rainbow!
l-Is that true....?
Did I really say that?
It's such a romantic story!
And you don't remember?!
I kept those words
in my heart....
and endured all the training with Gramps,
and lived in the mountain!
Hey Koga!
How can you forget such words?!
You're despicable!
Kagome....
Stupid Inuyasha!
You let Naraku's demon go!
You're the stupid one, Koga!
You're Ayame's fiancé!
How dare you flirt
with Kagome!
What fiancé?
Don't hide it!
Whether it's arranged or not,
she's gonna be your bride!
Shut up!
I still have things to do!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Koga's Bride-To-Be"
Sorry Ayame....
That's how it goes.
Stop the act, stupid wolf!