Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku with my Tetsusaiga!
Naraku slays Kikyo,
then sends his new infant incarnation
to attack the darkness in our hearts.
Inuyasha has gone in
search of Kikyo
and is unable to come
to save me!
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Help!
Help me, Inuyasha!
Inuyasha is....
Inuyasha is searching
for Kikyo.
Inuyasha won't come to
save me.
Inuyasha...!
There!
I've grasped the darkness
in your heart.
Now hold me tightly.
Let our souls unite and...
become my eyes.
Inuyasha...
Find peace in death!
Why you...!
It's hard work to fight
without killing them.
It's easier to deal with demons.
This isn't good.
It's taking too much time.
Kagome, be safe!
Hmph!
They're still alive.
Furthermore, they don't intend to kill
the castle's soldiers...
They're easygoing, as usual.
But soon, they'll want to kill them.
After all, the soldiers are intent
on killing the monk and his friends.
The evil will of the soldiers
will become contagious
and soon, the humans will
kill each other.
The human heart is weak.
Hatred is easily bred.
This girl is no different...
Kikyo!
I followed the directions
of that old priest
and came to the river's edge.
But I don't catch Kikyo's scent
around here.
And there isn't a villager around
who's seen a priestess.
What's going on anyway?
This scent!
Demons?!
They're gone...
l-I think I eluded them...
But Inuyasha's nowhere
to be found...
And Kirara and I have
become separated.
I don't have any other
options left....
I guess I have to use this.
What're you doing, Shippo?
D-Don't scare me like that!
Kirara?
You're okay!
What? Kagome was taken
away to a castle?!
While I searched for Kikyo...
Was this...
a trap?!
Kagome's scent!
This way!
Kirara, let's hurry, too!
Forgive me!
Oh let me be in time!
Do not falter! Kill them!
It's over for us!
P-Please save us...
I'm sorry Sango, if I use my Wind
Tunnel, we could escape alive...
However...
I don't want to live at
the expense of others!
But Miroku!
Shoot!
We must go and save Kagome!
Absolutely!
It's not in my nature to give up!
Miroku! Sango!
Shoot!
Take this!
W-What...?!
Inuyasha!
Why you...!
Curse you demon!
Are you the leader?
Get out of here, you all!
Y-Yes!
They're mere humans...
This smell... Could it be.?!
Inuyasha, Kagome is inside the castle!
Right!
Dammit! This is Kagura's smell!
Let's go, Miroku!
Yes!
This priest...
He said that Kikyo was alive.
It WAS a trap!
Kagome!
Damn!
I'm too late...
Hey there!
If it isn't Kanna.
What? A Sacred Jewel shard...
Implant that tainted Sacred Jewel
shard into Kagome.
Then Kagome will be
completely under our control.
My mission is done.
Once this is over, I shall go
into hiding.
Hmm... With this, Kagome will
become Naraku's slave.
The same fate as Kohaku.
Kohaku...?
This impure light...
You intend to place that shard
in me?
No!
Huh?! I-I can't move!
Is it because this baby...
has a grasp upon my soul?
I have to break free...
I have to free myself
from him...
Wait, Kagura.
Huh?
She's a stubborn one.
She's regained consciousness.
Come save me... lnuyasha!
It's useless.
You know, don't you, that
he won't come to save you?
Rather than you, Inuyasha
has chosen...
Kikyo!
Dammit!
I'm such an idiot!
Go, Inuyasha!
Kagome!
This is no time to hesitate!
Hurry!
Kikyo is waiting.
Yeah...
Forgive me.
I'm making the same mistake again...
Inuyasha...
I lost Kikyo...
I thought I was the only one hurting...
and acted selfishly...
Now I'm about to lose
another precious person...
Dammit!
Wait for me, Kagome!
Wait until I get there!
Don't you die!
Think hard, Kagome...
When you learned that
Kikyo had died...
didn't you actually feel happy?
The woman who came between
you was gone...
But the moment Inuyasha heard
that Kikyo was alive,
he went after her again.
Whether she is dead or alive,
Inuyasha's heart belongs
to Kikyo.
Don't you feel bitter towards Inuyasha?
Don't you hate Kikyo?
It's okay to hate.
You are not wrong to hate.
Fill your heart with hatred
once more.
And let me grasp your soul!
So she gave in...
I hate Inuyasha...?
I loathe Kikyo...?
Yes...
But...
Huh?
What's going on?
She repelled the shard.
Hmm... Here's something even
this kid can't do.
Huh?
N-No...
She spoke.
M- My suggestive powers...
have no effect on this girl.
What you're saying is
all wrong.
Even though, rationally, I can accept
that Inuyasha can't forget Kikyo...
I still feel jealous.
Kikyo!
But....
Resenting Inuyasha...
And being jealous of Kikyo...
These are feelings that
any human would have.
And they're not used to curse people
like you tell me to.
There have been numerous times
when Inuyasha left my side
because he understood
how difficult it was for me.
There were times when I did
wish that Kikyo was gone....
but I felt bad that I even harbored
such thoughts...
Still...
all these feelings...
it all means that....
that I'm...
I'm in love with Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Inuyasha...
You came for me.
Kagome!
Kagome...
No wonder Naraku
can't stand that girl.
Why you...!
What did you do
to Kagome?!
Hmph...
I just tugged at her
soul a little bit.
Since you can't seem to
get over Kikyo...
there's a bit of darkness
in that girl's heart.
It's too bad.
One more step, and I would have
broken her soul.
Just what the hell are you?!
Inuyasha!
You're here...!
Are you all right, Kagome?!
Kagura! Kanna!
What? You're still alive?
The monk and the Demon Slayer...
How many soldiers did
you kill?
This infant... Was he manipulating
the castle's soldiers?
I hate to disappoint you,
but we don't kill
unnecessarily.
This infant...
the ghastly color of his skin...
Is he an incarnation created from
the clumps of flesh
which Naraku
was producing at Mt. Hakurei?
Are you Naraku's human heart?
Why do you think that?
Naraku hid himself away
at Mt. Hakurei
in order to create a more
powerful body.
And...
to cast away his human heart.
Naraku said he cut away his
human heart
which continued to yearn for Kikyo.
In order to get rid of Kikyo.
This kid...
is the human heart which
had feelings for Kikyo?
That can't be!
Toying with people's hearts
in a dastardly way....!
Well then...
Perhaps I am indeed the human
heart which Naraku once possessed.
I can clearly see into a person's heart.
Their weaknesses
and frailties.
I know just what to do
in order to make one suffer,
feel sorrow or hate.
I can see it all so clearly.
If there is one feeling that
I did NOT inherit from Naraku...
It's the anguish of yearning
for Kikyo...
Where do you think that
feeling went?
The disgusting clumps of flesh you
saw at Mt. Hakurei...
That is it.
That was the abandoned heart?
And so...
I am free of suffering and sadness.
Hah! In other words,
you're just a monster created
from Naraku's heart...
twisted and grotesque!
That's all I need to hear!
Prepare to die!
Wind Scar!
This kid...
Can he put up a barrier?
Damn, he's one creepy brat!
M-My Wind Scar is being sucked up!
Oh no!
Everyone, run!
Damn!
That kid...
He countered the Wind Scar!
Don't think this is over.
I'll come to see you again.
Shaddup, kid!
If you touch Kagome again...
That girl is the only one,
since Kikyo is gone...
who can see the Sacred Jewel shards.
What?!
Very, very soon...
Once Kagome's eyes become mine,
the Sacred Jewel will become whole.
A Sacred Jewel filled
with hate.
Are you crazy?!
As if Kagome would do
anything for Naraku!
Hmph!
There are countless ways
to corrupt her.
Inuyasha.... As long as you cannot
forget Kikyo.
Damn them!
Kagome... I'm sorry
I left you all alone.
I'll never let you fall into
Naraku's hands again.
Never...
will I let you suffer
like Kikyo.
Huh? What's wrong?
You look listless.
Quiet! I need to sleep.
Kagome's soul is
stronger than I expected.
I used up too much energy.
What's with this kid?
Did his struggle with Kagome
tire him out?
He may be Naraku's
infant incarnation,
but he's not all-powerful, huh?
I'm sorry, Kaede.
Say no more, Inuyasha.
Sister Kikyo was forced
to return to the living.
And while here, her soul
only suffered.
So....
I couldn't save Kikyo's soul.
For a second time, she was killed
by that bastard Naraku.
Sister Kikyo's soul has faded.
She won't need to suffer anymore.
But....!
So Inuyasha, you need not
suffer anymore either.
Yes, my sister is gone.
But....
I would have liked to bury her
bones here at least.
Will Kagome be all right?
She continues to sleep
even after returning here.
Inuyasha is with her.
She'll be fine. I'm sure.
Kagome, are you awake?
Oh, I see....
Inuyasha, you did come for me.
Are you okay?
Take it easy.
Kagome, I'm sorry
about what happened.
I wasn't with you and....
It's okay.
It's not okay!
I let you fall into
harm's way.
Any later and I would've
lost Kagome, too.
But, if you hear news of Kikyo's
whereabouts,
you'll go off to look for her
again, won't you?
No, I won't!
I won't ever leave you again!
Liar!
I am not!
You're the type who'd go!
How long do you think
I've known you now?
You would go.
No doubt about it!
And when you do go,
I'll be upset.
That's to be expected, right?
Kagome....
Hey, you're mad, aren't you?
Yes, I am, but....
Inuyasha will never
forget Kikyo.
But I still love him...
So there's nothing I can do.
Thanks, Kagome.
I came back to the present hoping
to get some serious studying done!
Chorus!
Drama!
Cooking demonstration?!
Why not?
It's a cultural festival.
Kagome, you didn't help at
all with the preparations,
so you're on standby
for everything!
We're counting on you, Kagome!
And if you mess up,
you'll be sorry!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Don't Boil It!
The Terrifying Dried-Up Demon!"
I'd rather fight a demon
from the Feudal Era!