Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a group
of strangers together.
500 years across time,
theirdestinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
It all started fifty years ago.
My sister Kikyo and Inuyasha...
a love song of their
tragic destiny.
My name is Kaede.
I am an old priestess
who has survived
through a violent age where
wars nevercease.
Sister!
Sister Kikyo!
But back then, I was just
an innocent girl
who knew nothing of
fighting orwar.
Sister Kikyo!
Do not come, Kaede!
Huh?
Oh....
That lady is....
a priestess named Tsubaki,
isn't she?
Hmm?
Is thatgirl yourlittle sister, Kikyo?
Are you sure about this, Kikyo?
I am perfectly capable
of handling this alone.
Take your sister and get back.
You need not worry.
I'm impressed.
Your own sistermay be
in danger,
yet you refuse to budge.
Demons!
A- Amazing!
You are such a cold woman.
No, you are not a woman....
you are definitely a priestess.
Yes, I am a priestess.
That is my destiny.
A strong, proud, beautiful priestess.
In my youthful eyes, my sister
Kikyo was everything.
But I had no idea of the sad fate
which awaited my sister.
Blast you!
This is not over....
not by a long shot!
Where are you?!
Where did you go, half-demon!
Right here!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
The fool!
No one calls me a "half-demon"
and lives.
Chief!
Yes? What's the matter?
It's the limestone cave!
Please come!
There's something wrong
at the limestone cave.
What?
Chief!
Do you know what's happening, Chief?
Huh?
What is this?
Chief! What's happening?
There's no mistake!
This must be Midoriko!
Midoriko? The legendary
priestess who made the Sacred Jewel?!
That's impossible! She's been
dead forhundreds of years!
What is this corpse?
That's the demon we
exterminated the day before.
I think it called itself
Mistress Centipede.
It gave us a lot of trouble,
but we smashed its head,
so it should be dead.
Chief!
Huh?
What is it?
This is it.
Midoriko's soul is reacting
to this.
Chief, could that be....
Yes, I'm seeing it for
the first time, too.
The Sacred Jewel.
What's the matter, Kirara?
Give it back!
Everyone, get away!
That belongs to me!
Chief!
Give back the Sacred Jewel!
Hiraikotsu!
Chief!
Are you all right, Chief?!
It's the power of the Sacred Jewel.
As long as this jewel is nearby,
it will... keep on reviving.
Don't let itget away, Kirara!
Go afterit!
Damn! We can't do anything
about this tainted jewel.
We must find a priestess.
Chief!
Find a priestess with the power
to purify this Sacred Jewel....
My sister Kikyo and I wandered
the countryside training and
exterminating demons.
Are you sure you don't want
yourreward?
Yes. You may have it, Tsubaki.
I see. Well then, thanks.
Kikyo, here is a bit of advice
from one priestess to another.
When a priestess abandons all
human feelings,
hertrue power comes alive.
But if one is a woman,
it's only natural to fall in love.
Love?
Me, fall in love?
Do not forget this.
You must not fall in love.
Do not let a man desire you.
If such a man ever appears
before you,
you will die a violent death.
Humph.... I shall remember
those words.
That Tsubaki is unscrupulous.
Huh?
She just placed a curse
on me.
A curse?
There's nothing to worry about.
Forthere is no way that
I would fall in love.
You won't get away, half-demon!
We'll avenge our olderbrother!
Damn! I didn't know he had
two brothers!
So there you are!
You won't get away!
Well then, take this!
Blades of Blood!
Why you...! Half-demon!
You got a problem with that?!
Wha...?!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Damn! To let these weaklings
hurt me....!
I must become stronger!
I must become much,
much stronger!
Welcome home, Mistress Kikyo.
Mistress Kikyo.... Ademon slayer
came looking for you this morning.
When I explained that
you were away,
he said he'd return tonight.
Ademon slayer?
I wonder what he wants?
Sister! Hurry and
come inside!
Sister! What's the matter?
What is that?
It is known as the Sacred Jewel.
I have been given the duty
of purifying it.
That was the first time I laid
eyes on the Sacred Jewel.
And after she took
custody of the Jewel,
my sister Kikyo's destiny
changed drastically.
Othergirls herage
were burning perfume incense,
coloring theirlips
and cheeks...
and enjoying theiryouthfulness.
I must hurry tonight!
What?!
Damn, it stinks of blood!
A mortal woman?
Is that truly a woman?
Huh?!
It's starting!
How long do you intend to hide?
Are you after the Sacred Jewel, too?
Sacred Jewel? What's that?
If you don't know it,
that's fine.
However, if you do not want
to be killed,
never appear before me again.
What kind of priestess is she....?
Mistress Kikyo!
Kikyo!
Sister Kikyo!
Mistress Kikyo!
Sister!
Kaede....
Are you all right?!
Yes....
Hmm.... He let me live.
I am not without luck.
It's near.... It's very near!
The Sacred Jewel!
I must increase my demon power,
or my body will not last.
So that's what it's all about.
The Sacred Jewel, huh?
Sounds interesting.
And hername is Kikyo....
Hey! Kikyo!
I hear the Sacred Jewel is
a sphere of good fortune
that increases the power
of a demon.
That voice....
I've heard it before.
I see, you're the one who was
hiding in the shadows.
Shaddup!
Give me that Sacred Jewel!
Whaa...!
I understand now. I thought
I sensed a different aura.
You are a half-demon.
With the Sacred Jewel,
you can indeed become
a complete demon.
Would you go that farto
find your place in the world, half-demon?
Do you believe that
is true power?
Shaddup!
I'll become the strongest demon around!
That's what I've decided!
And when I do, I'll kill you!
Humph!
As long as I am the one purifying
and protecting it, that will not happen.
Don't make me laugh!
You reek with the smell
of demon blood!
What? Did I touch a nerve with that, Kikyo?
If you don't want to be killed,
stay away.
Remember, there will be
no third time.
Hah! I'm notgiving up!
Even if you run away, I'll find you
without fail!
With that smell, I'll find you quickly!
Smell....
It's done.
Sister Kikyo....
Now then, let us go home, Kaede.
Yes!
Huh?
You!
Hah! Kikyo, give me
the Sacred Jewel.
So you've appeared again.
I told you that I wouldn't give up.
And we're gonna settle this today!
Hurry and tell that kid to run away!
Kaede, get back.
Sister Kikyo....
Apriestess that walks a bloody bath.
An existence that is neither human
nordemon.
Apitiful half-demon looking
forhis place in this world.
There is something I wish to ask you.
Why didn't you kill me that night?
It would have been an easy task
in my condition.
I don't pull dirty tricks like that.
I see.
What's so funny?!
Let me ask you one more thing.
Half-demon, what are you called?
You do have a name, at least?
Even if you're a half-demon.
Quit harping on the half-demon thing!
Then tell me....
And I shall never call you
"half-demon" again.
It's Inuyasha.
Inuyasha? I shall remember it.
Prepare to die, Kikyo!
Wait up, you!
Why do you always leave
without killing me?!
Stop squirming around.
My arrows are wasted on you.
It was a mystery to me, too.
Why didn't Sister Kikyo
finish Inuyasha off?
Why didn't she use her
sacred arrows on Inuyasha?
From around that time,
Kikyo went to cleanse herself
every day.
Looking back, I think it began
from the day she met Inuyasha.
Saruhozuki....
I remember Kikyo telling me this
helps to reduce swelling.
The Sacred Jewel!
- I shall take you hostage...
- Help!
and get the Sacred Jewel
from Kikyo!
Get away, kid!
Hah! No way would I let a
weakling demon like you
have the Sacred Jewel!
Um....
Huh?
Thank you for saving me.
Don't get me wrong!
ljust don't want anyone else
to have the Sacred Jewel.
I was puzzled...
Why didn't this Inuyasha take me
hostage like Mistress Centipede?
Sister Kikyo knew that the corpse
of Mistress Centipede
still contained demon power.
The powerof the Sacred Jewel
cannot reach in here.
Inuyasha, you're there, aren't you?
Come down.
This is the first time
we've spoken up close.
So what of it?
I understand you saved Kaede.
Oh that....
I want to thank you, too.
Don't do something
that's unlike you.
Inuyasha....
How do I look?
Do I seem human?
Huh? What're you talking about?
I show my weakness to no one.
I must not hesitate,
so that demons cannot
overcome me.
I am human, yet I cannot
be human.
We're alike, you and me.
You, a half-demon....
That's why I could not kill you.
Hah? Making excuses?
That's not like you at all.
I guess so.... It's not like me.
Inuyasha....
Huh? What?
No, nothing....
Kikyo...
Kikyo! Come back here tomorrow.
Huh?
Err....
I want to give you something.
You want to give me something?
Good, because I have something
I've been thinking about giving you.
Huh? The Sacred Jewel?
No such thing.
I figured as much.
Aren't those the Kotodama sutra beads?
Are you giving those to Inuyasha?
Yes.
It may be underhanded of me,
but these will prevent him
from doing any more wrong.
Now then.... what trigger word
can I use to make the beads take effect?
At that time, it seemed to me that
Kikyo looked sort of happy.
I remembernow....That priestess Tsubaki....
put a strange curse on me.
Oh well.... I walk the path of carnage.
So why should I fear an
unnatural death?
Sister....
The triggerword will be....
"beloved."
What is this?
No sense in me keeping it.
I'll give it to you.
The only things
my motherleft me....
That and the Robe of the
Fire-rat.
Yourmother was human?
Yeah....well....
This must mean so much to you....
Don't worry about it.
The Robe of the Fire-rat is
useful enough.
I'm sorry, Inuyasha.
I didn't know and I shot so many
arrows at you.
Hah! Don't worry!
By the way, what were you gonna
give me?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I must have forgotten....
Geez! I was looking forward to it!
Are you sure I can have this?
Yeah....
Inuyasha and Kikyo....
That night, Kikyo colored
herlips.
She looked so beautiful.
But even to my innocent eyes,
there was a sadness
about her.
Now what would you like to play?
Inuyasha, come down from there
and join us.
You've gotta be kidding!
Let's play hand-ball.
Let's pick flowers!
I'll neverbe as good as Kikyo.
Good for you, Kaede.
Sister Kikyo!
Huh?
Oh, Sister....
Yes? What is it?
Nothing.
I see.
I wanted to see Kikyo
look beautiful...
I wanted to help her.
I thought I was the only one
with such thoughts.
K-Kikyo....
Yes. I brought some gruel.
Don't bother... with me anymore....
Go away!
Kikyo was harboring a bandit
named Onigumo.
Why can't I tell Inuyasha?
Knowing him, he will probably
become jealous.
Jealous?
Inuyasha, lend me your power.
What's this, all of a sudden?
I've been asked to exterminate
a demon from another country.
Buteven I will have
my hands full.
Hah! This is gonna cost ya!
Inuyasha, it's coming yourway!
Leave 'im to me!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Kikyo, that's its true form.
Right!
Hah! You got 'im!
Yo....kid.
It's Kaede.
Your sisterhas something
called the Sacred Jewel, doesn't she?
How do you know about it?
All bad guys are afterit.
You too?
And from what I hear....
the Jewel becomes more evil when
it absorbs blood filled with hatred.
I like that....
My sister is purifying it.
It will not become evil.
Kikyo always seems
so serene.
How I'd love to see her....
get all flustered.
I getexcited just
thinking about it.
I see....
So that's what Onigumo said.
Sister, I do not like him.
Forgive him.
That man will probably nevermove
from that spot for the rest of his life.
That is what SisterKikyo said.
But I had a foreboding feeling
about her kindness.
How admirable.
But I understand if you stand
beneath the cherry trees for too long,
you will go insane.
I wonder if it's because
of these cherry trees....
you seem like a completely different
person from last I saw you.
And your pitifully weak powers....
Specters and demons are
breaking through yourbarrier.
I see....
So you were unleashing
the specters.
Letting yourheartgo
to a man....
And he is that worthless half-demon,
is he not?
Give me the Sacred Jewel.
I shall purify it
in your stead.
Humph! You are not able to.
Die, Kikyo!
Damn you, Kikyo!
Get back! I shall spare your life.
Onigumo....
Onigumo....!
Your evil thoughts have
brought us here.
Ademon?
I will listen....
What is it you want?
I want a body that will
enable me to move freely,
so that I can make the Sacred Jewel
and Kikyo mine!
Done.
But in return, we will take
your soul.
My rotten soul is worth
something, huh?
Doesn't it look tasty?
You want to eat me, right?
Go ahead....eat!
And give me a body....
and power!
You've improved greatly.
Yes.
Next is the Arrow of Sealing.
The Arrow of Sealing?
This is the sacred arrow,
Fuuin no Ya.
We use it for demons
who are invincible.
And then what happens
to the demon?
They fall into an
eternal sleep.
They will only awaken when
the one who shot the arrow
deeply wants the demon to revive.
However, Kaede, beware
of this tree.
Huh? The Sacred Tree?
This is known as
the Tree of Ages.
It has the power to
transcend time.
Tree of Ages?
If you seal a demon
to this tree,
the demon's body will
remain intact....
Huh?!
W-What is that?!
So many of them....
Ridiculous!
How could I not notice
an aura this strong?!
Go, specters!
Go and take the Sacred Jewel!
The Sacred Jewel will give you
immense demon power!
Become the greatest demons of
them all and destroy the priestess, Kikyo!
Specters!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Inuyasha!
You're late, Kikyo!
Forgive me!
My spiritual powers
have weakened.
All right! Me too!
Blades of Blood!
Inuyasha!
Watch out! Kikyo!
Kaede!
Huh?!
Forgive me, Kaede!
l-I'm all right.
What happened to hereyes?
I've done a terrible thing.
It's all my fault.
I was too timid.
Don't blame yourself too much.
These things happen all the time
when you're fighting.
Inuyasha....
Are you unable to be yourself
unless you are fighting?
You asked me something
like that before.
Wouldn't you like to
stop fighting?
What?
Stop fighting and
become human.
Me? A human?
You can become one.
After all, you are
half human.
When the Sacred Jewel is
in the hands of an evil demon,
its evil powers increase.
But if I use it to
make you human,
it will become purified
and most likely, disintegrate.
But then, Kikyo, what will
happen to you?
I am the protector
of this Jewel.
And if the Jewel ceases
to exist,
I will become an ordinary woman.
Oh....!
Kikyo....
Kikyo, I will become a human.
I'm not saying this on a whim.
I will become a human.
Inuyasha....
So you can become
an ordinary human, too....
My....
Enough....
Do not say anymore.
Kikyo!
I feel....
Inuyasha, are you
sure about this?
About what?
About me....
Are you sure?
Hah! Do you even
have to ask?
Tomorrow afternoon....
Huh?
In front of the Sacred Tree
in the western forest.
Wait forme there.
I will bring the
Sacred Jewel.
Uh-huh. All right.
As if I will....
let her!
Who is it?
Kikyo, it's me.
What's the matter?
Has something happened?
I can't wait any longer!
Kikyo, can you make me
human right now?
That's impossible.
The night is filled with evil.
If we are to use the Sacred Jewel,
it must be afterthe sun rises.
All right.
Then do it right after
the day breaks, all right?
You are hopeless!
Huh?
Inuyasha....
Kikyo, where are you going?
Oh.... Just out.
It's still early.
Go back to sleep.
But....
I'm justgoing out to find
medicinal herbs foryour wound.
Medicinal herbs?
There's a lot here.
Huh?
There may be something
more effective.
I'm going to take
anotherlook.
Thank you, Kikyo.
Kaede, do youreyes hurt?
No, it's much bettertoday.
I see.
I'll return right away.
At that moment, I felt lonelierthan I'd
everfelt before.
I wanted my sisterto
stay with me forever.
I didn't want herto go
anywhere that day.
I wished forit very strongly.
I'm late!
Inuyasha....
He's not here yet.
That Inuyasha....
Maybe he overslept.
Even if you try to pretty
yourself up with this,
you can't hide your
true nature!
W-What?!
This rouge doesn't become
you at all!
Demon blood is good enough
foryou!
Inuyasha....
Fool!
I neverwanted to become
a human!
Thanks forthe Sacred Jewel....
It's mine now.
I'll have to make it suck more
blood filled with hate.
I'll slaughterthe villagers.
Curse you! Inuyasha!
So you intended to trick me
from the very start!
Were yourwords all lies?!
I'm not saying this on a whim.
I will become a human.
So you can become...
Damn!
Damn you!
Now then, next is....
that half-demon....
Kikyo!
She's not here yet.
So you've come, half-demon.
Kikyo....
What did you just say?!
I said, "half-demon."
Can't those ugly dog ears
hearwhat I say?
Why you...!
I can't let a half-demon like
you have the Sacred Jewel.
I will destroy you right now!
Die, Inuyasha!
Begone, half-demon!
Dammit!
Now the Sacred Jewel will be
tainted with hatred and bitterness.
Damn! You tricked me!
You just used me?!
Then tell me...
And I shall nevercall you
"half-demon"again.
That's what you said...
And yet!
Why now!
It's Inuyasha!
Hah! Serves you right!
With this, I can become
a real demon!
I won't let anyone call me
a half-demon again!
Inuyasha!
I believed in you!
I trusted you!
I neverdoubted you!
Yet you!
Inuyasha!
K-Kikyo....
You dared to....!
Sister! Sister Kikyo!
- Mistress Kikyo!
- She's badly injured!
How did you get this?
Am I going to die like this?
Don't say anything more.
I guess that's okay.
Kikyo, even though it ended
like this...
I still feel...
The Sacred Jewel....
Just because of someone like him....!
Listen well, Kaede.
Take the Sacred Jewel and
burn it with my body.
So that it will neverfall into
the hands of evil again!
Sister!
I will take the Sacred Jewel
with me to the netherworld.
It has been fifty years...
that Inuyasha has been sealed
to the Sacred Tree.
Inuyasha looks exactly the
same as he did then.
At that time, my sisterknew
that she was going to die.
So why did she choose the
Arrow of Sealing to seal
ratherthan the Sacred Arrow
to destroy?
Why did she seal Inuyasha
on the Sacred Tree,
the Tree of Ages said to be able to
transcend time?
And Inuyasha was filled with
hatred towards my sister
who took back the
Sacred Jewel
and sealed him to
the Sacred Tree...
But why did he have such
a peaceful expression on his face?
I understand nothing, afterall.
Will the day come
when I understand it all?
15 years ago
It's born!
My firstgrandchild!
A beautiful girl!
It's okay....
Good girl.
Yourname is Kagome.
Ka-go-me.
So nice to meet you, Kagome.
15 Years Later
Kagome, yourfriend....
The notes for practice?
I'll bring them today.
I know!
I'm off!
There are rumors
of one Hijiri-sama
who can protect people
against demon birds.
Hakudoshi hears of this
and takes action.
Humans who fearthe birds
have gathered to worship him.
By now, Princess Abi and herbirds
have begun an assault on
this Hijiri-sama's village.
Even Inuyasha's red Tetsusaiga
cannot hurt Hakudoshi.
Just then, a barrier-breaking
Sacred Arrow comes flying...
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Single Arrow of Chaos"
That can't be!