Hey, Myoga...
I hope you're not deceiving me.
Has this Inu-whatever
really mastered the Tetsusaiga?
His name is Master Inuyasha.
Inuyasha? Oh, I remember.
The son of the Dog General...
who gave me his fang
from which to forge the sword.
Is he the younger
of the two doltish brothers?
Watch your mouth.
It happened only once...
but with one swing,
he killed a hundred demons.
Being accused of abandoning you...
isn't something I'll enjoy...
waking up to in the morning!
But there's been nothing ever since.
And I'm stumped as to what to do next.
Well then...
maybe I should just test him...
to see whether he's deserving of the
famous Tetsusaiga which I forged.
H-hot! H-hot!
What a place this is!
Even the rocky ground is burning hot!
Mmm... the smell of roasting meat.
Hmm?
Oh, this is it!
Are you here, Totosai?
I hope you have completed
the sword that was commissioned!
This is the promised date of delivery!
Hmm?
Hey! Come on out!
Huh?
"Moved"?!
Damn that sneaky badger!
Where'd he go?!
Oh... Oops.
I see... So Totosai has run away.
Please forgive me,
Master Sesshomaru!
The swordsmith Totosai
is a man of extreme likes and dislikes.
From what I have heard,
he will create a sword...
only if he takes a liking to the client.
In other words,
he has no intention of...
making a sword that suits me.
Well... How can I put it...
He doesn't like you.
Y-you're smiling!
Oh please!
Please get angry!
I fear a smiling
Master Sesshomaru much, much more!
Please I beg you!
My life was shortened
by a hundred years.
My Sacred Jewel fragments
were taken...
Don't worry about it, Kagome.
But...
That wasn't all there
is of the Sacred Jewel.
We'll just start collecting 'em
one by one again.
That's so unlike Inuyasha.
Why's he being so understanding?
Well, because the one who stole
the Sacred Jewel fragments was Kikyo.
Geez... A crime committed by
the woman he loves!
Hey you!
Are you implying that
I'm trying to defend Kikyo?!
W-what?! Do you think that, too...?!
If you have any complaints,
just speak up!
A cow?
Where is it?
Huh?
Up above?
What's going on?!
Inuyasha!
Just who are you?!
I am called Totosai.
Draw your sword, Inuyasha.
The old geezer...knows me?!
If you refuse,
I'll go on the offensive!
Get back, Kagome!
Uh-huh...
He thwarted the Tetsusaiga
with his hammer!
The resonance is way too dull.
Maybe this kid isn't the right one.
Just who are you?!
He stopped the sword!
With a piece of leather!
The blade is full of chips!
You've been too rough with it!
What a shame!
J-just who are you?!
Totosai, isn't that enough?
Myoga?!
The swordsmith
who forged the Tetsusaiga?!
Precisely.
I, Totosai, forged the Tetsusaiga
from a fang your father gave me.
In the world of
sword-wielding demons...
I am famous
among those who know...
and among those who don't know,
I'm not.
Huh? What does that mean?
Doesn't it mean that
he's not very famous at all?
Whatever!
Just what does the swordsmith
want with me?
I took a good look at
the Tetsusaiga earlier.
It was the sword of swords,
forged by a master swordsmith...
but the sound of the steel
is terribly dull.
It's a very sad thing.
If you're picking a fight,
just say so.
Inuyasha!
Oh... it's useless.
Myoga, the Tetsusaiga can't be
used by someone...
so short-tempered and
so eager to fight.
So rather than blindly relying
on the Tetsusaiga's strength...
and fighting recklessly...
better for Inuyasha to just
give up the sword, huh?
Well, the sooner the better.
I'll just break the Tetsusaiga
in two now!
What didja say?!
You may have made the sword,
but now, it belongs to me!
Oh, I won't break it.
Sorry about that.
Stop hedging.
What are you going to do?
At night, when everyone has
settled down...
I will quietly steal it away.
Oh, no... I won't steal it!
Master Inuyasha...
as it is, you won't be able to master
the mystery of the Tetsusaiga...
which enables one to slay a
hundred demons in one sweep.
But this Totosai knows
its secret.
I think you both need to
get to know each other...
and you must cooperate to awaken
the Tetsusaiga's true power.
What mystery?!
I'll get the hang of it in time.
You are collecting fragments
of the Sacred Jewel.
Some time has passed since the
fragments were scattered.
There may even be a
demon who already possesses...
two or three fragments.
In order to destroy a demon whose
strength is enhanced...
don't you want the Tetsusaiga to be
awakened to its true potential?
Inuyasha, he has a point.
I think you should listen to him.
Awright!
So what'm I supposed to do, Totosai?
Someone seeks my life!
Huh?!
There is a fool who has ordered
me to forge a sword...
to rival the power of the Tetsusaiga...
else he will kill me.
Show me that you can
protect me from him.
Why don't you say "please"?!
I never heard of that!
Describe this person.
He has white hair and wears
furry, warm-Iooking clothing.
What?! Another old geezer?
Wrong!
Wait a minute... If he's dressed
like that... and not old... and...
he wants a sword stronger
than the Tetsusaiga...
Could he be?!
He's here!
Huh?
Sesshomaru!
Who is he?
Inuyasha's older brother.
So he is the one who's after you!
Exactly! It's that Sesshomaru!
Inuyasha... why do you
plot with Totosai?
Isn't it obvious? To punish you!
Oh, Totosai... I see you
are rushing headlong into death.
Oh no... I just thought...
after you beat Inuyasha, maybe
I can make you a new sword...
- What?
- Just a thought...
Hey! What you said earlier
is the exact opposite!
Huh? Is that so?
Totosai, do not forget
what you just said.
You heard him, Inuyasha...
You can die for the sake
of my new sword.
Kagome, hurry and get away!
Uh-huh...
I'll kill you instead!
They are both so hot-headed...
You're the one who instigated this!
Oh... is that right?
You!
No wonder he's Old Myoga's friend!
Acting so innocent!
Huh? Old Myoga...
Where are you, Myoga?
Kagome,
Old Myoga is on Miroku's shoulder.
Hurry here!
It's dangerous over there!
Oh no!
Hey, what're you doing?!
How awful!
Too slow.
Gotta be kidding!
No good at all!
Hey, Myoga...
has Inuyasha really mastered
the Tetsusaiga?
Well, just once...
It's not a lie!
Besides, each time it's Inuyasha
who ends up beating Sesshomaru!
Miss, are you sure you
haven't been dreaming?
I am not like you!
Pardon me.
Totosai... do you not
feel sad for the Tetsusaiga?
The famous sword is no
better than a piece of log.
All Inuyasha does is
swing it around.
Depending on its user,
a sword can live or die.
A wise observation...
my opinion precisely.
Don't agree!
Damn! You can cut your jokes.
I'm only warming up!
Don't be shocked at my real power!
Prepare yourself!
Oh no... the blood's rushed
to his head...
This is bad.
Well, Totosai...
do you still refuse
to make me a sword?
No way!
What're you doing, stupid?!
So you absolutely refuse?
Shut up!
I have already made you
a fine sword!
That famous sword at your hip:
Tenseiga!
I, Totosai, made the sword from
a fang given to me by your father!
The Tenseiga for the older brother...
the Tetsusaiga for the younger one...
that was your father's last will.
It is a great sword of swords...
no worse and no better
than the Tetsusaiga!
Why don't you learn to love it more!
So that old man also made
Sesshomaru's sword!
However, in all the battles until now...
I've never seen Sesshomaru
unsheathe that sword.
You're right...
You dare imply that this stupid,
useless sword...
is worthy of me?!
Oh! He's angry! He's angry!
I guess I'll take my leave!
They've escaped.
Wow! You're so strong!
I'll say.
Why bother to have Inuyasha
to protect you...
when he's weaker than Sesshomaru?
What did you just say?
How could Sesshomaru call his
great sword useless...
how could Inuyasha be so weak...
how utterly wrong I was
about them both!
What?!
Owee!
I am not weak!
Old one... I've been thinking.
That sword Sesshomaru has...
Is it also a powerful sword?
You mean, the Tenseiga?
You could say
its power is awesome indeed.
But when the Dog General
commissioned me to make it...
I questioned at first about
its powers.
A sword that won't cut?
How're you supposed to fight
with a sword like that?
The Tenseiga is not a sword
you use against foes.
To put it simply,
it is a sword of healing.
Healing?
While the Tetsusaiga is the sword
to defeat the powerful...
the Tenseiga is the sword to
save the lives of the weak.
Save lives?
If one has the true kindness
of heart towards people...
the Tenseiga has the power to
save a hundred people in one sweep.
Kindness of heart?
The Tetsusaiga can kill
a hundred in one sweep...
while the Tenseiga can save
a hundred in one sweep?
And does this sword
function as a weapon?
It is able to bring back dead souls.
In this Feudal era,
it can be used in many ways.
I intended to name the sword,
"Coffin-Cheater"...
but it was christened with
a fancy name like Tenseiga.
Well, it was your father
that named it.
I see...
No wonder Sesshomaru
wants a new sword.
A sword to help others...
no way that guy'd have any use for it.
Won't it work out?
It was your father's will.
Given your brother's personality...
He wouldn't be happy with it,
even if he could use it.
Looks delicious!
A very nice roast, indeed!
Let's dig in!
Hey! Don't eat it all!
Oh! My meat's gone!
You just ate it all!
Huh? Who are you anyway?
And where am I?
I was not aware of it, either...
that the sword is also
your father's memento.
What kind of power does it have?
You want to know, Jaken?
It makes me extremely curious
about the two swords...
forged from your father's fang.
The two swords are like... brothers.
Oh no... I didn't mean to compare
them with you and Inuyasha!
I'm not concerned at all that you
who hate half-demons...
would be related to Inuyasha...
well, I am concerned, but!
Jaken!
Yes?
Lord Sesshomaru!
What are you doing?
Get up.
Huh?
I'm not hurt!
Why?
I was slain just now!
Do you see now?
This Tenseiga is a sword
that cannot kill!
Wh-what?
What's happening?
Oh no! There!
Why did my father bestow
this Tenseiga upon me...
and the Tetsusaiga upon Inuyasha?
I have a gift now.
Let us go and see...
the Tetsusaiga.
There!
See you!
See you? You plan to escape alone?
I can't rely on Inuyasha.
Come on...
Leave 'im!
Who needs an old geezer like that?
Give it back!
You cannot use the Tetsusaiga!
I will break it into pieces.
Shaddup, you geezer!
Hey, Inuyasha!
You'll regret this!
He's frank, isn't he?
I can't tell whether that
old man is strong or weak.
Poor thing... That Inuyasha
will be killed by Sesshomaru.
After all, Inuyasha hasn't
even been able to see...
the "Wind Scar" which
awakens the Tetsusaiga's power.
Aren't you going after him,
Inuyasha?
You were lucky enough to
meet the Tetsusaiga's maker!
Hah! That old fool is full of it!
He's back.
Sesshomaru!
Stay put!
I will tear both you
and Inuyasha into pieces!
Did you hear that?
What'll you do?!
Old one... you don't want to make
Sesshomaru a new sword, right?
No!
Well then...
I've had it up to here with
all this about Tetsusaiga.
It's about time
to settle this once and for all!
Rest assured.
It will all end today!
As long as you cannot see...
the "Wind Scar."
Inuyasha's father had given
his two sons each a sword.
But the older brother Sesshomaru...
doesn't like that
Inuyasha has the Tetsusaiga.
The mystery of the "Wind Scar"
is finally revealed!
Inuyasha totally defeats Sesshomaru!
The sword of life,
the Tenseiga, is drawn!
Whose life does Sesshomaru
ends up saving?
Next on Inuyasha:
"The True Owner of the Great Sword!"
Don't miss it!