Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the
shards of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Miroku's a bit lecherous,
but he carries the burden of
Naraku's curse, the Wind Tunnel.
Did he sense the same sadness in her?
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Poor thing. You got lost
in the snow.
Father...
You'll be fine now.
Who are you?
My name is Koyuki.
Did something happen
to your father?
My father passed away.
I have no kin anymore.
If you have nowhere to go,
come to my house.
She was a beautiful woman
with skin as white as snow.
Wh-What are you doing?!
A mosquito.
And?
Anyway, because I once trained here,
I know these parts well.
And what about that woman?
Nothing more.
It was seven years ago.
When I was still a
rosy-cheeked child.
See? Got it.
Huh? What's that?
Hang on! Open your eyes!
Don't die!
Hang in there!
Snow at this time of the year?
Hey!
He's regained consciousness.
How wonderful!
What a relief!
- Excuse me.
- Huh?
What happened?
Will you tell me?
Oh, monk!
Lately, a snow demon has
been appearing hereabouts.
Several village men
have been found like this.
Better to return to the hut
and tell everyone about this.
What about you?
I'll put an end to the demon,
so it won't make any more trouble.
I don't sense too much evil.
Don't worry.
That monk was quite a young man.
I wonder if he'll manage.
The demon is supposed to be
a vision with skin as white as snow.
Most men would be mesmerized
and follow her.
No sign of Naraku here either.
What're you doing?
I was cleaning out
my backpack and found it.
I brought it to play
with everyone.
I forgot all about it.
Huh?
I wanted to make sure
it didn't get damp.
Wow! What's that?
A sparkler. A sparkler.
Isn't it pretty?
Umm... that so?
Snow... now?
But why?
Miroku!
You're a traveler?
You seem to be having
trouble in the snow.
Is there anything I can do?
Yes...
Miss... will you bear my child?
Have you forgotten?
I already have.
Huh?!
Please hold him.
Your child.
Miroku! Where are you going?!
Miroku!
Kirara, let's eat this together.
No work, no food.
We don't need to share
with the others.
Wow! Looks good!
What a greedy guy!
Followed the smell of
the fish, didja?
Are you kidding?
It was the snow.
No wonder it's so cold.
Where're Sango and Miroku?
Not yet.
They'll get hungry and come back soon.
That fish belongs to
Kirara and me!
Don't be stingy!
C'mere Kagome and eat.
It's good.
Sango! Miroku!
Sorry for making ourselves home
like this.
Don't worry about it.
It's snowing so hard.
Boar meat.
It'll warm you.
It's good!
It's still raw.
He's so uncouth!
Better to stay here until
the Snow Maiden passes through.
Snow Maiden?
Yes. If a young man walks alone
on a day like this,
a young woman stops him.
And if he follows her,
it's the end.
The next day, he's found
pitifully frozen.
And this woman is as fair
as the snow.
And so beautiful.
Even if I end up frozen,
I'd like to see her just once.
Miroku is in danger!
But isn't Sango with him?
Oh, then it's all right?
You don't understand at all!
Huh?
As if Miroku would leave
such a woman alone.
The question is:
How will Sango react.
Gives me the shivers just
thinking about it.
Why?
Isn't it obvious?!
Sango has feelings... for Miroku.
It's useless.
How many times have we
discussed this...
and he never gets it.
That's true.
But...
If this one's another demon who's causing
trouble due to Naraku's disappearance,
we can't ignore it.
I'm going!
Inuyasha, I'm coming too!
Wait!
Take this.
It's a special restorative.
Miroku!
Sango!
What's the matter, Kirara?
Everyone!
- Sango!
Drink this! It's a restorative!
It's supposed to work wonders when
you're chilled to the bone.
Wow! It does work!
It's a mixture of potent wine,
viper, newt and worms.
I'm so glad you're all right.
Where's Miroku?
Miroku!
Have you forgotten?
I've already borne him.
Please hold your child.
By now...
he's living happily...
the family of three!
A barrier...
Now please come, my husband.
This woman is not of this world.
But why does she harm humans?
Does she kill men and
suck out their life spirit?
Welcome home, Father!
They're?
Dear, please keep them company.
I will prepare rice gruel.
Huh? But...
The diapers are over there.
But all these children...
Certainly...
You have not forgotten?
They are your children.
M-Mine?
So many?
I heard it with my own ears!
About his child!
Hah! Maybe it's time for
him to settle down.
This may be the perfect time.
What?!
Stupid!
You two!
Don't take a demon's words
so seriously.
A barrier?
The miasma is coming...
from inside here.
Damn!
I'll tear it apart!
Now!
There, there!
There, there.
Don't blow your nose
on my kimono!
My staff is not a toy!
Monk!
Yes?
Yosaku needs to be fed.
Sutematsu's diaper needs to be changed.
And please sing Otora a lullaby
and put her to sleep.
All right.
Okay, okay.
Don't cry now.
Is it good?
Let's change your diaper.
Rock-a-bye...
Don't pee over there!
Huh?
The toilet is over there!
Thank you.
You've been taking care of all
these children alone?
Every mother does that.
But are they all mine?
Children whose villages were burned
down in the war.
Children who were parted from
their mothers right after birth.
As I took care of such children,
they grew in number.
Such a burden on you.
All of them are so pitiful.
Be careful... it's nearby.
Isn't that Miroku singing?
I guess even he will dote
on his child.
Inuyasha!
Look!
A mansion?
So there it is.
She's sleeping soundly.
Good girl.
You're a good girl.
Grow up quickly.
Such a good baby.
There, there...
That's!
Miroku is under a spell.
Snap out of it, Miroku!
Hushaby...
Miroku!
What the...!
Inuyasha!
You there...
You cannot pass!
Oh, Sacred Jewel shards.
Appear! Snow panther!
It's so cold, Kirara can't transform
to full strength.
Defeat them and take possession
of the Sacred Jewel shards!
Why you...!
I'll kill you!
Done!
Such an easy prey!
Inuyasha!
Huh?! What...!
Inuyasha, run!
There you go...
There, there...
- Umm...
- Yes?
Was there some disturbance outside?
Some stray dogs got in.
Oh...
Do not worry.
We'll chase them out in no time.
Blast you!
The children!
Miroku!
Inuyasha?
Come to your senses!
I have my senses!
Then look good and hard!
This is!
You won't get away.
You resemble a woman I remember...
So I didn't want to be
rough on you.
I don't taste good at all!
Hiraikotsu!
- She's so fast!
- Leave it to me!
Wind Scar!
She withstood it!
Hatred... Full of hatred!
Why would one so kind-hearted
deceive men and do harm?
I hate... I hate this world.
I hate being born into
a world like this!
Find eternal peace.
Forgive me!
What's that?
What's happening to it?
Heat! Their weakness is heat and fire!
All right! My fox fire!
Take that!
It's not working at all!
Huh?! I know!
This is it!
Over here!
I'll take you on!
Kagome!
Hiraikotsu!
Now!
Wind Scar!
Is that a snow demon, too?!
All right! All at once!
Wait!
That spirit isn't possessed by
the Snow Maiden any longer.
That is the soul of a woman who
died because of the war.
She gathered the spirits of the
children who left this world
and took care of them.
A snow demon took possession of
that spirit.
How tragic.
There's too much suffering in the world
of wars... especially for women.
Still...
Why did you follow her when
she told you she had your kid?
You must've remembered her.
Inuyasha!
He IS a fool, after all.
Well...
Miroku purposely fell under her spell
in order to save the
poor demon.
Huh?
Yes... that's just it.
Miroku would never
make such a mistake.
Right?
Another mosquito.
Mosquito?
Let's get going.
Yeah, let's.
She really resembled her.
No... but...
The one who saved me that day
when I was still a youth...
That Koyuki...
I'm sure she's living happily
somewhere in this world.
Parting snow...
The northern mountains just ahead
of where Naraku disappeared...
The Wolf-Demon tribe who live there
have been attacked by a specter,
by the name of Kyokotsu who
possesses a Sacred Jewel shard.
Why you...! You rose up
from the grave?!
I'm gonna take
your Sacred Jewel shard, too!
Neither human nor demon.
What is the goal of this
resurrected specter?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Assault on the Wolf-Demon Tribe!"
Forget it! We avenge my comrades first!