As we continued ourjourney in
pursuit of Naraku,
in a strange turn of events,
we ended up helping an
old woman exorcist.
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
However, this exorcist
is a bit suspect...
since she can't even
sense a demonic aura.
Through her, we were hired to
exterminate a demon
terrorizing Demon's Head Castle.
And we learned of the
clan's strange lord
and met his daughter,
a dazzling beauty of a princess.
Since the princess requests it,
I shall exterminate this demon
and free this castle.
Wind Scar!
But on the night that the giant demon
head appeared,
Inuyasha's Wind Scarhad
no effect.
It is probably an illusion.
But then, the true form must
be somewhere else!
The lord... Ourlord!
Let him go!
So this is the true form
of the demon.
Damn you!
I added my own spiritual power
to the exorcist's purification salt.
It seems to have some effect.
But this is bad...
This demon is quite powerful.
And my body won't move
due to the demonic aura.
Monk, there's no help
forthcoming.
Besides, that half-demon is
probably fighting
the lord back at the castle.
I used my magic to manipulate
that puppet lord.
W- What?!
Inuyasha!
M-My lord!
You've gotguts showing
yourtrue self.
Huh, Demon?!
Prepare to die!
He's using the woman
as a shield!
Inuyasha, don't use Tetsusaiga!
D-Damn!
Shaddup!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Nothing much, are ya!
Hold it!
l-It's gone!
Fool!
It's too early to breathe easy!
You women, protect the princess!
B-But...
Is anything the matter?
Actually...
The underground burial site of the
demon head?
Y-Yes...
She wanted to show it
to the monk.
Sango!
I'm going to get Miroku!
I'm coming with you!
It's saferthan staying here.
Madam Exorcist!
But didn't it turn out well?
Weren't you worried?
That the monk and the princess
were in each others' arms?
But at an underground
burial site?
Nothing romantic
could go on there!
What're you saying
at a time like this?!
You like him, don't you?
The monk, Miroku.
It's written all over
yourface.
I said it's not like that!
Huh?
What're you doing?
I'll leave you behind.
You cannot move, huh?
No one can overcome the
grip of my demonic aura.
You intend to eat me?
All the monks and priestesses
who came to slay the demon
were all devoured by me.
Monk...
You are exactly the 100th one.
I shall devour you and
your spiritual powers...
and I will be completely reborn.
I shall soon bid farewell
to this borrowed body.
Such a pretty face, monk!
Don't worry.
You're not fatally wounded.
I have to stop the bleeding.
T-Thank you...
Don't try to talk.
It'll sting a bit,
so please endure it.
They've all been killed
by the demon!
Let's go.
We may find someone
who's still alive.
Is anyone here?
Here... This is the room the
lord refused to leave.
Kagome! Look at that!
Someone's asleep.
Excuse me...
The princess?
What's going on?
The princess is supposed to be
underground... at the burial site.
S-She's...
...dead!
Take that!
Damn you!
Quit this already!
Damn! He backed off.
W- What was that?!
Fora second, the demon
seemed transparent.
Something's strange...
This demon keeps backing away
and neverattacks.
Almost...
as though he's
buying time!
Someone has touched
the host body.
Miroku!
You're!
I... can't move!
Kirara... you too?!
Woman, watch carefully.
While I devourthe monk.
D-Damn!
That's!
Evil demon begone!
Take this!
Purification salt!
Huh?!
This old woman...
My demonic grip doesn't
work on her?
Madam Exorcist...
Throw all the purification salt
on her!
Huh?!
Take that!
Why you...!
You put your spiritual power
into the purification salt!
M-Miroku!
Are you all right?
I thought I was going to die.
But Madam Exorcist...
Huh? What is it?
How did you overcome the grip
of the demonic aura?
Demonic aura?
Was there such a thing here?
You really don't sense it?
I guess it means she's
very extraordinary.
Anyway, we can't
be wasting time here!
The demon head flew off!
What's this? The demonic
aura is thickening.
What is this?
What's that?!
This feeling...
Huh?!
The demonic aura... is
rising from the castle.
This one is just a decoy
to distract me!
The real one is inside
the castle!
Damn, no time to waste!
Why don't you get back...
inside the castle?!
Then the demon took the
guise of the princess...
and devoured the monks and
priestesses
who came to exorcise
the castle?
She said I was the hundredth one.
Hmm... the demon...
Why did it come afteryou,
and not me?
That demon devours
spiritual power.
Once it devoured the powers
of one hundred,
it was going to be
completely reborn.
Oh, I see!
It means I was number 101.
Otherwise, there's no way
it wouldn't have come after
someone with my powers.
Right?
Are you listening?!
Ademon head?
What're those things coming out
of the princess'body?
W-What is iteating?
I hid the spiritual powers
of 99 victims inside that body.
One more...
I missed my chance
with that monk.
Young woman... What is that
on yourperson?
The Sacred Jewel shards!
It may be more effective
than the powers that
a mere human possesses.
She's going to eat me!
As if I'm so meek as to
let you eat me!
Shippo!
Yourfox fire!
O-Okay!
Fox Fire!
Now's our chance!
N-Not so fast!
You will notget away.
Stay put and be eaten!
Why you...!
So the true form
finally showed up!
Inuyasha!
You're late!
She was just on the verge
of being eaten!
Shaddup!
Be grateful I came at least!
W-What?!
Now, now...
Why you...!
How dare you...
How dare you scar
my face?!
Unforgivable!
You won't get away
with this!
So what're you gonna do?!
Causing all this trouble!
Well, it's coming to an end!
You half-demon!
This time, I won't miss!
Prepare to die!
The demon!
Is it unconscious?
The... lord! Lord!
Why you...!
Quit moving around!
What's so funny?!
The occupants of this castle
buried my head
as a means to ward off evil.
Foolish humans!
That's why I cursed the princess
to death.
And I borrowed her appearance.
And into her corpse, I hid the
spiritual powers
that I stole from those
I devoured.
So the lord was merely guarding
the princess' body.
As well as a decoy
in case someone came close
to figuring out the truth!
Too bad, Demon Head!
That you had to deal
with us!
Think so?
Now you die!
Stop!
Miroku!
Whaddya want, Miroku?!
Don't interfere!
Before you're destroyed,
I must ask you something.
Like what?!
Monk...
Why didn't you make an
appearance sooner?
You had me overpowered.
Ademon with a powerful
demonic aura like that...
you could've appeared
anytime you wanted.
Until now, I had to be extremely
careful about coming out.
Because I knew that there was
a demon with
a more powerful demonic aura that could
take control of me.
Huh?
A strongerdemonic aura?
Yes... The mass of demonic
aura controlled by Naraku.
However... Naraku is no longer
in this region.
So there's no need to hide
myself in this castle anymore!
Damn!
Now I can have my fill
of monks and priestesses!
Well, I won't let you!
Wind Scar!
He did it!
It's still alive!
The Wind Scardidn't work!
This is just the beginning...
I'll restore my body
and wreak havoc
on this land!
What?!
Wind Tunnel!
It's all over.
Damn, what a nuisance!
Look!
The sky's returning to normal!
The demon was destroyed
and the demonic aura overthe
castle has disappeared.
So it's all because this demon
named Naraku is gone?
That's why the demons in
this region are acting up?
It seems so.
Then I'll be getting
very busy!
Business will be booming.
Old woman...
I have one piece of advice.
Retire!
You're just a fake exorcist anyway.
Inuyasha, don't be so blunt.
Shut your mouth!
If it weren't forme, the monk
would be dead meat right now!
And I'm grateful to you.
Will ya listen to her?!
I think it's made her
overconfident.
Yes, but I think people like
herlive a long time.
Well, I agree about that... but...
Say something?
Err... no!
Hey, let's get going.
If anything comes up,
I'll be happy to help.
Yes, we'll be counting
on you!
Granny, take care!
But what a problem.
With Naraku's disappearance,
even the demons who were
in hiding are now making a move.
They're just small-fry demons
who were scared of Naraku.
I can take care of
every one of 'em.
In any case, this doesn't mean
Naraku is gone from this earth.
I'll find him, without fail!
Why am I living in this world?
Why do I wander this land?
And where am I going?
What was it that turned
my fate awry?
The time... that I spent with Inuyasha.
When I saved Onigumo.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kikyo's Lonely Journey"
Is that Mount Hakurei?