I have put up a barrier.
Those insects cannot
get through.
Without the souls of the dead...
you cannot move.
Kikyo...
Just what are you thinking?
In the mountain where the
Fuko spell was cast...
many demons were sealed inside...
in order to create my new body.
Lured by the miasma
around the mountain...
Inuyasha stumbled onto
the scene...
and began fighting with the demon
being forged into Kodoku.
Then you appeared.
Your arrows have the power...
to easily break the seal of the spell.
At that time, if you had wanted to
protect Inuyasha...
from being fused with the demon...
you should have shot the demon
with your arrow.
The demon would have
disintegrated...
and the Fuko spell
would have been broken.
Were you trying to see...
what waited beyond
the creation of the Kodoku?
And there you were.
That is a fine
disguise, Onigumo.
Onigumo, huh?
How nostalgic.
Fifty years ago...
you saved a wounded fugitive...
and sheltered him in a cave.
Onigumo offered his body to
the demons...
latched onto his
evil soul...
and thus was born me - Naraku.
That's!
Exactly...
The very thing you gave your life
in trying to erase from the world...
a fragment of the Sacred Jewel.
I have heard that you
killed me...
in your desire to possess
the Sacred Jewel.
It's laughable
I'm telling it all to you...
a mere collection of
the souls of the dead.
But the fragments are gathering
within my grasp.
Do you know the girl who
resembles you?
A battle between those who
possess the power to purify evil.
If you yearn for this world...
defeat her.
Don't you think those two
have been acting strange?
Yes...
Inuyasha...
Hey!
Let's go!
We must save Kikyo.
They can't have gone
far yet.
I'll go alone.
Don't be ridiculous, fool!
Naraku is the one who
took Kikyo.
Naraku is the evil creature...
who created this nuisance of a
hole in my right hand! I owe him!
We are all after Naraku.
It's not your problem alone, Inuyasha!
We're all worried about
you and Kikyo.
So stop sneaking around and
trying to solve everything alone.
Sneaking around?!
When did I ever do that?!
Inuyasha! Look!
They're Kikyo's soul collectors!
Kikyo is close by, after all!
- Let's follow them!
- Okay!
Kagome... why aren't you hitching onto
Inuyasha's back like usual?
Well...
Inuyasha's mind is full
of Kikyo right now.
Besides, why did I always
go onto his back...
when he was not
even my boyfriend?
Oh dear...I feel so embarrassed!
Oh dear...how embarrassing!
What's the matter with Kagome?
Dunno...
Kikyo died because of Naraku.
I will not let Naraku have Kikyo!
The number of soul collectors
have increased.
They're!
Everyone, it's a trap!
Watch out!
What's that?!
That's!
Where am I?
He's the one who
attacked the village!
That's Inuyasha!
It's Inuyasha!
Where am I?!
This is?!
the Sacred Jewel!
Inuyasha!
Kikyo!
I know...
this is fifty years ago...
in this village, on this day,
Kikyo killed me.
I attacked this village in order
to steal the Sacred Jewel.
Kikyo, this was a trap!
Kikyo! Wait!
Wait, Kikyo!
No... a dream?
What is this?!
Inuyasha and the others
are gone.
The wind is picking up.
The sound of the wind...
From my Wind Tunnel?
I'm being sucked in!
All right, Kirara...
there's nothing behind us.
Hmm? What's going on?
Kirara has disappeared!
Huh?! Kagome! Sango!
Wait!
Everyone's clothes!
What happened to everyone?!
Where did their bodies go?!
Inuyasha!
Miroku!
Kagome! Sango!
Kohaku!
My evil spell... of Illusionary Death.
Truly, the heart is such a weak thing.
Sadness... Fear... Confusion...
If the negative forces
inside their hearts...
are touched by the creepers
I've placed here...
their soul will be consumed
into the dark.
Where have they all gone?
What are these vines?!
Oh yuck!
Is it because she has the
Sacred Jewel fragments?
That girl alone is
unaffected by my sorcery.
Only she will succeed
in reaching here.
I have set the stage for you.
Such cunning...
She destroyed my puppet.
How dare she defy me.
Kikyo!
Kikyo! You're all right!
Everyone was so worried...
Kikyo!
Naraku fears you.
So he tried to control me
with a Sacred Jewel fragment...
and force me into fight you.
Are they saving me?
There's a Sacred Jewel fragment
in your chest!
I am the priestess who
held the Sacred Jewel in check...
I have not fallen so low as to be
controlled by a mere fragment.
Kikyo!
Kikyo has been suffering...
all alone.
Kikyo...I will never allow you
to be alone again!
Rest assured... I will protect you!
What's that?
Does it mean there is another
I must protect?
Who?
Who is the other one...
I must protect?
Kagome...
That's right!
What happened to Kagome?
Where's Kagome?!
Inuyasha!
Is that girl more precious to you?!
This was all an illusion!
Miroku!
Miroku! Snap out of it!
My arm... The Wind Tunnel...
This guy is actually scared!
Miroku! Wake up!
The Wind Tunnel was sucking
up my body...
The vines of this tree
are the cause.
Miroku, find Sango
and Shippo.
They're probably under the
illusionary spell of the vines, too.
I'll find Kagome!
Kagome!
Where are you?!
Inu... yasha?
Kagome!
If you touch these vines,
you'll get caught in an illusionary trap.
You seem to be okay.
Uh-huh...
Kikyo...
That's... Kagome's Sacred Jewel!
Kagome?
Kikyo... what did you do
to Kagome?!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Aren't you going to rejoice
that I am well?
Answer me, Kikyo!
What did you do to Kagome?
If I tell you that I tried to kill her...
what will you do then?
Will you kill me?
What captured your heart...
when you were under
Naraku's illusionary spell?
I...!
Rest assured... I will protect you.
I doubt that you can
kill me.
I will be waiting...
for the day we can
embrace death together.
Kagome...
what happened with Kikyo?
She took my Sacred Jewel fragment...
I'm sorry.
I'm not asking that!!
Did Kikyo?!
Don't ask!
Kagome...
It's not right... It's like
I'm snitching on her.
Umm... Are you finished talking?
To Kikyo...my life is meaningless.
If you touch these vines,
you'll get caught in an illusionary trap.
You seem to be okay.
Uh-huh...
Illusionary Death...
We were all put to the test by the pain
and confusion in our hearts.
And I...got a small glimpse
into my own heart.
Inside my heart...
Inuyasha and Kikyo...were kissing.
You are careless, Naraku.
Kikyo...
With your puppet broken,
you could see nothing, huh?
Remember that...
your petty sorcery does not
work on me.
And the barrier around this castle...
preventing Inuyasha and the others
from approaching...
was very easy to break.
You coveted this, didn't you?
I will leave it in your possession.
After all, no one needs the power of
the Sacred Jewel more than you...
Demon Naraku...
rather...
half-demon Naraku.
I, Naraku, a half-demon?
You may have disguised
yourself well...
but the blood of the thief, Onigumo,
that courses through your veins...
cannot be erased.
You desire the Sacred Jewel...
in order to become
a full-fledged demon.
Then why hand me these
fragments of the Sacred Jewel?
Am I not the one you seek...
to avenge your death
fifty years ago?
Humph... My physical self
died on that day.
But with this borrowed body,
I feel more comfortable.
I do not expect you to understand.
I will return to my shrine.
I will neither run nor hide.
If you have business with me,
send a messenger.
It's appeared again.
No matter how often
I change my body...
the burn scars of the
thief Onigumo...
will not disappear from
my back.
Naraku... Go and gather the fragments
of the Sacred Jewel.
When you have the
complete Sacred Jewel...
I will send you to Hell.
I am free to hate.
My soul is much more free
than those days.
Free to hate...
Free to love...
Oh no! My Sacred Jewel fragment
has been stolen!
Without it, I can't return
to the Present!
Miroku, please let me borrow
your Sacred Jewel fragment.
I have a test tomorrow, and
I must go back!
Oh Sango!
You'll lend me yours?
Thank you sooo much!
Old Myoga, who is this?
The man who forged the Tetsusaiga?!
Next on Inuyasha,
"Tetsusaiga and Tenseiga!"
Don't miss it!