My eternal liege, the ultimate demon who
knows no rival...
my Lord Sesshomaru.
His father's heirloom, Tetsusaiga,
known to fell a hundred demons
in one sweep...
And only my Lord Sesshomaru is
worthy of its magnificence!
Such a sword is wasted on
Lord Sesshomaru's younger brother...
Inuyasha, that despicable half-demon
with a mortal for a mother!
Rin.
Yes, Lord Sesshomaru?
When you're hungry,
you must find your own food.
All right! I'm off!
My goodness!
Lord Sesshomaru instructed Rin to
find her own food.
Then he tells me to go
help her!
Master Jaken, how far
must we go?
How far?! Until we find food!
Master Jaken?
Just how are you of
service to Lord Sesshomaru?
W-Whaa!
I serve him in many ways!
- Many ways?
- Yes!
For instance...
Inuyasha's Tetsusaiga
turned bright red.
I can't fathom
how Lord Sesshomaru feels.
But Inuyasha's sword can even
break through a demon barrier.
It's become extremely dangerous.
Yes, Lord Sesshomaru has
his sword Tokijin.
As well as Tenseiga...
But no good can come out
of Inuyasha wielding such
a frightening sword.
That's it! Just prevent
him from holding the sword!
Master Jaken!
Listen Rin!
Today, you shall witness...
how I serve my Lord Sesshomaru!
Okay, next! Next!
Ready!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes! We win again!
Sure feels good to win
over and over again. Right?
Let's see...
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Next!
Sango, can you hear?
Yes!
Miroku, can you stop sighing
so much? It's irritating.
If you hadn't shown the same
hand as me,
we'd have had another chance.
Oh, I get it.
Sango, you really wanted to
stay back with me, huh?
Listen! l just lost, okay?
Or... is this hand cursed?
It's your personality
that's cursed!
Rock, paper, scissors!
We did it!
We've won again!
We won with paper...
So that's Wind Tunnel.
Wi-nd Tun-nel!
Hey! Sure you aren't cheating?
Stop being a sore loser.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Here they come! At last!
Stop dawdling!
They're coming!
Appear, No-Man!
You summoned?
No-Man, Inuyasha and his
group are coming.
Get close to them and
steal Tetsusaiga!
You are a demon borne out
of the regrets of Man.
You should be able to
grasp Tetsusaiga.
Now go and steal it!
Tetsusaiga?
The one that Inuyasha
treasures so much!
Is it valuable?
Yes, so go and get it.
Rock, paper, scissors!
We did it!
We won again!
Kagome, you're so strong.
Yup, I'm really good at this.
Now then, scissors is...
Hi-rai-ko-tsu.
Geez, I can't see Kagome anymore.
If we can't see them,
we won't know if they cheat.
That's why!
Miroku!
Inuyasha, something's coming!
What?!
What is it?
A mist?
More like smoke.
A mountain fire?
No, it's not fire.
W-What was that?!
Don't touch me!
It wasn't me who did it!
Someone's pulling at me!
Kagome!
Why you!
It's gone!
The Sacred Jewel shards are gone!
What?!
Oh... he's late!
Master Jaken!
The treasures!
Oh! Did you get Tetsusaiga?
What? No, no!
These aren't it!
What are these?
Mmm... treasures.
Fool!
I have no need of these!
You didn't get Tetsusaiga!
Tetsusaiga?
Inuyasha's sword.
He had an old, rusty sword.
Fool! That's it!
It sure didn't look like a treasure.
What are you saying?!
Now, go and get it!
He's so slow.
Master Jaken, are you sure
that demon can handle it?
How I wish I had
my henchmen.
Oh, I remember those days...
When I was the commander
of many.
Back then, I led hundreds
of demons
and controlled the
plains of Musashi.
At that time, we were at battle
with demons
who controlled the
eastern mountains.
Their leader was Bikuni, who,
despite being several hundred years old,
was a formidable foe.
Just then!
You're in my way!
Move.
Who are you?!
I said you're in the way.
Do you not understand?!
W-Who is he?!
Clear... clear the path!
How beautiful...
He's so dashing!
Master Jaken!
Forget me!
Forgive my rudeness!
It may not have been
your intention,
but you have saved my life!
I beg you! I beg you!
Make me your servant!
A moment, please!
Here!
Um... What is this?
If you can use it,
I'll entrust it to you.
Yes sir!
Err... your name?
Please tell me your name!
Sesshomaru.
Lord Sesshomaru?
Sir!
Several decades have
passed since that day...
and I have long sought
to repay my debt to him.
I cannot leave this
to No-Man.
Now then...
Master Jaken is so busy.
So...
You're the robber?
Turn over the Sacred Jewel
shards or you'll be sorry!
You have some nerve,
stealing things from us.
Hmm... a sword... a sword.
Oh there.
What're you doing?!
Give me Tetsusaiga.
Hah! You bounced right off
Tetsusaiga's barrier.
That's what happens when
a demon tries to touch Tetsusaiga.
In this age of wars, men have
lost lands and farms...
Lost homes to return to.
The amassed regret and bitterness
of such men
gave rise to this demon
No-Man.
I... I sorta feel sorry for him.
Look, if he returns everything,
let's let him go.
There're the shards!
- My top!
- My things, too!
Don't do anything bad now!
If you do,
We'll have to destroy you!
If you'd like, I'll recite
a sutra for your spirits' repose.
He was pretty earnest
about this.
Strange demon.
Well, there are all kinds.
Damn! That hopeless demon...
What is this?
Hot!
Hot! I'm burning!
Hot! Hot!
Help!
Water! Where's water?!
Water! Water! Water! Water!
Huh?!
Huh?
Did you hear a
weird voice just now?
Huh?
Probably your imagination.
We've taken care of
the demon...
let's move on ahead.
Let's.
That Inuyasha!
Does it hurt, Master Jaken?
Of course!
- Then will you give up?
- I will NOT!
Move away!
Rin, just go away!
You said you wanted me
to watch you in action.
I did not!
Just wait, Inuyasha!
I SHALL take Tetsusaiga
away from you!!
Man! We sure wasted
time back there.
Hello there... travelers.
Huh?
What's this?
"In training. Will examine
your lives and sharpen for free."
I dunno what that means,
but something smells weird.
This is good for
building character.
That Inuyasha... This incense
has dulled his sense of smell.
And he doesn't recognize
that I'm Jaken!
If you desire, I will sharpen
your lives.
Lives?
He means your weapon.
This?
Oh yes... yes!
Hmm... Unusual to find
a sword sharpener.
So you're a craftsman of
the feudal age.
Maybe I'll take you
up on it.
It's free, right?
Free? That's nice.
Please do a good job.
You're a generous man.
Umm...
So that's about it.
We'll stop by later.
Counting on ya!
Damn! That Inuyasha!
All right! I'll sharpen them!
If these weapons are
super sharp,
Inuyasha will want me to
sharpen Tetsusaiga, too!
And... that will be
the perfect opportunity!
Now, now, now!
Sharpen!
Go for it, Jaken!
Come on, everyone, together now!
You're in my way!
Humph! Who cares
about Master Jaken!
Huh?
I thought of something!
Come, Aun!
Wow! So shiny!
This is fine work!
Yes, very good.
I'll say!
Shucks! I shoulda left
my sword, too.
But this old man is fast
asleep from exhaustion.
Let's not wake him.
Let's just leave him
a thank-you note.
Oh well... too bad.
"Thank you very much."
Huh?!
Oh no!
Gone!
All gone!
They've left!
I've been duped!
I sharpened those weapons
to trick Inuyasha
and steal his sword!
But I've lost my chance!
Oh yes... I still have
that option.
Just watch, Inuyasha!
On this night, you and Tetsusaiga
shall be separated!
Now that I've gathered flowers
for Lord Sesshomaru,
we have to get back.
Err... How did we
get back?
Huh?
I don't know which way to go.
Say, do you smell Lord Sesshomaru?
I see... Oh well...
Let's go to Master Jaken then.
We sure walked a lot today...
Yes.
Huh?
Is that... a hot spring?
Huh? Really!
Wow! Looks great!
Such luck, huh?
Shall we bathe together?
I guess we'll go separately.
We'll go first!
While Inuyasha is
in the spring,
I shall steal away
his Tetsusaiga.
Such a nice bath!
Inuyasha isn't around.
Do dog-demons hate baths?
I shoulda asked, too.
You're talking about
that sharpener?
Yeah... He looked pretty skilled.
Sharpener?
Should I appear as a sharpener?
Then I can take Tetsusaiga!
All right!
Hey, we're done here!
- Yeah!
- Shall we go then?
What?! He's gonna bathe?
Make up your mind!
Don't peek!
Oh, sorry!
Who'd peek at you!
Oh, he didn't mean me.
Nice bath.
Yeah!
Stay in there for a long time.
Oh!!
Found Tetsusaiga!
My bad! Wrong move.
I know!
Use this to...
Oh!
Did it! Got it!
That's!
Sesshomaru!
Everything's spinning...
Same here...
Inuyasha!
Yuck!
S-Sessho... maru is...
I'll try to stall him.
Do something about these two.
Let's go, Kirara!
But do what?!
Over there... my clothes.
There! I found their clothes.
But where's Tetsusaiga?
Master Jaken, there you are!
Huh? Rin?
Why are you here?
I'm lost.
Hold it!
Oh no!
No, it's okay.
Rin is human, she can
hold Tetsusaiga.
Rin, take this and
go to Lord Sesshomaru.
But!
Hiraikotsu!
Rin, go while I hold her off!
You're not getting away!
Go around him, Kirara!
Not so fast!
Hold it, Jaken!
Return my Tetsusaiga!
I dunno what you're
talking about!
What?!
Master Jaken!
Rin, you fool!
Why did you come back?
Inuyasha!
Are you all right?
Yeah...
That's!
A girl?!
Grab on, Master Jaken!
Rin!
Hang on tight, Master Jaken.
Rin, why did you return?
Well, I was worried about you.
Oh yes, where is Tetsusaiga?
Huh?
Oh!
Oh?
No!
Huh? What's the matter,
Master Jaken?
Master Jaken!
Hey!
Damn that Jaken!
I'll get 'im next time!
Tetsusaiga seems to be
what he wanted.
Sesshomaru himself was
nowhere to be found.
Jaken worked alone on this.
What's the matter, Kagome?
Was something stolen from you?
No, it's nothing.
No one's noticed.
Sesshomaru is supposed to
despise humans.
Yet it was...
It was a human girl
who saved Jaken.
What's the meaning of this?
All that work for nothing.
They all look so good.
Which would you choose,
Master Jaken?
Whichever! I don't care!
Maybe I'll take two,
even three.
Lord Sesshomaru
and his whims!
Keeping a human girl
at his side.
This is so sweet, too!
Master Jaken, you keep
watch okay?
Oh well, it cannot be helped.
I was worried about you.
That moment, if Rin had
not returned,
I would have been beaten
badly by Inuyasha...
Huh?! You're!
Sesshomaru can be
so careless.
Taking his eyes off
his ward.
Ohh!
Rin!
Riiiin!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Rin has been abducted!
It was Naraku.
What's he up to anyway?!
Fool! Did he think that I would
take action
over a mere mortal?
And yet, he still walked straight
into Naraku's den!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Talk about shy and reserved!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Sesshomaru and the Abducted Rin"
Wait! Lord Sesshomaru!