Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha loses his demonic powers
in the sacred grounds of Mt. Hakurei
and is pursued by Jakotsu
of the Band of Seven.
And what is the source of the eerie
presence that Miroku and Sango
come across
deep inside the mountain?
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
I'm not going to get purified!
I'm gonna make it!
You're in a hurry, aren't you?
But if you go any farther,
even if you're only a half-demon
you'll be purified. Is that it?
Then go!
Y- you see...? I'm still...
Huh?
My demonic powers are gone! And
it's not even the night of the new moon!
Damn it! It's this barrier's fault!
So, you're Inuyasha? You're
pretty cute even as a human.
Jakotsu!
My, my. This makes
me so happy!
I've been waiting for the time
when I could fight you again!
Miroku!
Yes, let's go!
Who'd have thought this would
lead to a place like this....?
This....looks like a mountain temple.
This level of purification...
This must mean we're at the heart
of the sacred grounds!
It's a living Buddha!
It's Saint Hakushin!
Who are you?!
You're alive?!
Who is it who comes to violate
my sacred territory?
The mummy is alive....?
You're Saint Hakushin,
aren't you?!
Correct.... My name is Hakushin.
Has Naraku brought him
back to life....?
Saint Hakushin, in life you
were a man of high morals
and saved many people!
So how is it that you are
working to help Naraku?!
You have the powers enough to lay
down this strong, pure barrier!
I can't imagine that you
are assisting Naraku
because you can't see
through to his real self!
I know what he is....
But whether he's a demon of
great wickedness or not
is not my concern.
I'm doing only what I want to do.
Shippo!
Kirara? Is the barrier
hard on you, too?
Inuyasha!
I hope you're all right...
If it's too hard, just
hurry back here!
I wonder what's happening?
He's taking so long....
Even a half-demon would find
the sacred grounds a strain.
I wonder if he's met his end....
Inuyasha has....?!
Listen, you two....!
Hey, what's that for?!
We were just worrying
about him!
Just keep your mouths shut!
Kagome?
I'm sure Inuyasha's all right.
Thank you, Shippo.
Dammit!
Keep trying to get away.
I want to have my fill of fun.
I can't tell you how often I've
dreamed of cutting you up....
You were cute with dog ears,
but your human form is so luscious
it makes me want to hug you....
What a pervert! Everything
you say makes me gag!!
Damn it! Even the Robe of the Fire
Rat has lost its power?!
It's not serving as
armor anymore....
I'll cut you up, piece by piece.
And when I do, even a smart-mouth
like you will become soft and pliable.
And in the end, you'll be on your
knees, crying and begging me:
"Jakotsu, please hold me
gently in your arms...."
Feh! Any more of that and I'll
separate you from your head!
That's the spirit! I can't
wait to see you cry!
That sword...!
If I don't counter his blows right...
I won't be able to read his moves
and I'll be in deep trouble!
Go on, run away some more!
I adore chasing fleeing prey!!
Damn it all!
The barrier you created is hiding
and protecting the evil Naraku
and yet you still....
When I was alive, I never
hesitated to help people.
I entered Nirvana after several
years of great famine.
Disease was rampant and
corpses were everywhere.
It was a time like that.
Holy Saint, that is a bad man
who attacked our village!
You needn't save a man like him!
No, no.
All men, both good and evil,
are worthy of salvation.
Saint Hakushin...
Th... thank you...
May you rest in peace.
Saint Hakushin! Please help us!
There's nothing to eat in the
village! We have nothing at all!
Saint Hakushin!
I, also, while tending the sick,
became ill and collapsed.
The people gathered
around, lamenting....
If you're gone, Saint Hakushin,
what will we do?!
Who will save us?!
I had to give them an answer....
Never fear, all ye people...
I will become a living Buddha
and will look after the folks
of this land forever.
As I promised, I was buried alive
in front of all the people.
So that's how you
became beatified....
My only connection to
the outside world
was a short piece of bamboo
so I could breathe.
In the pit, I rang a
small bell continuously.
When the bell fell silent, it told
those outside that I was dead.
Outside all were praying that I
would enter Nirvana magnificently.
They are wishing for my death...
No!!
For the first time I was
overcome with regret.
Between my attachment to life and
my fear of the great darkness....
No! I did everything in my power to
help people out and still...!
Why do I have to die?!
And so I died....
My remains were sanctified
as a living Buddha,
but my soul was left
behind in the darkness,
with no hope of salvation,
for a long time....
And then came his voice....
Hate!
Hate them!
It's all right to hate.
How sad...!
Even though they revered
you as a holy saint,
they never allowed you to
have doubts or to suffer;
they never thought
of you at all.
He was speaking of things
I'd never dared to say....!
Don't deceive yourself any
more. You wanted to live.
So come with me.
Come with me and live.
Do you blame me?
Can you revile me?
I am no saint myself.
I have no intention
of judging you.
But I cannot allow to stand a
barrier which protects Naraku!
My barrier is impenetrable!
Miroku!
I'm all right!
That mutt! .... Causing Kagome
all this worry!
And I wonder what he's up to....
Where are you going?
That mutt is taking too long!
I'm going to go check on him.
That's crazy!
I know it's crazy!
No!
What?
Let's just trust Inuyasha and
wait for him here.
So! You can't move as
you'd like to, can you?!
This is no fun....
Let's hear a little louder
crying from you....
Good! Now you're panting
very satisfactorily....
That Inuyasha! I hoped he'd be
able to at least wound Jakotsu...
Damn....!
He can hardly move... He's going to
be tortured to death by Jakotsu...
It's almost time for our embrace....
all slippery with your blood.
Dammit...! My vision is going...
Give it up, Inuyasha....
I won't kill you yet.... I want to spend
a lot of time on you first.
Now!
That was close....
This little punk was aiming for
my jewel shard!
I don't have time to spend
playing with you....
Hmph! Threatening me
with that dull old sword!
You don't scare me!
Inuyasha....
Don't lose consciousness.
I want to hear you cry!
Damn...! I've lost too much blood...!
I thought I could try to
catch him off guard...
Cry! Cry for me!
It's no fun if you don't cry!
Take that!
So foolish.
Miroku! Place some sutras
on my Hiraikotsu!
Okay!
Go!
No good?
It's useless.
The powers of a novice monk like
you can't break my barrier.
So it seems.... In that case....
Forgive me, but I have
to get rid of you!
He can withstand the Wind Tunnel?!
If you're going to kill me,
then get on with it.
There's no need to rush things.
That's... Miroku and Sango?
Mt. Hakurei is....!
What on earth is going on there?
The barrier is broken!
Saimyosho?!
Mt. Hakurei...? The power of the
sacred ground is weakening...
Something is getting away!
As you wish, I'll finish you off.
At least give me one sweet little
scream of agony at the end....
What is this?! The demons are
starting to go crazy...
What?!
These guys....They're not supposed to
be able to pass the barrier!!
Take that!
They're still coming!
The presence of the barrier
is dissipating!
Miroku.... Sango.... You must be safe!
You've taken down the barrier!
I came to rescue you and you
ended up rescuing me!
So, you've gotten your
demonic powers back, have you?
Jakotsu, you're so stupid!
Because you didn't just get rid of
me, it'll cost you your life.
I couldn't help myself.
I only get excited when I can
cut you up slowly....
And I've already died once.
Being unexpectedly brought
back to life
and being able to meet a sweet thing
like you was a real bonus!
I guess you and I can never
have a serious discussion.
Well, things are heating up around
here, so I guess the fun's over.
But I'll take those dog ears
of yours as a souvenir!!
Like hell you will!
All I have to do is pull on this
sword and you'll be in pieces!
Bye-bye, Inuyasha.
Of all the men who've died by my
sword, I liked you the best....!
Kikyo comes into contact with Saint
Hakushin's soul and takes an
unexpected course of action.
Inuyasha, whose demonic powers
have returned,
brings his battle against Jakotsu
to a climax.
Forgive me, Jakotsu.
But I need every Sacred Jewel
shard I can get my hands on.
What the heck.... It was a lot of fun.
After losing all his comrades,
Bankotsu explodes.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Fare Thee Well: Jakotsu's Requiem"
Band of Seven, let this be
our final battle.