Ourarch-enemy Naraku had
totally concealed himself from us.
Fifty years ago, Onigumo the brigand
gave rise to Naraku.
Rasetsu Kansuke, who harbored a
deep grudge against Onigumo,
met Kikyo shortly before
his death.
Just about that time, as we journeyed
in our search for Naraku,
a chance meeting awaited us.
It seems like such a peaceful village.
No sign that Naraku's been here.
But this place is...
Huh? What is it, Sango?
Every field is in ruins.
What happened?
A boar, perhaps?
It's very strange.
- There!
- Huh?!
No mistake!
- Please wait!
- Villagers?
You there... the silver haired one!
Those ears!
He's not human!
Do they mean you, Inuyasha?
Who are you guys?
Please save us, Dog God!
Huh?
Dog God?
Dog God!
Dog God? Me?
What's this? Pickled vegetables?!
We realize that for someone
of your stature,
pickled vegetables
may not suffice...
But this is all we have in
the village.
We have no choice but
to appeal to you!
Hurry, hurry!
Fan him! Fan him!
Appeal to Inuyasha?
They must be very desperate.
What do you mean by that?
Ourfields are being ravaged
by monkeys.
Monkeys?
We have long heard that monkeys
feardogs.
Please, Dog God,
lend us yourpowers!
Please exterminate the monkeys!
I understand.
We accept.
Hey! I'm no Dog God!
What's with a little monkey business?
We have no time!
Rest assured.
Sango and I will continue on
and keep searching for Naraku.
He's right.
Inuyasha, we can't ignore
the villagers' plight.
Damn... what a joke!
Why should I deal with monkeys?!
Can't be helped.
You're the Dog God.
Yup, the Dog God!
Is it you...?!
D-Demon Monkey!
Dog Demon, huh?!
So the villagers, knowing how
I hate dogs, hired you, huh?
Well, you'll die instead...!
Now this is fun!
It's better when the opponent's
a demon!
Huh?
Little monkeys!
Oh, how cute!
Hey! Are you the ones
plundering the village fields?
You win!
Huh?
As proof that we'll never
do evil again,
please accept our spiritual stone!
Hah! Since you put it that way,
I have to accept...
Inuyasha...
What? Shippo?
It's a basic trick in
the mini-demon world
to catch your enemy off guard
and make an offering.
So I don't think you should accept.
Maybe it's too late.
Why didn't you say so sooner?!
Serves you right!
The dog demon can't move!
Moon, moon!
Monkey butts are crimson red!
Stupid fools!
You'd better cut out your silly tricks!
It's useless threatening us!
Until our spell is broken,
you're stuck to the rock!
I see. Then...
Then I'lljust clobber you
with this hand!
Inuyasha!
Yay! Yay!
Afterthem, Kagome!
K-Kagome!
Inuyasha... wait there!
Oww... hey!
We can't lose them!
Like they said, only the
perpetrators can undo the spell!
What?!
Shippo!
Miroku, weren't we supposed
to look for signs of Naraku?
We don't have Inuyasha who can
sniff out Naraku...
Nordo we have Kagome who
can sense the Sacred Jewel.
So what can we do?
Hmm...
I had to say that or Inuyasha
wouldn't have lifted a finger to help.
I'd better shape up!
I'd better do something!
Go!
What!
Transform!
Combine!
Smashing Top!
Spinning acorn!
You're pretty good!
You too!
Okay, all of you.
Time for a snack!
Why do you keep pillaging
the fields?
We're not pillaging!
We're looking for the Monkey God
who has been kidnapped.
Monkey God?
The deity who was enshrined
in this village.
As sprites who serve
the Monkey God,
ourjob was to protect the shrine
while continuing our training.
But because of the war,
the shrine was burned down.
And the sacred object containing
the spirit of the Monkey God was stolen!
And you think that the sacred object
is in the village?
Yes.
We believe that the sacred object is
buried in the field.
I know this because
I had a dream message.
I saw it, too.
I had one, too!
The message said ourgod was
in a dark, dank place.
Mine said it was small
and suffocating.
In my dream, our god said
it smelled of vegetables!
Something's coming closer.
Listen... I won't make any
judgments.
But the spell you put on Inuyasha...
you should break it.
No way!
Why?
Well...
We've forgotten how
to undo the spell.
What did you say?!
If you feign ignorance,
you'll get hurt.
Inuyasha doesn't know how
to take it easy with kids.
We're not feigning ignorance!
We really did forget it!
Oh dear...
You'll die!
Wait!
If we find the Monkey God,
your spell can be broken!
Besides, we learned the trick
from the Monkey God!
We must hurry back to the village
and find the sacred object!
Huh?
We're going on ahead!
What?
You shoulda just waited back there!
Hey!
Aren't you tired, Inuyasha?
Don't ask!
No way am I gonna keep
hanging on to this... rock!
How clumsy, Inuyasha.
Look at you, mutt!
W-Wha...!
You!
Such a shame that you can't
use Tetsusaiga with that arm.
- How wasteful...
- Hey, stop!
Give it back!
You can leave Kagome to me!
Why you...!
I, yourelderbrother, shall
gladly use Tetsusaiga.
Let's go, Kagome!
Wait, you!
Wait... - !
No way will I wait!
The sacred object of
the Monkey God?
Yes, it's supposed to be
in this village.
- Yeah, you have it!
- Give it back!
I know of no such thing.
He's here already!
Hey, what's the hold-up?!
Ourlives are at stake!
Huh?
The Dog God!
Where's the Monkey God?!
Get this rock off,
or I'll kill you!
That was quick, Inuyasha.
Hey, don'tgo nearhim!
Why you...!
Can't you remember how to
undo this spell?!
Not at all!
Yourhand got stuck to the boulder
due to a spell those monkeys put on you?
Are you really a Dog God?
That's why I've been telling you,
I'm not!!
He's the farthest thing
from a God.
Only the Monkey God can
undo the spell.
That's the story!
So if you're hiding anything,
I'll destroy the village!
Inuyasha! Sit!
Kagome... you!
Be quiet.
Shall we split up and search?
We don't want anymore plundering.
Thank you so much!
So what's it look like?
It's a rock about this size.
It's engraved with the
symbol of the Monkey God.
It's perfectly round.
Could that be it?
There was a rock like that
up in the mountain in the back.
- It's in the mountain!
- The mountain!
The mountain!
Awright! The mountain
overin the back, huh?
- This one?
- Nope.
No?!
Damn it!
Inuyasha!
I remember seeing it
along this riverbed.
- The riverbed!
The riverbed!
This one?
Nope.
It doesn't look godly at all.
This isn't it?!
Inuyasha!
Maybe it's that rock
in the forest.
Next to the Jizo shrine
overin the east...
I know! The one over
in the south valley!
There was a rock under
the house...
We're back.
Inuyasha...
What are you doing?
You guys help look
forthe sacred object, too.
I see.
So all this happened
in my absence.
It's such a problem.
I understand.
I'll do something with
my spiritual powers.
What?!
You'll find the Monkey God?!
Of course.
However, my powers are only
effective from morning.
It's okay!
What do you mean?
Well, I wanted to have a place
to stay tonight.
We've been saved!
You're being tricked.
Are you sure about
telling such a lie?
It'll work out somehow.
There's something fishy
about all this.
How pitiful, though.
Falling for such a trick.
Hey!
Hurry up and do something,
or you'll regret it.
Why?
With my hand like this...
I can't use the Tetsusaiga!
If Inuyasha...
remains stuck...
Hiraikotsu!
Wind Tunnel!
Get back, Miroku!
Stone-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
W-What?
It's a good thing, Inuyasha.
Yes, yes.
You have anotherweapon.
What're you picturing,
you two?!
If Inuyasha is stuck like this...
I'm going back home
to the present time.
Hey wait, Kagome!
I'm not waiting!
Don't just leave!
Damn!
This may be good.
Hey you...!
What're you picturing?
I know, Inuyasha.
Shall I suck up the rock
with my Wind Tunnel?
Can you just suck up
the rock?
If I stop in the nick
of time, it may work.
I'll open my Wind Tunnel
like this,
suck up the rock and
just as you get near it,
I'll close my...
Huh?
Huh?!
What's this "huh"?!
Well... if you're half
sucked in...
Err... nevermind.
What're you imagining?!
Nothing, nothing.
Let's try it.
Don't worry. I WILL NOT
suck you in.
H-hey!
Stop!!
Go on inside.
You don't have to stay
with me.
Well, isn't it lonely all
by yourself out here?
l-I'm not, silly!
I'll go if I'm a bother.
N-No, you're not!
- Really?
- Yeah!
But what a problem.
Isn't there anotherway?
Excuse me!
Is that?
Huh?
This is about all we
can offer.
And... what of it?
This is quite amazing.
T-This is!
Hey! Weren't these vegetables
grown in the fields here?
This is unmistakably the glow
from ourMonkey God!
Just as he said in my dream...
Dark and dank.
Small and suffocating.
With a smell of vegetables!
The field is the only place!
He must be buried deep
underground!
Awright! We'll turn the village
upside down!
Yeah!
Is he serious?
Sit!
I'd like to see something.
I thought so...
The pickling stone has a glow.
It's the sacred object!
Monkey God!
- Glow?
- We don't see anything.
What a terrible thing
to do to the sacred object!
You DID steal it, after all!
No, I found it on the
outskirts of the village.
I thought it'd be a perfect
weight for pickling.
Then you found it right
outside the forest?
Liar!
The sacred object was kept in
the shrine deep in the forest!
We sprites guarded it dearly!
Yes! Even that day...
We desperately took the sacred object
out of the burning shrine.
We've brought it farenough.
It should be fine now.
Uh-huh...
Oh... acorns!
Lots and lots of'em!
Look... overhere, too!
In otherwords,
you forgot all about it.
Now then, the purification water.
I've been waiting!
Monkey God!
We've longed to see you!
It reeked of vegetables!
Monkey God!
Has anything strange happened
in my absence?
No! Not a thing!
Hey!
Yep, they forgot about him.
If you build a new shrine
and make offerings,
the Monkey God will
protect you.
Yes sir!
Aren't you glad, Inuyasha,
that the weight is off yourhand?
Damn! What a waste of time!
Shrewd young girl!
You did well to find me.
I thank you.
Oh no... your dream messages
were so clear.
You three were
just too stupid.
What did you say?!
You thought it was
underground, too!
I wanted to get out
as soon as possible.
I was concerned about
the strange occurrence outside.
Strange occurrence?
Shortly after I was placed
in the pickling tub,
I felt an awful evil aura,
the likes of which I had neverfelt...
pass over the skies above
the village.
Huh?
What?
Monkey God, what was it?
I don't know what it was.
But I felt its presence while
I was in the pickling tub.
And?
Where did itgo?
It disappeared.
Disappeared?
It didn't just pass over completely.
It suddenly disappeared.
Inuyasha.
There's no mistake.
It's Naraku!
The miasma headed in the direction
of the ox and tiger.
Ox and tiger?
That's northeast?
I can't pinpointexactly
where it disappeared.
Shall we go?
Yeah...
We know which way to go now!
W-What the...?!
Acorns!
Why you...!
Scared ya!
Moon ya, Shippo!
Moon ya, Inuyasha!
We'll meet again!
What's with them?!
They were some adversaries, huh?
Just pesky monkeys!
Hey, Shippo!
Hey, wait up, Inuyasha!
Shaddup! Let's go!
We head northeast!
Kagome is sick?
She must've been exhausted with
all this searching for Naraku.
Her cold got worse
and she's running a fever.
I had her return home to her time.
Was that okay?
They've got medicine and doctors
there... I hope she recovers quickly.
Inuyasha went back to see her.
To wish herwell?
Like he's the kind of guy
to do that?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Nursing Battle of the Rival Lovers"
Rivals? Whose?