Master!
Are you Tsubaki
the Dark Priestess?
If you came to break the curse,
it's too late.
The ceremony is over.
Who cares about that?
I came to get you.
Are you a demon?!
Cut it out!
Troublesome hag.
But someone wants to
borrow your powers.
What does a demon want
with me?
Do you still bear a grudge
against Kikyo?
Kikyo, you say?
What's this?!
I don't have a clue!
I don't get it at all!
I don't understand a thing!
Read the next line, Higurashi.
I've forgotten everything
I learned earlier...
I'm falling so far behind!
Kagome looks so depressed.
I'll bet it's that old boyfriend!
You mean, the one who jilted Kagome.
The jealous, two-timing, bossy guy?
She probably can't get him
out of her mind.
Cheer up, Kagome.
Just forget him!
Yeah, he's not worth it!
Who?
Not Inuyasha?!
If you broke up,
you just have...
to get over him.
Oh, well we...
What now?
We made up.
You're back together?
With him?
He has his kind side.
Really?
Then that's normal.
So why were you so down?
I've been absent a lot and
there's so much schoolwork...
I see. You do miss school a lot.
Even if you never miss class,
it's difficult to follow sometimes.
I know...
But if you keep up and work hard,
classes are fun, aren't they?
What? What?
What? Did I say something strange?
Err... no.
You're so studious.
I've got to go!
When I'm late, he comes for me.
He comes to meet you?
He's really nice then!
Nope... He's just jealous.
He's spoiled!
Bye-bye!
They're back together.
I wonder if Kagome can
handle it?
Huh? Why?
What an ominous barrier.
Hold on tight, old woman.
Naraku, I found her.
So you're here...
Dark Priestess Tsubaki.
What do you want,
calling me here?
Do you remember battling a priestess
named Kikyo fifty years ago?
You were trying to steal the
Sacred Jewel.
Oh... I'm amazed that you know
of such an old incident.
Dark Priestess Tsubaki...
Would you like to use your
evil powers for me?
Naraku, you say?
How will helping you
benefit me?
You shall have
the Sacred Jewel.
What?!
The Sacred Jewel?
You have it?
The old hag
transformed herself!
Watch what you say!
This is my true form!
This old woman... sold her soul
to a demon in order to preserve her youth.
However, the demon didn't have
much standing.
This woman seeks
even more power.
If you really have the Sacred Jewel,
let me see it.
What do you desire from
the Sacred Jewel?
Eternal youth?
Naraku... Just what do you want
with me?
This one's for Shippo and
this is Inuyasha's favorite.
Don't only take sweets.
Here... How about this?
Thanks, Mom!
I still have lots more.
Oh, thank you.
Kagome! Don't forget the
charms and amulets!
Grandpa, that's okay.
R-Really?
Sis, are you going already?
They're waiting.
You mean, Inuyasha?
No, everyone!
I wish I could go back
in time, too.
Even if you came,
you're such a scaredy cat.
You'll want to go home
right away.
She's right. Sota, you're
still so young.
Don't you get scared, Sis?
I'm sorta used to it now.
So heavy!
Can you carry it, Sis?
Can't be helped.
I'll leave these.
Kagome is late!
She said she'd be back by dusk!
She said she'd be back by dusk.
What're you doing?!
Shaddup!
Hey!
What's that?
You sense it, too, Shippo?
I don't know what it is, but...
Something stinks!
This aura...
Kaede...
Miroku!
You sensed it?
Yes.
Evil is lurking.
As though it's crawling
over the ground.
What could it be?
I don't know...
Here I am!
Boy, that was heavy!
Oww!
W-What's?
I was bitten?
But by what?
There's nothing.
You're late, Kagome!
Inuyasha!
I was bitten... by something.
What?!
That's it!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
Paper?!
Good work.
You have the girl's blood?
Are you done?
Yes.
Now take me back.
So bossy!
There was something strange.
I got it, though.
I can handle this alone.
Sure, as you please.
It's true!
But there's no bite mark.
He's right.
But...
There was something strange there.
Let me see, Inuyasha... That paper.
By the way... Kagome...
I didn't forget.
Here you are.
Yes! This is the one!
And for you, Inuyasha.
How about some of this, everyone?
This is... Shikigami.
Shikigami?
What's that?
Huh?!
The Sacred Jewel Shards!
What's the matter, Kagome?
Miss Kagome?!
Huh?!
The Shards have turned black.
Kagome!
The Shards are entering
my body...
Kagome!
The Shards which enter the
woman's body...
synchronize with this Sacred Jewel which
has been defiled with Naraku's evil...
and will slowly fester inside her.
In both body and mind.
Then... her life will be mine
to control.
Tsubaki...
Don't underestimate this Kagome.
Don't make me laugh!
She didn't even realize that
she had been cursed.
You said she was the reincarnation
of Kikyo,
so I wondered how formidable she
would be.
Now what shall I do?
Kill her immediately?
Or...
Let us show Inuyasha a
bad dream again.
The woman he loves...
the woman who wants to kill him.
Such a nostalgic dream.
Hey, Kagome!
Wake up!
Hang on!
Kagome!
Kaede, what does this mean?
That evil which lurked...
Someone has placed a curse
on Kagome!
Someone's put a curse on her?!
Probably the work of
the Dark Priestess.
Kagome was bitten at the well...
by the Dark Priestess' messenger
demon spirit, Shikigami!
Dark Priestess?!
Inuyasha, you know of her existence.
She specializes in curses...
a wicked evil shrine maiden.
It's her power that turned the
Jewel Shards black.
And they've entered
her body completely!
She may die from the poison
unless we do something!
Let's go, Sango!
We'll find the Dark Priestess
and destroy her.
That's the only way to
break the curse.
Then I'll go, too!
Inu... yasha!
You stay here with Kagome.
That would be best.
I sense evil coming
from this direction!
Get on, Miroku!
We're counting on you!
Kagome!
Kill him!
Who?!
Kill who?!
Kill Inuyasha!
Kill him!
Who?
Kill who?!
Kill Inuyasha!
Stop!
Please stop!
Humph! She's resisting.
I told you, Tsubaki.
Kagome is the
reincarnation of the priestess, Kikyo.
She'll require more effort
than usual.
Kikyo, huh?
That woman!
At that time, Kikyo was infatuated
with a half-demon.
And her powers were weakened.
It was the perfect opportunity to
steal the Sacred Jewel from its guardian.
But...
That woman...
She hurled the Shikigami I sent
straight back at me!
Relax. I will spare your life.
That smug look on her face!
Just thinking about it
makes me boil!
Will she be all right?!
Will she?!
I will change the water.
Over there!
Let's hurry, Miroku!
Will Kagome be saved?
Kagome is probably fighting
the curse with all her might.
Kagome is strong.
Yes...
But...
The longer it takes, the weaker
she'll be to resist.
Is it going to take much longer?
She'll stop resisting soon.
Now then, Naraku...
You shall have your wish.
Damn!
Haven't they found the
Dark Priestess yet?!
Damn!
Kagome is suffering!
How can l just watch?!
Kagome!
Die, Inuyasha!
Why?!
Kill Inuyasha!
Kill him!
Get... away, Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Y-You!
Stubborn woman.
I have control of her body.
But her mind still resists.
This is becoming even more fun.
Tsubaki...
If Inuyasha should run out of there,
then go ahead and kill Kagome.
Get away...
Kagome is being manipulated
by the Dark Priestess.
Miroku, aren't you done yet?!
The miasma is getting stronger!
Hurry, Kirara!
There it is!
Miroku!
This is!
I can feel it...
This evil... I have faced it once before.
I can kill this woman anytime.
Inuyasha, what will you do?
Be killed by Kagome?
Or will you run and
get Kagome killed?
Get... away...
What do you want?
Suffer Inuyasha!
Get away!
Inuyasha!
Before she collapsed, Kagome
said she was bitten by something.
It was probably the messenger snake
of the Dark Priestess.
Hurry, Miroku!
We must find her!
Or else, Kagome will
kill Inuyasha!
But this barrier is too strong...
I am powerless against it!
Look there!
Kikyo!
Why is she here?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kikyo and the Dark Priestess!"
Just what happened fifty years ago?