It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
for our dreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
Demon rats go on a wild stampede.
Just what is Naraku's aim
in causing this?
And Kohaku, the one who
manipulates these rats,
comes to a decision after
much anguish.
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
You're not healed yet,
Hakudoshi?
It's because of that arrow.
Go!
Naraku!
That same arrow broke my barrier
once before.
Kikyo is alive.
Only she could imbue an arrow
with so much will.
Why don't you go immediately
to kill her?
I cannot sense her presence.
Is she seriously trying to
hide herself?
Then it will mean that she
has not completely recovered.
I must lure her out now
and finish her off.
There's no mistake...
Naraku and Hakudoshi's heart
is Hakudoshi's other half-
that infant.
Neither Naraku nor Hakudoshi
have died.
Is it because they are demons?
What must I do to defeat Naraku?
Hey Kohaku....
Huh?
You haven't been told?
About what?
That infant.
After you took it out of that castle,
where were you supposed
to take it?
I don't know.
That infant?
Even if it meant killing everyone
in the castle,
I was ordered to take it
out of the castle.
What would you do
if you knew its whereabouts?
I'm always telling you....
one day, that Sacred Jewel shard
will be removed from your body
and you'll die.
If Naraku isn't killed,
you won't be saved.
If the infant is found,
can Naraku be killed?
Kagura is trying to
betray Naraku.
But...
I don't know anything.
Oh really?
I can't have them finding out...
That I've remembered everything.
That I'm after Naraku's life.
If I keep pretending to
be his slave,
I'll come across that infant again.
Until that time,
I must not disobey Naraku's orders.
Come one, come all!
With this amazing sword,
I shall cut this sheet of paper.
From one into two!
Then two into four!
Then four in eight!
Then 16, 32 and 64 pieces!
Hey, where did Inuyasha
go leaving us here like this?
Umm.... I wonder....
I wonder where?
To Kikyo.
Huh?
To the spot where he
last met Kikyo.
But that's....
Huh?
It's okay. He can do as he pleases.
Inuyasha...
Kikyo!
You've hidden yourself away again.
You haven't recovered all
your strength yet?
Inuyasha is late.
Hey Kagome....
Shouldn't we have gone
with him?
He probably wanted to
talk to Kikyo alone.
Why do you have such
an understanding heart, Kagome?
No reason.
That Inuyasha is such a problem!
Still wagging his tail and
going after a woman from his past!
Although it is said about dogs:
Once a pet,
a dog never forgets.
Who's a pet?
And so?
What did you talk about?
Kikyo wasn't there.
You don't have to lie.
Huh?!
Why would I have to lie?
Stupid!
Sit.
Why you...!
Sit!
I was kind to you and
let you go off by yourself.
Sit!
At least be up front about
what you talked about!
Sit!
There's no sense in
having any consideration for you!
Sit!
I guess Kagome was feeling
hurt, after all.
Poor Kagome.
It doesn't pay to be
understanding.
You guys....
Here, I got it for you.
Hakudoshi, lure Kikyo out.
And take.... Let's see....
- Kohaku.
- Huh?
Do as Hakudoshi tells you.
Yes.
The method is up to you.
Just make sure that Kikyo
cannot stay in hiding.
Right.
You let your subordinates
eat the meat of their prey,
and devour the bones yourself.
You are Zushinezumi....huh?
Huh?
Brat.... Are you a survivor
of this house?
Perfect timing.
I had a hankering for
bones like yours.
Hmm....
You're quite skilled, Kohaku.
Bring that little shrine that
he has on his back.
All right.
Don't make a mistake
and open it here.
Or you'll die.
T- That's...!
What is that?
No!
Do you sense something strange?
Huh?
Something's coming!
H-Help us!
Grandpa!
Are they being pursued
by something?
That's....!
Huh?!
Demon rats!
Inuyasha!
Stop!
Wha...?!
What?!
They've increased!
I knew it.... Zushinezumi.
Wha...?!
Why these...!
Don't kill them!
These Zushinezumi....
The more you kill, the more they increase.
How do you exterminate them?
With toxic smoke.
But without special medicinal herbs....
You don't have them with you?
Unfortunately....
Then there's only this....!
Wind Tunnel!
The village was attacked?
Luckily, my grandson and I were up
in the mountain behind the village.
But....
everyone else in the village....
Grandpa!
Sango....
You called them Zushi....nezumi?
There should be a large rat
who is their chief.
He keeps the rats in a
miniature shrine
which he carries on his back.
And he releases them to
kill humans and animals.
But....
He only attacks what
he plans to eat.
I've never heard of a large
pack of rats attacking a village.
There's bound to be many more.
I can smell rats far away.
And it's as though their numbers
are steadily increasing.
l-Increasing?!
You two must get further away.
What about you?
We're gonna check to see
what's happening!
I can smell them!
The way they're increasing
isn't normal.
What's going on anyway?!
They keep coming, don't they?
The rats will scatter everywhere
and attack wherever humans live.
Huh?
R-Rats?!
Why you...!
And wherever they go,
their numbers will increase.
In time, this land will
be devoured by rats.
Will Kikyo come out of hiding?
Oh...
That's right.
I suppose she will.
She'll soon know what's
happening here.
Resorting to this,
just to lure Kikyo out of hiding!
Kocho.
Yes?
There is something I need.
It is in the western mountains.
Everywhere is overrun by rats.
Sango....
You said that Zushinezumi increase
in proportion to the numbers
which are cut, right?
Yes.
They don't die even if
you cut them,
so they keep increasing.
Since they've spread so far,
we can't trace the source.
By source, you mean
the miniature shrine?
Yes.
I heard that if you destroy
the shrine,
the rats will disappear.
Miroku and Sango are
so late.
Geez! Why do I have to wait
inside the barrier, too?
When you get mad,
you tend to go crazy and swing
your sword around.
That'll only make the rats
increase.
Are you implying that
I'm stupid?
Wow, for someone who's stupid,
you figured that out quickly.
Owwee!
Inuyasha! Look!
Saimyosho!
Does that mean Naraku is
behind
this rampage of the Zushinezumi?!
Hah! I figured as much.
I didn't think he died
in that fight.
Oh, they've returned!
So you saw them, too?
The Saimyosho?
Yes.
Is Naraku looking for us
to get revenge?
I think....
He wants us to know that
he's the one behind
all this.
Whaddya mean?
Doesn't it seem as though
he's trying to lure
someone out?
Us....or....
Kikyo!
He's right!
Naraku's after Kikyo...
Mistress Kikyo....
Kocho is back.
Here is the branch of
ogatama which you asked for.
Good.
Asuka, Kocho,
we are descending the mountain.
What is....?!
The rats who were scattered
are starting to gather.
It's like they're headed
for one place.
Look....
They're forming one line.
Somewhere, there is a mayose.
Mayose?
A spell that lures demons together,
then destroys them.
But only one with immense
spiritual power can cast such a spell.
The only one capable of this...
is Kikyo.
At the end of this flow of rats
is Kikyo!
Let's go, Inuyasha!
K-Kagome!
I'll try to go to the source,
where the rats are coming from.
Sango!
It bothers me....
that the number of rats
hasn't decreased at all.
Which means that the shrine
is still releasing rats.
So we must go to the source
or this will not end.
Let's split into two groups.
I'll go with Sango.
Huh?
Kikyo has made her move.
Kohaku, you stay here.
Guard the shrine.
Do not close the doors.
Yes.
Say Kagome....
If Kikyo is up ahead,
do you think Naraku will appear, too?
Huh?
Yes...
Naraku is after Kikyo's life.
Are you scared of Naraku, Shippo?
Then you shoulda gone with
Miroku and Sango!
No way!
When you and Kikyo meet
and that funny feeling
comes over you,
who's gonna console Kagome?
Huh?
Do you get it, you two-timing dog?!
Keep it up and
I'll drop you!
Inuyasha, look at that!
Huh?
I'm scared, Grandpa!
It's okay, it's okay.
Namuhachiban daibosatsu...
Shippo! Do you have anything
that rats hate?
How's this?
Fire bomb!
Make your escape now!
O-Okay!
Thank you.
How's that?!
The power of my fire bomb!
Inuyasha! Look!
The rats are climbing something!
l-It looks like a tree.
A tree?
It reaches up all the way
to heaven!
The rats are disappearing
into the sky....
Is this the mayose?
This village seems to have
been devoured some time ago.
Yes, it was in the path
of the rats.
How cruel....
Hurry, Kirara!
Why?
Kikyo has come out of hiding.
Do not close the doors.
That bastard!
He was enjoying this!
If I close these doors,
the rats will stop.
Even now...
It may save some lives.
I'm being watched...
If I close the doors,
Naraku will know that my
memory has returned.
Kohaku!
Huh?!
Were you behind this?!
Sister...
Kohaku....
On my way here,
I saw countless villages
devoured by rats.
How I wish you were not
a part of this!
I cannot....disobey my orders!
Kohaku!
Sango!
Do you know how many villages were
devoured
just to lure Kikyo out of hiding?!
When you see him, tell him....
As long as you keep running away
from Naraku,
this will happen over and over again.
Kohaku, you're going to end up
fodder for the rats, too!
I'm sorry, Sister.
But I cannot disobey my orders!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kohaku's Decision and Sango's Heart"
I must defeat Naraku as soon as possible!