Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
At Mt. Hakurei, Naraku,
who has been newly reborn,
produces another incarnation
and leaves after slaying Kikyo.
The tragedy brings darkness
into our hearts
and yet another trap is set for us.
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Kikyo!
Huh? So that bastard Naraku
put up that huge barrier
and cooped himself up in that mountain
in order to kill a mere woman?!
Lady Kikyo was no mere woman.
Naraku feared Kikyo's
spiritual powers.
And Naraku wanted to rid himself
of his heart....
The human heart
that yearned for Kikyo.
Once before, Naraku tried to cut
out his human heart.
That was when he created Muso,
the one who possessed the heart and
memories of the bandit, Onigumo.
Now feed upon me!
And give me a body
and power!
But Naraku absorbed Muso back
into his body,
saying it had been too soon
to produce him.
Kikyo!
This tenacity... This greed!
Then Naraku was....
Yes....
Those ominous fleshy forms
we saw inside Mt. Hakurei....
He was creating a body
he could cast out
which contained his own
human heart.
So now that he's killed off
that scary priestess,
does it mean Naraku can do
just about anything he wants?
Well.... As if I'd let him.
I'm going.
We found you!
Koga!
W-We finally found you.
Hey.
I'm off, Kagome.
Take care, huh?
Koga, take it easy too.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I don't hear the mutt complaining.
Hey, where is that idiot anyway?
He looked awfully depressed.
Stupid Inuyasha!
He left Kagome to go
in search of Kikyo.
Inuyasha hasn't been able
to accept Kikyo's death.
I understand how he must feel....
Inuyasha...
Kikyo...
Why'd you try to fight him alone?
Why didn't you wait until
I got there?!
Kikyo!
Even if it's flowing into the river,
the miasma isn't weakening.
Kikyo!
You're there, aren't you?!
I don't care to know what your
connection to that woman was.
But the one who killed
Kikyo was Naraku.
And the one who wasn't able
to save her...
was you, Inuyasha.
I will slay Naraku
with my own hands!
So you don't have to fight anymore.
I will protect you.
Kikyo...?
Watching you now,
I realize it so well.
As long as Onigumo's heart
exists inside Naraku,
there will be an opportunity.
And I will use that chance to
totally destroy Naraku
and rid him from this world.
Kikyo!
Kikyo didn't believe me...
That's why...
Dammit!
Damn!
Kikyo... Did you really die here...
all alone?
Kikyo!
Keep up, guys!
We're chasing after Naraku!
They said a huge demonic
aura went south.
First north, now we're going
back south.
Shouldn't we have stayed
in the south from the start and waited?
With Inuyasha gone, this is the perfect
chance to win Kagome over!
He was pretty nonchalant
about leaving her.
I don't understand him!
I'll find Naraku and destroy him
in place of Inuyasha.
You just wait, Kagome!
Day's breaking...
Inuyasha...
How far did you go
in search of Kikyo?
Huh?
l-Inuyasha!
Inuyasha, have you returned?
Kagome?
You waited up for me?
Yes.
Couldn't you find Kikyo?
I want to ask, but...
I thought....
I'd be able to find
her remains at least.
Inuyasha....
What can I say to him?
I can't stand to see him
in such pain...
I don't know
how to console him...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I'm....okay now.
"Okay"?
Inuyasha...
You don't look okay at all.
What am I to do?
What can I do?
This area too....
Caused by Mt. Hakurei's collapse?
I wonder if Shintaro and the others
are okay?
Kirara!
Here you go.
Eat it all up.
Shintaro!
Miroku! Kagome!
All of you together!
You are all safe!
Aren't you glad, Inuyasha?
Huh? Yeah....
Hey, I'll help.
In many villages, demons
are running rampant.
I'm glad that Shintaro
and the others are all right.
But Inuyasha looks so troubled.
We left Mt. Hakurei so quickly
in pursuit of Naraku...
But I wonder if that was
okay with Inuyasha?
Maybe he really wanted to stay
and search for Kikyo.
Such a frightening thing.
Could the rumors be true?
It's said Mt. Hakurei crumbled away
in one night.
I hope nothing bad
comes from it.
What is that?!
That demonic aura....
Dammit!
Inuyasha!
So horrible!
This is the third village....
I only catch the scent
of weak demons.
Could this be the work of demons who
escaped the barrier of Mt. Hakurei?
Damn! This is awful!
We cornered Naraku and forced
him out of hiding...
But this is even worse
than before.
On top of that, Kikyo was killed.
Miroku, I picked flowers.
Put them over there.
You there....
Such a tragedy....
Let me assist you.
Priest....
You came from the area
of Mt. Hakurei?
Yes. I have been on a pilgrimage,
traveling around the country.
I heard that Mt. Hakurei,
the sacred mountain, had collapsed
and that an evil aura was
spreading south.
I see....
It's exactly as that priestess said.
Huh?
Priestess?
It was about two days ago.
An injured priestess had been
washed up on the riverbank
in a region beyond the mountain.
She mumbled something about
Naraku wounding her.
That she had to go
after Naraku.
That has to be Kikyo.
She survived!
Kikyo is...!
But her injuries were
so serious.
She may have died from them.
Go, Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Kagome?
This is no time to hesitate.
Hurry!
Kikyo must be waiting.
O-Okay....
Forgive me.
Are you sure about this, Kagome?
It can't be helped.
Forgive me, Kagome.
I have to make sure this time,
if Kikyo is dead or alive...
Otherwise, I won't be able
to go on!
Inuyasha hasn't returned.
Well, let's go on ahead.
Inuyasha will pick up Kagome's scent
and follow us.
I guess.
He's right!
You there! Halt!
You all look suspicious!
Suspicious?
Does he mean your
appearance, Kagome?
There have been many
strange happenings here lately.
We have been ordered to detain
all suspicious looking travelers
and take them to the castle.
Now come!
Well....
What'll we do? We can
easily beat them and escape.
Don't start talking like Inuyasha.
Besides, these officials are
ordinary mortals.
We can escape anytime.
Stop your mumbling!
Tie them up!
T-This is bad!
We have to get Inuyasha back.
Let's go, Kirara!
Please forgive me!
I am not suspicious! I have the
proper travel documents!
Execute him!
Will we all be killed?
Not even a hearing, huh?
H-How terrible!
This is very disquieting.
She's here.
Kagome!
Come, wench!
It is My Lady's orders!
Just me?
What's going on?
I have no use for
the others.
Kill them.
Miroku! Sango!
Inuyasha! Where are you?!
Inuyasha! Inuyasha!
With Kikyo dead, you are the only one
able to see the Sacred Jewel shards.
Huh?
The priest from yesterday....
Honestly, I've had it!
Making me baby-sit
a kid!
Kagura!
This priest....
What else?
I was controlling him with
my Dance of the Dead.
Then the story about Kikyo
being alive was a lie...
No one will come to save you.
The monk and the Demon Slayer will
be killed by the clansmen.
It's not the woman speaking.
Inuyasha won't come.
Inuyasha is obsessed with
finding Kikyo.
This infant....
is an incarnation of Naraku!
This baby is an incarnation of Naraku,
born at Mt. Hakurei.
Just what do you intend to
do with me?
I told you.
You're the only one who can
see the Sacred Jewel shards.
I want your eyes.
Resign yourself to death!
A hidden weapon?!
Damn wench! How dare she?!
Get them!
Miroku!
My thanks!
I'm taking these back!
R-Run!
Hey! You're not getting away!
Out of the way!
These men are nothing much.
Still.... They're just mortals following
orders from above.
We can't kill them, on top of that
we're far outnumbered.
This may take some time.
But Kagome was taken away
all alone. We must hurry!
Kagome....
I will make good use
of your eyes.
Kagura, untie the rope.
Are you sure?
No!
What are you afraid of?
You think I'll take your eyes
and eat them?
What? This girl's soul...
I can't find her darkness.
That can't be.
In every human, there is
darkness in the heart.
Anger, hatred, and...
What is this?
This terrible feeling....
It's like he's digging around
inside my heart.
Help...
Inuyasha, help!
Inuyasha....
Inuyasha isn't coming.
I'm okay now.
Inuyasha is....
Inuyasha is searching
for Kikyo.
Forgive me.
Inuyasha won't come to
save me.
Inuyasha...
Found it!
I've grasped the darkness
in your heart.
You can't get away.
Now hold me tightly.
Let our souls unite and
become my eyes.
Inuyasha...
Kagome was captured while
I was searching for Kikyo!
The human heart is very fragile.
And hatred is so easily bred.
This girl is no different.
Use that tainted Sacred Jewel shard.
You mean Kagome will now become
Naraku's servant?
I feel bitter towards Inuyasha?
I hate Kikyo?
Yes.... But....
Next on Inuyasha:
"Transform Heartache into Courage!"
It means that I love Inuyasha!