How beautiful you must have been
when you were alive...
Midoriko.
Was it that beauty that
gave you the power
to create the Sacred Jewel?
Said to give powerto those who
possess it and grant theirevery wish...
the Sacred Jewel.
It was from that time,
to search forthe shards
of the Sacred Jewel,
that ourjourney began.
We continue ourpursuit of Naraku
who possesses most of
the Sacred Jewel shards.
The breeze feels so nice.
So peaceful...
We haven't found a single
clue to Naraku's whereabouts!
And here you are,
wasting time like this!
Hurry up and eat!
And because of Naraku's disappearance,
all sorts of demons who have
lain low all this time
are coming out of the woodwork.
It's terrible.
So what'll we do?
ljust want to be able to
enjoy my meal at least!
Grow up a little, Inuyasha.
What?!
Unlike us powerful demons,
Kagome, Sango and Miroku
are weak mortals.
Don't ask for the impossible.
Did he call us "weak mortals"?
It helps that Shippo is
so mature.
What? Did I say something weird?
Not at all.
I'm not wrong, am I?
Who's the "powerful demon"?
Dammit all!
Just wake me when
you're done eating.
Okay.
Hmm... the air feels great
and the riceball is delicious!
- Such nice weather!
- And fine weather.
What's this?!
Is something wrong, Kagome?
I may be imagining it.
But I feel something...
like the Sacred Jewel.
Why can't you be more
sure of yourself?
This time it's different.
Which way?
Overthat way.
It's coming closer!
Stop!
Leave 'im to me!
- You're safe now.
- Don't worry.
What's the big idea, runt?
Trying to interfere?
Is he the one, Kagome?
Uh-huh. He has a Sacred Jewel
shard in his belly.
But...
So where'd you get
this Jewel shard?
Now that you know about
my Sacred Jewel,
you'd betterhand over
that fellow quietly.
Why don't you leave that
Jewel shard here
and quietly get lost!
Impudent kid!
Know the might of my power!
Nothing to brag about!
Ridiculous... this isn't supposed
to happen!
Huh?
What's that?
The Sacred Jewel!
Impossible!
Huh? What's this?
Inuyasha shattered
the Jewel!
Fool! The Sacred Jewel
wouldn't break so easily!
But I sensed the same presence.
It's an imitation Sacred Jewel.
Huh?!
There is a demon trying to
duplicate the Sacred Jewel.
What're you talking about?!
Pardon me, but may I
have a drink of water?
Oh...
Please drink this.
Ohh... this is...
such a beautiful water container.
Just who is he?
My name is Izumo.
My family has served as
guujifor centuries.
Guuji? What's that?
Beats me.
They are shrine keepers.
Like my grandfather.
I see! That's why you
are a priestess.
Go on!
I began my studies in order
to better serve the gods.
And I became engrossed
in scholarship
and traveled to many countries
to learn, research and record.
I don't care about you!
Tell us about the
imitation Sacred Jewel!
The purpose of my studies
is precisely to learn about
the Sacred Jewel.
That's why you know
about its existence.
All the universe, everything in life,
is created from four spirits.
Aramitama, Nigimitama,
Kushimitama and Sakimitama.
When these four spirits are in synthesis,
they become one,
and in the human body
becomes the heart.
Are we going back to that again!?
I heard that before,
but I neverreally understood.
Same here...
Explain how that demon
got possession of
the fake Sacred Jewel!
Because someone gave
it to him.
Who?
Ademon.
You looking for a fight?!
No, ljust...
Stop it, Inuyasha!
Um...
Why was that demon
chasing you anyway?
Well, that's because
I saw the demons.
Huh?
I heard that there was a shrine which
told the legend of the Sacred Jewel.
And I made my way
to the mountain path.
Buteventually, I got lost.
Then I came upon a demon
handing the Sacred Jewel
to that demon you just saw.
Was he called Naraku?
No. He called himself Orochidayu.
And he said that the Jewel was
not yet complete,
but that soon a true Sacred
Jewel would be made.
You're saying that a demon
is making Sacred Jewels?
That's all I overheard.
I don't sense any presence
of demons.
It was just around here
that I witnessed that demon.
I don't catch any scent
of Naraku.
It doesn't seem like
he's involved.
Well, Kagome?
Do you sense the presence
of the Sacred Jewel?
No, not at all.
It's not like it's a
strong presence to begin with.
'Cuz it's a fake!
It probably doesn't
work that well either.
Say! There's a village
overthere.
No one's around.
Not a sign of anyone.
I wonder if something happened.
Hey!
Where is he?
Huh?! Izumo!
Hey! What're you doing?
Oh...
Hey!
Word has it that this shrine
houses the Deity of Origin.
Huh?
It's empty.
What is the Deity of Origin?
There is a legend that says
from the heart of this Deity
were born the spirits
Kushimitama and Sakimitama.
Oh... is that right?
Kushimitama which embodies
Chi (knowledge)
and Sakimitama which
embodies Ai (love).
Aramitama symbolizes Yu (courage) and
Nigimitama symbolizes Shin (friendship).
Yu, Shin, Chi, Ai.
These are the four spirits
of the Shikon Jewel.
Arghh! I don't understand!
Never mind such talk.
I'm getting a weird feeling
from this area.
We should investigate
a bit deeper.
Yeah, I'll check the
village outskirts.
Uh-huh.
We haven't found a thing.
What're you doing?
Why is the sun so warm
and blinding?
It's only natural that
the sun is blinding.
Only natural?
But it's wondrous to me.
Is something burning
overyonder?
Furthermore, just how far
is it to the sun?
He thinks up such
weird stuff.
No... I've nevermet a man
who thinks like he does in this world.
I'm impressed.
Is it common in
yourworld?
Why does night fall?
Izumo is a scholar.
Say...
Yes?
About the four spirits...
What do they mean?
This Yu and Shin...
You mean, Yu, Shin, Chi, Ai?
Y-Yeah...
Yu means courage.
I understand when you
explain it like that.
You're right.
Shin means friendship...
to be intimate.
Chimeans knowledge...
to know things well.
Ai is love.
Now I understand.
Something-mitama...
or whatever...
I couldn't understand
thatgibberish.
Aramitama of courage.
Nigimitama of friendship.
Kushimitama of knowledge.
Sakimitama of love.
When you gather these
four spirits into one...
And when good and evil are
sealed amidst chaos,
then it is possible for
a Sacred Jewel to be created.
Again, I'm lost!
Stop, don't run!
It's Sango's voice.
I won't do a thing!
Stay away!
We're travelers.
We will not harm you.
What's wrong, Sango?
Stay away, demon!
Neither Shippo nor
Kirara are bad.
What's the matter?
Did something happen
in this village?
Don't be afraid.
Whatever happened,
we'll protect you.
The demons...
The demons came and...
Did demons attack
the village?
Everyone was taken away.
I was punished forbeing
naughty and
put in the chicken coop.
Come on out quietly.
Otherwise, we'll burn you alive
in yourhomes!
Wait! Please wait!
Pa! Ma!
Every single one of
you must come out.
Is anyone hiding?
Find them!
Everyone was taken away
by the demons...
When was this?
About five days ago.
I've been hiding in the coop
ever since.
So now we know why
the village is deserted.
Tell me...
What happened to them all?
Why did the demons take
Pa and Ma away?
Tell me!
Were they eaten up?
No.
If they only came to eat,
they wouldn't have taken
them all away.
Izumo!
I can't believe they've
been eaten.
Yes!
The demons aren't fools.
They know that
if they attack villages ruthlessly,
people would hire
demon slayers.
If they took them alive,
there's a reason.
Then Pa and Ma are
still alive?
We'll go find them.
And we'll slay the demons, too.
Thank you! I'm so relieved!
But...
It will be night soon.
I hope we can find
theirwhereabouts.
The night...
Hides everything in darkness.
Even the most beautiful
is covered by the
darkness.
Well, I guess you're right.
I sense the Sacred Jewel!
What a surprise!
I thought I sensed the
presence of mortals...
but to come upon
real Sacred Jewel shards...
It's them!
The demons who kidnapped
my parents and the others!
Hand overthe Sacred Jewel
shards quietly now!
You're the ones who
should be quiet!
So you're Orochidayu?
Where did you take
the villagers?!
Monk... I've heard rumors
about you.
The one with the Wind Tunnel.
Well, if you're aware of it,
it'll be quick.
Go get him!
Wind Tunnel!
Now, will you behave?!
Seems this Sacred Jewel
is a cluster of noxious vapor.
Miroku!
And it's probably toxic
to humans.
It's an evil spirit!
That Jewel will defile
the human soul!
They all possess fake
Sacred Jewels!
Why you...!
Izumo, take the boy
and hide!
I understand!
Hurry up and go!
This way...
Hiraikotsu!
You're strongerthan
the average demon.
Even though it's an imitation,
could it be the Sacred Jewel's power?
But how did they make
such a thing?
This is no time to
worry about that!
Now then, give it up.
I'll use my Wind Tunnel!
No, you can't!
But...
Inuyasha!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Where were you?!
Shaddup!
I didn't know this
would be happening!
Tsuchigumo! Ikkaku!
Don't think that swallowing a
fake Jewel will make you strong!
- Release us!
- Leggo!
- Izumo!
- Stop!
Kagome!
Wind... Scar!
He did it!
No, I didn't.
The others got away.
Sango!
Overthere!
Let's go!
Delicious-looking souls!
Don't you eat any of them,
Gamajiro.
Remove this kid's soul, too.
Pa! Ma!
You'll soon join them.
Gyu-oh...
Now then, we shall see your skill.
Are you sure it's this way, Inuyasha?
Yeah... this place reeks of demons.
What about you, Kagome?
I think it's straight ahead
in this direction.
But I can't sense that
Sacred Jewel too well.
I can feel the Sacred Jewel
coming this way!
Why you...!
They're all fake Sacred Jewels!
What?!
Come at me, you foolish half-demon!
So what if I'm...
a half-demon!
Atoxic miasma!
What is he?
Don't get too cocky!
Even the Wind Scar didn't work!
Priestess...
Priestess with the
Sacred Jewel.
What do you want?
The human soul must be polished, too.
Otherwise, it's just a mere pebble.
What does he mean?
My mothernamed me Gyu-oh.
So it's all yourdoing?
You tricked us all!
Priestess...
Your soul and the Sacred Jewel
shards will become
the basis of a real Sacred Jewel!
But they are notenough.
That is why I mustgather
a supply of souls.
I will use the power of the
Sacred Jewel
to free myself from this destiny.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Sacred Jewel Maker, Part Il"
I shall possess all things beautiful
in this world!