So... you found yourself another arm!
This replacement arm...
can act as a shield against
Tetsusaiga's barrier.
That's a dragon's claw!
It'll be far stronger than
some demon's arm.
But what does he intend to do with it?
Hah! I don't give a damn
if it's a dragon's claw!
But just one thrust seems to have
damaged it considerably!
The Tetsusaiga is quite amazing.
Even without its true bearer...
a dragon's claw is no match against it.
However...
why doesn't it reveal its "Wind Scar"...
to the one it has allowed
into its barrier?
Tetsusaiga...
cut through the empty space!
Reveal your true power!
Sesshomaru is able to
see the "Wind Scar"!
Old man... just what is
the "Wind Scar"?
Simply put, the secret to
mastering the Tetsusaiga.
Slaying a hundred demons
is impossible...
unless you can read the "Wind Scar."
Sesshomaru is able to see it.
Then please teach the secret
to Inuyasha, too!
Right now!
It's impossible to teach.
Inuyasha must discover it for himself.
If he cannot...
Inuyasha will die here.
Damn it! He's just using
brute strength!
Inuyasha!
The sword is crying!
Do you think Sesshomaru is
only aiming for the Tetsusaiga?
This is bad!
He's hacking away at the peak
of wave pattern of the sword.
Even the Tetsusaiga will snap
if it's hit repeatedly like that.
What's with him?!
Sesshomaru is fighting
the Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha!
Stop!
Don't interfere!
I will kill Sesshomaru...
with the Tetsusaiga!
He intends to break the Tetsusaiga!
As if I'd let him do that so easily!
Inuyasha has been able to
master the Tetsusaiga albeit one time.
Even if it was coincidence...
it still required the talent.
But if he can't use it right now,
he'll be killed!
Inuyasha!
Why won't you roar, Tetsusaiga?
Then you shall die
with your master.
He protected his sword!
I haven't broken in
this sword yet...
and I'm not about to let it go!
Damn! I can't see!
A miasma!
Demonic aura!
a vortex of demonic energy!
The smell of the wind scraping.
The fissure where the
flow of demonic energy collides!
No! The smell of the wind!
Is right there!
Is it over?
So that was the "Wind Scar."
You did it, Inuyasha!
That's the secret to
mastering the Tetsusaiga.
Did Sesshomaru die?
Probably...
He received a direct blow
from the Tetsusaiga.
What direct blow?
All he did was swing his
sword around...
because his eyes were hurting
from the poison.
Whaddya say, OI' Man?!
Now listen...
I will praise you for finally
seeing the "Wind Scar."
However, all it means...
is that you can do what
Sesshomaru can.
Actually, he has become
even more formidable.
What do you mean?
In that battle, Sesshomaru's life
was protected by the Tenseiga.
The Tenseiga protected him?
Didn't Sesshomaru die?
Inuyasha, I'll bet you didn't sense
your attack hit Sesshomaru...
now did you?
Is that true, Inuyasha?
Yeah...
His presence dispersed with the
light emitted by the Tetsusaiga.
I didn't blow him away.
It was more like he just
suddenly vanished...
Amidst the light and power
being released by the Tetsusaiga...
the Tenseiga protected Sesshomaru.
It acted on its own judgment.
Acted on its own?
The Tenseiga is the sword of healing,
to save life.
And Sesshomaru despised it.
However, when Sesshomaru's
life was endangered...
without regard to its owner's will...
the Tenseiga saved Sesshomaru.
That's about it?
So how will you defeat such a foe?
I have no idea.
Well, I sharpened the sword.
Now, you just have to keep training...
to be able to defeat
Sesshomaru and Tenseiga.
Inuyasha and Sesshomaru were
each given a sword by their father.
Tenseiga and Tetsusaiga.
This was their father's way of telling
the brothers not to fight each other.
Oh well... They'll learn it in good time.
Mind your own business.
I don't eat what humans eat.
I knew it!
Rin! You're the culprit!
You stole the fish from
the fish preserve!
You're an orphan...
so the village took pity on you
and raised you!
If you try this again,
we'll beat you to death!
Damn! What a creepy kid!
Won't even cry!
Can't be helped.
Her family was killed by brigands
in front of her eyes...
and now she can't speak.
No thanks.
I told you I don't need anything.
What's with
those bruises on your face?
If you don't want to talk,
that's fine.
What're you smiling about?
I only asked a question.
What? Is this old hut yours?
- Wolves!
They've caught up already!
Damn!
I searched for you... You thief!
Now hand over the Sacred
Jewel fragment you stole.
All right... I won't run.
Thanks... You're gonna lemme go?
Fool! I just forgot.
All right! Work's done.
I'll going on ahead.
You can stay in the village
and eat what you like.
What's the matter, Kagome?
You've been so quiet.
Hmm... It's very slight, but
I can sense a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Is that true, Kagome?!
In which direction?
Lord Sesshomaru!
Please answer!
Where are you?!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Is it possible that
Lord Sesshomaru...
was slain in one sweep by Inuyasha?
In one sweep?
Talk about one sweep...
At that time, Lord Sesshomaru...
without any hesitation,
he drew his sword.
In one sweep...!
He mentioned that the
Tenseiga was unable to kill, but...
could he really have been
testing his sword on me?!
Testing his sword... Not...
Testing his sword...
He was testing his sword?!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Would you have let me die that time?!
Were you testing your sword on me?!
Weren't you looking for me
out of concern?
Err... well...
Lord Sesshomaru,
I'm so glad to see you well...
Blood...and the smell of wolves.
The smell of this blood...
What is that?
Oh... She's a goner.
Must have been attacked by wolves.
She's been bitten to death.
Lord Sesshomaru, do you
know this human?
Lord Sesshomaru?
I see...
I can see them...
They are from the netherworld?
Should I try it?
The power of the Tenseiga.
T-test it?
Lord Sesshomaru,
what did you just say?
She's come back to life!
Lord Sesshomaru... did you save
that girl with the Tenseiga?
L-Lord... Sesshomaru...
Lord Sesshomaru saved a human...
I'm almost in shock...
But didn't he just say
that he was testing it?
T-then... did you really
test that sword on me?!
Lord Sesshomaru!
I am so sad!
So sad is Jaken!
Lord Sesshomaru! You are so cruel!
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru, please wait!
Hmm... Tenseiga, huh?
It made me save a human.
What is this?
Is anyone here?!
The work of a wolf pack?
These are wolf tracks.
And many of them.
Could this be from the Sacred
Jewel fragment Kagome sensed?
Probably.
Demons have to be involved in this!
There!
Man-eating wolves!
Let's have it out then!
Without the pack, they're helpless!
I'll get rid of you all!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
They're howling!
Calling their comrades!
I sense Sacred Jewel fragment
coming closer!
And very fast!
A man emerged from the wind!
You...
Why did you kill my minions?
He... has Sacred Jewel fragments...
on his right arm and both his legs.
So you're their leader!
A pack of wolves has
attacked the village!
Then a man with Sacred Jewel
fragments appears from the wind!
It seems that demons are
fighting for territorial control here.
An ominous shadow
cuts through the wind.
I sense Sacred Jewel fragments!
On his arms and legs?
No... I sense it in the sky!
The fragment is inside
the bird-like demon!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kagome Kidnapped by Koga,
the Wolf Demon!"
Don't miss it!