Kagome, this way?!
It's near! Beyond this forest!
We were in search of
Sacred Jewel fragments...
when we met up unexpectedly
with Kohaku...
who was being attacked by
Naraku's demon.
The demon was after the Sacred
Jewel fragment in Kohaku's back.
Kohaku!
Sango was overjoyed at
this reunion with Kohaku.
But Kohaku's memory had been
erased by Naraku...
and remembered nothing
about Sango.
Kohaku has come back to me.
He's escaped from Naraku's grasp...
That's what I want to believe.
About Kohaku... It's Naraku's trap!
I believe in Kohaku!
That's Naraku's aim.
What else can I do except
to trust him?!
Just then, Kagura appeared
to take back the fragment...
bringing an army
of demons with her.
If the Sacred Jewel fragment is
removed from his back, Kohaku will die!
In order to protect Kohaku...
Inuyasha and Miroku began
fighting them off...
while Kohaku and I escaped
into the forest.
I want to remember...
about her and everything else.
But...what's this feeling?
I feel scared... Something I don't
want to remember...
Something...
Kill her... Kill Kagome.
You're all out of arrows.
Kohaku!
Hiraikotsu!
Don't worry, Kohaku!
I'll never let Naraku
take you away ever again!
Kagome!
Kirara!
Inuyasha, remember.
We must distract Kagura and
her demons as much as possible.
I know that!
Kagura! You need a whole army
just to capture one kid?!
Fine with me!
They're falling for Naraku's plan.
Do your work, Kohaku.
What perfect timing!
While we're at it,
we'll slaughter you all, too.
Inuyasha... your head is mine!
Dance of Blades!
Kohaku?
What's going on?
All of a sudden, he's changed!
Kohaku, kill Kagome.
Kill her!
Kill!
Kohaku...
Kill! Kill!
Kill!
Kohaku...
Kagome! Kohaku!
Sango!
Kohaku?
So you are still...
Kagome!
I'm all right. It's not serious.
Kohaku...
Kirara, stay with Kagome.
Kagome, it must hurt.
Sango...
I'm sorry.
Sango?
Sango's not planning to... ?
There's no end to this!
Dance of Blades!
What's the matter?
Why don't you draw your sword,
Inuyasha?
Using the Tetsusaiga to kill the likes
of you is wasteful!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Are you using your claws because you
still can't control your sword?
You're so smart!
Stupid!
Sorry, Inuyasha!
So that's it?
Shut up! I'll kill you!
The Tetsusaiga!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
You're having an awkward
time of it with your sword.
Damn! It's still too heavy
to wield easily.
We must keep those demons
believing that...
Kohaku is hiding inside the hut.
Miroku!
Pay attention!
So the hut was empty?
You had us fooled all this time?
You're not going, Kagura!
We still haven't finished this fight!
Could it be... ?
Don't be tricked, Inuyasha!
Why, Miroku?
We thought Kohaku was
Kagura and the demons' aim!
Yet, none of them
are trying to go after him.
Maybe... they faked all this...
and we were the ones
who were tricked!
If Naraku's true aim
was not Kohaku...
Kagome!
She's taken Kohaku into the forest!
So Naraku is still in control of Kohaku!
You only realized it now?
It's probably too late.
Damn you!
Using Kohaku to get to Kagome!
Yeah...
Kagome, the one who uses
the bow and arrow...
She's a nuisance.
Miroku! What're you doing?
There are poison insects!
Wind Tunnel!
Miroku! Don't be so rash!
Miroku!
You're sucking in
the poison insects, too!
Inuyasha, go after Sango and Kagome.
Gotcha! Sorry, Miroku!
Don't you dare die!
- As if I'd let you get away!
- Don't move, Kagura!
If I turn, I'll suck you in, too!
Damn!
No thanks!
She escaped!
Miroku! Are you all right?
We... must... hurry after Inuyasha...
Yes.
Damn kid! Looking like
he wouldn't even hurt a fly!
Kagome!
Kohaku!
So, after all...
you haven't escaped
from Naraku's grasp.
You came to hurt Kagome...
to steal the Sacred Jewel fragments.
Rather than let Naraku continue
his control over you...
I'd rather...!
Kohaku, I will free you!
Kohaku! I won't let you go alone.
I will follow immediately.
So...
Kagome!
Inuyasha! Go after Sango!
She seemed strange...
Kagome!
You've been hurt by Kohaku.
It's just a scratch.
And that boy, if he really wanted to,
had a chance to kill me.
But he didn't.
Sango doesn't know that.
She may intend to kill Kohaku.
All right, I understand.
Kohaku didn't finish off Kagome.
Does that mean he disobeyed
Naraku's orders?
If so...
even if he is being mind-controlled,
Kohaku still has a human heart!
Kohaku!
Uh...
It's...
This is embarrassing...
What're you so shy for?
We're siblings.
Kohaku, you won't go
anywhere anymore.
Because you're my brother...
because you're my
one and only brother...
I'll kill you, then kill myself.
This is the only way to get
you back from Naraku!
Forgive me, Kohaku!
I'll kill you, then kill myself.
This is the only way to get
you back from Naraku!
Forgive me, Kohaku!
Stop, Sango!
l-Inuyasha...
Don't stop me, Inuyasha!
Stupid fool! Killing Kohaku
will only please Naraku!
Kohaku! Why don't you...
snap out of it, too!
Kagura!
As ordered,
Kohaku will kill Kagome.
Kohaku is unable to defy Naraku.
What?!
Inuyasha...
why do you think Kohaku
has lost his memory?
Because Naraku
is controlling his mind!
That's part of it.
But Kohaku himself
is resisting remembering...
such terrible memories.
Stop! Don't say anything
more in front of Kohaku!
Why you... Kagura!
Kohaku didn't want to remember...
so Naraku granted his wish
and erased his mind.
Now, it's so easy to manipulate
someone with no memory.
Kohaku! Remember!
Remember it all!
About Sango and the slayers!
Inuyasha!
Remembering each and every detail!
If you want to live!
Stop!
If he doesn't remember it all...
he'll continue to be under
Naraku's control...
and Naraku will take the Sacred Jewel
in his back and kill him!
You say awful things, Inuyasha.
Wait, Kagura!
If he really remembers
everything he did...
this kid will truly be destroyed.
It's kindness to let him die
without remembering a thing.
Kohaku...
Damn...
Not again?!
Sango...
It's the same thing all over again.
Damn, what troublesome siblings!
Inuyasha!
Hey, Sango!
Let me tell you this,
so you don't jump the gun next time!
Naraku ordered Kohaku
to kill Kagome!
But Kohaku didn't kill her!
That's because he still
has a human heart.
That's why we cannot kill Kohaku.
Get him alive!
Got that?!
Yeah.
Kohaku...
I spared your life
and made you forget everything.
Yet you failed to kill Kagome.
Why is that, Kohaku?
Do you want to
regain your humanity?
Then do you want to remember?
Remember it all?
No! No!!
Good.
I'll let you live for now.
Forget it all.
Yes.
But...I can't forget
that woman's face.
A village is attacked by bandits.
Gatenmaru, the vicious leader, is
actually a moth demon in disguise.
Inuyasha and Miroku are
trapped in a poison cell!
Meanwhile, Sesshomaru searches for
clues to how Inuyasha transforms...
and learns frightening secrets from
a tree demon.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Inuyasha's Soul, Devoured"
Don't miss it!