Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku with my Tetsusaiga!
Miroku and Sango reach the depths
of the sacred grounds of Mt. Hakurei.
What awaits them is
an enormous demonic aura.
Hurry Inuyasha!
They're both in danger!
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Do it now, Wolf!
- He did it!
- He's up again, mutt!
Take this.!
Inuyasha!
I'm so glad!
You're not hurt, are you?
You're okay?
Kagome...
This leads to the depths.
Let's go, Sango. No doubt about it,
Naraku is deep inside!
Is Naraku in the depths of the
sacred mountain beyond this barrier?
As everyone gathers at Mt. Hakurei,
something is about to happen!
The aura is getting even
stronger...
As I had surmised, the barrier
around this sacred mountain
has been hiding the source of
this evil in its depths...
Cloisters....?
The demonic aura is really
thick in here...
Naraku's demons!
I guess he doesn't intend
to hide it any longer!
Those are!
Naraku's poison insects!!
Miroku! You mustn't use
the Wind Tunnel!
If you suck them in,
the poison will get you!
Hiraikotsu!!
Take that!
Well. I never would
have thought...
Two humans made it this far
inside all by themselves?
But then, that Inuyasha
can't come in, can he?
Kagura!
I'll grant that
you've got guts...
But don't think you'll make
it out of here alive!
I guess this means that they
don't want us to go any further!
Yeah! And it means we must
be closing in on Naraku!
Sango! This way!
Fools!
Sango!!
Miroku! You go on without me!
No way!
Don't worry!
Finding where Naraku is hiding
is our first priority, isn't it?
Kagura!
Hiraikotsu!
Are you aiming for me?
I am the wind, remember?!
Kohaku!
Pay attention, fool!!
Sango!
Sango!!
Come on! Wake up, Sango!
How touching, Monk.
If you'd gone on ahead
without her,
you might have lived
a little longer...
You can't use the Wind Tunnel for
fear of the insects' poison!
Who do you think I am?!
If it means that the girl I care
dearly for can live on instead....
Then I don't need this life!
Wind Tunnel!
What...?!
He really did open
up the Wind Tunnel!
The insect poison
is spreading through my body...
Miroku and Sango are late...
They've been gone too long.
I hope they haven't had trouble.
Kagome, you wait here.
What?
I'm going to pop over and see
what's up at the mountain.
What are you saying? You can't
go into the sacred mountain!
I'm only a half-demon! I wouldn't let
sacred lands purify me!
That's crazy, Inuyasha!
You don't know what will happen
if you enter there!
Never mind! You just wait here.
This is no time to be
arguing about it.
Hey, Wolf! You're there,
aren't you?
Uh-oh...
He's on to us...
Whaddya want, mutt?
You stay here and
keep Kagome safe.
What's going on?
Miroku and Sango went into
Mt. Hakurei and haven't come out.
The only answer is for me to go.
The sacred grounds won't be as
bad for me as for a real demon....
Fine with me. Good riddance!
Don't put your arm around her!
And don't talk to her!
Remember, if anything happens
to Kagome, I'll kill you!
Got that?!
Inuyasha!
Is he gonna be all right?
Even a half-demon will find
it hard in the sacred grounds.
Inuyasha....
Please! Don't push too far!
This is... worse than I thought...
If you want to throw your life away,
then come on!
You'll fall prey to my Wind Tunnel!
I guess even demons value
their own lives...
Is the monk totally unaffected?
He must've gotten a huge dose
of the Saimyosho's poison...
Wind Tunnel!!
That monk must be really desperate.
Since I don't want to be sucked up,
I can't chase him any more...
And besides...
Sorry to tell you, monk, but
that's not where Naraku is...
Please... Don't approach me again...
If I open the Wind Tunnel one
more time, then I'll be...
Sango... forgive me...
Ka-chew! Man, is it cold!
I've gotta find some clothes!
And I found 'em!
- Who goes there?!
- Get out of our way!
And what'll you do if I don't?
All right, now...
I guess this'll do...
Jakotsu!
Hey! I've been looking for you!
I heard from the bugs that
Suikotsu bit it, huh?
Yeah, it was pretty sad.
Oh, right! Big Brother Bankotsu...
This is a memento from Suikotsu.
A shard of the Sacred Jewel.
Here.
Jakotsu? You're giving it to me?
Sure. You're the one who said to
hand it over if we got one.
Jakotsu! You're...
You're such a pal!
Huh?
You're the only one in the
whole world I can trust!
Even if you are a bit weird.
Is that so?
See...? I knew it!!
I'm not being purified!
I'm gonna make it!
Damn it! Now I can't move...
Does that mean if I go any
farther, it's dangerous...?
What should I do...?
Well, well. Inuyasha.
You can't go any farther?
You're looking a bit weak....
Renkotsu!
So unlike you... not to notice
that I was following you...
You again?! The Band of Seven must
be really short-handed.
Your mouth is as sharp as ever.
Tell me, Inuyasha...
You're in a hurry, aren't you?
But if you go any farther,
even a half-demon like you
will be purified. Is that it?
Then go!!
Oh no!!!
And....does that finish it?
What?!
Y- you see...? I'm still...
My demonic powers are gone! And
it's not even the night of the new moon!
Damn it! It's this
barrier's fault!
Well, well. What a surprise.
I thought the sacred grounds
would purify and vaporize you.
But it's only your powers
that have disappeared.
How convenient that you're
only a half-demon.
Thanks to that I'm
much lighter now!
You're never at a loss
for words, are you?
But now you're just
a human brat!
Damn you!
I'm not letting you escape!
I don't have time to waste
with that Renkotsu...
I'm going to keep on running all
the way into the mountain!
Miro...
That's right! I was hit
by the Hiraikotsu...
Miroku?
He opened the Wind Tunnel and sucked
in the insects'poison?!
Miroku! Wake up! Please!
Oh, what am I gonna do...?
This is my fault!
Miroku? Miroku!
Please! Open your eyes....!
Miroku....
Miroku!
Sango....? Good.
You're conscious again....
Sango, go on without me.
No! Only if you're with me!
I think....I might have
pushed myself too far.
So you have to be
the one who survives.
No!
If it means leaving
you behind....
Then we'll die together!
Sango....
What's happening to me...?
My body is feeling
better and better...
Miroku?
Those demons... Why aren't
they attacking?
Now that you mention it...
They were purified!
They can't come any closer.
Right... This is still
sacred ground.
It's even powerful enough to
purified the poison in my body...
Let's go, Sango.
There's something up ahead.
Miroku, are you sure
you're all right?
Yes. I guess we won't have to
die together, after all.
Huh?!
Oh, geez! What did I say?
What did I say?!
She can't remember?
How long do you think
you can get away from me?
Take that!
It's a dead end.
I guess this is
as far as you go....
Why you....!
This is...?
Die!!
Is it over?
There's no body....
So, he slipped through
this crack.
Renkotsu!
Jakotsu?
Whatever are you doing
in such a place?
So, we're all that's left
of the Band of Seven?
Yeah, and it's a problem.
What is?
Band of Seven means seven,
not three people!
We have to think up a new name.
Oh, by the way, what happened
to Suikotsu's jewel shard?
I gave it to Bankotsu.
Yeah?
He has no avarice...
But anyway, this is bad news.
Bankotsu is collecting
all the shards...
Eventually he'll get
Jakotsu's shard, too.
I can't let that happen.
Jakotsu, something really
interesting has happened....
Huh? Interesting?
Miroku!
Yes! Let's go!
This hole is really deep...
I wonder if it goes
all the way down...?
Well, just as Renkotsu said!
So, you're Inuyasha? You're
pretty cute even as a human.
Jakotsu!
My, my. This makes
me so happy!
I've been waiting for the time
when I could fight you again!
Let's do it....
This mummy is St. Hakushin?
Saint Hakushin, in life you
were a man of high morals
and saved many people!
So how is it that you are
working to help Naraku?!
I was enshrined and became
a living Buddha,
but my soul was left in the darkness
and hence, could not be saved.
That man's voice called to me.
I will not judge you, still....
Next on Inuyasha:
"Divine Malice of The Saint"
I cannot ignore the barrier which
protects Naraku!