Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
Kagome has fallen into
the hands of Hoshiyomi
who is after the
Naginata of Kenkon.
Just you wait, Kagome!
Tetsusaiga has lost its power,
but I'll rescue you without fail!
So you're Hoshiyomi, huh?
Move outta my way!
Too easy!
Huh?!
Demon Ninja technique....
Shadow Incarnation.
Kagome....
Could the "Kagome" that was
written on that scroll be...
Go!
Hojo! Take the Ken blade
and run to Furai Shrine!
Huh?
I cannot leave you by yourself!
Kagome!
Haven't you figured it out yet?
All the power you throw at me
is being absorbed by the blade.
What?!
What is that?
This aura is from
Hoshiyomi's Kon blade!
You're okay!
Where's Kagome?!
Kagome was....!
What about Kagome?!
Kagome!
What will you do now?
Do you want to protect the Ken blade
even if it means this woman's life?
Kagome!
Why, you!
Inuyasha, are you all right?
What can you kill with
a rusty sword like that?
My Tetsusaiga....
If you want to get her back,
come to Furai Shrine.
What?!
And don't forget the
Ken blade.
Kagome!
Dammit! Wait!
Inuyasha!
I will go with you!
You'll only be in the way!
Please take me with you!
Hold on, you two!
According to Lady Kaede,
the Furai Shrine is the place to
purify the Kenkon blades.
So why did he choose that shrine
for the exchange?
Get to the point!
It must be some kind of trap.
This is not the time
to be thinking about that.
Kagome is in danger because
I involved her in my problems!
Damn right! I'm going!
Please wait!
Let us go, too!
Right! Kirara!
Let's go!
We will now proceed
with the ritual
for the resurrection of
the Naginata of Kenkon.
Do not allow them
to get near this shrine.
Yes, sire!
Leave that half-demon to me.
With that rusty sword,
he'll be no match for me.
Then I'll take the monk.
I'll tear apart the woman.
That leaves the young
samurai for me.
Over there!
What is that light?!
A barrier?!
You won't get past us.
You smell quite tasty.
I am Seiryu of the Moon.
Let's get to know each other.
Sango!
Where are you?!
I'm your opponent!
Hey Shippo! Snap out of it!
Wake up!
Oh, I guess I have no choice!
Have you come to?
We've all become separated.
Hurry to Inuyasha!
Gotcha!
Oww!
Akitoki, are you all right?
I think I bruised my hip.
Shape up!
Oh my, such nice buns!
Hey, cute samurai!
I'm Suzaku of the Flower.
Nice to meet you.
Huh?!
You're really unlucky to have
to face me, Genbu of the Darkness.
Get outta my way.
And what can you do
with a useless blade like that?
Are you deaf?
I said to get outta my way!
Huh? Did a mosquito sting me?
It's not working, is it?
Hah! I don't even need Tetsusaiga
to fight you!
Take this!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
I keep telling you
it's useless.
His body's so tough!
Is that it?
Well then....
My turn!
Demon Ninja technique!
Spinning Demon Shell!
Hah! You can't get away!
I haven't hunted a
female prey in a long time.
I'm going to enjoy this.
You're disgusting!
Hiraikotsu!
Whoa!
W-Where'd he go?!
Demon Ninja technique,
Dance of Scales!
What is that?!
Demon ninja technique,
Scale Storm!
Sango!
I'm coming!
That's only if you can
beat me, Byakko of the Snow!
I'll use my Wind Tunnel!
As if I'd let you, Monk!
What's the matter, Monk?
Is it over already?
Let go!
I won't let you have
the Ken blade!
Stingy!
If you give me the blade of Ken,
I'll use the skin off of your cute
face to decorate it.
I don't want you to do that!
Can't you be more agreeable?
Well then, every morning,
I'll kiss a wall hanging
made from the skin of your face.
How's that?
Stop it! You're disgusting me!
Oh, I can't watch this!
It's the end of the world!
I gotta....I gotta keep it together!
Fox Fire!
Hot! Hot!
There!
I'm saved!
This is hot!
What are you trying to do?!
Damn kid!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
So you're awake.
This man's eyes...
They're so sad.
Why? Why is it?
Huh?
Why is a human like you
traveling with that half-demon?
What are you to that half-demon?
Why do you ask?
It's none of your business.
Humans and demons have
no love for each other.
There could never be a
bond between humans and demons.
That is because humans always
end up betraying demons.
And someday, you too, will betray
that half-demon.
That won't happen!
Humans are weak creatures.
They are weak in body and soul.
Even though they are weak,
they try to live proudly.
That's why humans betray....
in order to protect themselves.
You misjudge humans.
Did something happen between
you and humans?
That's it, isn't it?
That's why you say such things.
A female samurai?
Who is that in the painting?
Tsukiyomi....
What are you doing here?
Hoshiyomi....
Forgive me!
Rin! Pyo! To! Sha! Kai! Chin!
- Retsu! Zai!
- Tsukiyomi!
Zen!
W-Why?!
Why are you doing this?
Tsukiyomi!
Why? Why?!
I was sealed in here by Tsukiyomi.
Of the Naginata of Kenkon....
The Ken blade was taken to
Mt. Fuji to the Hojo family.
And the Kon blade was
taken to Mt. Hakurei.
When Mt. Hakurei collapsed,
I took back this blade of Kon.
And that's why Old Kaede said
that the Naginata of Kenkon could be
purified at Furai Shrine.
Tsukiyomi betrayed me.
She promised to live
with me, yet she betrayed me.
No.... Tsukiyomi must have
had a reason.
Humans are weak.
They are weak, yet they try to live.
So they struggle and betray.
My desire is to save humans
from that struggle.
Save humans? How?
I will resurrect
the Naginata of Kenkon
which was created
from the corpses of 222 demons,
and kill all humans.
You think that is
saving humans?!
Humans have an existence
that is beyond saving.
So death is the only way
to save humans.
You're wrong!
Just as I thought.
When I first saw you,
I felt a spiritual power whose scope was
similar to that of Tsukiyomi's.
So why did I not take the
Ken blade back then,
but brought you here instead?
I am going to use your power in
the ritual to resurrect the Naginata of Kenkon.
What?!
My strength....
Do you yearn for it so much?
Rest assured. The other blade
shall soon be in my possession.
W-What is this?!
W-What....!
Whaa-!
What's happening?!
Akitoki is going up
the waterfall!
Demon Ninja technique,
Shell Crusher!
You won't get away now....
you half-demon!
Do not worry.
I shall take good care
of your body.
Mi....roku....
Sango!
Concerned about that girl, too?
Well, don't worry.
You'll soon meet in
the netherworld.
Why, you! Take this!
Tiger Fang Attack!
Monk, I don't know what
you're trying to do,
but you can't move an inch.
Shippo! What'll happen
if you don't keep it together?!
You're right!
Unless I keep it together,
it'll all be over!
Akitoki! You just hang in
there for just a bit!
Shippo!
Now, grab on!
Hurry!
You're not getting away,
my cute samurai!
Stop! Owwee!
Stop! Stop!
I'll crush you!
Miroku...
Damn you!
Why, you!
Blades of Blood!
Wind Tunnel!
W-Wha...!
Sango! Grab onto something!
Miroku!
Wind Tunnel!
What the.!
What's happening?!
T-This is bad....!
N-No! Don't...!
Sango!
Are you all right?
Uh-huh.... Thank you.
Miroku!
Are you all right?
Pretty much.
But we'd better hurry....
to Kagome!
You're all right, Akitoki!
I'm sorry.
The Ken blade entered that building....
What's this....?
I got a bad feeling....
Huh?
Kagome!
It has been restored!
My Naginata of Kenkon!
W-What?!
I shall tell you....
Kenkon signifies the yin and yang.
Heaven and Earth!
It represents the two opposing forces
of the entire universe.
What if I were to use the power
of the Naginata of Kenkon
to cut the invisible wall which
separates the two?
I don't need a lecture!
Just hurry it up and
give Kagome back!
Humans are weak.
Humans betray.
Thus, all humans must perish
from this world.
What is that?!
We're being sucked in!
Inuyasha!
Akitoki!
I can't use the Wind Tunnel
if he has Kagome!
Kagome!
Inuyasha! Doesn't Tetsusaiga
have its power back?
Dammit, it's no good!
Kagome....
It's....It's all my fault!
I got Kagome involved
in all this!
And I let her fall
into his hands!
This is no time
for whining!
We must do everything possible
to save Kagome from that monster!
But how?!
And Tetsusaiga is still....
All you hafta do is put some spirit into it!
And anything is possible!
I will never forgive humans!
Why did Tsukiyomi seal me away?!
I wanted you to remember!
Tsukiyomi!
I wanted you to remember
the kindness you showed
during the days we spent together.
The power of loving someone....
Isn't that capable of winning over
the sadness that is enveloped
in those terrible blades?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Eternal Love: The Naginata of Kenkon"
There has to be a dream
that never fades
even if it never comes true.