Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
An incarnation of Naraku which had
been split into two was still alive.
And the legendary demon horse, Entei,
released from its seal
now presents himself
to his chosen rider!
I'm going to look into your soul.
Is that?
Entei...
Hiraikotsu!
That's enough outta you!
What the hell do I do
with this one?
It's not even breathing.
It moved....!
Hey. Did you come back
from the dead?
He's alive....
He's...!
Huh?
You're....!
It's so fast!
We can't catch up!
Dammit!
It's useless! It's getting away!
Huh? It's descending!
Entei's master must be there.
You mean the man-eating demon that's
sealed up there?
Well, I'll destroy 'em both,
Entei and him!
So the priest is dead?
Coming to greet your master....
Now that's a nice thing
to do.
Shall we raise hell like
old times?
I won't let you!
You're Rengokuki?
Who the hell are you?
None of your business!
Just get back in your grave!
Just who do you think I am?
I am the great Rengokuki....
The only one Entei allows
astride his back.
You've got guts if
you wanna fight me.
Why you...!
Take this! And this! And this!
Damn bastard!
And this!
Hah! What's the matter?
You almost had him!
It'll take some doing to
get that demon horse, Entei.
A human attack will have
no effect on me!
I am destined to conquer the world!
Shaddup!
Huh?
Wind Scar!
He countered it again!
The problem is that speed!
Damn!
One more time!
Run, Entei!
Stop!
It's hunger! I'm hungry,
that's why I don't have strength.
I'd never lose to a guy like that
otherwise.
Why that...!
Dammit!
Inuyasha!
Where are Rengokuki and Entei?
I was too late. They got away.
We must find them.
Otherwise, there will surely
be casualties.
Rengokuki is a man-eating demon.
We have to do something fast!
At any rate, let's follow in the
direction they flew.
I can track them by their scent
if we get near.
- Get on.
- 'Kay!
Let's go!
"Bring me new apparel"?!
The second he wakes up,
that kid starts ordering me around!
Huh?
What could have happened here?
Huh? Who are you?
What kind of demon are you?
Mind your own business.
Let me tell you this....
The humans who were here
are all mine.
Whatever.
Wait!
What?
Be my wife.
Huh?
In time, I'm going to rule the world.
And you'll be my wife.
It's not a bad deal.
You don't look like you can
conquer the world.
W-What?!
So long!
That's what you think!
Entei! I'll give her a taste
of my power!
What a pest!
Dance of Blades!
That horse....
Hold it!
He's really irritating me!
Come down.
I'll take you on.
If you apologize and ask me
to take you for a wife,
I'll forgive you.
Hah! You'll regret picking
a fight with me.
Bitch!
I'll show you my power
which even Entei acknowledges.
And I told you that
you don't look strong at all.
- Kagura...
- Huh?
I'll handle him.
Who the hell are you?!
Huh?
Is that it?
You cocky kid!
What's wrong, Entei?
Hey, Entei!
Oh....
What's the matter, Entei!
I'm your master!
Have you forgotten?!
I think he has.
Shut up!
He decides who is the most fitting
to ride on his back!
And it is my power he chose!
I'm the victor!
Behold! I am the rider
of Entei!
Let us go, Entei!
Entei!
What do you see in
a kid like this?
Watch me!
That kid....
Where'd he go?!
Here.
Why you...!
Am I going to be killed....
by a mere kid?!
Not bad.
Isn't it too big for you?
Save your wisecracks.
I want to get used to
this body quickly.
This kid... Unlike Naraku,
he doesn't mind getting his hands dirty.
Now then....
All the people who lived
here were killed.
Did Rengokuki do this?
Huh?
Here! Over here!
Hoof marks.
It's huge.
Let's find them as soon as possible.
Entei's prints go in that direction,
but stop right here.
He must've flown
from here.
Does that mean he flew
in that direction?
What's this?
What's the matter?
This scent!
Huh? Be careful, everyone.
An aura....
A demonic aura is
coming near!
Is that Entei?
You're brave, coming
to me like this.
Wind Scar!
It's going to hit this time!
A barrier?!
That's some greeting
Inuyasha.
Who is that?
It's not Rengokuki.
I killed Rengokuki.
Who is he?!
It seems Entei here has
chosen me...
after witnessing my strength.
A kid?
A mere child!
Or maybe, it was for
freeing him from the seal.
Are you the one
who released that demon horse?!
The ones who broke the seal
were Kagura and that baby.
The baby was split in two
by the priest's spiritual power.
Ha! As if I'd die from the
spiritual powers of a mere priest!
Does that mean you're that baby?!
I am Hakudoshi.
As you've guessed,
I am one of Naraku's
incarnations.
Hakudoshi?!
So you're Naraku's....
Hakudoshi!
I have heard that you have
killed monks and priests
in search of the border between
this world and the next.
What is to be found there?
Would you like to search
for it, too?
The Sacred Jewel shard?
Sacred Jewel shard?!
Hey, is it wise to
talk about that?
There's no need to hide it.
There isn't?
The more, the merrier.
Be grateful that I've
given you that lead.
He seems to be telling
the truth about the shard.
Hah! I don't give a damn about
the next world or whatever,
but if there's a shard to be
found there,
you can go there yourself!
Dammit!
He got away...
I won't let 'em get away!
I'll find them, no matter what!
What'll you do now?
Kill another priest?
Not anymore.
Humans aren't strong enough.
What I saw inside the priest's soul
before he split me in two...
was that the border between
this world and the next?
What I saw was a world of white mist.
I want to know more about
what I saw.
Which means...
Demon.
What?
Find a demon who
seems strong.
Demon?
I see... Nothing in this area either?
Yes. As you can see, it's
very peaceful here.
No demon horse... and no child
riding it?
I've not seen anything like that.
I'm sorry I'm not much help.
Oh no, thank you.
Since that day, we've had
no clues at all.
But it's odd.
Ever since we saw Hakudoshi,
there've been no stories about
attacks on shrines and temples.
Yes, but now, I keep sensing
a strange demonic aura.
And more than one.
Strange demonic aura?
By themselves, they're not much.
But their movements are wild.
They're not headed someplace?
No... It's like they're wandering.
Smells yummy!
Are you all right, Shippo?
l-I'm fine.
Miroku and Sango should be
returning soon.
Yes.
But what a shock that Naraku's
incarnation would reveal
the location of
the last Sacred Jewel shard.
Yes.
The others are held by Koga
and Kohaku.
The rest are all in
Naraku's possession.
We can't let Naraku have
any more of the shards!
That Inuyasha...
Huh?
Where'd he go?
He probably couldn't sit still.
Dammit! I can't pick up
any scent of Hakudoshi!
And I don't get this thing
about the border
between this world and the next.
Isn't there some kind of clue?
Anything at all?
What is it?
Looks delicious!
Huh?
Inuyasha?
W-What is that?!
Run, Kagome!
Kagome!
Inuyasha!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Kagome, are you all right?!
Where WERE you, you idiot!
Do you know what would have
happened to Kagome if I weren't here?!
I know.
Sorry, Kagome.
It's all right, but...
Just what is this demon?
Kagome!
Sango, Miroku!
Did you do this, Inuyasha?
Yeah.
You sure got carried away.
Whaddya mean by
carried away?
You chopped off his head...
No, this demon was
headless from the start.
From the start?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yeah, that's why it was
so scary.
Could it have something to do
with the wandering demonic aura?
Yes, this was probably
one of them.
This one looks like it was
killed with a blade.
You mean, it was beheaded?
Yeah, but demons are resilient.
That's why the body was
moving by itself.
Then the other demonic auras...
But why?
Just look at this cut.
Whoever did it was
a terrible swordsman.
Is it really that bad?
Yeah.
Huh?
What're you doing, kid?
Do you realize that
this is my territory?
Why you.!
This brat... just what is he thinking?
Let's go.
My name is Kanta.
As you can see, I'm...
A raccoon dog?
An otter.
Kanta's father has been slain
by Hakudoshi.
If we can find his body,
we may be able to save him!
But once a body is destroyed,
it cannot be restored.
Hurry Inuyasha!
We may make it in time!
I know, but there's a troublesome guy
near Kanta's old man.
Next on Inuyasha:
"3000 Leagues in Search of Father"
Is Tenseiga telling me
to save it?