It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
for our dreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
It's a secret from Inuyasha.
I'm back in the modern era and
I'll be able to relax for a change.
At least, that's what I thought...
My classmates Eri, Yuka and
Ayumi start pestering me about
meeting Inuyasha and
create a fine mess!
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Well, I'm off.
Okay. Take your time over there.
We'll be doing some
recuperating, too.
Those rats chewed them up
pretty bad.
Use the medicine.
I'll bring more.
Okay.
Kagome....
Huh?
Never mind. We'll be seeing you.
'Bye!
She's gone.
I see....
Sister Kikyo, huh?
So my sister is still
in this world....
You don't seem very surprised, Kaede.
No....
A little while ago, two girls
who seemed like shikigami appeared
and took dirt from my sister's shrine.
That dirt was probably used to
heal wounds
which were inflicted on her
by Naraku.
I don't know how you feel about it,
but I'm glad that Kikyo
was saved.
Also....
the one who saved Kikyo from being
eaten away by Naraku's miasma
was Kagome.
I see.... Kagome?
It's been so long!
This feels so good....
Buyo, you're heavy.
I wonder how Inuyasha
is doing....
Kikyo....
I came back without telling him.
I hope it's okay.
Kikyo seemed to have regained
her spiritual powers and looked well....
but she disappeared again.
Maybe Inuyasha really wanted
to go after her.
Even on the way back to
Old Kaede's village,
it felt awkward speaking to him.
I guess I'm second fiddle to her.
Why? Why'd you let Kagome
go back?
We don't have to ask you permission
for everything, do we?
- Inuyasha....
- Huh?
Weren't you telling Kaede
about Kikyo?
So what of it?
She couldn't interrupt you.
Kagome was being considerate
of you.
I wasn't....
I wasn't telling her anything
that I didn't want overheard!
And you blame me?!
Oh....! Be quiet!
Sit!
Good try....
But I guess it only works
when Kagome says it.
Hah! Of course, stupid!
For a second, I thought
it would work.
Geez! At this rate,
he'll never repent.
W-What's this?
A hand-me-down from
our neighbor.
You said your bike was
lost over there, didn't you?
It's a bit rusted, though.
No, I'm really grateful.
Thank you, Mom!
Sis, aren't you going to school?
You'll be late!
Just a bit longer.
It's gonna get dirty as soon
as you take it back there.
Never mind.
It's not bad when Inuyasha
carries me on his back,
but I can really use this.
There! Perfect!
It's sparkling!
Hey! Kagome!
Huh?
Huh....?
Oww!
Inu....yasha....
Did you come to play again?
I don't have time for that.
Hey Kagome, why'd you leave
without asking for...
What do you think you're doing?!
You broke it, stupid!
W-What're you talking about?
Geez!
See!
It's bent!
Sis, you polished it until
it was so shiny, too.
Just do this and it'll go back....
Huh?
Hey....!
l-I just have to fix it, right?
Do not touch it!
But....
It's okay....
But you're upset!
It's not okay!
Sit!
- Good morning!
Geez, what's he doing here?!
And he seems upset
about something.
No joke!
Yup.
Oh, Kagome!
Yuka! Eri!
It's been a long time!
Huh? What's with the long face?
What? Did something happen
with that boyfriend of yours?
How come they're always
so sharp?
Huh?
Are you serious?
That's tough.
So your delinquent boyfriend
is two-timing you again?
Well, sort of....
There are circumstances
that can't be helped.
So he's cheating on you
because he can't choose
between you and the other woman?
Huh?
Choose me or the other woman?
I know that Inuyasha
has feelings for Kikyo.
But...
I was the one who decided
to stay by him.
I thought it was okay
because I like Inuyasha.
It's okay if he can't make
up his mind,
but it's the pits if he's decided
who's first and who's second.
Huh? First and second?
You mean who he likes better?
I see....
His first love or Kagome.
Who does he like more?
Well, who is it?
First or second....
Well, I guess I'm probably
second....
You know, Kagome....
being second isn't
necessarily a bad thing.
Second stock is good
for miso soup
as well as for stewed dishes.
But fine restaurants always use
first stock.
Y-Yes....
But remember....
in baseball, the catcher is number two.
He's the control tower
calling the pitches.
And there's the second actor
in kabuki and he's always handsome!
You're right.
But....
Look....
Maybe you'd be better off
not seeing him, Kagome.
Huh?
That's one way to deal with it.
But I can't help it,
if he follows me home.
Even today, from so early
in the morning....
Huh?!
He's at your house?
Umm....
I want to see!
I want to see him!
Kagome's delinquent boyfriend!
Here. Help yourself.
Can it be fixed?
I think so.
I heard that she got this from
somewhere
to replace the one that
got broken over there.
Yes, our neighbor
gave it to her.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
For breaking it.
But you're going to fix it, right?
Y-Yeah....
Do your best.
Awright!
Somethin' like this....
you just....
Huh?!
It collapsed!
Dammit! Why doesn't it work?!
What the...!
Leggo of me!
Leggo, I said!
Won't listen, huh?
Fine!
Take this!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
No way can one or two rings....
defeat me!
I wonder what kind of boy he is...
this selfish, two-timing ruffian boyfriend.
I can't wait!
I didn't think they'd really
come along.
Just awhile earlier, they were
telling me not to see him!
L-Look, we're all busy with exams.
This is no time for....
It's okay.
This is more important.
Huh?
Besides, we have to scold him
for hurting you.
Please don't! If you do that,
he'll have a fit!
Have a fit?
He's sounding more and
more unlikable!
We'd better put him
in his place!
This is bad!
I can't let them meet Inuyasha!
He's a half-demon and
I can't let his identity
be revealed.
This is all Inuyasha's fault!
Coming around uninvited!
Kagome seems troubled again.
Maybe you said too much, Eri.
Huh? It's my fault?!
Maybe we shouldn't.
You're right.
No matter what kind of person he is,
Kagome likes him.
And to root her on....
is what friends would do.
Right!
Huh?
Don't worry.
We're on your side, Kagome!
Huh?
No matter how violent
he is....
No matter how two-timing
U-Umm....
I'm home!
Oh, Inuyasha!
Whaa...! What is this?!
An iron cart....
But....
It looks worse than
it did this morni-!
What'll I do?!
If I don't fix it,
Kagome will....
Why don't you just
pay her back?
Here....
Isn't this the Adamantite stone
that you mentioned?
Yeah, that's it!
This is called a diamond.
With one of these, you can
buy lots and lots of bicycles.
Then leave it to me!
I'll make oodles of 'em
with my Tetsusaiga!
Really?
You can?
Just watch me!
Adamant Barrage!
Strange....
Adamantite spears are
supposed to come out.
Inuyasha, don't break anything more
than you already have!
Geez! What a bother!
Then how's this?!
Huh?
Stop! That's dangerous!
Lemme at it until
they come out!
No way!
Grandpa....
Huh?
Inuyasha wants to work
part-time.
He'll work really hard for
breaking the bicycle.
Hah! I'm really expensive!
Oh boy, I'm home already.
What am I going to do?!
It's even more trouble to
explain to Inuyasha
that he's not to come out.
Kagome's back has "anguish"
written all over it.
When we meet her delinquent boyfriend,
let's be nice to him.
Even if he has a gangster haircut?
And even if his pants are purple
or pink!
Yes!
Huh?!
W-What's that?!
An avant-garde sculpture?
Inuyasha!
Inu?
- Is that her boyfriend's name?
- Hey, I know you're here!
- Maybe that's his gang name.
- Come out!
- He's a delinquent, right?
- Inuyasha!
Awright! This one goes here.
And, next is this one!
Part-timer, that box goes
over there.
Right!
Inuyasha!
Oh, I think Kagome is calling you.
You probably imagined it.
Really?
Oh, bring that jar
over here.
Huh? This one?
Don't you dare break it!
That jar has a storied history.
Be very careful....
Sit!
Aghh! The jar!
Wasn't me!
Huh?
He's in the shed.
What's wrong?
Kagome!
Grandpa, where's Inuyasha?
He....ran away.
Geez!
He breaks everything!
Umm....
l-I think he already left.
Huh? Boring!
We were looking forward
to it!
But he comes around
quite often, right?
W-Well, not really.
Oh well, I think
it worked out.
After all, he's so weird.
Kagome, come and
get the tea.
All right.
Make yourself comfortable.
Too bad.
I wanted to see him.
I'll say!
We came all the way here.
Hey Kagome.
You've been upset
since this morn-
You wouldn't happen to be....?
Say....
Could he....
You guys....
The Pekopon who ran amok
at the school play!
Huh?! The one who had a run-in
with Hojo during the cultural festival?
That was Kagome's boyfriend?!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Did Kagome ask you
to do that back then?
Err....yeah.
Why?!
Why is Inuyasha...?
They're going to find out
that he's a half-demon!
When did you start seeing Kagome?
It's been a while.
That kimono.... Do you work
at the shrine?
Your eyes are an unusual color.
Do you bleach your hair?
I was born with it.
It's such an unusual color.
Think so?
Can I touch it?
Yeah, but you're weird.
- They're carrying on a conversation.
- It's so soft!
Say, is he half?
Hafu?
Well, Kagome?
Umm....well....
I guess.
He's a half-demon, after all.
Oh....he's so cool!
So divine!
I'm jealous, Kagome!
So cool!
Huh?
- You lived overseas?
- When'd you come here?
Thank you very much!
I'll be seeing you.
'Bye!
Kagome, he's not as bad
as you made him out to be.
Yeah, I thought he'd look and dress
like a street gang member.
Umm....well....
He is a bit different, though.
He's not at all like I had imagined.
See you!
You two get along!
Now the problem is Hojo.
Yeah, he doesn't know about
the boyfriend.
Were they praising Inuyasha?
All right! They think he's cool!
Oh, Kagome....
You don't need it, do you?
That thing.
Huh?
What thing?
That iron cart!
I'll carry you, right?
Yes.
Huh?
I told you, Grandpa,
Inuyasha said he can create
diamonds with Tetsusaiga.
Why don't you make him
repay you?
One, two....
I'm missing the third.
You don't believe me, Grandpa?
It's missing....
It's okay.
I'll apologize to Mom.
Huh? You're not angry?
It just....doesn't matter to me.
A young girl who is chosen
to be the bride of a demon
makes a shocking confession!
I'm telling you that I was
betrothed to Miroku!
I'll forgive you!
I'll forgive the past,
so come and live with me
at the bottom of the lake.
Sango! I can explain!
Don't come near me!
I guess this wasn't meant to be.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Miroku's Past Mistake"
Sango, can't you trust me at all?