It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
for our dreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
There is just one way of
defeating the invincible Naraku.
And now,
Kikyo, Naraku,
Inuyasha and all the rest of us connected
to this story gather!
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Dead parasite chrysalis!
Damn!
So the rumors among
the villagers were true.
They said that seven days ago,
the mountain disappeared
overnight.
Does this have something to do
with the parasite chrysalis?
It's faint, but there's a lingering
smell of Naraku.
Naraku?!
And the smell of demons....
which permeates the soil here.
Damn! No matter how many I kill,
there's no end in sight.
Huh?
Did you find the nest?
Kagura....
But just what are these bugs?
Parasite chrysalis.
But it's strange.
They use giant demons as
their hosts....
there's no way they'd
build nests outside.
You're awfully familiar with them.
What else do you know?
Don't act innocent.
Why did Naraku order us to
kill the parasite chrysalis
immediately upon finding them?
I don't....know why.
Saimyosho....
They're telling us to go back.
Let's go.
You really haven't heard anything?
Unlike me, you have Naraku's trust....
- Huh?
- Huh?!
I didn't imagine this.
The mountain really moved
just now!
Oh no...!
The parasite chrysalis had
no place to go...
It means they couldn't live any longer
inside a large demon.
Naraku ordered us to kill the
parasite chrysalis
because he did not want
this to be known.
A mountain that moves...
Could it be...
the host of those parasite chrysalis?
Kagura!
She has a bad habit of
willfully going off on her own.
There's no mistake!
That mountain is alive.
That Naraku...
What does he plan to
start this time?
I don't understand why
Naraku keeps such
an unreliable woman alive.
Kohaku....
Naraku orders this.
Save Kagura.
Go.
It's near!
I smell a demon!
Wha...?!
Inuyasha, look!
The mountain....!
is moving!
Who are you?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Are you Naraku's henchman?!
Naraku?
You said Naraku?
That's the name of the fool
who entered my body and
disturbed my sleep.
What?!
Naraku entered this demon's body?
After deeply inhaling his filthy aura
and miasma,
I was awakened from my
200-year slumber.
What does this mean?
He stole the protective stone
from within my body and escaped!
Protective stone?
Where is Naraku?!
If you are hiding him,
I will not spare you!
Idiot! We're after Naraku, too!
Tell me where Naraku is!
Otherwise, my ire will not subside!
I already told you I don't know!
I'm looking for Naraku, too!
You just said that Naraku stole
your protective stone.
What is this protective stone?
The stone that is essential for me,
Gakusanjin, to exist in this mountain.
The stone that allows me to continue
my sleep as a mountain....
the Fuyoheki.
Fuyoheki?
Master Gakusanjin....
The Fuyoheki is the stone
that keeps you passive?
It is my protective stone....
which dissipates my miasma
and keeps enemies from approaching,
so that I will not engage in
unnecessary battles.
His miasma?
Dissipates it?
If we get a hold of the Fuyoheki,
will it mean that Naraku's miasma
will also disappear?
And he can hide himself from us?
Hey, what kind of shape
is this Fuyoheki?
What color? Does it have a scent?
Why ask?
I'll get it back for you!
I do not trust such words!
Dammit! Do you always wake up
in such a bad mood?!
Wind Scar!
We ain't gonna hear anything
more from him!
Inuyasha....
Let's go!
Brat!
Why don't you kill me?
You could have.
Huh? You want to die?
Inuyasha....
There's just no sense in
our fighting you.
We have only one enemy: Naraku.
If in our pursuit of Naraku
we find the Fuyoheki,
we will return it to you!
Why you...!
Take it.
What?!
These are crystals of my miasma.
Grab a few.
When you are near the Fuyoheki,
the crystals' aura will disappear.
If you move away from it,
the aura will reappear.
This will help in locating Naraku.
It seems he trusts us.
Yes....
Umm.... Thank you.
Enough. Go now.
But that Naraku....
Why did he steal something
like the Fuyoheki?
What's he gonna use it for?
Even now, we're having a hard time
looking for Naraku...
So why does he still need to
hide his miasma?
I'm starting to figure it out.
That Naraku is gonna use the
Fuyoheki
to camouflage that infant's miasma
and keep him hidden.
Hurry....
Kanna is supposed to be
with the infant...
I'll finally find it!
Kagura said that if the infant is found,
Naraku can be killed!
What?
Finish them?!
The blessed lock of Mistress
Kikyo's hair is unraveling.
There is something nearby....
Shikigami? But whose?
You are Naraku's....?
I sense the Sacred Jewel shard!
Just one shard!
It's Kohaku!
Kohaku?!
The Sacred Jewel shard keeps
you alive.
Does Naraku control your life?
Why do you obey Naraku?
Your soul is....
The aura is disappearing from
Gakusanjin's crystals.
Does that mean that
the Fuyoheki is up ahead?
No doubt about it!
Then Naraku is there, too....
Not only that!
I'm starting to smell Kikyo!
It's been a long time, Kikyo.
Since Mt. Hakurei, I believe.
Naraku!
I truly believed that I had
killed you back then.
Things won't always go
the way you expect!
I didn't notice that he was
standing right behind me.
I didn't sense his presence.
Even now, I don't sense
Naraku's miasma.
What does this mean?
What's wrong, Kikyo?
Didn't you want to see me?
I can't grasp my next arrow....
What are you staring at, Kohaku?
Take Kikyo's head.
Are you hesitating, Kohaku?
Kohaku!
Sister!
I cannot sense Naraku's miasma.
Is that the power of the
Fuyoheki?
Kikyo!
Naraku, why you...!
I'll purify it!
Naraku!
He got away!
Are you all right?
I was careless.
I didn't sense Naraku's miasma.
He stole the Fuyoheki in order
to come after you?
Fuyoheki?
A protective stone that
makes miasma disappear.
However....
although Kikyo was his target,
Naraku seemed unusually casual.
That's true.
Kohaku...
Say Kagome....
It's happening again,
but are you okay with it?
Kikyo is not the type
to travel with us.
They're probably saying
their goodbyes, like always.
It sure is a long farewell.
It can't be helped.
We're always with Inuyasha,
but Kikyo is...
It sure is taking long.
I wonder what
they're talking about...
Then Naraku was a decoy?
Probably....
My shikigami had found
something else.
What was it?
Naraku did not die
by my arrow.
Yeah.... Ever since Mt. Hakurei,
he won't die no matter how
many times I hit him.
It means his heart is
somewhere else.
His heart....?
So that's what he's trying
to hide with the Fuyoheki?
In order to destroy Naraku,
I guess I must find his heart.
Kikyo....
This Fuyoheki will mask
your miasma.
The original owner said that
it was to keep him from senseless fighting.
Humph! Now how will you use it?
Look, Kohaku....
Human souls.
Human souls?
So many of them were eaten.
The demon, Haku, ate them.
Let's hunt him down.
Slit open his belly.
Take care that you don't
damage his stomach.
What is it? There's something
shiny inside.
That is a human haku.
Haku?
The lives of the people he ate.
I thought that since we had
these crystals that sense miasma,
we could catch up to
Naraku easily.
Naraku's heart, right?
Yeah, that's what Kikyo said.
Hey Inuyasha!
Huh?
Is that all you spoke to
Kikyo about?
That's all!
If that's the case, they didn't
have to huddle together like that.
It looked suspicious.
The air feels heavy.
Let us endure it....
It happens all the time.
Huh?
I smell a demon!
Corpses of demons scattered
everywhere....
What the hell are these demons?!
What is it?
Looks like a combination
of various demons.
That's the soul of a demon!
No, that's the Haku.
All humans, animals and demons
have within them
the Haku and Kon spirits.
Kon is the heart, or soul.
And Haku is the power
to move the body.
What happened to the Kon
of this demon?
It was probably released
when it died.
So only the Haku kept
the demon moving.
In other words, as long as the Haku exists,
even a dead, soul-less body can move?
Could Naraku be involved?
The corpses of the demons are
scattered in four directions.
Maybe this demon isn't the only one
with a Haku that keeps him moving.
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Hiraikotsu!
Wind Tunnel!
Well, Inuyasha?
I can smell 'em!
There're still lots of 'em!
Inuyasha! Behind you!
Another one, huh?!
Wind Scar!
They're looking
more human.
Compared to the earlier ones, it's....
Yes....
It's as though the earlier demons
were all tests....
This smell?!
It's that Hakudoshi!
So you sniffed me out?
Hakudoshi!
What're you planning this time?!
Ask Moryomaru here.
What?!
That demon....
They are getting closer and closer
to humans.
I created many and tested them....
but it's easier to make them move
when they're more like humans.
With human haku, human bodies
work best.
So it's all your doing?!
Moryomaru, fight Inuyasha.
You intend to test him out
with Inuyasha?!
Sounds like fun.
I'll use you to practice some
new moves!
Moryomaru!
Adamant Barrage!
Gone!
So he disappeared on me!
Inuyasha, above you!
Wha...?!
Wings?!
Why the surprise?
I created Moryomaru from
various demons.
Making him fly was easy.
Who cares?!
He just flew away to
avoid me.
It's not like he deflected
my Adamant Barrage!
Take one more blow!
Adamant-!
Inuyasha!
He'll be devoured by
Moryomaru!
Devoured? Just try it!
Adamant....
Barrage!
He broke away!
Hakudoshi protected Moryomaru?!
What?!
Miroku!
I'm okay....
I'm not hurt.
But... he outsmarted us.
Why do you say that?
He stole the demon crystals.
What?!
It was our way of
finding the Fuyoheki....
I'm ashamed of myself.
The main thing is that
you're not hurt, Miroku.
There are other ways
to find Naraku.
But that Moryomaru bothers me.
Yes, Hakudoshi even went as
far as protecting him.
He wasn't gonna let him
be destroyed.
As you asked, I stole
the demon crystals.
I am leaving Moryomaru.
Use him as you please.
Moryomaru....
I will....put a soul inside you.
Kikyo searches for Naraku
as does Sesshomaru!
In order to destroy him,
we must get to his heart.
Kagura betrays Naraku,
and guides us to where
the heart is hidden....
But we are sent right into
a demon's belly!
You will all dissolve inside
the demon and disappear....
leaving only the Sacred Jewel shard.
Will we live or die?!
This is our final battle!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Bond Between Them:
Use the Sacred Jewel Shard!"
Please Kagome!
Please sustain me!