Inuyasha and Kikyo?
Why? What's going on?
Kikyo...
Kikyo!
How? How can he not avert his eyes?
Kagome!
Let's see...
This is the antibiotic
and this one's an ointment for pain.
And... I brought lots of
gauze and bandages.
Okay! I'll be off then.
Huh? Kagome!
Are you going back?
Well...
I just came to bring
some medicine.
At least make up with Inuyasha.
It was a silly argument.
Oh right, I had a fight with Inuyasha.
I don't care how you feel about me!
I won't let Naraku have you!
Only I can protect you from Naraku!
I had forgotten all about
the argument we had.
Miroku,
Kagome seemed very depressed.
Yes. Well, I can guess why
she's feeling that way.
Those lights!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha, Kagome went back
to her home again.
I see...
Inuyasha, you were seeing
Kikyo, weren't you?
Huh?
And Kagome saw the two of you.
Isn't that so?
Yeah, she saw us.
How could you sneak around like that?!
Inuyasha!
Your face looks like the Buddha!
Why's your face looking
so calm and divine?
That moment, Inuyasha didn't try to
avert his eyes from me.
Inuyasha tried to tell me something...
but I was afraid to listen
and ran away.
Inuyasha had already decided.
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha and Kikyo hated each other
because of Naraku's deception.
Kikyo followed Inuyasha and died.
And Naraku who separated them
is now after Kikyo again.
I don't care how you feel about me.
I won't let Naraku have you!
Only I can protect you from Naraku!
There's no place for me between them!
I can't forget Kikyo, after all.
So, Kagome...
I can't see you anymore.
I mustn't.
Kikyo gave her very life
for Inuyasha's sake.
I can't compete with that.
I can't return to Inuyasha.
Inuyasha won't come for me anymore.
But what'll I do?
I brought the Sacred Jewel fragments
back with me.
I should return them.
Yes, after I return them,
it'll be the end of it all.
I'll return to my normal existence.
She returned so soon...
and she hasn't spoken at all
since she returned...
I wonder
if something happened to Sis?
This is the cause.
A thumb?
Fool! A man!
Ah...
Could she have had an
argument with Inuyasha?
Ahem, Kagome...
Grandpa!
Would you like my egg?
Oh, thanks.
May I be excused?
- Sis...
- Sota!
These pickles are nice and crunchy.
Try some.
Uh-huh...
Kagome, no need
to wash your dishes.
I'll do them all together later.
Thanks.
I'm off.
- Sis...
- Kago...
Have a nice day!
What are you doing?!
Yeah!
Aren't you worried about Sis at all?
These pickles are really good!
Kagome!
'Morning!
You're out of the hospital?
You had some kind of
mysterious rash all over your body?
I guess we're running out
of feigned illnesses.
Say, never mind that.
Whatever happened?
- Huh?
- Don't act innocent!
You know, the jealous, rude
and spoiled guy of yours!
Did you split up?
- Huh?
- Kagome?
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
He dropped me flat!
Kagome isn't the one
that dumped him?!
Does that mean... ?
That she still loves him?!
But I'm really fine.
You've gotten over him?
Yes! So...
don't bring him up again, okay?
I'm fine.
She doesn't want to be
reminded 'cuz it hurts...
- She's scary.
- Her fake smile is scary.
Inuyasha!
How could you?!
You were so upset because
Kagome got friendly with Koga...
yet now, you want to
think only about Kikyo?!
How shallow your feelings were!
Inuyasha, go see Kagome.
Stop it, will ya?!
I've decided not to see her again!
Stop misunderstanding me!
Kagome took Sacred Jewel
fragments with her!
I'm telling you to go get them!
Only you can pass through the well!
Just the Sacred Jewel fragments?
Don't you care about Kagome?!
It can't be helped.
Inuyasha picked Kikyo.
It's cruel to ask Kagome
to come back.
Inuyasha...
Are you really sure about this?
What, Kaede?! Not you, too!
The present Kikyo is made
from earth and bones.
She's not of this world.
But Kikyo's spirit still remains.
Do you understand?!
You two can never be together
in this world!
Sister Kikyo's wish is for the
two of you to die together.
Fine... I'll go to hell with Kikyo,
as she wishes.
If that's my destiny with Kikyo.
I must go to return
the Sacred Jewel fragments.
But I don't want to. I'm afraid!
Once I give this back,
I won't be able to see Inuyasha again!
Sorry, Kagome.
I'm going to Kikyo.
Don't tell me!
That's...!
Kikyo...
I wish Kikyo would just disappear!
Have... Have I turned into
such a horrible woman?
I... I probably have a horrible
look on my face right now.
I can't see Inuyasha
looking like this.
The fragments...
The sacred tree...
Yes... This tree...
This is the tree on which
Inuyasha was sealed.
Five hundred years ago...
this is where I first
met Inuyasha.
What's that confused look
on your face, Kikyo?
So, are you satisfied, Miss Kikyo?
Do it with one shot, will ya?
Like the time you killed me!
Say, you keep calling me
Kikyo, Kikyo!
Let me tell you, my name is...!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha...
Kagome...
Why did I ever meet him?
If it were going to hurt this much...
I wish I had never met him!
But I want to see him!
I want to see Inuyasha once more!
I...l'm in love with Inuyasha!
Before I knew it,
I had grown to love him so much!
Kagome!
Mom...
Mom!
Kagome...
Huh?
When you're close to this sacred tree
don't you feel a strange power?
As though you feel more
true to yourself...
like your heart feels much more pure?
This is where
your father proposed to me.
What?
Of course, I loved him.
But the day before,
we had argued over something silly.
I wasn't sure
if we could make a go of it together.
The moment I walked under this tree
I felt things clearing up inside me...
and I accepted his proposal.
And because I did,
I was able to have you and Sota.
I'm grateful to this tree.
I won't ask what's troubling you.
But I have faith in you, Kagome.
That you are a child who will choose
the path that you believe in.
Thanks, Mom.
Inuyasha!
Shut up! I know!
I haven't said a word yet.
You're gonna tell me
to go see Kagome.
If you know that, hurry!
But that'll mean saying
goodbye to Kagome.
Saying something I couldn't
say the last time...
I'll have to this time.
You're not the one who's
having a hard time.
It's Kagome.
Miroku is absolutely right.
You've already made up
your mind, so fine.
But Kagome is probably
so confused right now.
If you're a man,
you'll go to see Kagome...
and make a nice, clean break.
I'll say... instead of dallying
around forever.
Do you want me to split
up with Kagome that much?!
Don't you want to split up?
Who... Who said that?!
I decided to protect Kikyo.
So how can I ask Kagome
to come back...
Where is everybody?!
Boy, what a poor sport!
We'll call him "Two-Faced"
from now on.
Gotta keep things together.
Why you...!
Nope... I can't ask her
to come back.
Kagome knows that.
I must go.
I must see her
and bid her farewell.
Otherwise I can't go on...
Kagome...
While I was back over there,
I gave it a lot of thought.
About you and Kikyo and... me.
Kagome, I...
I understand.
I understand how you feel.
So I thought I couldn't stay
here with you.
Kagome...
Until I met you,
I never trusted a soul.
But... you cried for my sake.
You always stayed by my side.
When I'm with you, I'm happy.
You soothe my soul.
But...
I'm not supposed to be
happy and have fun!
Kikyo...
Kikyo followed me in death.
I must repay her with my death.
I know. I can't compete with Kikyo.
Because... I'm still alive.
I've thought a lot about Kikyo, too.
Kikyo and I are so different.
Even the talk that I'm a
reincarnation of Kikyo...
But I'm not Kikyo.
My heart belongs to me.
But I've come to understand
one thing about how Kikyo feels.
Something she and I share.
The desire to see you again.
Huh?!
When I realized that Kikyo and I
felt the same thing, I felt a bit better.
The desire to see you is the same.
That's why I conjured up the courage
to come and see you.
Kagome...l've wanted to see you, too.
But...
I want to stay with you, Inuyasha.
I can't forget you.
Kagome... How am I to answer you?
Inuyasha...
Can I ask you one thing?
Will you let me stay?
You'll stay with me?
Uh-huh.
I can never break the bond
between Inuyasha and Kikyo.
I understand that.
But Inuyasha...
I realized this.
My meeting you was no coincidence.
I want you to live, Inuyasha.
Kagome...
Let's go, Inuyasha.
Yeah...
I want you to be happy.
I want you to laugh a lot.
I don't know
what I'll be able to do for you...
but I'll always stay by your side.
Kohaku finds himself under the
care of a kind old couple.
But a demon attacks him...
intent on stealing the Sacred Jewel
fragment on his back.
We all rush to Kohaku's rescue.
But he has no memory that he is
the son of a demon slayer...
or even his sister, Sango!
Why? Is this some trick by Naraku?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kohaku's Lost Memory"
Don't miss it!