Who is that?!
Hey, are you all right?!
Here it is... Right here!
There's no mistake!
Just enough moisture...
And the soil is good, too.
Intruder! I asked who
you are?!
- Identify yourself!
- Silence!
I just have some business
with the urn buried here!
Once I possess it, I'll leave
this sore sight of a village!
So... She knows what's
buried here!
Leave immediately!
Else I'll show no mercy!
You talk too much, you stubborn
ignorant old woman!
Didn't I tell you not
to interfere?!
Priestess Kaede!
T-that is my sister's!
I will not let you have it!
Not a demon like you!
I am the demoness,
Urasue!
Kikyo's ashes...
are now in MY possession!
Inuyasha!
Damn!
Who is that?!
That's...Kagome?
No, it's not...
That's Kikyo...
The one who bound
me to the tree!
A dream...
Brought back ugly memories.
They look alike...
Kagome looks exactly
like Kikyo.
Inuyasha?
Stop scaring me like that!
I thought you were
a scary demon.
Huh? Did I punch you just now?
Sorry!
Nope, not like her at all!!
What is?
Not one little bit!
What're you talking about?!
What is it, Inuyasha?
Nothing!
What's that?
What? A demon?
What is it? I'm getting the
scent of new blood...
Hold it... The smell of
that blood...
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Why the sudden urge to
go back to the village?
I'm still sleepy!
Priestess Kaede, you
mustn't move yet!
Never mind!
It's not a serious wound.
Granny Kaede!
You?
What happened to you?
So you're still alive.
I guess not even a flesh wound
will keep you down.
So, you caught the scent of my blood
on that demon.
Look, think of your age and
take it easy!
So... He wanted to return because
he was worried about old Kaede.
What's this?
This used to be my sister,
Kikyo's gravesite.
A grave, here?
I was not strong enough
to stop her.
I take possession!
My sister had unusually strong powers,
even for a priestess.
If her ashes get into the hands
of some demon...
who knows for what evil
purpose they will be used?
Inuyasha!
Forget it!
Kikyo and I were enemies.
Have you forgotten who shot an
arrow into my chest?
You're right...
I heard that happened
fifty years ago...
It's Inuyasha!
Inuyasha the half-demon wanted
to take the Sacred Jewel...
and become a full-fledged demon.
When he came to the village to
take the Jewel...
the priestess, Kikyo, shot
a sacred arrow which...
held him fast to a tree.
Hah! Now that I have this,
I'll become a real demon!
Inuyasha!
K-Kikyo...
Why you!
But in that battle,
Kikyo would lose her life.
Sister!
Demoness Urasue...
She didn't just steal
Kikyo's ashes.
I could smell the dirt from
the grave...
Just what is she up to?
Let's go, Inuyasha.
Where?
Don't you feel sorry for Kikyo,
that her grave has been violated?
Forget that you were once
bitter enemies.
Kikyo died long ago, right?
- Hey!
- What?
Since yesterday, you've been
avoiding looking at me!
It's nothing...
I know! It's because
I look like Kikyo!
That's why you don't like me,
right?!
It's not!
Huh?
It's not like that.
W- what?
W-what is it?!
W- what was that just now?
What?
What was that?
Darn! What're you doing?!
Y-you're the one!
What did I do?!
Huh?
Granny...
I am also a priestess.
I will take back my sister's ashes
with my own hands.
Inuyasha, at least tell me in
which direction...
Urasue is headed?
Do you wanna die, old woman?
Inuyasha!
Well, I'll have to go
to find out.
Granny Kaede, you mustn't!
You're in no condition!
It's useless to stop her!
That's why I hate dealing
with old people!
I'll get Kikyo's ashes back.
And I'll be sure to bring home
your bones, too.
Inuyasha, thank you.
Granny Kaede, may I come along?
Kagome?
Inuyasha's eyes just now...
He wasn't seeing me...
He was seeing Kikyo
inside me.
Granny's asleep.
You'd better get some sleep.
We'll attack tomorrow.
So soon?
I can smell it...
She's not far.
Inuyasha...
He's asleep.
When I first saw Inuyasha,
he was sleeping, too.
Actually, he was bound
to a tree...
But to me, he looked like
sleeping peacefully.
I thought he hated Kikyo...
I know! It's because
I look like Kikyo!
That's why you don't like me,
right?!
It's not!
Huh?
It's not like that.
Inuyasha's eyes...
weren't the eyes of hatred.
My heart is still pounding.
I wonder if Inuyasha...
Maybe Inuyasha...
actually was in love
with Kikyo.
We must retrieve Kikyo's
ashes as soon as possible!
I have a dreadful feeling
about this.
Well, it's too late now, isn't it?!
If you didn't want the ashes
stolen...
why didn't you just scatter
the ashes into the river?
You stayed sentimental and
kept hanging on to them...
and see what happened?
Inuyasha, how do you feel
about a grave?
A grave is not simply a place
to bury a body or ashes.
A grave is necessary for the
hearts of ones who are left behind.
Hearts of those left behind?
My sister was born a priestess.
And she used her special powers
for the good of the villagers.
She kept demons
away from the village...
and battled illness and
famine countless times...
encouraging the people around her.
Even after her demise...
the villagers have not weakened,
they are resolved to live.
However, man is weak.
Danger and uncertainty can
weaken his heart.
The grave was a place
of reassurance.
A place where hearts
could find peace.
Hmm? Just like that time...
Inuyasha is thinking
of Kikyo...
Inuyasha was in love
with Kikyo.
But she shot an arrow
into him...
and he was bound for
fifty years...
I feel really sorry for him.
Huh?
It was unrequited love...
Unrequited love...
unrequited love!
What's with you, Kagome?!
That look... gives me the creeps!
Why're you looking so sorry for me?!
Oh, sorry! I was thinking nonsense.
Huh? What?
Well...
What is it?!
Well... What were you thinking?!
Hey!
Oh, shut your mouth!
Now then!
Let's see the result of my
special magic...
Kneading the earth from the grave
with the ashes...
and baking it in my Demon Kiln!
Hmm... Looks quite good!
Now then...
Let's see...
Arise! Open your eyes, Kikyo!
Kikyo... I have heard that as
a priestess...
you foiled many an attempt
by demons...
to possess the Sacred Jewel.
I also hear that the Jewel is
now in fragments...
and a demon who possesses
even one fragment of the Jewel...
doubles its powers!
I want it... I want every fragment
of the Sacred Jewel!
Now, you will go and destroy
every demon who seeks it...
Burn and destroy them!
You will serve me... the one who
has brought you back to life!
You will gather the fragments
of the Sacred Jewel!
Huh... W-what is this?
A soul... The soul hasn't returned!
There is no way my magic would
fail to bring back the soul!
Does this mean that the soul has
already been reincarnated...
in another body?!
Then all I made was a hollow shape
in the form of Kikyo!
Damn! Making me work
so hard and wasting my time!
Setting me up for failure like this!
How maddening!
I can't stand this! I can't stand it!
What's this?
Earthen dolls? How creepy!
Well, there it is.
Huh?!
We have to cross this?!
I'm so scared!!!
You don't have to come.
I'll go in and
talk some sense into her.
Don't be silly! I refuse to
be left behind on a bridge like this?!
So come...
Wait!
There're more of
the earthen dolls.
What's that?!
Soldiers of the
old demoness!
Those are the dolls we saw...
It can't be?!
Inuyasha! Behind you!
Kagome, Old Woman...
It's gonna shake a bit.
Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
Are these guys really
made of mud?!
Foxfire!
They're not that strong!
Just that they're so many of 'em!
What's the ruckus outside?
Oh, I can't stand this!
I'll go out and work off
this frustration!
Hey!
Let go! This belongs
to me!
Inuyasha! Watch out!
What does this mean?
Could it...
The resemblance!
Such a close resemblance!
What coincidence!
Such good fortune!
That face... No mistake!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Granny! Shippo!
Hey, let me go!
If I let go, you'll die.
And now that I've found my
reincarnated soul...
As if I'd let you go!
I need you! In order to fully
resurrect Kikyo!
Resurrect... Kikyo?!
Kikyo who died during the
Warring States Era is resurrected!
If the Sacred Jewel burst out
of my body...
then perhaps, I really am the
reincarnation of Kikyo.
Urasue forces me to drink
a potion and...
my soul is sucked out of me!
Kikyo and Inuyasha's reunion
after fifty years...
Rather than fond memories...
Kikyo still harbors a deep grudge
and she goes after Inuyasha!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Return of the Tragic Priestess, Kikyo!"
Don't miss it!