Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
Mysterious robberies in the middle
of the night...
The culprit enters leaving no clues
and is never seen!
Could it be the work of a demon
who can really become invisible?!
Naraku is on the verge of
completing the Sacred Jewel.
Learning that, we continue our journey
in search of the few remaining shards.
And who'd have thought that
during our travels,
we'd come upon that
old woman again?
Demons, away with you!
A bit miserable for a dinner, huh?
Can't be helped! We didn't
catch anything.
Are you all out of your
ninja food, Kagome?
Completely.
Miroku, why didn't you stock
up on more food?
I would have, if my pockets
had been full of money.
We're out of money?
Yes. So we'll have to earn some
money along the way.
Oh?
Huh?
Ehh?!
Just about done.
Let's dig in.
- Right!
- Yeah!
I'm bigger, so I'm hungrier!
I'm a growing boy,
so I need more food!
- Hah!
- Huh?!
Got it!
That's mine!
As if you can win against me!
Not a chance!
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Sit!
- Now!
- No way!
Thanks!
We'll be able to eat our fill
tomorrow.
Stupid Inuyasha!
Just you wait!
I'll get back at you
for taking what's mine!
We're counting on you, Madam Exorcist.
Yes.
You just leave it to me.
This wind seems ominous.
Really?
It's just the wind picking up.
It struck again!
Madam Exorcist!
We've been robbed!
I was mistaken.
He struck a different house
this night!
Hmm....
This is quite a lively town.
Something wrong with that?
I don't know if we'll be able
to find any house
in need of sutra charms
or exorcisms.
Makes no difference since
your exorcisms are fake anyway.
Even then, unless the house
has some kind of problem,
it will not go smoothly.
Will not go smoothly?
He shouldn't be proud
of what he's saying.
At this rate, even if we're
in a town like this,
we won't be able to
sleep in an inn.
What's wrong with sleeping outdoors?
Come on!
I want to take a bath!
And I want to sleep on
a nice, warm bedding!
And I want to eat
good food, Inuyasha!
I'll second that.
So whaddya suggest?
There ain't nothing we can do!
Oh, you all....
It's been a while.
How have you been?
It's the old....
Exorcist!
Hmm... A demonic aura?
I don't sense anything.
I see...
Some exorcist.
Hah!
- Come get me!
- Wait!
Demon, disperse!
Over here!
Sit!
Wha!
Stop it, you two!
You still have much to learn
about life.
What?! You fake exorcist!
I'm not sure about her
skills as an exorcist,
but she's pretty sharp
when it comes to women.
You were worried, weren't you?
That the monk and the princess
were getting along too well.
Huh?!
You like him, don't you?
That monk, Miroku.
Ohh... it's written all over
your face.
I said, it's not like that!
Huh?!
What are you doing?
I'll leave you behind!
You seem to be doing very well,
Madam Exorcist.
I'm just fine.
And that's why I can still
pursue my work as an exorcist.
She's still doing exorcisms.
I'm amazed at how she
manages to stay alive.
But I'm glad that you've
come to this town.
Will you help me with
a certain job?
I'd like no one better.
Is there some profit to
be made here?
Huh? Well, I just can't
handle this alone.
And I was just looking
for some help.
Well then,
let us hear you out.
Mysterious happenings in
the dead of the night.
Only the homes of
the wealthy are targeted.
No matter how tight the security,
something manages to break into
the house and steal everything of value.
And since the methods used
are too mysterious for the usual thief,
rumor has it that a demon
is responsible for these evil deeds.
What do you mean by
mysterious methods?
The house can be tightly locked,
but the thief still enters.
And even if someone senses
an ominous presence,
nothing is ever seen.
In other words, it's said that
this thief can go through walls
and become invisible.
Just like a ninja.
That's impossible, even
for a ninja.
Then does it mean it really
can become invisible?
An invisible demon?
I see....
If it's not the work of humans,
then it must be a demon.
Leave it to me!
The enemy is undoubtedly
using demon magic.
I'll see through his tricks!
Maybe you can see his tricks,
but I'll sniff him out first.
You're always being duped by
demon magic, Inuyasha.
And the only magic you perform
is to run away!
That's not true!
I let myself get tricked
on purpose!
Stop it, you two!
- Kah!
- Humph!
Huh? Where's Miroku?
What are you doing there?
Let us go!
This is the town's second
richest household.
Oh....!
Both the richest and second richest
homes have been robbed already.
And I've been employed
by both.
So I want to break up into two groups
and stake out each house.
Two groups? How do you want
to divide up?
I won't team up with Inuyasha.
Damn right! We don't need you!
Inuyasha will end up being
tricked by demon magic!
Shaddup!
I'll cut down the robber
with my Wind Scar!
Stop it, Inuyasha!
Well first, Miroku and I must
work separately
since we both use
spiritual powers.
Huh?!
Spiritual powers, huh?
Sango, can you watch over
the old woman?
Sure.
Come on, Kirara.
Then you, the other girl,
go with them.
So I'm on Miroku's team?
Miroku will probably be more
effective than that old woman.
Miroku's more useful
than that old hag.
If Inuyasha goes
on that side,
no one will be there
to control him.
My thoughts exactly.
Shippo....
Will you help the exorcist
with your fox-demon magic?
What? With my demon magic?
You can run to us if you want.
Hah! I'll use my fox-demon magic to
uncover the robber's true form.
Well then, I leave you in charge
of this house, Miroku.
We're off to the town's
richest house.
Please do your best
to help us.
What should we do?
Demon or whatever,
this thing only strikes at night, right?
All we can do is wait.
Well, let us rest and save
our strength for later.
You think it's all right
to ask for a bath?
Do whatever you want.
If you tell them it's in
preparation for tonight,
I'm sure they won't object.
So let's just relax and
enjoy ourselves.
I wonder if Shippo and the others
are all right?
Please do your best.
He seems so depressed.
Well, his house may be
broken into tonight.
So what are we going to do
from now?
I was going to come
up with a plan....
Huh? The tea leaf is
standing up.
That is a good omen.
What kind of plan?
You really know how to
use demon magic?
Of course!
And can you disappear, too?
I can't, but I've heard of
demon magic like that.
I've never heard of
demons who can become invisible.
Neither have I.
Although I have a talisman that
can hide your presence.
I have a trick like that, too.
If the enemy can hide,
then we shall do the same
and hide ourselves.
Oh....
Shall we try combining them?
You're right! It's worth a try!
Fox Magic!
Hidden Cloud!
Ohh!
How was that?
You were almost there.
All right....
He disappeared!
It works!
How was it this time?
You disappeared.
You were invisible.
Yes! I now possess
a new power!
Let's try it on other things now.
Huh? Me?
Fox Magic!
Hidden Cloud!
I've perfected the technique
of Hidden Cloud!
That was amazing!
Huh? Right....!
I need to do something
before we slay the demon.
I'll be back by sundown.
Huh? He left?
Umm.... I must go out
for just a while, too.
Huh? What did you say?
Here! Here!
Give it back!
Go!
Hah! If you want it back,
turn around three times.
Boys, cut it out.
Give it back to her.
A talking cat!
Huh.... A demon cat!
Here.
Bye-bye.
Thank you, lady.
Huh?
Oh stop it, Monk!
No, no. I'm dead serious.
Really?
Certainly.
Then say it....
Once more!
Will you bear my child?
Ohh.... My goodness!
Yikes! She saw me!
Why did you call out to us?
Err.... Well....your hips....
Y'know?
Oww!
See?
Oh, monk!
Uh-oh....
Why?
By this time,
she'd have intervened...!
Why? Why is she so silent?
Why does she follow
me without a word?
And... What is that sutra
on her forehead?
Is it some kind of
message for me?
Monk....
How come you're so
silent all of a sudden?
Well, I'm speechless because
I'm surrounded by such pretty women.
Oh, stop!
Hurry! Hurry and lash out at me!
Why is she acting so differently?
Monk, sit here.
The food here is great.
P-Please go easy on me!
Huh?
If you're going to censure me,
say it loud and clear!
Y-You can see me?
And what is that sutra
on your forehead?
Isn't it directed at me?
Umm....
Miroku....
You can see me?
See you?
What do you mean, Sango?
Oh, no....!
I....
Huh? Sango!
Wasn't that Shippo just now?
What's with this kid?!
Shippo! You think you're
being funny or something!?
Huh?!
Damn that Shippo!
I don't know what he's up to,
but that kid kicked me several
times and ran off!
That's how close you are.
How?!
You and Shippo fight so much
because you're close to each other.
But Shippo is much smaller,
so go easy on him.
Like I care! Hah!
That was careless of me.
Inuyasha has a keen
sense of smell.
He must have caught
my scent.
Let's hope that the invisible
demon doesn't have a sharp nose.
Err.... Shippo....
What is it, Sango?
Oh.... It's nothing....
It will be dark soon.
We've been asked to guard this
family's heirloom....
a precious scroll.
A scroll?
The invisible demon has been
stealing scrolls and rolls of silk.
Now then....We've had our dinner....
And taken a bath....
All that's left is to wait
for the culprit to appear.
I wonder if he'll show up?
What if he doesn't show up?
Well....
Does that mean we have to stay
on guard without rest?
Kagome, you can go sleep
in the next room.
I'll stay up as long as I can.
It may not be this house.
Now then, I wonder which
house will be hit.
Don't you sense something?
Not particularly.
Oh right... that's how she is.
By the way, where's Shippo?
He made himself hidden
back in the room.
Huh?
Even if that demon were
to enter the house,
Shippo can't be seen,
so he'll be safe.
Shippo....
Huh?
No! The hanging scrolls!
Fox Fire!
Just what do you think
you guys are doing?!
Y-You can see me?
This is bad....
Sango! Old woman!
How'd this guy get inside
the house?!
And he's not invisible.
Give it to me....
Give me the treasures....
He disappeared!
He is an invisible demon, after all!
He hasn't disappeared!
Hand it over.
You demon! Where are you?!
Damn demon! Where are you!
- Give me the treasures!
- Here?! Or here!
Why're you stumbling around?
Inuyasha!
Looks like you're guarding
the treasures.
Now then....
Inuyasha!
Found you!
You're not getting away!
H-How?!
You're the only one with
an unfamiliar scent.
- Inuyasha!
It's all over.
What'll we do with him?
Please spare me!
Then you will turn over everything
you've stolen until now.
Wow!
Things which are thin and shiny
attract me,
and I couldn't help
but take these.
So many of them....
Should we divide them
up amongst ourselves?
You're giving them back
to their rightful owners.
Oh well, I'm sure we'll
be richly rewarded.
My new Fox Magic trick
was almost complete, too.
New Fox Magic?
But I ended up being saved
by you, Inuyasha.
I've still got lots to learn.
Hah!
If you've learned your lesson,
don't come near human
settlements again.
Yes, thank you.
I'm off then.
Wow! He's paper-thin!
That's why he looked
as though he was invisible.
I really thought the invisible
demon had appeared.
And I was terrified.
Are you stupid, Shippo?
I'm not stupid!
An invisible demon wouldn't "appear"!
I see....
Akitoki came to us with
a nagging family problem.
According to his story, he had set out
on a journey
to seal the demon halberd known
as the Naginata of Kenkon.
He was the ancestor of Hojo, my friend.
And on the genealogy scroll which
had been passed down to his family,
I saw the name Kagome.
What if I couldn't return
to the modern age
and end up married to Akitoki?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"An Ancestor Named Kagome"
I sense a storm brewing!