Stop, Kohaku!
What's happened, Kohaku?!
The thread...of a spider!
Why that!
Damn!
Sister...
Ko... ha... ku?
I...
Sister!
Kohaku!
A white baboon?!
Yes.
It's Naraku!
Tell me in detail.
The slain bodies of
countless villagers...
and the half-demon who
attacked them...
His name is Inuyasha.
Inuyasha seeks the power of
the Sacred Jewel...
to turn himself into a
full-fledged demon.
Sacred Jewel?
He must have believed that he
would find the Jewel at the village...
and thus attacked it.
Sango!
Give me my weapon!
I will get the one who
attacked my village...
I will kill this half-demon
Inuyasha!
A horse cannot make it
from here on.
Sango... is dead?
No way! Until I get that Inuyasha,
I'll not die!
That's good.
But can you fight decently
in that condition?
Slaying demons is
my profession.
So you can't be stopped?
Well then, I will send Naraku
with you.
He is my advisor.
He's very familiar with demons
and should prove useful to you.
And...
when your mission is complete,
come back here.
You have lost your family and
all your fellow villagers...
I am much saddened for you.
I will never return.
I do not have much
time left.
Please...my body...
hold up a little longer.
Until I complete my
final task.
The cave where the Sacred
Jewel was created?
Yes. We are headed now to
the outskirts of the village...
to the limestone cave.
Actually, this village served as
a sort of factory.
Factory?
They made weapons and armor from
the skins and bones...
of the demons that were slain.
And unused portions were disposed of
in this cave.
Hence, this limestone cave is filled
with the remains of demons.
And it seems that deep inside
the cave was once...
full of carcasses of demons.
That's where the Sacred Jewel was?
Yes... that is the story that has been
passed down in this region.
Good work, Myoga.
Thank you for the compliment!
I did my best in the hope that
it would be of help to you.
Really?
When you stay by me,
you're always in danger...
so I thought you just
ran away.
Master Inuyasha, how could you
think that?!
Sorry about that.
Shall we go in?
All right... let's go.
Just a minute, Master Inuyasha!
What is it?!
A strong barrier has been placed
at the entrance...
and one cannot just walk in.
Then say so earlier!
S-sister!
Kohaku!
Sister!
Are you in pain, Sango?
Damn!
Pitiful thing...
But you won't be able to rest in peace
even if you died.
Would you care to try this?
T-that's...
a Sacred Jewel fragment!
Why are you in possession of it?
Just who?!
I have had this from
long before.
I am willing to lend
it to you.
To me?
You may believe that the
Sacred Jewel is used only for evil.
But there are good uses for it as well.
Inuyasha!
Damn!
It's hopeless.
There's no way into the cave...
and everyone who could've
talked to us has been killed.
Not everyone.
What?
The more skilled Slayers went
to some castle.
That's right!
If those men had been in the village...
they would easily have turned back
an attack by the demons.
All right... Let's go to that castle...
and talk to the men about the
secret of the Sacred Jewel...
and find out how to get into
that cave... easy!
Now then, let's get started.
Hurry, Kagome!
Or we'll leave you!
Wait!
Myoga...
is the castle this way?
Hmmm?
Master Inuyasha, were you walking
without knowing which way to go?
Huh?! Err... You didn't say a word...
so I figured I was going
the right way!
Inuyasha...
the castle shouldn't be too far.
Can't you sniff it out
from here?
Uh-huh... I can't get a whiff
of anything here.
Huh? What's the matter?
You are Inuyasha?
I will slay you!
Just who are you?!
Sango!
Someone from the village?
Master Inuyasha!
You must not cross swords
with Sango!
Hiraikotsu!
This ain't the time to say that!
Tetsusaiga is losing!
Inuyasha!
Why do you come after me?!
Silence, half-demon!
I will avenge everyone
from my village!
Old Myoga! What's she saying?!
I have no idea!
Master Inuyasha, it's coming again!
We must do something about
that weapon!
Agreed!
Wind Tunnel!
Got it!
Look! Naraku's poison insects!
No, Miroku!
You suck them in, you'll be poisoned!
W-why are they here?!
It can't be!
Naraku!
Inuyasha, give up and
let her slay you.
Why you!
Not in a hundred years!
I am your opponent!
Why you! Interfere and
I'll kill you first!
Try it!
You may have said those words
when you killed my people?!
But I'll not die so easily!
She believes that Inuyasha
attacked the village!
She's being deceived by Naraku!
She has a Sacred Jewel
fragment in her back!
Before that weapon returns!
Poison Powder!
A miasma!
Demons with ears like yours have
a weakness against strong scents!
I can't get close!
Leave it to a Demon Slayer.
Well, well... if it isn't the monk.
Naraku... die now!
I can't. Not until I gather all
the Sacred Jewel fragments.
I don't know what you are
scheming, but it's over!
He did it!
Kagome!
This is not for the
likes of you.
Now that I have the fragment
in my possession...
I need not to linger.
Naraku... why you!
Farewell, Monk...
and Inuyasha.
- Why you...!
- You won't get away!
Sango... I await you at the castle.
Kill Inuyasha without fail
and return.
Naraku... Can I really trust him?
Kirara...
You're still alive!
Kirara, follow him.
If he does anything strange,
kill him.
You won't get away!
Stop, Naraku!
Inuyasha! I will fight you!
You will die right here!
Are you still saying that?!
I must kill him now!
Before my life wanes.
Cut it out!
No!
Without your weapon!
Poison Powder!
My poison shield mask!
What is he up to?!
H- he's...not trying to save me?!
No, he isn't!
He's the enemy who attacked
my village!
Inuyasha!
You! Haven't you realized yet that
Naraku is tricking you?
And... you're covered with blood.
W-what?!
l-I didn't know it was this bad...
I didn't feel any pain.
Inuyasha, are you all right?
I am.
Kohaku, are you afraid about
becoming a Slayer?
N-no...
Kohaku... this is just between
you and me.
There isn't a soul who's not
afraid of fighting a demon.
Huh?
Then, you too?
Yup... not only me.
Father and all the others.
But we're not fighting alone.
We're always together.
We fight together with our comrades.
So it'll be okay, since we're
with everyone.
Kohaku!
Sister... I'm afraid.
Is she dead?
She just fainted.
Inuyasha, she has a Sacred Jewel
fragment imbedded in her back.
No wonder...
I knew from the scent of her blood
that she was badly injured.
That Naraku... He used the
Sacred Jewel...
to make her fight until
she died.
No way will I lose him!
Thanks... you're gonna give
me a ride?
Naraku!
Don't take me lightly!
W-why... you!
Sister!
I have no voice!
My body won't move!
What's wrong with me?!
Someone's back... Warm.
Whose... ?
You!
Conscious, are you?
Put me down! What're you doing?!
What?!
We're going after Naraku.
He took our Sacred Jewel fragment.
Your name's Sango, right?
Keep bothering me, and
I'll leave you right here!
What?!
Inuyasha! You're so rude!
No wonder people misjudge you!
Forgive him. He talks rough,
but he's actually quite nice.
Hey you!
Sango, Master Inuyasha and the others
could not leave you to die...
with your deep wound.
Old Myoga...
Let's speed it up!
Naraku... You won't get away!
Is Naraku's appearance
a deception?
Deception or not...
find out for yourself!
Damn! No matter I slash them,
they revert back!
He'll impale me!
Miroku!
What're you doing?!
You're hopeless!
Inuyasha, behind you!
Inuyasha, so you're still alive?
As if a human can kill me!
You looked to be losing to
that wounded Slayer.
Shaddup!
Naraku, you're the one, huh?!
You turned the pack of demons
on the village...
and annihilated everyone!
I just told the demons that...
the guard on the village
was down.
So he...!
Was your goal to get the fragments
kept at the village?!
Oh? Very perceptive of you!
I must say where there's
a Sacred Jewel fragment...
there's always a fight to
be found.
For just that...
you killed so many?!
Naraku!
Sango?
The demons in the castle...
the demon spider...
Were they all part of
your trap?
Trap?
Is that what you call
just simple games?
I thought that the Slayer
of this village...
could handle any sort
of demon.
Why you!
Sango!
Fool...
No way I loan the Sacred Jewel
to one who defies me.
Sango!
The fragment suppressed
the pain...
Damn!
You should have believed Inuyasha
was your sworn enemy and killed him...
then you would have died happily.
F- father...!
Kohaku...!
You always trample on
people's feelings!
Are you remembering Kikyo?
Shaddup! You son of a bitch!
Damn him!
Too easy... Could this really be the
Naraku I was pursuing?
A punk like this... made Kikyo suffer...
as well as countless others.
Inuyasha, watch out!
His body is moving freely!
I will not die!
His head is alive too!
What's going on?!
He's reverting back to himself.
He's using the power of
the Sacred Jewel!
Why didn't I notice it?
I spent time with such a demon...
yet I sensed nothing at all.
In fact, even now...
No! I can't sense any
demon spirit!
Then...he is...
Inuyasha! That's just a
demon puppet!
A puppet?
In demon puppetry, the true
apparition is hidden...
in the deepest part of the body.
His heart!
Aim straight for his heart!
Humph... so you figured it out.
Take that!
He did it!
What's that?!
This is demon puppetry.
This paper wrapped around the doll
belongs to Naraku.
Then who was it that
we fought all this time?
A counterfeit Naraku.
Probably the real Naraku was
somewhere safe controlling this puppet.
Young Lord...
Neither the girl-Slayer nor
Naraku have returned.
Could they have been killed?
That is possible.
Continue a strict guard
around the castle.
Yes, Sire.
This castle...and this body which
hides my true identity...
I will use to great satisfaction...
my dear Kagemaki.
Sacred Jewel is also known as
"Jewel of Four Souls."
How did the souls form a jewel
with the power the demons covet?
Deep in the cave
near the Slayer' village...
lies a priestess's mummy.
She was killed in a battle
hundreds of years ago.
The Sacred Jewel's glint awakens
a gigantic monster!
Next, "Secret of the Jewel
of Four Souls Revealed".
Look forward to it!