Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The battalion of resurrected specters...
The Band of Seven appear
one after another.
We've taken refuge in
a temple,
but we're attacked by
a merciless rogue.
Inuyasha rushes to save us,
but he finds himself in a bind, too.
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
W-What is that?!
Get down, Shippo! Kirara!
What...?!
Inuyasha...
You helped your friends escape,
so you should have no regrets.
You've awakened.
I'm glad.
Put your mind at ease
and rest.
A Sacred Jewel Shard!
Then this man...
... belongs to the Band of Seven?
What do I do?!
I can't use the Wind Scar
in these conditions...
What can I?
I may as well try.
Accept your fate and die!
It's useless!
Wind... Scar!
Kagome!
Kagome, wait for me!
What's this smell?
The smell of dead bodies
and graveyard soil...
Are the Band of Seven
up ahead?
No... It's different!
This smell is...
Perchance, are you Inuyasha?
I have been waiting for you.
What?
Ahh...
She's all right.
You're being pursued?
Who are you?
As you can see...
I am the monk of this temple.
There has been talk
in the village...
that the dead spirits of the Band of Seven
who died over ten years ago
have somehow been resurrected, bringing
calamity to this region.
Band of Seven...?
The dead that I buried just
a while ago
were also burned to death
by them.
And you're the only
survivor?
I was so frightened, I hid myself
behind the Buddha statue.
I understand that you are
being pursued by the Band of Seven.
Hey Monk!
Get one thing straight!
We're not being pursued!
We're the ones doing the pursuing!
If you know... will you tell
me the answer?
Why have the Band of Seven
been resurrected?
And what'll you do
if I tell you?
I serve the Buddha.
But I was helpless against
the killings committed before my eyes.
I wish to make amends.
If I am able, I want to settle
those dead souls.
This smell...
Forget it.
This isn't something a
monk can handle.
I guess he's not one of
the Band of Seven.
I'm catching the smell
of a living person.
Hmm? That's!
Fly lower!
Oh... there's no mistake!
That's the after-effect of
Inuyasha's Wind Scar.
I guess Inuyasha didn't come north
simply to enjoy the hot springs
and the mountain scenery.
Huh?
Fly higher! Much higher!
Fly away!
Get away now! Crow!
Wait, Koga!
When it comes to Kagome,
he gets so excited!
Which way is Inuyasha's scent?
Huh?
This is...
the smell of graveyard soil?
Someone named Naraku...
called forth the dead souls?
Who is this Naraku?
Sorta like a demon.
Which means?
He's not completely a demon.
Right now, he's hiding himself
somewhere.
He's undergoing a transformation
and increasing his power.
The Band of Seven is being used
as a decoy to buy time.
That Ginkotsu's attacking!
He's still alive?
Monk! If you wanna live,
stay hidden!
Damn Ginkotsu...
He should've taken
his time in coming.
But I've learned one thing.
That Naraku cannot
be trusted.
You three can die now.
Inuyasha!
Ginkotsu!
Still wanna fight?!
That's useless!
Steel threads!
I gotcha!
Stupid fool!
As if... this can...
hold me down!
Take that!
Serves you right!
I smell smoke!
Kagome!
I am Renkotsu of
the Band of Seven.
Why you...!
That monk...
What's going on?
I smell human blood!
What's wrong, Inuyasha?
You look so shocked.
Your nose is extremely
sensitive, right?
I thought you were on
to me earlier.
But what?
My body didn't emanate the scent
of dead bodies or graveyard soil?
I get it!
Damn it!
It's this place...
It seems taking over this
temple was a wise move.
It's surrounded by
graveyard dirt.
It overpowered my own scent.
Furthermore, I took over the
raiments the live monk wore.
Your scent is so sharp,
you caught that smell right away
and it put you at ease.
Why you...!
You killed the monks
of the temple?
You saw me earlier...
burying those bodies.
If only I had seen through
him earlier!
What's that smoke?
Aghh!
Oh no, it's Kagome!
Wake up, Shippo!
It's me! It's Myoga!
Shippo!
What happened... to me?
I got sleepy from the smoke
from the incense the monk brought.
Aghh!
Miroku! Wake up!
Sango!
Kagome!
No! They're not waking up!
It's that poison!
Poison smoke!
You can't get away from
Mukotsu's poison.
Kagome, hang on!
You're the one who
has the Sacred Jewel shard.
Kagome! Kagome!
Run away!
Shippo...
No, I won't!
I gave you an antidote,
but it didn't work!
That's right!
First, I must put
out the fire.
Something...
Isn't there something?
Huh?!
I'll use the wind from
the Smashing Top.
Fox magic!
Smashing Top!
Agh!
It's having the opposite effect!
Kirara!
You set the temple on fire...
Those flames will send
them to the netherworld.
They were half-dead from
the poison anyway.
Move!
What...!
I cannot let you pass.
Why... you...!
I've been picking up the smell of
dead bodies and graveyard dirt...
You're...
Koga of the Wolf-Demon tribe.
Another strange one!
You!
You must be a pal of
that demon, Kyokotsu.
I pick up the same scent.
Have you come for some
revenge?
Hmm...
I like the waist wrapping.
But... that is just not my taste.
Hey! What's this fool
talking about?
I dunno!
Now I'm gonna
take care of you quick.
Hah! That's my line!
What's that sword?
It's wiggly like a snake!
I'm in a rush, so quit resisting!
You'll make me miss
Inuyasha's death.
What?
Hey! Whaddya mean by that?
What'd you just say about Inuyasha?
Huh? What's your relationship
with Inuyasha?
Forget Inuyasha!
There's a cute girl with him.
She's not in any danger, is she?
Shaddup!
Who cares about a girl...
She's long dead.
What?! You...!
Kirara! Kirara!
Snap out of it!
It's that wound...
I'll move the wooden post
off you!
They've all stopped breathing!
Everyone, wake up!
Please wake up!
It's not working!
That's right! I can't stand
around and cry!
I must be strong!
Until Inuyasha comes,
I'll protect them all.
But...
I don't have the strength
to drag them all out.
What'll I do?!
Use your head!
There has to be a way!
Ummm!
Kagome...
Wait!
I'll be right there!
Give up, Inuyasha.
It's over for your friends.
They'll die from my flames
or from the poison.
Either way, there's no saving them.
Shaddup!
What?!
I must be strong!
Ginkotsu...
I have another trick.
I'll skewer you!
As if I'd let you!
What...!
Arghh!
If you lose your sword,
it's over.
Shaddup!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
What...?!
No you don't!
I don't have time to
waste with you!
Wind Scar!
The temple...
Miroku!
Sango!
Kagome!
Move, you!
Staying to kill me
wasn't worth his time?
How dare he take me lightly!
Still, I've heard enough about
what Naraku is like.
And I now possess the
Sacred Jewel shards.
Well... it'll do for today.
Kagome!
Whoa... that was scary!
It's the first time anyone's
sidestepped my thrust.
This guy's becoming a problem!
Hey!
I don't have time for
a kid like you right now!
But be prepared to die
when we meet again! Fool!
Hey wait, Koga!
He sure doesn't hesitate
to retreat, huh?
Kagome!
Kirara!
Shippo!
l-Inuyasha...
You're alive!
I knew... I knew I had to be strong...
I tried so hard!
I know!
You protected everyone from
the heat with your fox fire.
But... but... but...
Even though I tried so hard...
Everyone stopped breathing!
But everyone stopped breathing!
I messed up! If I had seen through
Renkotsu's true self...
What are you cursing
yourself over, Inuyasha?
Sesshomaru!
After all, you're only a half-demon.
You can barely take
care of yourself...
and yet you wield the Tetsusaiga
which was forged to protect others.
It was impossible
from the start.
Next on Inuyasha: "Inuyasha Shows
His Tears For The First Time"
This is not real!
Open your eyes, Kagome!