Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gather
all the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
A new battle is beginning.
Now, I'm going to return
to my present world and study hard!
That's what I intended,
but what awaited me was a battle
more frightening
than fighting the demons of
the Feudal Era!
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
It's all right for me to go back?
Sure, there's nothing for
you to do here anyway.
Okay then....
Sis!
Welcome home!
Nice to be back.
Welcome back!
You were gone for
some time.
It was hard coming up with
excuses for your school.
But I'm glad you came back safely.
What's the matter?
Tired?
Not really....
Here you are.
A present.
They told me it's a kind of
rare dried food or something.
Oh....
I can't wait to try it.
I'll be resting in my room.
I won't ever leave you again!
You're the type who'd go!
And when you do go,
I'll be upset.
That's to be expected, right?
Kagome...
Maybe I'm getting weary
of all this...
All right!
Huh?
Sis, aren't you eating too much?
I'll be going to school tomorrow
after a long absence.
I need to store up energy.
I think I'll be able to stay here
for a while,
so I'm going to switch gears
and study hard to catch up
in all my classes.
She's raring to go!
Seconds, please!
Certainly!
What?
Nothing.
I'll get a good night's sleep and forget
all about the Feudal Era for a while.
I'm back to what I am...
a junior high school student.
What?!
What's going on?!
Oh, Kagome!
Kagome!
You're well enough to
return to school?
Y-Yeah....
You were absent a long time
this time.
What did you have?
A rare illness that made your ears
cause hallucinations?
Never mind me,
what's going on?
Nothing unusual.
That's right!
Kagome's been absent for
such a long time,
she doesn't know.
You're right.
That's true.
What is it?
It's the cultural festival.
Huh?
Preparations for the cultural festival.
Cultural festival?
But what about classes?
Classes? We're too busy
with all this.
We just have classes
in the morning.
Why did I have to come back
when classes aren't crucial?
Kagome?
I'm going home.
Hey!
Besides, there's no sense in my being
here or there right now.
Why're you so depressed?
Shake it off, Kagome.
C'mon, let's cheer up.
Say, let's sing!
Sing?
Yes, it's energizing!
Right! Kagome, you can participate
in the festival, too!
Huh?
That's right!
We sure need help.
W-What?!
A reserve?
Yes, like a stand-in or substitute.
All right? Do your best.
Fine then. I'll do it.
So, what do you want
me to do?
Sing in the choir.
Sing?
Present the dishes.
Dishes?
Perform on stage.
Stage?
As the heroine's friend,
Brilliant.
Brilliant, huh?
Now which do I do?
- All of them!
- Why?!
- Because you're our reserve.
- And I want you to sing!
We've gone through a lot of practice
and preparation!
But you'll be done with all this
in a few days.
Three duties should be easy!
Okay.
Begin!
Kagome, sing louder.
From the heart.
I want to create
something unique.
I'm good at outdoor cooking.
Like a barbecue?
Grilling river fish over
a wood fire.
Or grilling fern roots
over a wood fire.
Don't say anything. Just keep
your hands moving.
All right.
Now then, we'll start with
Brilliant's line in Act 2.
Ever since my grandfather collapsed
from lumbago, I've been....
No, no!
Outstretch your arms
and be more appealing....
Once more.
My grandfather collapsed
from lumbago....!
How does it taste?
It's not bad, if I do say so.
Then I wanna taste, too!
I'm home.
Sis is back.
Huh?
What happened to all
that energy you gathered up?
I used it all up in one day.
Were your studies that hard?
Even studying would've
been better.
Kagome, this is good.
The dried food you brought
back is perfect with sake!
I see. I'm glad.
Naraku's tried to use
Kagome's eyes?
Yes. To use her to
find the Sacred Jewel shards.
Which means Naraku doesn't know
the whereabouts
of all the Jewel shards?
Yes. And the fact that he went through
the trouble of kidnapping Kagome,
must signify that there are shards which
Naraku himself cannot find alone.
Like which shards?
Probably the ones
in hard-to-find locations.
And that means he's having
a hard time, too.
So you've come, Naraku.
I heard you coming
from four leagues away.
Oh? Then that will
make this quick.
Mimisenri, they say that you possess
ears that are able to hear
all things in this world.
You are right, Naraku. And I have
heard rumors about you, too.
Do you intend to take my ears
and make them part of you?
Rest assured.
Your filthy body doesn't
interest me at all.
Then why have you come
all the way here?
Have you heard of the
whereabouts of the Sacred Jewel shards?
Hmm.... According to the demons,
Naraku, you possess nearly
all of the shards.
Just one. I need just
one more shard.
But its whereabouts has
eluded even me.
I see....
Then let me use my ears.
All our shards are now
in Naraku's possession.
Other than those, Koga has
two in his legs.
And there's one which
keeps Kohaku alive.
Sango....
If Naraku succeeds in
completing the Sacred Jewel,
Kohaku will die.
Don't worry, Sango.
We won't let Naraku succeed, ever.
Inuyasha....
We'll find the remaining shards.
Uh-huh, that's what I intend
to do, too.
Inuyasha....
I know there's no need
to remind you....
but you must be more
diligent about Kagome.
So that she never falls
into Naraku's hands again.
I know that!
Hey! What're you eating there
all by yourself?
This?
The villagers and mountain priests
we saved recently?
They gave it to me in gratitude.
Some of their dried food.
Sheesh!
We Demon Slayers keep warning them
not to do it, but it's useless.
What do you mean?
No, Kirara.
These are demons.
What?
This is a hypha of a fungal
demon called Shironyudo.
But they're safe to eat?
Yeah, it's safe.
But if you put it in water
and heat it....
Meaning, if you boil it?
A new Shironyudo is born.
Is that what that was?
Well, I prefer that they be
thrown out.
It was so tasty.
That's why they're such a nuisance.
Forget about the dried food!
In any case, finding the Sacred Jewel
shard will solve everything.
Yes, that was the start
of it all.
Wherever Naraku is hiding,
he's sure to appear where
the Sacred Jewel shard is!
All right, next pitch.
Huh?
I'm sorry, Ayumi.
I caught a cold.
Huh?!
I'm so sorry!
It's all right. It can't be helped.
- Kagome!
- Huh?
You'll sing her alto solo.
What?! What solo?
Okay?
Hand me that tape, will you?
Here!
Thank you.
Maki, are you all right?
It hurts!
Take her to the infirmary.
- How is she?
- She has a sprained ankle.
She won't be able to
move around for a while.
- Brilliant....
- Huh? Yes?
From this moment, you are
no longer Brilliant,
but Escargot Pudding,
the female lead!
What?!
Now let's continue with rehearsals!
Escargot, get on stage.
That's...!
Isn't that terrible of
both of them?!
This isn't being a reserve!
Right?
It's no good. There aren't
any good recipes.
Honestly!
Isn't there something that
packs a punch....?
Something with impact?
That no one has tasted?
- Nope.
- Then can you find one?
What?
I....
I have individual practice
for the choir.
- Then I have stage rehearsals.
- I'm counting on you!
Don't count on me!!!
You've really recovered, Kagome.
Hojo....
I hear you've taken on
a lot of work.
Not "taken on"!
Forced to!
At first, it was just
helping out.
Then it got more and more....
You haven't been back
in a while,
so everyone wants to give you
a big role in the festival.
- Think so?
- Yes.
Say, Hojo, do you know
any unusual dishes?
I'm not really into cooking....
I guess I have to depend
on Mom.
- Oh!
- What is it?
I think I have an idea.
Say, Kagome....
Now that you're playing
the heroine,
we'll have quite a lot
of scenes together.
So how about we practice
together?
Huh?
Kagome?
I'm back!
Here it is!
Sorry, Grandpa.
I, Escargot Pudding, will
neither run nor hide!
Great!
What's this?
Something that packs a punch
and has impact....
yet is not familiar to anyone.
I'm off.
Yeah, we need to start looking
for the Sacred Jewel shards.
Got that right. Kagome takes her
sweet time when we leave her alone.
Hey Inuyasha, ask Kagome for
more ninja food!
He's so impatient.
These dried foods are tasty,
but a bit tough.
Maybe I can boil it.
Oh? A festival....
Hmm.... The economy, huh?
Huh?!
Oh, it's been a long time.
What're you doing?!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
What's wrong?
So that was the Shironyudo
Sango mentioned.
Where's the rest?
Rest of what?
The rest of the dried food!
Oh, the one in the pot is
the last of it.
I ate the rest.
That's okay then.
Oh, welcome!
Inuyasha, did you come
to have some fun?
I'm not here for fun!
But you'll have dinner with
us, won't you?
Wait just a bit.
Huh?
Sure.
I'm home!
You're here!
Hey! We're goin' back
after we eat.
Hold on a minute!
You never said anything about
my returning early.
Shaddup! You know we can't
find the shards without you!
Really?
'Course!
Is that all?
Huh? Whaddya mean?
Forget it.
I feel like my old self again.
I felt like seeing you....
Got a problem with that?
Nope.
Boy, you're selfish, Inuyasha.
I'm sorry, but I can't go back
just yet.
Huh? It's not another one of
those "tests"?
No. A cultural festival.
Cultural festival?
Sis, what're you doing?
Oh, this and that.
Singing in the choir, cooking,
performing on stage.
Can family members come
to watch?
Sure.
Then we'll all go.
You don't have to.
No! I must see
my granddaughter perform!
- Hey, can I go?
- No!
Why not?
Because! Imagine the uproar if
people find out about you?
Hah!
I have a lot to do, so I'm going.
Let's get ready, too.
I'm so excited.
I'd better dress up for this.
Oh yes, my suit....
Inuyasha and Kagome are
taking a long time.
Gee, it's tough.
Fox fire!
It smells so yummy!
What is it?
Hiraikotsu!
Are you okay?
A demon in an area
populated by humans?
That was a reconstituted demon
of a Kurotengudake fungi.
A demon fungi?
We're going to get rid of all
the dried food we received.
You still had them?
Geez.... They're so tasty, too.
Shironyudo, Kurotengudake,
Yumenamazu, Waraiazami,
Hamadaruma, Kamitsuki-suika,
and the Esedaikoku....
You had so many!
Is this all?
Kagome took the rest.
- Kagome?
- Back home?!
Well, Inuyasha is with her.
You're right. It'll be fine since
Inuyasha is there.
But I heard that Inuyasha can't
really do as he pleases
when he's in Kagome's country.
'Scuse me!
Okay then, let's put the baked goods
out on the table.
On the day of the Cultural Festival,
the Home Economy classroom
is in a shambles!
Darn it.
That's the demon Kurotengudake!
Demons terrorize the school!
Where did they come from?!
I'll exterminate them with
Higurashi Shrine sutras!
Kagome, you have an important
presentation to make!
I'm scared, but I'll help too!
This is it!
Prepare to die, demons!
On the next Inuyasha:
"Battle Against the Dried-Up Demons
at the Cultural Festival!"
What're you doing, Hojo?!
They're for real!