Well then, I'm going back home.
Did you hear, Inuyasha?
Be quiet, will ya?
Just go already!
Every time you return,
you two get into some argument.
Granny Kaede,
please take care of the rest.
Inuyasha,
are you just going to let her go?!
Who cares!
Inuyasha you fool!
I only stopped the fight because
I was worried about your injury.
Kagome!
Shippo!
Please be patient, Kagome.
Inuyasha always gets jealous over you.
Kagome, you're my woman.
Inuyasha is small-minded.
That's why he takes Koga's
words so seriously.
He's a pitiful fool who is
actually very insecure.
And because he's so in love with you...
Thank you, Shippo.
I'm just going back to get
more medicine and bandages.
I'll be right back.
But don't tell Inuyasha that.
Sometimes,
it's good to make him worry.
Oh! I understand.
Kagome, please return quickly.
Uh-huh.
Naraku... what do you want?
Sharp as usual, Kikyo.
How could I not notice you?
Not only today, you've come
to spy on me countless times.
You seem to be quite
concerned about me, Naraku.
What's so funny?
Naraku... You can't help but
be concerned about me.
Because...
Onigumo's heart beats strong
within you.
He's gone.
I'm back.
Kagome.
Sis!
Oh, welcome back!
Do you want to eat?
Or do you want a bath?
A bath.
You look so tired.
- I'll run your bath right now.
- Thanks.
Now, now... put down your bag.
I can't believe that was a conversation
between a mother and a daughter.
More like a husband who's been away
on assignment and his wife.
Uh-huh.
Kagome, how long are you staying
this time?
I'll take a nap, then leave.
Oh, Sota...
can you get me the
bandages and antibiotics?
Okay.
Oh... A bed is sooo nice.
I'll make sure that Inuyasha
worries a little bit.
Naraku... You can't help but
be concerned about me.
Because...
Onigumo's heart beats
strong within you.
A woman like that
can be killed off anytime.
But the reason I can't...
is that because within me
still beats...
the heart of that Onigumo
who so coveted Kikyo?
Onigumo's heart...
That shallow, evil criminal...
He was unable to move...
yet he yearned for Kikyo
so much...
that he offered his body to
countless demons...
to be reborn as Naraku.
That foolish human's heart
still yearns for Kikyo...
and it still beats inside me...Naraku.
Ludicrous!
You belittle me, Kikyo.
I, Naraku, am not Onigumo!
Now that I have the Sacred Jewel
nearly whole...
I find Onigumo's heart useless
and unnecessary.
What is that dark cloud?
It's been hovering over the temple
for a while now.
It seems ominous.
Those lights...lost souls.
It's devouring the lost souls.
What is that?!
Naraku...is coming after me.
Priestess Kikyo, what's wrong?
I need to borrow your horse.
Priestess Kikyo!
That demon...does he intend to eat
all the lost souls in this region?!
I will not allow it!
No! It took lost souls from me!
Not again!
Why you...!
Miroku, how is your wound?
Does it still hurt?
It's much better now.
Thanks to the care you
and Kaede have given me.
But Naraku has many incarnations.
You're talking about
Juromaru and Kageromaru?
Yes...
The fourth incarnation,
Juromaru, the younger sibling.
Fighting is his only volition.
He won't even heed Naraku's orders.
Even though the Naraku that was
handling him was a demon puppet...
Juromaru ruthlessly chopped off
Naraku's head.
Even Naraku seemed to have
trouble controlling him.
Alongwith Kageromaru, the oldersibling,
who hides inside Juromaru.
They were both brutal...
and so mysterious.
We don't know what kind of
enemy will attack next.
We must be even more careful.
Say Inuyasha... aren't you going to
call Kagome back?
Shaddup! We're better off without her!
Well then,
can you stop your fidgeting?
It's really irritating.
Kagome is so patient
in dealing with you.
I couldn't agree more!
I'm just going back
for more bandages and medicine.
I'll be right back.
But don't tell Inuyasha that.
It's good to make him worry sometimes.
I promised Kagome.
I'll keep quiet.
No matter how you look at it,
Koga's love is one-sided.
No need to be so nervous.
What a bother!
Listening to you all talk,
it's as though it's all my fault!
I won't apologize! Not me!
Stupid Kagome!
Just 'cuz you didn't come
back right away...
I'm getting all the blame.
What'd I do anyway?
Kagome,
are you angry with me, after all?
I wonder what she's doing now...
A demon's scent!
W- what's that?!
A giant soul collector?!
K-Kikyo!
Inuyasha...
Kikyo!
You're badly hurt!
What happened?!
Poison insects?
Is this another one of
Naraku's tricks?!
W-where is?
He plans to get rid of Kikyo!
I won't allow it!
As if I'd allow Naraku
to kill Kikyo!
Kikyo... I'll take care of that demon
right away.
So stay quiet here.
Demon!
My coming here...
is your death sentence!
Die!
Take this!
Without the souls of the dead,
you cannot stay alive... Kikyo.
Kikyo!
Inuyasha?
Why are you here?
That's my line.
The demon came after me.
And you came here hoping
that I'd save you.
Don't be a fool, Inuyasha!
I kept running desperately
and found myself here.
Kikyo?
It's night already!
Why didn't anyone wake me?!
You were still asleep?
Fifty years...
What? What are you thinking?
We haven't changed at all
since fifty years ago.
Silly words... I have changed.
Since that time
I sealed you against this tree.
Because of Naraku's deception,
we hated each other...
and I was sealed here
on this tree for fifty years...
and you died.
Kikyo, tell me, have I changed then?
Before I knew of Naraku's existence,
I did resent you.
But you told me
that my life was yours.
Well then, your life...
is mine.
You're no different
from Naraku, after all.
I'm the same... as Naraku?
Inside Naraku...
Onigumo's heart still beats.
Onigumo's heart?!
That evil man desired me.
Killing you with my own hands...
was something that the jealous heart
of Onigumo schemed.
Jealous?!
Over something so ridiculous?!
Yes... ridiculous!
That is what humans are.
Onigumo's heart remains
inside Naraku?
Wait, Kikyo...
Then does Naraku care about you?
He doesn't want to acknowledge it.
But there's a lingering feeling for me.
And he's trying to erase that
feeling by getting rid of me.
Enough, Inuyasha.
I have replenished myself
with lost souls.
Kikyo... You...
You aren't planning to destroy
Naraku alone, are you?!
You can't!
Naraku is in love with you?!
I can't stand the thought!
There!
I'm so late! Oh well...
I guess Inuyasha would
have calmed down...
What are those lights?
Inuyasha and Kikyo?
Why? What's going on?
What happened in my absence?
I don't care how you feel
about me now!
I will not let Naraku have you!
Only I can protect you from Naraku!
What?! Are you... crazy?!
Let me go!
I will be the one to slay Naraku!
So... you don't have to fight anymore.
I will protect you.
Inuyasha...
Kikyo...
Kikyo!
Men are such fools.
They believe that as long
as they embrace a woman...
she belongs to them.
- Kikyo?
- Don't move!
Watching you now,
I realize that so well.
As long as Onigumo's heart
exists inside Naraku...
there will be an opportunity.
I will use that chance to purify Naraku
and totally destroy him.
Kikyo...
Kikyo!
Once the thread of fate is tangled,
it cannot be undone.
Kikyo!
Envy...
A human emotion from the heart
of that simpering fool Onigumo.
Despicable!
Those lights...
Lost souls.
My sister Kikyo...is she nearby?
Kagome! Were you watching?
Inuyasha is looking straight at me.
How? How can he not avert his eyes?
Inuyasha has sworn to protect Kikyo.
I can't stay by him anymore.
So I ran back to the present world.
But I still have a fragment
of the Sacred Jewel.
I should return it to
the Feudal Era...
but if I return it...
then it will really mean
the end.
I stand in front of the sacred tree
where I first met Inuyasha.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Back to Where We First Met"
Don't miss it!