Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
The frightening bird master, Princess Abi,
sends her demon birds to attack the village.
But the holy one, St. Hijiri,
stands in her way.
St. Hijiri, who was able to break through
Hakudoshi's barrier with a single arrow...
Could the true identity
of this person... be Kikyo?!
This arrow....
Inuyasha's Red Tetsusaiga could
not break through Hakudoshi's barrier,
yet this arrow did...
Only one person is
capable of that...
Kikyo... is alive!
It's not Kikyo.
Huh?
No one said anything.
But you're all thinking it.
Even I wondered the
same thing.
However....
I don't get Kikyo's scent
from this arrow.
It's different....
What is this smell?
In any case, it's not the smell
of any of our allies.
Not the smell of
an ally?
Thinking about
what you said....
when that arrow was shot,
I didn't sense Kikyo's
spiritual powers.
Then....
who was it?
That arrow helped Inuyasha.
Perhaps it was a friendly hand
lent by St. Hijiri.
That's right.
That could be it.
St. Hijiri...
We must hurry to
this St. Hijiri.
The birds must be
headed that way, too.
St. Hijiri, we are almost
at the village.
I hope they were
able to hold out.
Everyone, do not move.
W-Will we really be safe?
Won't they break through?
When will St. Hijiri return?
Hah! A barrier?
Such insolence!
Quite strong for something
erected by humans.
Then I'll force them
to come out.
Go!
Aghh! The birds are aflame!
We're surrounded by fire!
We'll be burned alive!
I can't take it anymore!
This side's not burning.
Huh?! Let's make a run for it!
Do not leave the barrier.
St. Hijiri has returned!
Please save us!
The one who erected
the barrier...
Slay him!
Huh?!
We're saved!
My birds....are gone!
Damn! What's going on?!
Ever since Naraku came
into the picture,
I've had nothing but
interference!
S-She's gone!
It's the power of
St. Hijiri!
Thank you!
You saved us, St. Hijiri!
We passed the summit.
We should reach St. Hijiri's
village soon.
When we reach the village,
we may learn St. Hijiri's identity.
There it is.
Yeah!
I smell blood and
something burning.
What?
It's coming from around
that craggy mountain.
Let's hurry!
This is....!
St. Hijiri exterminated them.
We're so grateful.
He wiped out a whole flock
of birds with a single arrow.
A single arrow?
And where is this
St. Hijiri?
St. Hijiri has left
this area.
Huh?
He said he would find the
birds' nest and destroy them all.
We are ever so thankful.
Seems we just missed him.
Inuyasha....
Should we go after him?
After this St. Hijiri?
It could be Kikyo, you know.
Kagome....
Inuyasha...
Kikyo... was killed by Naraku.
But...
I didn't see Kikyo die.
Nor did I see her body.
But Kikyo... if you are alive,
why haven't you shown
yourself to me?
Kagome....
Kagome is so brave.
How is she able to
speak up like that....?
You mean, about Kikyo?
If St. Hijiri turns out
to be Kikyo,
we're sure to cross paths
at some point.
If her aim is to find
the birds' nest.
Yes, but....
Inuyasha becomes so indecisive
whenever he sees her....
And each time, Kagome
has forgiven him.
If it were me, I'd push him
over some cliff,
and make him a cripple.
Are you talking about me?
She's serious!
Kagome, you okay with this?
With what?
Besides, what about you?
If St. Hijiri turns out
to be Kikyo....
I dunno....
Huh....
He's so honest.
But....
But if that's true....
it'll mean that Naraku failed
to kill Kikyo.
And that means...
he'll come and try to
kill her once more.
In any case, we'll just
concentrate on
finding the birds' nest and
destroying them.
Yes.
Damn! Just who are you....?
to be able to break
through my barrier?
Such a stubborn kid!
Huh?!
Am I really seeing this?!
No, this kid...
I can hear his heart,
but he's hollow
inside.
Is his heart...
somewhere else?
Mistress Kaede!
Terrible news!
What is it?
Well....
What?! Is that true?
Yes!
And where did you see
this suspicious light?
We just saw it
falling from the sky....
towards our lady Kikyo's shrine.
What?!
There it is!
Huh?
W-What....
Demons?
Mistress Kaede,
what were they?!
Hmm.... They weren't demons.
They were probably shikigami
messengers sent by someone.
I did not sense any
evil aura from them.
Mistress Kaede!
Huh?
Take a look at this!
What is it?
It looks like they
dug here.
What?!
Once before, Kikyo's ashes
and dirt from her grave were taken.
Not again!
Who would take soil from
Sister Kikyo's grave?!
For what purpose?
Naraku's demons?
They seem to be
looking for something.
Uh-huh....
Probably looking
for St. Hijiri....
You're right. For Naraku,
he poses a problem.
So Naraku realizes this
as well?
That St. Hijiri may
be Kikyo...
If so...
Does he intend to find her
and kill her again?
St. Hijiri....
We've heard rumors.
We heard that he
was seen hereabouts.
I dunno....
But it could be a
sign from him.
Just before dawn, two
strange streaks of light
appeared in the sky.
And they were sucked
into the forbidden mountain.
"Forbidden"?
Yeah.... Only the selected
may enter.
Shall we go, Inuyasha?
Yeah.... Besides, we have
nothing else to go on.
Weren't we looking for
the birds' nest?
Huh?
Somewhere along the way,
that goal seems to have changed
to meeting this St. Hijiri.
Shippo, don't say things like
that in front of Kagome.
Kagome probably noticed
that already.
It's that mountain.
Inuyasha, something
is sparkling....
Water maybe?
Yeah, could be a waterfall.
Demons....
They're looking for St. Hijiri.
Inuyasha, have you
noticed them?
You mean Naraku's demons?
Yeah.
They're following us, huh?
Or....
There're more and more of them!
It seems they're all heading
toward the forbidden mountain.
Does that mean Kikyo is there?
What the.!
A sacred arrow!
So, St. Hijiri is here
in this mountain!
Let's go!
T-They're coming from below!
Hiraikotsu!
Move!
This is no good!
Miroku! Sango!
Take care of Kagome!
Huh?
Go on ahead, everyone!
Inuyasha, what're you....!
Isn't it obvious?!
After I destroy these vermin,
I'll follow you!
Go and find this St. Hijiri!
Huh?
Go on!
Kirara!
Inuyasha!
Is it okay for us to
see him first?
If St. Hijiri is really Kikyo...
I don't know...
what I'll do.
But...
Wind Scar!
I have to meet him and
see for myself...
Or I won't be able
to get on with my life.
Is that Kikyo?
I don't get Kikyo's
scent from him.
But...
Your face! Let me see your face!
I wonder if Inuyasha will be okay?
He'll come after us
as soon as he's done.
She's right.
Inuyasha is the one
who most wants to meet St. Hijiri.
Sango!
More demons!
Kagome, Shippo....
Stay here!
Uh-huh!
Kirara!
Hiraikotsu!
K-Kagome....
l-I'm with you!
Uh-huh!
I must be strong!
K-Kagome....demons!
Huh?
What's that?!
Soul Collectors!
K-Kagome!
Where are you going?
So Kikyo really is...
Kagome!
I'm going after them!
Kikyo may be there!
Wait! Don't be so hasty!
S-She disappeared!
A barrier....
Answer! Are you Kikyo or not?
A potent aura has
ravaged her flesh.
Her body cannot
be restored to its original form.
She also lost her voice.
She fights with her
spirit alone.
However....
soon her strength
will run out.
Back then...
She didn't die?
Kikyo!
You are Kikyo!
Huh?!
Kikyo!
Huh?
This is....
A paper doll?
Damn that Kikyo
is elusive!
Kagura!
What's going on?!
That's my question.
Sending me on
a fool's errand!
Is Kikyo alive?!
Hmm....
At least Naraku thinks so.
The arrow that broke
through Hakudoshi's barrier
had dirt from Onigumo's
cave on its arrowhead.
Huh? Onigumo....?
So that was the scent
from that arrow...
The soil there is infused
with Onigumo's longing for Kikyo.
And that protects Kikyo
from Naraku.
Kikyo is the only one who
can benefit from Onigumi's dirt.
In any case, we've been
chasing around after a fake.
See ya!
Naraku's most troublesome hindrance
is still alive...
Hah... this is starting
to get very interesting.
Those two have also disappeared....
Is Kikyo really...
Kikyo... is alive somewhere.
Are they calling to me?
Huh?!
A waterfall....
Kikyo...!
When I was alone at
the base of the mountain,
I met St. Hijiri!
It was actually a
paper doll controlled by Kikyo.
The real Kikyo is submerged
underwater....
Is she alive?
Or....
Please choose....
if you will save her or not.
You are the only one
who can save her.
Right now, you hold....
her life in your hands.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kagome's Instinctive Choice"
Only I can save her?
That's why you're telling
me to choose?