- I win!
- I lose!
Fool! This is not a race!
Look Master Jaken!
Just as Lord Sesshomaru said,
there's a dead demon!
My goodness, who could have...
It was Inuyasha.
Lord Sesshomaru.
Although... I don't think he got
away unscathed either.
I can smell it
on this demon's fangs...
The scent of Tetsusaiga.
Just as I thought...
these fangs broke Tetsusaiga apart.
- Let us go.
- Are you taking that?
Silence, Rin.
You make too much noise.
All right!
I knew immediately
what happened here...
by the smell in the wind, but...
one thing - what was it?
The smell of Inuyasha's blood changed.
That's right - it was not the smell
of a half-demon.
It was the same smell as my blood
and our father's.
When Tetsusaiga was broken in two,
I thought I was gonna die.
When I said to myself
I didn't want to die...
my body started to get hot.
And before I realized it,
I had killed Goshinki.
At that time, I felt something
I never felt before...
something strange.
I only felt pleasure at
tearing apart Goshinki.
Here.
It's ready.
Let's eat.
Yeah...
What's the matter?
Moping over some broken sword!
My fish!
This is the bull that belongs to Totosai,
the swordsmith who forged Tetsusaiga.
Only his bull?
Master Inuyasha!
Old Myoga!
Myoga! So you were
hiding out at Totosai's?
How rude you are!
You ran away to him.
You ran away.
Never mind that.
Master Inuyasha...
What happened to Tetsusaiga?
Oh... no!!
This demon called Goshinki
bit it in two.
I knew it.
I came when I noticed that the scent of
Master Inuyasha's blood had changed.
Master Inuyasha, you must take
the pieces of the sword...
and go to Master Totosai.
Does that mean the Tetsusaiga
can be repaired?
Yes!
That bull will take you to
Totosai.
Now hurry!
Well, see ya!
Master Inuyasha really transformed?
Yes.
Does that have anything to do
with Tetsusaiga being broken?
Yes.
You know the Tetsusaiga is an heirloom
left to Master Inuyasha by his father.
Besides protecting Master Inuyasha
from his enemies...
it also serves to keep the demon
side of him sealed.
Seal the demon side of him?
The Tetsusaiga being broken means
Inuyasha will die.
Yet the strong desire to live...
awakened the demon's blood
which flows through him.
Once awakened, even if
the Tetsusaiga is repaired...
that part of him will be
harder to control.
He has tasted the pleasure of
slaying an enemy.
Does that mean Inuyasha's heart
is becoming a demon's?
Y-you!
Inuyasha...
Oh you... are such a fool!
Look what you did to
my dear, dear Tetsusaiga.
Will you shaddup?!
Instead of bawling,
hurry and fix my sword, old fool!
You young punk!
You think it's so easy!
Can't you fix it?
You're speaking to Totosai!
I can put it back in three days
and three nights.
However, I need something
to bond it with.
Bond?
Inuyasha, open your mouth.
Like this?
Well, I guess this fang will do.
What're you doing?!
Silence! Your fang will
grow back in half a day!
Damn you are such a pain in the neck!
Make sure you bring it to me
fixed in three days!
Why three days?
You just said you can fix it in
three days and three nights!
Cripes! I'm counting on ya, old man!
See ya!
All right... you can look forward to it.
Who are you?
You are Kaijinbo?
Because you created too many
deviant swords...
you were banished by your
master, Totosai.
Totosai, huh?
Haven't heard that name
in quite a while...
but it still makes my blood boil.
Well, Kaijinbo?
Would you like to forge a sword
out of that demon's fangs?
Don't joke!
No way can I make a sword
out of something that's dead!
Is Lord Sesshomaru going to use
the Tenseiga, the sword of healing?
I can see...
the messengers from the
netherworld.
Wow, this is totally different
from earlier!
Kaijinbo, let me tell you.
This sword, the Tenseiga, was forged
by the master who banished you.
And the fangs of that demon...
broke the Tetsusaiga, a sword
also forged by Totosai.
Amazing. These fangs will make
a most powerful sword!
Tetsusaiga should be repaired
by tomorrow.
But this all happened at such
a bad time.
The night of the new moon.
Damn it all! Totosai is late!
He's just like a human.
You didn't know, Sango?
I only heard about it,
and it's the first time I'm seeing it.
Half-demons like Inuyasha
have one night...
when they lose their demon powers
and become mere mortals.
See, he doesn't have fangs, either.
Interesting, huh?
Miroku, you're having fun with this,
aren't you?
You figured it out?
If attacked by an enemy on this night,
he can be killed.
Hence, the night of new moon
when Inuyasha...
Ioses his demon powers
must be kept strictly secret!
So how do you know about it?
Shippo, you!
Stop, Inuyasha!
You blabbermouth!
Stop! I didn't mean any harm!
You better not have
intended harm!
Damn!
How come more and more people
know about my secret?
That's okay.
It means you have more
people concerned about you.
Still when I turn mortal...
I can't stand this feeling
of unease.
When I become a full-fledged demon,
it'll be good riddance to these feelings.
Inuyasha!
But if I become a full-fledged demon...
Kagome and the others will be...
Here.
Don't stray too far from us tonight.
Hah! Be quiet!
Even I have times when
I want to think by myself.
W-what?!
Inuyasha, do you still want to
become a full-fledged demon?
I...
I was scared that time.
What're you saying!?
If I hadn't transformed that time...
you'd all have been killed
by that Goshinki!
I don't mean that.
It's not the face that changed,
or how scared I felt.
Was I that scary-looking?
I just... felt like your heart was
beyond my reach.
That you were going to forget
about me... and that scared me.
That time...
when I transformed...
My heart was...
Are you crazy?
No matter what happens,
I'm still me!
I wouldn't forget about you
or Miroku and the others.
Don't ever forget.
Please, Inuyasha!
Kaijinbo!
It's been three days!
Have you forged a sword from
the demon's fangs?
It's done!
A magnificent demon sword!
This must be Kaijinbo's doing.
I was slain by Kaijinbo!
I knew it!
Let's go, Jaken.
Hurry and put your body back.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Did you perhaps use Tenseiga
to bring me back to life?
Who else besides me
is capable of such a thing?
No one... Lord Sesshomaru!
Did Kaijinbo finish the sword?
Y-yes, he did.
Kaijinbo claimed that he
had forged the demon sword.
But his eyes looked so strange.
Like... Like he was possessed
by the sword.
Hmm... I see.
Inuyasha, why don't you get
some sleep?
Miroku...
Just leave me alone!
I never sleep
when I take on the human form!
Are you too scared to sleep?
W-what?!
Oh, I'm so scared!
So what?!
Good to be honest.
I have a lot of enemies.
If I'm attacked when I'm like this,
I don't have a chance.
Well, it's a good lesson for you.
Miroku, do you sense it?
A very powerful aura.
Which one of you is Inuyasha!?
Who are you?!
I am Kaijinbo.
A master swordsmith.
Swordsmith?
This sword which I forged
named Tokijin...
is crying for a taste of
the blood of Inuyasha.
This swordsmith,
why is he after me?
Hmm... so you are Inuyasha?
This sword has told me so.
D-damn...
Why, I thought you were some demon.
But you're just a mortal.
Inuyasha, can you think of any
reason why he begrudges you?
None...
Heard that?
As I told you,
this sword wants to kill you.
This Tokijin was forged from
the fangs of the demon...
who broke the Tetsusaiga,
the sword created by old Totosai.
Made from the fangs of Goshinki...
the demon who broke
the Tetsusaiga in half!
So it's a sword filled with the
hate of Goshinki.
I'm tired of listening to
your jabbering!
Just come and attack, Kaijinbo!
I'll turn you into mincemeat!
Stay back, Inuyasha!
Let me and Sango handle this!
There's no way you can win,
the way you are now.
Inuyasha, bear with it!
Hiraikotsu!
Where are you aiming?
The Hiraikotsu!
Useless.
Without a doubt, it is
a formidable sword.
Well then... I have no choice!
Heaven's punishment!
He did it!
I thought the Wind Tunnel was
Miroku's only legitimate weapon, but...
he has spiritual powers.
Watch out, Miroku!
Tokijin... you are amazing!
The ultimate sword!
The enemy is not Kaijinbo...
it's the sword!
Playtime's over.
His head is split in two,
yet he's acting as if nothing happened!
It's almost like...
he's being controlled by
Tokijin the sword!
Come at me, Inuyasha!
Or are you so afraid that
you can't move?
Hiding meekly by the girl and child!
Inuyasha, don't be lured
by those words!
Hah! I'm not that stupid!
However...
it's me that he's come after.
I will not hide nor run!
Inuyasha!
He's such a simpleton!
Totosai!
Is Tetsusaiga repaired?
Oh dear... I wondered what all
the noise was about.
Totosai, you're late!
Give it here!
No, Master Inuyasha!
Old Myoga!
Tetsusaiga will not transform...
when wielded by a human who
has lost his demon powers.
Kaijinbo, it's been a long time.
Are you still alive, Totosai?!
You've crafted yet another
awful sword.
What is that evil aura?
Totosai...
I'll show you who is the
better swordsmith.
Master Totosai!
You know Kaijinbo?
Yes, he's a former pupil...
One I banished long ago.
He killed ten children in order
to create a sword.
He smothered the blade with
human blood and oil...
in order to make it
seethe with hatred.
Draw your sword, Inuyasha!
I'll crush that sword before the
very eyes of old Totosai!
No sense going easy on you!
Totosai! You'd better have made the
Tetsusaiga even stronger than before!
A little.
That won't do!
That sword is made from the fangs of
the demon that broke the Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha!
This is it for you!
I'm relieved, Tetsusaiga.
You seem to be a bit
more powerful.
It's not broken!
Of course not.
But Inuyasha is...
Hah! Before the sword breaks,
your body will break.
Too bad, Kaijinbo.
I'll admit that sword of yours
is pretty strong...
But you're not good enough
to handle it.
You should've killed me
in one sweep.
Before this happened!
He's transforming!
Dawn is breaking!
I'm gonna test the Tetsusaiga's
new blade on you!
Totosai! What'd you do
to my Tetsusaiga?!
Answer, Totosai!
What'd you do to the Tetsusaiga!?
Hmmm? You having problems?
Shaddup!
It's super heavy! What'd you do?!
Oh, that's from the fang I used
as a bond.
Don't worry about it.
Hah! No use having a sword
you can't even hold!
I'll slice you in half along
with your sword!
Raise your sword or you'll die!
How can you be so unreasonable?!
D-damn!
Tokijin, a sword filled with
Goshinki's hatred...
possesses the swordsmith Kaijinbo.
With unusual powers,
it attacks Inuyasha.
Then the true owner appears!
As though trying to test something...
Sesshomaru, Inuyasha's brother,
turns Tokijin on Inuyasha.
Kagura, Naraku's incarnation,
approaches Sesshomaru.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Sesshomaru Wields Tokijin!"
Don't miss it!