It's Inuyasha!
That'll teach you!
With this in my possession...
I can become
a real demon!
Inuyasha!
Ki... Kikyo!
Why, you!
Sister!
Lady Kikyo!
She's badly wounded.
Sister... How did you get hurt?
My cowardliness...
has resulted in this.
And all for this...
"Jewel of the Four Souls."
Sister, we must tend
to your injury!
I am beyond saving.
So listen to me, Kaede.
Take the Sacred Jewel...
and burn it with my body.
It must never get into
the hands of evil-doers!
Sister!
The Sacred Jewel...
I will take it with me
to the other world.
A sacred jewel?
Yes!
This jewel will bring happiness
and prosperity without fail!
You're selling this marble thing?
Keychain charms are out of style!
It's no ordinary keychain!
The ball at the end is
the Sacred Jewel...
This shrine's... Huh?
Now heed this, Kagome.
The origin of this shrine's
Sacred Jewel...
Huh?
The origin of this Sacred Jewel is...
Hey Gramps! Remember what
day tomorrow is?
Oh, how could I forget my dear
granddaughter's birthday?
A present for me?!
The mummified hand of a water imp
is sure to bring happiness.
In fact, the origin of that is...
Have a snack, Buyo.
No, don't give it away!
"Origin." Origin, huh?
My family has been the caretaker
of a shrine for generations.
Now then, the origin of
these pickled vegetables is...
They're donations from
a shrine-visitor, right?
Huh!?
The thousand-year-old sacred tree.
The legend of the Hidden Well.
Everything has some origin.
I've been told the stories
countless times.
Yet I never paid any
attention to them.
Until today...when I turned fifteen.
Kagome! Phone call!
The review notes?
Sure, I'll bring them today.
I know!
I'm off!
Huh? Sota?
Sis...
You're not supposed
to play around here.
But Buyo...
Did he go into the Hidden Well?
Buyo!
I think he's at the bottom.
Why don't you go down?
This place gives me
the creeps.
Such a scaredy cat!
Be a man!
Something's down there!
Yeah, the cat!
Aw, man...
That sound?
From inside the well?
Buyo!
You scared me!
Don't scream so loud, Sis!
Watch it! I'm down here
'cause you're scared!
Sis!
Huh?!
Such joy!
I can feel my strength returning!
My body is coming
to life again!
You have it, don't you?
Don't you?
Let me go!
You're disgusting!
Let me go, I said!
You little!
You won't escape from me!
The Sacred Jewel!
The Sacred Jewel?
Huh?
Am I inside the well?
Was that a dream?
It wasn't a dream!
I gotta get out!
Sota! Are you there?
Get Gramps!
That kid! He ran away!
Huh?
Where's this?
I know I fell into the
well at the shrine, but...
Gramps! Mom?
Gramps! Mom!
Sota... Buyo...
The shrine is gone.
The Sacred Tree!
What a relief!
I'm close to home!
A boy?
Hey, what're you doing?
These...
aren't human ears.
I want to touch them...
Though maybe I
shouldn't be doing that.
You there!
What're you up to?!
Hey! Why am I tied up?!
A young girl in
strange clothing.
From a foreign land?
Will there be war again?
Just before rice-planting season?
We're so short-handed as it is!
Perhaps she's a fox
in disguise?
Better a shape-changer
than another war.
Topknots...topknots...
All of them have topknots!
Where is this place?!
Make way for
High Priestess Kaede!
Great. Here comes
ANOTHER weirdo.
Hey! What're you doing?!
They told me a demon was
found in the Inuyasha Forest.
I thought some ritual
purification was in order.
Then could she be
a foreign spy?
Yes, but to spy on what?!
We can barely feed
ourselves in this village.
You there. Let me take a
good look at your face.
Look clever, girl!
You!
Such a likeness...
to my sister Kikyo.
Looks delicious!
Thank you!
Forgive us.
With so many wars these days...
our young ones have
become rash.
Even if I tell them we've no
business with wars...
they refuse to listen and only
give me more to worry about.
This, uh... isn't Tokyo, is it.
"Tokyo"? Never heard
of such a place.
Is that your homeland?
Yes, well...
I'd like to go home soon.
Not that I know HOW, exactly...
Sister, we must tend to your injury!
Take the Sacred Jewel...
and burn it with my body.
Fifty years have passed
since that day.
What's going on?!
An evil spirit!
That again!
Hand me the Sacred Jewel!
The Sacred Jewel?
Do you have it?
I don't know! I don't know
about any Sacred Jewel!
Give it to me!
That demon!
It's coming after me!
Our spears and arrows
have no effect!
We must throw her into
the Dry Well!
A dry well?
The well in the Inuyasha Forest.
That's the well
I climbed out of.
Which way is the forest?
Where the light is shining?
What did you say?!
It'll pursue me!
That girl!
How can an ordinary girl see the
foul vapors that rise from the forest?
Priestess Kaede!
Will I be saved?!
Will I?
Gramps! Mom!
Save me!
Someone help!
Someone help me!
I can smell it...
The scent of the woman
who killed me!
It's approaching!
Damn!
Give me the Sacred Jewel!
I don't have any such thing!
Oww!
Hey, Kikyo!
Why are you wasting time
with the Centipede Monster?
Did I just hear...talking?!
Are you alive?
Kill her in one strike, Kikyo.
Just like the time you killed me.
Huh? Don't look so dumb!
Lost your mind already, Kikyo?
Kikyo? Kikyo?
Who's this Kikyo?!
You listen here,
my name is...
She's coming.
All right! Heave!
Right!
I'm saved...
So hopeless, Kikyo!
Hey you!
Don't mistake me!
I said I'm not Kikyo!
Shut up!
Who else would give off
a scent like you?
Huh?
Or... maybe not.
Finally!
My name is Kagome!
Ka-go-me!
Kikyo seemed smarter.
And she was a beauty.
Let go of me!
Ouch! You let go of me!
Priestess Kaede!
The Inuyasha!
The Inuyasha has awakened?!
The spell that was cast
was eternal! So why... ?
- Give me the Sacred Jewel!
- Let me go!
The Sacred Jewel?!
Stop!
That's right!
Something like this
happened in that well...
But... why can I do
these things?
Something is shining!
From within me...
Is that the Sacred Jewel?
Give me that Jewel!
Huh?!
Hurry!
I heard that a half-demon brat
was after the Sacred Jewel.
So you're the one?
A half-demon?
What is he anyway?
Don't underestimate me,
Centipede Monster!
I can take care of you...
if I really get down to business.
You! You're awfully arrogant.
Are you strong?
Huh?
Well, are you?
What can he do,
strapped down like that?
He's under a powerful spell.
Just stay where you are
and watch!
Damn you!
It swallowed the Jewel!
No!
What will happen, Priestess?!
Its arms are growing again.
Rejoice! My power is
being restored!
It's got me!
Hey, can you pull out this arrow?
Huh?
I'm asking if you can pull out
this arrow!
This arrow?
This one?
Do not remove it!
That arrow secures the spell
on the Inuyasha!
You must not free the Inuyasha!
You old hag, wake up!
Do you want to become
fodder for the centipede?!
Once it completely absorbs
the Sacred Jewel, it'll be the end!
Come on! Do you want to
die here, too?!
l- I don't understand,
not any of it...!
But I know one thing...
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
It disappeared...
the arrow that held
my sister's spell.
Inu... yasha?
You brat!
Shut up, old hag!
Iron Reaver, Soul Stealer!
Wow... He really is strong.
It's still moving!
Do you see the flesh
that shines?
The Sacred Jewel is
embedded there!
You must remove it, else
it will keep rejuvenating!
N-N-No way!
There! I can see it!
Only you can possess
the Jewel.
You, who seem so like
my sister, Kikyo.
Why was it inside my body?
This jewel which can empower
such a demon?
Exactly! Which a human
has no possible use for it!
If you don't want to feel
the pain of my claws...
just give me the Jewel
and get it over with.
But...
But!
But isn't he supposed
to be the HERO?!
When you say "half-demon"...
you also mean "half-HUMAN,"
right?
So why isn't he fighting
on the side of the humans, then?
A "yôkai"demon is after the
sacred "Jewel of Four Souls"...
Why would it be inside ME?
And who's this "Kikyo"
I supposedly look like?!
Would someone please tell me
why I'm stuck in Feudal Japan?
Next time.
"Seekers of the Sacred Jewel"
See you soon!