Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
Inuyasha...
Inuyasha!
Now do you understand?!
Anything you do is useless.
Just lie quietly and become fodder!
l just don't use Tetsusaiga, right?
l just need one arm to deal with
that disgusting demon!
Hold your tongue!
Blades of Blood!
Don't get too cocky!
Kagome!
Why you!
Do not forget, Inuyasha.
I hold Kagome's life
in my hand!
Damn! What'm I gonna do?!
What?!
Kagome... Are you in pain?
I'm okay...
I'm okay, so...
Miroku.
We must help Inuyasha.
Otherwise, Kagome won't
be able to hang on.
No... Whether Inuyasha wins or loses,
Tsubaki intends to kill Kagome.
But!
Yes... The only way is to break
Tsubaki's curse.
Either we destroy Tsubaki,
or we destroy her messenger
demon spirit, Shikikami.
Before Kagome fell ill,
she said she was bitten
by something.
Yes, that was probably the
messenger demon of the Dark Priestess.
It had to have been
that snake.
Please help, Sango!
Miroku!
Hiraikotsu!
Hah!
Sutra exorcisms?
Useless tricks!
Fool! My curse cannot be broken!
Shucks!
Miroku!
So stubborn...
If you resist me, Kagome's suffering
will be prolonged.
Or, it's so easy to do...
Shall I send Kagome to
the netherworld now?
Kagome!
Kagome! Hang on!
Sango, I know.
I'll wake up in a minute.
Please wait.
What's this sound?
So noisy...
Kagome... Kagome...
Kagome!
Huh? Someone's calling.
Who was that?
Kagome! Wake up
or you'll be late for school.
How long're you going to
stay in bed?
Where's Sango?
Inuyasha?
And Miroku...
Why am I back in
this world?
What're you mumbling about?
Hurry and come down.
Don't you want breakfast?
'Morning, Sis.
Can't you at least say
a morning greeting?
'Morning.
Say, when did I come back here?
Here?
Did you go somewhere?
What're you saying?
The otherworld...
500 years in the past.
Remember...
When I enter that old hidden well,
I enter the civil war era where
there are oodles of demons.
You went into that well?
I've come and gone
so many times already!
Inuyasha came here, too.
Inuyasha?
What is that?
Have you forgotten Inuyasha?!
Gramps, are you all right?
Remember, the one that has
dog ears.
Are YOU all right?
Sis, maybe you should
stay home from school today.
She's still half asleep.
Everyone...
This is!
Sis, you'll be late.
What's going on?!
Has everything been a dream?!
What's the matter, Kagome?
You look so depressed.
Well...
Have a problem?
Like boyfriend trouble?
Boyfriend?
That's right! You remember
my boyfriend, don't you?
Of course!
Yes! It wasn't a dream, after all!
It's Hojo in Group B, right?
No!
Remember... the jealous, rough,
spoiled one...
Who's that?
You were two-timing Hojo?
N-No!
Kagome, you sure go for it.
I don't understand,
but I've suddenly been thrust back
into my old life.
Higurashi!
Yes!
Read the next part.
Err...
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Entrance exams are coming up soon.
Pay attention!
Entrance exams...
Yes, I'm supposed to study
for exams.
That's my real life.
That was my hope.
But...
Higurashi!
Hojo!
Here!
I heard you were feeling down.
It's good for your health.
Step on it.
Uh-huh...
Something's different.
Like this is not right.
I want lots of children.
Oh stop!
Grandma, buy me a
sacred jewel keyholder.
The Sacred Jewel!
Now then, the origin of the
Sacred Jewel is said...
Let's go, Grandma!
All right.
Oh, you're leaving?
Buyo... something's wrong with me.
So many things are going round
and round in my head.
I feel like I was supposed to
do something.
All the things I should remember
are getting so mixed up.
I just have this feeling that
what I'm doing now is wrong.
But... what am I supposed to do?
This pain that I feel sometimes...
I'm getting used to it.
And I don't worry about it much.
Who...
Who am I?
And why am I here?
What am I doing?
Why am I so anxious?
Why am I uncertain?
What's wrong, Kagome?
I'm sorry... I'm sorry, Hojo!
Kagome!
All right! Next up!
So, you've finally come.
Want to try?
Huh?
Isn't that why you're here?
That target.
Aim well.
Okay.
Your line is good.
Hit the mark!
You have much to learn.
Your concentration is lacking.
Umm...
Who...
Who are you?
Huh?
Who are YOU?
I...
Are you me?
As it is, you'll end up
killing Inuyasha yet again.
Inuyasha?!
Kagome!
Hang on, Kagome!
Damn!
l-Inuyasha!
W-Wait!
I must get out of this world!
Wait, I said!
Who are you?
Now isn't the time...
This world is your world.
You have decided who you are.
So answer.
Who are you?
Kagome...
Inuyasha...
Inuyasha!
What...!!
You! Why can you still move?!
Hey you!
You're lacking in concentration!
Humph! You've managed
to endure my curse.
Well, I guess being Kikyo's reincarnation
wasn't a lie, after all.
Although, if you were the REAL Kikyo,
that arrow wouldn't have missed.
So you're just an imitation Kikyo.
You!
Who are you?
I AM Kagome!
No one else!
Silly fool!
Rushing to your death.
Kagome!
Kagome won't last like this!
Hang on for just a bit longer.
I can.
Kagome!
I've had enough
of you two!
I'll never let her kill you!
You're in the way, creep!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
This is it, Tsubaki!
Well done, Inuyasha!
All right!
Too bad about that, Tsubaki.
You're so naïve.
Do you think the curse
has been broken?
What?!
The curse still holds!
She's not recovering... even though
the Shikikami has been destroyed.
Kagome will die.
And, so will you all.
She still had more demons
inside her!
Damn it to hell!
Kirara! Stay by Kagome!
Hiraikotsu!
Shikikami!
It couldn't be...
Damn!
These demons were a diversion!
Realized it only now! Too late!
Shikikami! Bite off that woman's head
and get the Sacred Jewel shards from her!
Kagome!
Damn! I won't make it!
F-Forget it!
I... I...
I...
I won't lose to you!
What?!
She threw back Shikikami!
She reversed the curse to me!
Just like Kikyo did...
Just like that last time!
Why must I be done in
by that young twit?
The Shikon Jewel is beginning
to purify!
The shards are out!
Why you!
She's getting away!
Not from me!
Hold it, you!
W-What!
Damn!
She got away.
Kagome!
Inu... yasha...
You're gonna let it go...
The Sacred Jewel shard?
I'll get it back right away.
Besides...
Besides?
I must give the Dark Priestess
a chance for revenge.
You're so kind.
My powers have waned.
No thanks to them...
the demons have all died.
I was so close!
But as long as I have
a Sacred Jewel this large...
I'll be able to increase
my powers immensely.
Next time, I'll get you...
You shall pay,
Inuyasha and Kagome!
Kagome must be so tired.
Can't be helped.
She fought the spell for so long.
Hey! Inuyasha! Kagome!
Sorry, Kagome.
All because you're with me...
It's all right.
I want to stay with you.
Kagome.
Is that true, Kagome?
Does the Dark Priestess Tsubaki
still possess the Sacred Jewel?
That's no fun.
Who are they?! Tsubaki's helpers?
But the Red Priestess and
the White Priestess...
Looks so auspicious!
What?!
I'm tricking Kagome and
Miroku and the others?
That's a lie!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Red and White Priestesses"
I have to shape up!