Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
The castle which the demon-birds attack...
What is the secret that Naraku
has hidden there?
Among those fighting to
defend the castle
is Sango's younger brother, Kohaku!
Kill Naraku?
Yes, Mother.
Nothing good has come
of being involved with him.
There's been interference
after interference.
And gathering human blood with
which to dilute the poison in your body
has become increasingly difficult.
But what I can't forgive is that
I, Princess Abi,
have been drawn into some
petty fight between half-demons.
I see....
Then let us attack a castle
and destroy it.
A castle?
Yes.
There is a very suspicious
castle.
It is probably connected in some way
to Naraku.
Mother, is that....
It was just about the time
that St. Hijiri appeared.
That one....
Go!
T- The birds are in flames!
St. Hijiri has returned!
Please save us!
The one who erected
the barrier...
Slay him!
Huh?!
W- We're saved!
My birds... are gone!
Damn! What's going on?!
Ever since Naraku came
into the picture,
I've had nothing but
interference!
It seems this St. Hijiri is
a hindrance to Naraku.
Huh?
Naraku's demons covered the skies
in search of St. Hijiri's whereabouts.
I used our birds to spy on them.
And there was one spot which
the demons would not approach.
It was a human castle.
Naraku's demons flew over it
without even bothering to look there.
The demons had no need to
check this place
because there is a connection
between the castle and Naraku.
So try and attack this castle,
in order to find out what
Naraku is hiding there.
My lady, the young heir is sleeping
very peacefully.
I know.
He sleeps right through the night, too.
Such a fine young babe.
It's as though that frightful night
never happened.
The night I gave birth
to this child,
everyone who tended to me
in the birthing room died,
and...
right after that, those strangers
appeared.
But I can't remember.
With each day, the memory of
that night recedes.
Huh?
Kohaku, do not go there!
You cannot come here.
What is it?
Oh, my lady....
My humblest apologies!
The youth has only recently
come to apprentice,
and knows little of the ways
of the castle.
It is all right.
But let me see his face.
Huh?
Raise your head.
Have I met you somewhere?
Oh, absolutely not!
A highborn lady like yourself
would never cross paths
with the likes of him.
Isn't that so?
Yes.
I see....
I guess I was mistaken.
You may go.
Yes, my lady.
The lady seems very nice.
That she is.
We're so happy
that she has borne an heir.
Kohaku...
You and Kanna will stay
at this castle.
Yes!
Live in the castle.
Protect the child.
Kohaku, you must eat more.
Thank you!
Okay, I'll haul these away.
Oh, I can do that.
Don't worry! No problem.
This castle is so peaceful.
I have this feeling...
that long ago, I used to live
in a similar manner with many people.
But I don't remember when...
Yes, birds that suck blood.
Do you know of them?
Oh yes, there's been a
huge uproar.
I've heard many rumors
about them.
Have they been seen
in this area?
Never seen them.
Besides, we're so close
to the castle.
No way would demons
come here.
I guess this is the wrong place, too.
Can't be helped, I guess.
Huh?
We have no clues about
the location of the birds' nest.
I guess we have no choice
but to find lodgings in this village tonight.
No choice? Which way are you headed?
My, what a handsome man!
Please stay and have some fun.
Oh, how I would love to
have fun with you....
There he goes again.
He never learns.
That kid, Hakudoshi, has
no heart.
That's why he won't die
no matter how often he's killed.
Where is his heart?
Kagura....
What are you thinking?
Shut up!
Leave me alone to think!
Birds?
Which means...
She must be Princess Abi,
the bird master.
Kagura, go after them.
Huh?
But just watch them, that's all.
Don't try anything unnecessary.
And just what is "unnecessary"?
Go!
Naraku's saimyosho....
Have they come to spy on us?
Hah! Serves them right!
So...
It seems that female demon
has turned on Naraku.
Hey, Kohaku!
Kohaku!
What's wrong?
You were moaning.
You okay?
Were you having a nightmare?
U-Uh-huh....
What did you dream about?
I don't remember.
Here, drink.
Huh? Thanks.
Feel a little better?
Uh-huh.
That's good.
Have a good dream this time.
Uh-huh....
Oh boy.... Once he starts snoring,
it's so hard to fall asleep.
Everyone is so kind.
Well? Aren't you going to thank me?
What?!
After all, I saved your little brother's life.
Kohaku!
Why?! Why do you protect Naraku?
I made him forget.
Forget about you...
forget everything about himself.
Kohaku...
What are you doing now?
The bath felt wonderful!
Sango, why don't you bathe too?
Uh-huh.
Huh?
Princess Abi's birds!
They're heading for the castle.
Kohaku, you don't remember
your parents' faces?
Uh-huh....
Did they die in a battle?
I don't know.
I see....
But it's a good thing you
ended up here in this castle.
Yeah.
We're all one big family....
those who work here.
Help!
Demon birds!
Watch out! Get back!
A-Amazing!
K-Kohaku!
Do not go outside!
Understand?
Kohaku!
Kohaku... protect the child.
My lady....
l-I'm all right.
My baby is with me.
Everyone in the castle
will protect us.
Even if it costs them
their lives.
So the birds appeared!
The castle is under attack!
I sense a Sacred Jewel shard!
What?!
Just one....
It's Kohaku's shard!
Kohaku is at the castle?!
What I'm sensing....
It must be him.
Kohaku...
Has Naraku ordered
you there?
What are you planning this time?
Kohaku, protect the child.
- Protect the young lord!
- Do not let them get near!
Have the demon birds discovered
that the child is in this castle?
What the hell are you doing here?
You're the new apprentice.
Go and hide yourself!
Y-Yessir!
They're protecting me!
Sango, when we get to the castle,
you go straight to Kohaku!
What?!
I'll handle those birds!
Now go, Sango!
Go!
Thanks!
I sense the shard over that way!
Kirara!
Kohaku!
Wind Scar!
Inuyasha....
Not you again!
Princess Abi!
You despicable....!
Inuyasha, you're Naraku's enemy!
So why protect this castle?
What?!
This castle?
Are you saying that Naraku is here?!
That's what I'm here to find out.
So far though, only humans are
resisting us.
What's going on?!
Aren't you and Naraku
allies?
Are you kidding?!
He's the one who
came to me for help.
So you cut your ties
with Naraku?
Then stop interfering!
We'll destroy Naraku ourselves!
I'll destroy you first!
Stay outta this!
The one good thing that
came out of helping Naraku...
is this trident's barrier.
Why you...!
A miasma!
Inuyasha!
Oh, it can even do this....
That's enough!
I can't believe that Naraku planned
to have Princess Abi and Inuyasha fight.
But is there something
in that castle?
The birds are on fire!
My lady....
Fire!
W-What are we to do?
My lady....please hurry outside.
You'll all burn to death
if you stay here.
You're....
that youth named Kohaku.
Hurry!
But there are demons outside!
She's right!
I must protect my baby.
He is our precious heir!
Do not fear. I will protect
you with my life.
Now hurry, this way!
Hurry!
I can't breathe!
Hang on!
My lady!
Our young lord!
They're okay.
You are?
He saved us.
This boy?
Kohaku....
Thank you.
My lady....
We must take them
to safety!
Kohaku, you stay by
our lady's side.
I will!
Here they come!
I owe you one, Kohaku!
That way!
Everyone, hurry!
Right!
Where did you learn
to fight like that?
I just learned by copying.
You're just like a demon slayer.
Huh?
Here they come!
We're counting on you!
Yes!
Demon slayer...?
Go!
Take that!
What's this?
I feel as though I fought
like this a long time ago.
Together with my comrades,
combining our strength.
Run!
Why you...!
You half-demon....!
Our lord....our lord has been slain
by a demon-bird!
The castle....has fallen.
Kohaku!
It's okay.... Don't worry, my lady....
Kohaku, take the child.
And kill everyone around you.
Kill them.
Don't let your guard down!
My lady....
We....we will be safe.
Kohaku! Where are you?
You're good, Kohaku!
You're a big help!
Kohaku....
Kill them.
Kill everyone around you.
Kill them!
Just who am I?
Kohaku has lost his memory
and is being controlled by Naraku.
Who is she?
And when they meet again, he cannot
remember his own sister, Sango.
You did it again, didn't you?
Again?
While Princess Abi and Inuyasha
continue their battle,
Sango and Kohaku, who share
a tragic past, confront each other.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Cruel Reunion of Fate"
I don't care if I die...
Even if we both die...