Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The battle continues to rage
against the Band of Seven
who are hell-bent on
avenging Ginkotsu's death.
And Renkotsu tries to steal the
Sacred Jewel shards from Koga
who has sustained serious injuries.
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
All right....
I should have mounted
this on him as well...
Your time is up!
Wha....?!
Damn it, I can't move....
What should I do with
Ginkotsu's Sacred Jewel shard?
If I carry it around
like this,
that Bankotsu will
just take it from me.
No way I'm letting that
happen! Not for that brat!
The wound is healing!
Dying won't do anybody
any good, you know.
Isn't that right, Ginkotsu?
You found him?
Good!
Don't worry about
reporting to Bankotsu.
I've got one more job for you.
I swear to you, I'm going to
steal Koga's jewel shards!
Look! He's awake!
Koga!
I'm so glad!
You were unconscious
all night long.
K-Kagome?
Koga? Do you remember anything?
You were caught in the explosion of
that iron monster, Ginkotsu!
Are you all right?
Somehow.... Jeez! I stink
to high heaven!
How come?! My whole body
just reeks of dog!!
That's because Inuyasha
carried you here.
What?!
Kagome asked him to do it.
How could you two let
him do that to me?!
You two should've carried me!
Well, you see, we also....
Were hurt some....
See? I told you we should
have left him where he was.
But, I never actually expected
him to show me any gratitude.
Whatever happened to you,
Inuyasha?! You're soaked!
Can't you guess? I had to wash
off that stink of wolf on me!
Say what?!
Makes me sick!!
Hey, that's my line!
Simmer down, Koga....
I'm outta here, Kagome.
Huh?
I carried him to a safe place.
Now it's no business of ours
if he lives or dies.
Hey, Inuyasha!
Don't talk like that!
You! You're always
chastising me
but you never say a word to
that thankless Koga there!
I'm sick of your whining about
that! All right! I'll say it.
Thank you, Kagome.
You saved my life....
You should be thanking me!
All you did was carry me.
He looks like he's feeling
all right to me. Leave him.
But it looks like he
can't move yet....
Well, what about
Miroku and Sango?
Yeah! What's going on with those
two who went to Mt. Hakurei?
They should be back soon.
Yes, probably....
Okay, let's go.
It's a poison insect!
You guys stay here!
I'll get him before he
gives this place away!
Hakkaku and Ginta? How are
you two feeling now?
I'm still a bit....
We got hit pretty hard....
I'm sorry.
I lost the first-aid kit so
I can't do anything for you.
Don't worry about it!
It's enough that you even
thought of us!
Unlike Koga, they're
very humble...
Huh?
Do you smell it, too, Kagome?
No, I sense the presence of
a Sacred Jewel shard nearby.
What is it you smell, Shippo?
Smells like gunpowder....
Huh?!
The river!!
What's that?!
What's wrong?!
Why you...!
Gotcha!
Kagome!!
What is this?!
It must be the Band of Seven!
I've poured a lot of oil on the water!
You can't escape now!
It's Renkotsu!
It's him!
Better go!
Koga, it's too dangerous here.
Why that....! I'll kill
him this time!
Koga....!
No! Don't, Koga!
You're too badly hurt.
I'll get him!
Is that....?!
Hah!
Kagome!!!
Inuyasha!!
For that Renkotsu to
show up so soon
means he's really anxious
for me to kill him....!
Wait a minute, Inuyasha!
You should wear this!
Right! The Robe of the Fire
Rat will protect you from fire!
No, you two wear it.
You can't depend on that
damned wolf to help you.
Keep your hands off him, mutt!
He's after my jewel shards! I'll
be the one to settle with him!
Ah, shut up!
If your shards fall into his
hands, we're in big trouble.
Why, you....!
But please be careful, Inuyasha!
That fiend is using two jewel shards!
That's fewer than Bankotsu had.
So! Inuyasha is back already!
What's wrong? A little
too hot in that hole?
Shut up! I'm coming to get
you so just wait there!
Wow!
In one leap....!
Why would I wait for you?!
A cannon....?
You can't dodge this
in mid-air!
Inuyasha!
It's Kirara!
Great! Kirara can't
be hurt by fire!
Way to go, Kirara! Now
let's go get him!!
I have no time for you!
Kirara! Get above him!
Here I come, Renkotsu!!
And here I go!!
Heh!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!!
- Kagome! Get inside!
- Hurry!
Did I get them....?
Humph. Looks like they've
been incinerated....
I'll take those Sacred Jewel shards,
if you don't mind....!
You fool! No
one's dead in here.
You should be grateful, Koga.
It's because Kagome managed to
cover you with Inuyasha's robe.
I'm not crazy about it
belonging to that mutt.
So you think you've
bested me, huh?
What....?!
This isn't over yet!
I'll blow you to hell!!
Those are fire bombs!
Are you crazy?!
If you set one of those off
inside here, it'll kill you, too!
Shut up!
There's no turning back for me!
It's true... I've been using the
shard that Ginkotsu left
without permission and
Bankotsu will kill me for it...
I'm on to you, that you've
been hiding
the Scared Jewel shards
you got from that girl, Kagome...
Please don't be angry.
I was going to hand
them over to you...
My, aren't you cooperative...
I knew you were a smart one.
Just don't let it happen again.
Koga, I'm going to have those
shards in your legs,
no matter what it takes....
Why you....!
Yeah! With those I can battle
with Bankotsu and defeat him....
This is no empty threat!
He means it!
I won't fall for that twice!
You won't get away
from here, either!
I won't die!!
I shouldn't die... as long as
I have the shards...
The only ones to die
will be you!!
Don't push your luck.
Inuyasha!
Why you...!
Do it now, wolf!
Huh?!
He got him!
He's up again, mutt!!
Take this....!
Inuyashaaaaaa!!!!
Why, you...!
Inuyasha?!
Inuyasha? Inuyasha....?
I'm sure we'll find
him soon....
He must've washed up
on the riverbank....
...provided the mutt isn't
in a million pieces....
Hey!
Koga....!
But it's true! Come on!
If that idiot hadn't....
Inuyasha wasn't even wearing
the Robe of the Fire Rat,
even though it's like
armor to him...
Kagome....?
Now you've made her cry!
Don't cry, Kagome....
It's all my fault! It's
because he let me wear this....
It's not your fault, Kagome!
I saw the whole thing!
He forced it on you even though
you really hated to touch it....
Hey?...Ah!
Listen, wolf.
Who hated to touch it?
Inuyasha!
You're all right!
My body is built
differently than yours.
And in addition to that,
sure enough, that punk Renkotsu
valued his life, after all.
At the last minute he
threw the fire bombs away.
Humph! That's what I thought
he'd do all along.
They say that idiots
don't die....
You think I'll let you
get away with that?
You gonna try it?
Today is the day I'm gonna
put your lights out!
How? With that beat-up
body of yours?
Inuyasha!
Huh....?
I'm so glad!
You're not hurt, are you?
You're okay?
Kagome....
I'm sorry I caused
you to worry.
Are you really, truly all right?
Yeah....
Jeez....
Koga?
You're just walking away?
I'll walk away for today,
seeing as how Kagome
is upset and all....
But listen up, mutt.
Don't think you've won!
I'm never giving up on Kagome!
Can't you tell that
you've lost, stupid?!
You get all smug just because
she hugged you? Stupid!
It gets you, doesn't it!
You deserve it! Stupid!!
Somehow... somehow it's getting
harder and harder to cry...
The one calling the other
stupid is stupid.
They're both...
...stupid.
Yep.
- What?!
I can't cry with
all this...
Nothing in here, either.
No sign of demons at all.
However, there is some
kind of connection
between Naraku and
the Band of Seven.
And it's a fact that Saint Hakushin
was protecting the Band of Seven.
But we don't know why.
If he is helping Naraku out
by putting this barrier around
Mt. Hakurei, then....
Yeah. I wouldn't be surprised
if Naraku were around here.
Anyway, let's go on to
the top of the mountain.
If we go back empty-handed,
we'll hear about it from Inuyasha.
You're right.
On top of that....
I have to do something
about this barrier.
Here we are, finally
alone together,
and I can't make a move!
At this rate, I'll never....
Huh?
Okay....
Damn it! I failed again!
I didn't manage to steal
Koga's Sacred Jewel shards...
If it gets out that I'm using
Ginkotsu's Sacred Jewel shard,
then Bankotsu will kill me...
What should I do now...?
Saimyosho....?
It's Bankotsu....!
Hey, Renkotsu. I heard
from the bugs here....
Ginkotsu bit the dust, did he?
Um....yeah.
Too bad. After all the time you
spent reconstructing him....
But at least you're still alive.
Suikotsu, who was after
Sesshomaru, is dead, too.
Suikotsu is?
And that means that finally....
it's just the three of us:
you, me and Jakotsu.
So, I guess I'm going to be
depending more heavily on you....
Yes....
All right, let's go.
This creep Bankotsu isn't aware
of Ginkotsu's jewel shard...?
Well, anyway, I guess I'm
still of some use to him...
I guess I got a reprieve this time...
What is it, Miroku?
The path....
It's gone.
It's almost like someone
destroyed it.
Look, Miroku!
A cave!
It looks like this path
led up to that cave.
- Wanna go in?
- Can we?
I'll give it a try.
Good!
Now....
My word....!
Here! Catch this, Miroku!
You're impressive, Sango!
It leads deep into the earth.
It's faint, but
I sense an evil aura here.
Let's go, Sango. No doubt about
it, Naruku is deep inside!
Right!
Damn that Naraku!
How long is he going to keep
me shut up in this place?!
Kagura....
Oh, it's you, Kanna.
Boy, you've got it good.
You don't emanate any
demonic aura
so you can come and go on
sacred ground as you please.
But if I make even
one step outside,
that annoying barrier will
will purify me! Damn it!
They're coming.
These two! The monk
and the Demon Slayer....?
Well, isn't this fun?
We're long overdue for
a little rumble....
There's a demonic aura
deep inside the sacred Mt. Hakurei!
Naraku is in here.
I can't believe two lone humans
actually came in here.
Kagura!
You're brave, I'll give you that.
But you're not getting outta
here alive!
Naraku's poison insects!
Miroku! If you suck them up,
the poison will....!
If in doing so, my beloved will
live longer, I don't care!
Wind Tunnel!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Into the Depths of Mt. Hakurei"
Forgive me, Sango.
But you, at least, must live!