Is this the place that the
monk spoke of?!
A hair cord...
Kikyo...
Are you really alive?
Didn't I tell you?
When I die, you die!
Stop!
Kikyo!
Kikyo!!
I died hating you.
And at that moment,
my soul became immobile.
As long as you live,
I cannot be saved.
Is Kikyo asleep?
She seems a bit sad.
You were able to break through
my barrier?
Barrier?
Was there anything like that?
Are you the one who has been
luring women's souls away?
If so, please let them return!
Isn't he with you?
Huh?
Inuyasha set out to find you.
I see... Inuyasha is trying to
come here.
What are you to Inuyasha?
Huh?
My body...can't move!
You are in the way.
T-that's!
The demons who were gathering
the dead souls!
A barrier...
Kikyo is behind this...
Kikyo, is it really you?!
I can't move.
Inuyasha is here.
Not to save you.
He's here to see me.
I won't allow any interference.
Interference?
You don't still mean to
kill Inuyasha?!
No, Kikyo!
Someone purposely set
you two at odds!
It wasn't Inuyasha who killed you!
You look as though you expect
me to be happy.
Huh?
The one who caused my death...
If that person dies,
will I be resurrected?
T-that's...
The dead wish for one thing...
To live once more.
Hah! A wish that cannot come true.
However, the dead can wish for
one thing which can come true.
I want to steal his heart...
from the one I will never forgive
if he dares to forget me.
Never forgive if
he forgets you?
Do you mean Inuyasha?
He wishes for my death.
That is good.
That means he has regrets about
our fight.
Regret all he wants.
I shall never let him forget... about me.
Time will not go forward.
Then I can exist is the time
that is frozen.
I will be able to continue
living in his heart.
Even now, Inuyasha thinks
about you!
Isn't that enough?
Inuyasha loves you!
He always has!
Isn't that enough?
Inuyasha and I parted
despising each other.
The love you speak of is but
a shallow emotion...
which only served to
deepen the hatred.
Nothing is stronger in strengthening
resolve than bitterness.
If he must love, then love
my consuming hatred.
As for me, I will love his heart...
which is about to fall
into deep despair.
No! Your hatred is pointless!
It makes no sense!
Inuyasha! Talk to Kikyo!
Tell her how Naraku deceived
you both!
Inuyasha?
Kikyo!
Inuyasha can't see me!
So it is you...
who's been gathering
the souls of dead women.
This body, molded from
earth and bones...
needs to be nourished with
human souls, else I cannot move.
Inuyasha... you must despise me.
Driven by my hatred towards you...
I have gathered the souls of the dead
to remain in this world.
How stupid!
You may hate me, but...
never a day went by
without my thinking about you!
I thought so... Inuyasha has
never forgotten Kikyo...
Of course! But I feel a bit sad.
Inuyasha's been taken from me.
Oh, what am I saying?!
Inuyasha's not my boyfriend
or anything!
No matter what your appearance...
I would never hate you or
think less of you...
Is that true?
Even if I were to kill you
with these hands?
Huh?! W-wait...!
Inuyasha...
after meeting you, I stopped
being a priestess.
I became a mere woman.
This is what I longed for
when I was alive.
Inuyasha... You're going to
accept her...
I guess... it's only to be expected.
What am I doing here anyway?
I'm such a fool!
I'm starting to cry!?
Cripes... what?!
This nostalgic scent of her...
It's just like back then.
The only difference is that
she has no warmth.
Her body died...so it's cold...
and sad...and lonely.
We cannot return to that time.
So I want to stay like this
a little longer.
I can't save you...
If I cannot do anything
for you...
to stay like this...
How I wish time would stop!
Is that all right?
If time would stop?
Yeah... I don't care...
if I'm with you.
Oh, I can't watch this anymore!
I won't interfere, so release me!
I'll go far away.
Hey, are you two listening?!
Inuyasha...
I will never let you go.
Come with me to hell.
He's being dragged in!
Inuyasha, what're you doing?!
You must get away!
No! He's unconscious!
Kikyo! You can hear me, I know!
You coward!
Inuyasha said he wants to
be with you...
but he never said
he wanted to die with you!
Unlike you, Inuyasha must go
after Naraku...
who tricked him fifty years ago!
More than anything, Inuyasha wants
to live to fight!
Inuyasha is determined to avenge
your death as well!
You understand?
Kikyo!
Will getting revenge bring
this body back to life?!
Inuyasha...
Rather than live with
my memory...
come with me.
You and I have the same wish.
How dare you!
If Inuyasha were conscious,
he would never follow you!
No way!
Get away from Inuyasha!
Do... not... touch... Inuyasha!
This girl...
She's taking my souls once again!
Before this body is
completely emptied...
Inuyasha! Come!
No! Wake up, Inuyasha!
Inuyasha! Inuyasha!
No! Wake up!
Kagome's voice...
Kagome...is...here?
Ka...go...me?
Kagome!
What're you doing here?
Huh!? What about you?
Me? Well... err...
Kikyo!
Is that girl more dear to you?
Huh... uh...
Wait, Kikyo!
I!
Inuyasha, do not forget.
My feeling when
my lips were against yours...
was real.
Do not forget.
Kikyo...
H-hey!
Don't come!
What're you so mad about?
You know, Inuyasha...
do you think you can find
the Sacred Jewels alone?
I... don't think I can help
you anymore.
What're you saying?!
You're the only one who
can see the Jewels.
Of course, you have to help!
That's all, right?
That's all you need me for.
What a thing to say.
Sorry! Forget I said that.
Maybe it's because I'm alone
in this strange world.
I'm feeling Ionely.
I'm here!
You have me, don't you?!
Inuyasha...
I get it.
You couldn't see me, could you?
Huh?
I'm sorry, but I did see it all.
See it all?
From the start to finish.
So, please leave me alone
for a while.
H-hey! What's this about...
Start to finish?!
Kagome!
What did I do?
Hey! Kagome! Tell me!
Sit!
Start to finish means
everything!
I saw everything!
From a front row seat!
I'm leaving.
What? You found her?
Inuyasha! What're you doing here?
Have you seen Kagome?
I've seen that pose before.
It must mean that
Kagome is just fine.
And that Kagome is
full of energy.
Sister Kikyo!
What's the matter, Kaede?
Are you afraid of your
own sister?
N-no...
Since the day you fell
from the cliff, I thought...
Yes, I am a dead woman.
But I guess I still long for
this world.
Do you still seek Inuyasha's life?
I just met Inuyasha moments ago.
And I barely missed killing him.
Tell me, Kaede.
Tell me everything you know
about this Naraku.
My rotten spirit has some
use after all.
Doesn't it look good?
Don't you want to devour me?
I want a body that moves freely.
In order to posses the Sacred Jewel...
and Kikyo.
Now eat me!
And pass on power... to me!
Everything started from
the evil designs of Onigumo.
He called forth the demons
and was eaten by them...
thus was born the demon Naraku.
I see... That wild robber.
Yes.
He used to say that
the Sacred Jewel grows in beauty...
when it is tainted.
He caused hatred between
myself and Inuyasha...
then stole the Jewel
that had been sullied.
My sister... Inuyasha was seriously
wounded by Naraku again.
So...
I just thought I should know the
circumstances of my death.
By the way, Inuyasha has changed.
His face had a softness.
Back then, he trusted no one...
his eyes were cold.
Kagome is a strange child.
She has been able to slowly
heal Inuyasha's heart.
That girl again... She's the one
who changed him.
If I had lived, I would have been
the one to heal his heart.
My sister... are you not able to
break away from the past?
We shall meet again.
How long will you linger... Sister?
She's gone.
Inuyasha, Kagome wasn't her
usual self.
Just what happened with Kikyo?
What you always do with women...
Huh?!
You! You participated in such
an act in front of Kagome?!
Whaddya usually do?!
Huh?
Will Kagome come back?
She seemed to be
quite troubled.
Never a day went by without
my thinking of you!
I spoke the truth.
My feeling when my lips were
against yours...was real.
And my words were real.
Is that girl more dear to you?
Now then, what will you do, Inuyasha?
Kikyo could not have gone far.
Will you go after her?
Hey! Isn't Kagome more precious?
Inuyasha, hurry and make up with her!
What's the matter with me?
I was in such a daze, I forgot
all my things back there.
Hey, is anyone there?
What will you do, Inuyasha?
Who will you choose?!
Now then!
Well?!
Can't I choose both?
You... two-timing!
Well, it often happens
with men.
However, no matter what happens,
she must not find out.
If what you just said should
ever leak out...
Sit!
Yes, it's sit.
It means divine punishment
for you.
Poor Inuyasha... He wasn't
being malicious.
We learn that a village nearby
specializes in demon extermination.
Maybe we can gain information about
the Sacred Jewel fragments.
It turns out we are not the only ones
who thought along that line.
Chain-Scythes attack the fellow
demon terminators!
The village under seize!
A brother and a sister trapped!
Is everything arranged by... him?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Enter Sango the Demon Slayer"!
Don't miss it!