It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
forourdreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
The final battle at the border
between this world and the next...
Naraku closes the way
back to ourworld
and we're in a
serious pinch when...
Sesshomaru appears!
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
It is finally mine!
The final Sacred Jewel shard.
The final shard?!
Don't you understand, Inuyasha?
It's over.
Huh?
What...?!
What is that?!
Sesshomaru!
Sesshomaru?
Vermin!
Damn it!
Hey....Kid....
Huh?
Do you still have the strength
to fight?
Huh?
Hah! You're betterthan Inuyasha....
I'll say that much for you.
E-Even the immense force of
Lord Sesshomaru's sword
could not break through
Naraku's barrier....?
Huh?
At this rate, the shard
will soon be assimilated
into the tainted Sacred Jewel.
Hah! We don't need you
to tell us that!
Before that happens,
slay me!
What?!
In orderto break through
Naraku's barrier,
slay me!
Hosenki....
Does that mean you will pass on your
demon powers to Inuyasha's Tetsusaiga?
That's right!
Tetsusaiga gains new demon power
each time it slays
a strong demon.
The blade has turned red!
But...
But what happens to you
if I cut you?
Hmm....
Is this the time to be
worrying about someone else?
Huh....!
Besides....
Huh?
Huh?! H-Hosenki's head is....
being covered by adamantite!
If you are not worthy
of possessing the shard,
you will not be able to slay me!
Instead....
you will lose your life
on this spot!
Huh?!
Do you have the resolve to do it?
Hearing that makes me
feel a little better.
What does this mean?
To lose his life?
You guys, stay outta the way.
Inuyasha....!
Here I come!
Inuyasha!
Adamantite shards!
Not even a crack!
Sesshomaru, do you wish
to strike me that badly?!
Well then....
I shall grant your wish.
Huh?!
N-Naraku has exposed his body
outside the barrier!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Inuyasha!
There isn't a single scratch!
Maybe someone should....
What's wrong, Inuyasha?
You said you had the resolve!
Shaddup!
I don't need you to tell me that!
I won'tgive up!
L-Lord Sesshomaru!
Huh?
W-What is that?
'Kay.... Fine!
Inuyasha! Stop already!
Inuyasha!
If you keep going, yourbody will....!
Shaddup!
I said I was prepared for this!
But....!
Just be quiet and watch!
Inuyasha....
Get back!
It's a miasma!
Kagome!
'Kay!
What's going on?!
Hah! As if this miasma would
affect me!
Well.... even if it doesn't
affect you....
Get back!
I'll purify the miasma!
I can breathe.
l-I'm saved.
What will you do, Sesshomaru?
Every time you cut me,
the miasma will increase.
And everyone in this area
will die eventually.
L-Lord Sesshomaru!
It's all right!
As long as we have Kagome's arrows,
I ain't afraid of any miasma!
I'm out of arrows.
What?
W-What?!
That was my last arrow.
Huh? Overthere!
There's one over there!
This one's different.
Kikyo's arrow...
is rejecting me.
Naraku....
Hmm?
Is that all you have to say?
I'm not so sentimental
that I would hold back my sword
forthe sake of humans!
Huh?!
Oh.... I knew it....
T-The miasma is approaching!
Everyone, go further back!
I'll get rid of the miasma!
Inuyasha!
What's the matter, brat?
I thought you were going to
slay me and
strengthen your sword.
Shaddup!
I'll get to you later!
Hmm.... Inuyasha....
has seeing your comrades
in danger
made you forget about your goal?
Fool!
So it doesn't matterif
everyone dies from my miasma?
You are a true demon, after all,
Sesshomaru.
Yourheart is made differently.
That has nothing to do with it.
Naraku....
I, Sesshomaru, will defeat you.
That's all there is to it.
The lives of your comrades
are more important than
strengthening your sword?
Is that because you
are a half-demon?
I am what I am!
And I'll do things my way!
Inuyasha!
And if you obtain my demon power
in such a way,
will you be able to
control it?
Hah! Then I don't want it!
You can keep your
"great" demon power!
Inuyasha....!
I'm gonna do what
must be done now!
Wind Scar!
Huh? This is!
Hah! Even if he uses
his Wind Scarto destroy the miasma...
W- What is this?!
The Adamantite Spears
of Hosenki?
Look!
Naraku's barrieris dispersing!
Tetsusaiga has....
transformed!
If you had raced
forward with greed,
desiring only to
strengthen your sword....
that shower of adamantite shards
would have taken yourlife.
Huh?
Hosenki split apart!
Inuyasha, keep that
spirit of a half-demon
and inherit the Adamant Barrage!
Huh?!
Naraku, I won't let you escape!
Adamant Barrage!
Huh?!
He did it!
He impaled Naraku!
Why you...!
I see that you no longer
have the strength to
put up a barrier.
That arrogance of yours
will be yourdownfall.
I, Sesshomaru, will deliver
the finishing blow!
Did he do it?
No, not yet!
He's disappearing.
Kikyo's arrow is...
This is bad!
Naraku is getting away!
Huh?
There's a shard imbedded
in his flesh.
Does this mean I should
use it now?
I can shoot this arrow!
I must do it!
This... this one arrow...
can finish Naraku...
no, it can put an end to all this.
Go!
Huh?!
A Sacred Jewel shard....
What about Naraku?
He disappeared....
Kikyo's arrow pursued Naraku
and disappeared.
If Naraku were to die at this border
between this world and the afterlife,
now that would be something
to celebrate.
But I guess that would be
wishing fortoo much.
A barrier?
Kohaku....
What's Hakudoshi doing?
I guess it's no use
asking you.
Kagura... where have you been?
You're awake?
Answerme.
Taking a breather.
It's tiring being with you
every single minute of the day.
Humph!
Huh?!
N-Naraku....!
Even afterall this,
Naraku won't die!
This arrow...
It was Kagome who shot it,
but its spiritual power
is Kikyo's.
Hakudoshi's barrierwhich
connected me to this world...
If I had been shot a moment sooner,
I would not have been able
to return.
I guess I still
haven't run out of luck.
Hosenki....
I'm gonna take this
Sacred Jewel shard.
As you please.
I....
I was not able to protect
the Sacred Jewel shard.
I didn't think that something evil
would pursue it this far.
I was not able to put an end
to the fighting overthe Sacred Jewel shard.
It won'tend.
Not until the Sacred Jewel shard
disappears.
I don't know how to rid this world
of the Sacred Jewel.
However,
I can fight those like Naraku
who are after it.
So until Naraku dies,
until there's no one left
who covets it,
I will continue to fight!
Hmm....
Instead of protecting the shard,
instead of running away,
you choose to fight?
Then return to yourworld.
If you linger, the gate will close!
Close?!
Inuyasha!
You must go after
Lord Sesshomaru!
Hurry!
Inuyasha....
Awright....
Now get out of here, half-demon!
Yeah.
Let's go, everyone!
- Right!
- Yeah!
I won't let go!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Please wait!
Pipe down
and quit making such a fuss!
What's the matter, Sango?
You look depressed.
Miroku....
You heard Inuyasha....
That until the Sacred Jewel disappears,
the fighting won't end....
And that means....
You're thinking about
yourlittle brother, Kohaku?
Kohaku's life is linked to
the Sacred Jewel shard
imbedded in his back.
Without the Sacred Jewel...
Kohaku's life is...
Naraku is alive.
His barrierwas destroyed and
his body was in tatters, yet...
Where... Where is his heart?
Is something wrong, Inuyasha?
Nah, it's nothing.
Hakudoshi makes the
demon-rats go on a rampage.
And we see Kohaku nearby.
The rats will scattereverywhere
and attack human villages.
Soon this entire nation will be
devoured by them.
But the rats soon begin
to gather.
This is a spell!
A spell that lures them together
and destroys them.
But only one with immense
spiritual power can cast such a spell.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Stampede of the
Countless Demon Rats!"
Kikyo is beyond this bend!