I!
Run!
Kagome!
I've wanted this woman!
I had wanted you!
No!
Why, you!
Kagome! Get away!
'Kay!
Hey! Don't interfere!
Hold it!
Why go after Kagome?
Kagome?
No! That woman!
...is MINE!
Why, you!
Die!
Wind Scar!
Woman!
You...
...are!
I wonder why he tried
to capture Kagome.
The spider scar
on his back proves
that he is an offshoot
of Naraku's body.
There's no way he survived
a direct blow from the Wind Scar.
And yet...
Yeah... I don't like it.
Inuyasha!
Old Kaede!
What is going on?!
You're too late!
Huh? What happened?
Nothing.
It's over.
It should be over.
Hey, are you all right?
How do you feel?
Better, thanks to you.
We'll change the poultice later.
Kikyo?
What's the matter?
You needn't be afraid here.
Master Muso...
My teacher was killed
and his face was stolen.
How cruel!
Who did it?
He was faceless!
And... on his back was
the pattern of a spider!
Spider?
I'm so afraid! So afraid!
Take him inside to rest.
Yes.
A spider pattern on his back?
It must be an offspring
of Naraku.
That demon! What is he up to?
Kikyo...
Naraku, you have reason to
be concerned about me.
Because...
Inside you the heart of Onigumo
beats steadily.
Damn that Naraku! How long does
he intend to keep me like this?
Damn him!
Kagura!
Naraku!
Do you want to be released?
I told you! I won't try
to run away anymore.
Follow the one
who calls himself Muso.
Muso?
Your younger brother.
Naraku's new offshoot?
And inform Inuyasha and his bunch
of Muso's whereabouts.
What?!
As if he would go
anywhere else.
Damn! How dare he do this to me?!
Who is this Inuyasha?
Inuyasha!
I... know... him?
Just... who am I?
See ya!
Are you really sure?
Yeah.
You'd better go back
for the time being.
How unusual. You're usually against
my going home.
I said you can go this time!
Really?
I'm worried about my test score,
so if it's all right to go,
I'm grateful.
I think it's wise for you
to lie low for a while.
Until we know just what
Naraku is up to.
He's right.
I'm uneasy, too.
Okay, then.
Hey!
Who are you?!
Hmm... Nice armor.
What?!
What is it about this scenery?
It looks so familiar.
Is it really better to go home?
I don't know just who
this Muso is.
But he tried to capture you, right?
Uh-huh.
But Muso was destroyed by
Inuyasha's Wind Scar.
Hmm... Inuyasha's being
extra cautious.
He's fought several
of Naraku's offshoots.
But he's never been
this cautious before.
Naraku, huh?
I have an uneasy feeling
about this, too.
I think I'll go take a look.
At what?
You go back home.
I'm going to the cave.
Cave?
You mean, that one?
Huh? What's that?
A cavern?
I think I know...
...this place?
Say, Inuyasha?
What?
Just where are we headed?
Naraku's castle.
You know where it is?
As if!
Then we're just
walking around in circles?
Stupid!
We're backtracking the path
that Muso took!
Should we take a look at the
villages he pillaged?
Perhaps we should go to the site
where the bandits were slaughtered, too.
Kagura!
Yo!
You! What're you doing here?
I'm not here to fight.
I thought I'd tell you
where Muso is.
Muso?
Then he's still alive?!
I had a bad feeling about that...
But why are you here to
tell us where he is?
You familiar with the cave where
Kikyo and Onigumo stayed?
Muso is headed there.
What?!
Muso's going to that cave?!
Anyway, I told you.
See ya!
Wait!
Did Naraku send you?
Take a guess.
Does Naraku know
Inuyasha's secret?
That's enough, Miroku!
Secret?
I... didn't see anything.
That woman!
What's she thinking?!
Kagura tried to run away with
the Sacred Jewel fragments.
It sure doesn't seem like
she's being obedient to him.
I wonder if maybe Kagura
hasn't told Naraku...
about your secret
on the night of the new moon.
Still, she's not an ally.
But what'll we do?
About Muso?
If we take Kagura's word
for it and believe her...
Huh?
How unusual! Usually, you'd
take off right away to fight!
Shaddup!
l just!
What's upsetting you, Inuyasha?
I'm not upset!
That Muso... He just bothers me!
Who the hell is he?!
I just don't understand
that Naraku.
Inform Inuyasha and his bunch
of Muso's whereabouts.
And keep watch over him.
It's like he's curious about
Muso's actions.
Does that mean that unlike me,
Muso isn't under Naraku's control?
Kaede.
Kagome, you didn't go home?
I thought I'd better take a look
at that cave, too.
It's up ahead.
I remember...
Right here... someone...
Who... is that?!
Over there.
So that's where Onigumo
once stayed.
This is... where it all began.
Kagome.
Err... It's nothing.
I wanted that woman.
I... l... was here and...
Watch your step.
Uh-huh. I'll be all right, Kaede.
That woman!
Yes!
I... wanted that woman!
Even if it meant selling my soul
to demons!
That woman... that woman!
Kikyo!
Muso!
Muso?!
Yes! I remember now!
I wanted Kikyo!
What?! Why now?!
Kaede!
I remember his aura!
But I can't believe it!
Why is he here now?!
Don't get in my way, hag!
I want that woman!
That woman who is identical
to Kikyo!
I knew it!
You are the fugitive Onigumo!
Onigumo?!
You're in my way!
Stop it!
I'm the one you want, right?
But you won't get me
that easily!
Granny Kaede, run now!
Hold it!
He's just!
Just who are you?
Looking like Kikyo!
Who are you?!
Kagome!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
Inuyasha!
Fool! Why didn't you go back?
Hah! Not you again!
Interfering again, huh, Inuyasha?
What?!
Kagome!
Why are you?!
It's Muso!
I finally remembered.
That I used to be a bandit.
And the time that I stayed here
in this cave with Kikyo.
Why, you!
What're you talking about?!
Inuyasha!
He's Onigumo!
Onigumo?
The bastard who fed his soul
to demons and
became the nucleus of Naraku?
Well said.
I see...
Onigumo's entire body was
badly burned...
Even his face was burned away.
That's why he kept stealing
his victims' faces.
So Onigumi's heart burst out
of Naraku?
I remembered everything!
Kikyo died back then.
Damn you! You!
You wounded Kikyo!
Are you kidding?!
Why do you think
I fed my very soul to demons?
I wanted possession of the
Sacred Jewel AND a free body...
so I could steal Kikyo away
and leave this cave.
But when I got my new body...
nothing went my way.
The first thing I did when
I left the cave...
...was to mangle the woman
I sold my soul for.
When Naraku was born, Onigumo
still had some will.
But Naraku was created from the union
of hundreds of demons.
And those demons
had one desire...
The death of my sister,
the shrine maiden.
And the result of all this was...
Kikyo followed that half-demon
in death.
Kikyo died.
And the Sacred Jewel burned away
along with Kikyo's corpse.
At that moment...
Disappear!
Someone locked me away
in a deep, dark place.
That was Naraku!
I don't know
how long I slept then.
But when I awoke, I had been
hurled into the outside world.
He remembered nothing.
Not even about Naraku.
Have you received no orders
from Naraku?
Hah! I don't take orders
from anyone.
l just kill everyone I hate,
then burn them away!
Now then, Inuyasha...
I'll start with you.
Just why are you still alive?
When Kikyo is dead?!
Speak for yourself!
Coming alive again!
After I kill you,
it'll be that woman!
W-What?!
Don't you dare touch Kagome!
I'll take you on!
All right! Let's do it!
Poison insect!
Mistress Kaede and Kagome...
please get back!
Hah!
I don't know why Naraku
let you out!
But you and Naraku are
one and the same!
I avenge Kikyo's death now!
Try it!
Huh?!
The scar closed on the sword!
I see! Muso has the ultimate power
to regenerate!
Who cares!
It seems that your weird sword
is useless against me!
Why, you!
My Wind Tunnel would've taken
care of him!
Does this mean Naraku is
protecting Onigumo?
Probably.
That's why he sent
the Poison Insects
to prevent me from
using my Wind Tunnel...
But Muso said he takes orders
from no one.
I don't understand Naraku's intent!
Again?
Naraku!
I wanted to see you
in person.
What do you want?
I came to test it...
My power right now.
I already told you.
A half-demon who harbors
Onigumo's heart,
has no power to kill me!
Onigumo's heart?
You're right... If I still had
Onigumo's heart,
I wouldn't be able to
lay a hand on you, Kikyo.
Even if your existence is artificial.
Why, you!
I knew you're weren't real...
Yet I was unable to reach out
to take you...
A woman made of clay
and bones.
What's wrong, Naraku?
Weren't you going to kill me?
Don't get cocky, Kikyo.
It's not because I fear you
that I didn't kill you.
It suits my purpose.
Besides, I'm not going to kill you.
I'm going to break you.
Onigumo isn't completely severed
from me yet.
What's the matter?!
Wind Scar!
Did he succeed?
I'm not sure.
His ability to regenerate...
It doesn't work.
Wind Scar!
Inuyasha!
I don't believe he can keep
regenerating.
I hope you're right.
Muso said he doesn't take orders
from Naraku.
So he's not under Naraku's control?
He's a part of Naraku,
yet is that possible?
Fool! Don't you understand?
That it's useless to no matter
how many times you try.
He resurrected himself again!
Damn!
Isn't there a way to destroy him?!
He's transforming even more!
Why, that!
I'm getting used to
this body!
Inuyasha! Above you!
Inuyasha!
Onigumi's heart was alive
and continued to beat inside Naraku.
Naraku got rid of it
and it became Muso.
But it's weird, Kagome.
Naraku is trying to
protect Muso.
Why help it if he tried
to get rid of it?
Naraku is trying to
absorb Muso back into his body!
Huh?! Muso got his claws
into Naraku!
What's going on?!
Are Muso and Naraku enemies?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Three-Sided Battle to the Death"
The key to it all is
that spider on the back!