Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
The shard sleeps here...
at the border between
this life and the next.
The gate at the Realm of Fire
has been opened.
But as we search for
another route,
another formidable enemy
appears.
Go!
It opened!
Wha?!
There! Beyond the gate!
Do you want to pass?
Or not?
Dammit!
Who'd want to pass, idiot?!
Then...
We shall close the gate.
Is that true, Kagome?
I'm sure of it.
When the gate opened,
I sensed the presence of
the Sacred Jewel shard.
So it's there...
Somewhere over in that world...
the Sacred Jewel shard.
Hmmm...
To think that the shard
was really there...
Myoga...
W-What are you doing?!
Were you aware that we'd turn
to stone if we went that way?
Would I have followed you into
such a dangerous place if I knew?!
That's true.
But at least we verified that
there is a Sacred Jewel shard there.
So it wasn't a futile exercise.
Yes.
Also, Hakudoshi and Naraku
are living beings of this world.
So they won't be able to pass
through to the other side either.
We're in the same predicament.
Well, I guess we just have to
find another way.
There has to be another path.
The path that the Sacred Jewel
shard took.
Yes. We must get the shard,
before it's taken by
Naraku or Hakudoshi.
Oh, a village!
Let us stay the night
in that village.
Something's weird.
There's no sign of people.
What's that?!
Huh?!
What?!
They're all dead.
Miroku, they've all had their
blood sucked out.
Hey! There're more over there.
What could have happened here?!
If they had their blood sucked out...
Could it be a demon like Old Myoga?
No way!
Hey, Myoga!
Do you know anything?
Huh? Gone already.
Hah! What a pathetic village!
No rice or sake!
What a waste of our time.
Men! We leave!
Yessir!
Huh?!
What's that?
Birds?
- They're no ordinary birds!
- Demons!
Men!
Don't fight. There's enough for all.
Now heed this...
Don't leave a drop of blood.
What's wrong?
The Bird Master, Princess Abi.
Who are you?
Create a path for me.
How dare you order me around like that?!
It's not an order. It's a trade.
Not again...
How terrible!
They've had their blood sucked out.
It's probably the work of
a demon, right?
Yeah. While we were in
the Realm of Fire,
some nasty demon wreaked
havoc around here.
Let us hurry.
Another village may become
a target.
Naraku... you said your name was?
If I lend you my help,
what's in it for me?
Princess Abi, you use your birds to
collect human blood.
For what purpose?
The one inside that cave
is your mother, am I right?
It seems that she is
on the verge of death.
She ate a poisonous demon
and became sick.
But she's not dying.
I'm giving her human blood to
dilute the poison.
Princess...
All you need to do is
to keep collecting the blood.
So that your mother
recovers quickly.
But if you promise to
help me,
I will help you gather
blood even faster.
Without any interruption
from anyone.
That is made from my bones.
I shall lend it to you.
Huh?!
Yo! Princess Abi!
Where is your mother?
Why should I tell you?
She ate our father!
She won't get away with it!
She sure ate him,
but he wasn't very good.
What?!
It doesn't matter! You will do!
We'll avenge our father!
Die! Princess Abi!
I won't fall to the likes of you!
Brother!
As if you could defeat me!
Maybe not one-on-one.
But feel our combined power!
Why you!
You shall die from our poison!
Don't mess with me!
Poison this weak...
You!
Who are you?!
Princess Abi's ally?
If you do not know who Naraku is...
you shall find out!
Those insects will be useful, too.
I doubt that!
Humph! Annoying bastard.
Use him...
Mother!
That Naraku has a powerful aura,
but he's still just a half-demon.
Yes, I figured that out.
Just use him and when he makes
a suspicious move,
feed him to the birds.
You're right. First, we must
collect blood.
Don't mess around with me,
you brat!
Are you in pain?
Naraku just grasped your heart...
from somewhere.
Just remember this, Kagura.
Naraku and I are connected.
So think before you act
next time.
Although...
I'd never be killed
by the likes of you.
That Hakudoshi is annoying,
but the real problem is...
Naraku.
As long as he has a grasp
on my heart,
I am not the wind.
I'll be chained and bound
to him...
A neighboring village was attacked,
and we fear that we may be next.
You're probably right.
All the villages we passed
had been attacked.
Huh?!
Just as we feared...
This is terrible!
What are we going to do?!
Inuyasha, don't scare everyone.
What? I'm just telling 'em the truth!
Fear not. We shall exterminate
the demons for you.
Is that true?!
We don't need payment for this.
We just ask for lodgings, food and women.
What did you just say?!
Just joking.
Well then, how about just the women?
I said I'm joking!
Don't even say it.
Uh-huh!
Are you sure about these people?
But who else can we ask?
Thanks to Miroku,
they've lost all confidence in us.
No kidding!
Pa!
What's this?!
Something's strange...
Do not go outside!
Yes!
What are they?!
Birds?!
These birds have the smell of
blood all over them!
Are they demons that
attacked the villages?
Yeah, I'm sure of it!
W-What's happening?!
They're attacking!
Wind Scar!
They're coming again!
T-They're on fire!
They're burning the houses
to force the villagers outside!
Grandpa!
Why you!
Hiraikotsu!
They're coming again!
Let's finish this!
Wind Tunnel!
Wow! In one swoop!
Saimyosho!
No! Miroku, you'll be poisoned!
That's!
Just who are you?
Why'd you interfere?!
I'd say the same about you!
Are you one of Naraku's minions?
Naraku?
The Saimyosho flying around
you are proof!
I know nothing.
I don't know what's going on
between you and Naraku,
but you killed my birds.
I'll kill every one of you and
drain every drop of your blood!
Now die!
It's not my style to slay women,
but I don't like your attitude!
Slay?!
That's a laugh!
You're just another half-demon
like Naraku!
What?!
How dare you involve me
in your petty half-demon quarrels!
Watch out!
We'll be killed!
Get the villagers outta here!
'Kay! Run, everyone!
- Hurry!
- This way!
Don't let anyone escape!
Suck out their blood!
Take this!
Damn you!
Inuyasha!
Curse you!
Damn!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
Who is this half-demon?!
His aura is stronger than I thought.
A barrier!
She deflected his Wind Scar!
This trident... put up a barrier?
This is made with my bones.
I knew it! You are one of
Naraku's minions!
That was Naraku's power!
Naraku...
Did he give me this trident to
force me to fight that half-demon?
Hold it!
She ran away?
Dammit!
The... village...
We should be thankful
we're alive at least.
But if you promise to help me,
I will help you gather
blood even faster.
He sounds too suspicious.
She called herself Princess Abi.
She seems to be connected
to Naraku,
but she really didn't seem
like one of his minions.
We're talking about Naraku.
I'm quite sure he's just
using her.
For what?
That female demon is using her
birds to suck the blood out of humans.
Why would Naraku be interested
in helping her?
But it's certain that she's helping him.
Naraku is trying to find a way to get
to the border between this life and the next,
in order to get the Sacred Jewel shard.
And is collecting human blood
somehow connected to that?
Well, it's the only thing
we have to go on.
Whatever the connection...
With your brain, Inuyasha,
you wouldn't be able to figure it out.
- What did you say, Shippo?!
- Owww!
- And you think your brain can?
- Oww!
Shippo, you said too much just now.
Hah! Heard her?
Inuyasha, now you're overdoing it.
S-l-!
In any case, we must stop
this Princess Abi.
Yes, before more innocent
lives are lost.
She reeks with the smell of blood.
It'll be easy to find her!
The path that leads to the border
between this world and the next.
It will soon open.
Fifty years ago, my sister Kikyo sealed
Inuyasha to this sacred tree.
Inuyasha, you who stole
my sister's Sacred Jewel...
How can you sleep
so peacefully?
Will you stop your fighting
and become a human being?
Me? Become a human?
Next, an Inuyasha special:
"The Tragic Love Song of Destiny"
The answer lies in the Bone Eater's Well.