My name is Shippo.
I'm a baby fox-demon of justice!
With vassals Inuyasha and others,
I roam the countryside
conquering evil demons.
But sometimes, even I need
a respite from time to time.
But the peace was to last
but a moment.
An arrow bearing
a message!
What?!
A challenge to a duel?!
Raiju... Soten?
This was just a prelude
to my continuing life
as a fighting warrior.
Soten, I have delivered the letter.
The time has come.
I, Koryu, have waited so long
for this day.
I beseech you to do your utmost
as the sole survivor of the Raiju Tribe!
Let's see...
"To Shippo...
"To uphold the honor of
the Raiju Tribe,
"I challenge you to a
duel to the death.
"On this day at sundown, I await
your coming at Raimei Valley.
"If you dare run away, consider
your friends' lives to be lost."
Is that a challenge to a duel?
Raimei Valley is close by.
Isn't that where the
Thunder Brothers used to live?
I wonder if Hiten and Manten
were relatives?
Hah! Sending a challenge like that...
shows some guts.
Hey you! Don't read my letter!
But it's strange...
What is?
If the Raiju Tribe wanted revenge,
their enemy shouldn't be you,
Shippo...
But Inuyasha who actually
fought the brothers.
That's right!
Well, that's probably because
Inuyasha is a half-demon...
and not good enough
for the Raiju Tribe.
What?!
What will you do?
Will you fight this Soten?
Can't be helped.
If I avenged my pa's death,
someone will come after
me in vengeance.
That's the fate of fighters.
Hah! What a show-off!
Hah! You're just jealous
'cuz I'm better!
What?!
Do you want us to help you?
We'll make it real cheap.
Feel free to ask.
All I want in payment is an
introduction to a pretty girl.
You two!
Hah! I won't lift a finger
no matter what happens!
Don't worry!
I can handle the Raiju Tribe!
That's the valley where the
Thunder Brothers lived.
That's no ordinary miasma.
Yeah... That's one place where
the weather always sucks.
Shippo, don't be proud.
Ask them for help.
No!
If I did, my honor as the recipient
of the challenge would be damaged!
Boo!
Hah! What honor?!
You talk big, but
you're scared already!
- Oh dear...
- This is bad.
- Think so.
- Me too.
What are you writing, Soten?
Koryu...
Stop waffling, and come here!
Yes!
This is our strategy.
Memorize it well.
Strategy?
Aren't you going to
fight fair and square?
Do you think a pretty child like me
has a chance against those ruffians?!
Well, that's true...
This monk named Miroku has
a Wind Tunnel that sucks up everything!
This Sango is an expert
Demon Slayer!
Furthermore, she has a
demon cat named Kirara.
I know that. Since I'm the one that
researched it all.
On top of that, this Inuyasha
and Kagome duo are even worse!
How many demons do you think
have fallen at their feet?
If I fought fair and square,
I would not live through this!
That would mean the absolute
extinction of the Raiju Tribe!
Then...
- Isn't it better to just live peacefully?
- No!
They are my hated enemies!
I must get Shippo, at least!
Oh dear...
Stop complaining and
put this plan into action!
They are already nearby!
All right!
Shippo... You!
Stop stalling like that!
Hey, calm down.
But Shippo, at this rate,
you won't make it by sundown.
Didn't it say so in the letter?
That's right!
The challenge!
Say Kagome...
Yes?
This is ONLY read as "Shippo"?
Yes.
There's no other reading?
For example, "Inuyasha"?
You! Can't you even read
your own name?
Don't tease me! I was just
checking!
Yes, it's me!
It's a letter challenging me!
Just wait, Soten!
I'm coming!
Shippo... You're not making
any progress.
I can't stand it any longer!
l-Inuyasha!
All right, everyone!
I really don't need any help
this time!
Who'd help!
Hurry it up!
Inuyasha!
The opponent is a member of
the dreaded Raiju Tribe!
Kagome, you can take shelter
somewhere safe.
All right.
You too, Sango and Miroku!
He really wants help.
I think so.
Why doesn't he just
come out and ask?
First, we separate Shippo
from the others with a boulder.
Kagome!
Shippo!
What's he doing?!
Nooooo!
It went well, Soten!
Ohhhh yes! I forgot!
Change!
Help!
Shippo!
- That klutz!
- He's done for.
Damn! He's hopeless!
Hey! Lemme outta here!
Welcome Shippo!
Huh? I don't have any business
with a small fry like you.
Where's the leader?
Call Soten the leader of
the Raiju Tribe.
- That's me.
- Huh?
- You must be lying.
- I'm not! Can't you see?
No, I can't.
That's why I'm asking.
How stupid! I don't have time to
be playing with a kid.
What?!
Don't treat me like a kid!
Oh, really?
Oh?
That's nice, what you have there.
Let me have it.
See? You ARE a kid!
What about you!
What?
I'm a fine full-fledged demon!
So am I!
Stop blabbering and give it to me!
- No way!
- Give it to me!
No way! No way!
They're both so childish.
Hey Koryu! There are things
you must do!
Oh, yes... You're right.
What's that?
Next, we take Kirara out.
Even if she transforms,
she's still just a cat.
She should get drunk
on silver vine.
Evil minds are so active.
What's the matter, Kirara?
- This smell is silver vine.
- What?
Oh dear... Is this another trap?
We'll just have to walk from here.
What's the matter, miss?
Please help me...
Miroku! Be careful!
It may be a trap!
Sango, I live according to
Buddha's teachings.
No matter when or why,
I will never turn my back on one in need.
If this is a trap,
I will gladly fall into it.
You're SUCH a nice person, Miroku.
Miroku's weakness is women.
And Sango cannot leave
Miroku alone.
We'll use those traits to
our advantage to get them both.
Please... Please come closer.
Oh yes, of course.
Stop, Miroku!
Please tell me what's wrong...
Good!
Didn't I tell you?!
It's all your fault!
I'm ashamed of myself.
Lemme out! I thought you
wanted a duel!
Don't try to intimidate me.
What?!
Didn't you send this?!
Fool! That was just a trap to
lure you out!
Trap?!
Why you! What're you planning
to do with me?
Hm-hmmm... I'm going to kill
you very slowly.
What?!
Cry! Scream! All you want!
Damn!
Oh, I guess...
You're weak.
That's why you're avoiding
a fight.
You're pretty shrewd.
But! I'm smart.
In order to compensate for
my weakness,
I've come up with
brilliant strategies!
That's dirty, you coward!
Silence! You're the coward!
Depending on your comrades for help!
I did not ask them for help!
They just came!
- Excuses! Weakling!
- I'm not a weakling! Coward!
- Weakling! Weakling! Weakling!
- Coward! Coward! Coward! Coward!
What are Miroku and Sango doing?!
They're late.
All right, here they come.
Inuyasha is helpless against
Kagome's "sit"command.
So this is it!
Inuyasha!
Sit!
Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit!
Hey!
Why?! Why doesn't
Kagome's "sit" work?!
What?! That's supposed to
be ME?!
Isn't she identical?
What's identical about her?!
Why you! Hope you're prepared.
Oh, I have to be getting back.
Wait! As if I'll let you go!
Oh dear...
Well?! Give up?
Silence! You're the one
who has to surrender!
But you have strange
writing utensils.
These? Kagome gave me
these... They're called crayons.
How nice! Give them to me.
Absolutely not!
Give them to me! Stingy!
Let's see... If you let me out,
I may consider it.
Look! Isn't it nice?
I want them! Want them! Want them!
Then come on... Let me out.
I won't fall for that.
I'm going to slowly kill you.
Then let's duel and the winner
can have the crayons.
Oh, that's a good idea.
He could be really dumb...
How unusual...
A flying snake.
A dragon!
Don't talk big!
You're a Raiju demon, aren't you?
How dare you!
I belong to the honorable dragon!
Don't talk big, I said!
Damn... Just one more time!
Hey! What do you think
my head is?!
Shut up!
Now I'll be able to escape.
Inuyasha!
Enough already.
Poor thing.
Kagome! Stay out of it!
I don't need your pity!
I belong to the Dragon Tribe!
Just hit me all you want!
Huh? You're pretty brave, aren't you?
Damn... It didn't work.
Come on... Where is Soten?
Shippo's with him, right?
Who'd tell?!
Why you!
That's it!
- Huh?!
- What?!
Shocked?
When my head is hit three times,
I transform!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Damn!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Why didn't you come at
us from the start!
Useless! It's useless!
What?!
Tetsusaiga won't work on him!
Now Inuyasha!
Prepare yourself!
Are you prepared, Shippo?!
That's my line!
On guard!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
What the hell do we do?!
If the opponent is a cloud,
the Wind Scar won't work.
Kagome!
Now! I'll take care of
the girl first!
Kagome!
l-Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
Take this!
Fox Fire!
That's nothing!
Lightning Attack!
Wow... You're pretty strong.
Of course!
Who do you think I am?!
All right... I'm serious from now.
Me too!
Even Inuyasha is helpless
against my arrows!
Inuyasha! Are you all right?
You're okay?
Okay? They were just claptrap.
What?!
Huh?! Ridiculous!
Then!
You can touch them.
Poke yourself.
Oh, you're right.
Say, this may work on
shoulder aches.
I know!
W-What!
What a waste of my time!
You change if you're hit
three times, right?
Really?
Don't act innocent!
How cruel!
Now take us to this Soten!
You're good.
You, too.
Fox magic! Smashing top!
Thunder magic! Falling daruma!
Take my screaming mushrooms!
Hah! Then try my laughing acorns!
H-Hey Soten...
Isn't it about time you give up?
Shut up! What about you?
Which is dearer?
Your life or the crayons!
Shippo!
Oh Inuyasha! You're alive!
Inuyasha!
Koryu! Did you fail?!
Forgive me, Soten.
Hey, wait!
Is he the one?!
Yeah! This is Soten, the one
who sent me the challenge!
So cute!
What?!
Good boy!
Hey! Don't treat me
like a child!
I'm the leader of the Raiju Tribe!
Okay.
Don't touch my forehead!
Hah! Have we been running around
because of this kid?!
Hah! I told you I didn't need
any help!
How old are you, little boy?
Don't insult me!
I'm not a boy!
I'm a girl!
Huh?!
You're a girl?
You're even cuter!
Don't touch my forehead!
G-Girl?!
She's a girl?!
This is so stupid.
I'm going home.
Hey wait!
Shippo, are you running away?!
Does that mean you admit
your loss?
Yeah... Here, you can have it.
Good children must behave.
Don't even think about
vengeance anymore.
And so, my battle to the death ended.
I succeeded in defying fate
and a vendetta.
And those evil conniving two,
Soten and Koryu, learned a lesson
and will never challenge me
to a duel again.
With this experience, I grew
even more mature.
However, there are still many
enemies lying in wait for me.
I must not stand idle
or look back.
Yes, that is the path of
a warrior like me
whose destiny is to fight.
Quit putting on an act!
Kagome!
Inuyasha is picking on me!
Inu-yasha!
Wait! Kagome!
Sit!
Good for him!
Damn! What is he?!
Sorry, Inuyasha!
I was telling everyone about you,
and the misunderstanding grew!
This isn't the time!
Another Naraku puppet
has appeared!
But... from misunderstanding
to misunderstanding,
now they think you're
just some delinquent.
The guy goes around killing people
and stealing their faces!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Terror of the Faceless Man!"
By the way, Kagome,
what's a "delinquent"?