Okay, three minutes are up.
Tastes great!
Kagome, this is really good!
Oh yeah? I'm glad.
Aren't you having some?
Listen you!
How can you eat in
a place like this...
the aftermath of
a battle?
You suddenly decide
you're hungry...
and take everthing out
of my backpack!
What's wrong with having
a leisurely lunch...
by a pretty stream
or a field of flowers?
Oh, you!
You're so uncouth!
I must say, though, Kagome...
your country has many
convenient things.
I was shocked at
your "bicycle."
But a thing that
tells time...
and by looking at
your strange foodstuffs...
you do much trade with
foreigners from the south.
Wow! Myoga, you're very smart.
However, did you know that cup noodle
was invented by the Japanese?
It was intended for use
up in outer space.
Outer space?
Yes.
Humans go to outer space...
Oh yeah, did you know we
even went to the moon!
The moon?
How?!
Using a rocket.
A rocket?
It's huge...
and fire shoots out
from the bottom...
and kaboom!
By next time,
I'll have studied up on it!
What?! It suddenly got dark.
What's this?!
Master Inuyasha, you mustn't litter!
This is no time to be
concerned about that!
You there!
You posses the Sacred Jewel!
What?!
A demon?
No...
That's fox fire!
Fox fire?!
Hand it over!
Or I'll kill you!
Oww!
Huh?
A child?!
What're you doing?!
You heathen!
Hey!
You've got a tail!
Hah! You're just a baby fox
in disguise!
Yea, I'm a fox!
Huh?! A fox?
How cute!
Let me hold him next!
Why're you lining up
behind me?
Huh?! Ajizo statue?
My things!
Here it is! A fragment of
the Sacred Jewel!
Ah-hah-hah! It's mine!
Farewell!
He disappeared!
My name is Shippo.
Why are you after the
Sacred Jewel fragment?
To avenge...
To avenge my father!
Avenge?
Was your father killed?
Hmm... So you wanted to
gain strength...
by using the Sacred Jewel fragment?
Hah! I'm strong even without
the Sacred Jewel fragment!
What're you doing?!
Are you listening?!
Huh?
What's that cloud?
Ready to hunt, Manten?
Yes, Brother Hiten!
Thunderbolt attack!
Witness our power!
They annihilated the enemy
in one blow!
Are the beast-monsters
our allies?!
Huh? Allies?
Don't make me laugh!
Boy, wasn't that fun, Manten?
It sure was, Brother Hiten.
I have so much power
left over.
The power of the Sacred Jewel
imbedded in my forehead is real.
I'll say!
So let's keep gathering
more and more, Manten!
Yeah!
We'll look high and low for beasts like
this fox who possess the Sacred Jewel
and beat 'em to death!
Your father possessed a
Sacred Jewel fragment?!
Those two go around killing demons
who possess fragments.
Those two?
The Thunder Brothers.
Thunder Brothers?
You mean, Hiten and Manten?
I have heard that they are
unruly, mean brothers.
So what?
If we defeat them, we'll get
several fragments at once!
Don't make me laugh!
You wouldn't be able to take
them on!
You're just a half-demon,
aren't you?
I can smell the
human in you!
Just a half-demon...
you should stay out of
demon affairs!
Shippo... That wasn't
a nice thing to...
Why you!
Inuyasha!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
As long as you understand.
In penance...
Hey you!
As long as the charm
stays on...
the jizo statue
will not move!
Shippo!
You're partly to blame, too.
Hah!
Inuyasha, stop playing around!
I can't get it off!
I don't like to play
tricks on women, but...
I need you to sleep
for a while!
That hurt!
Tadah!
I'll use this to lure out
the Thunder Brothers!
Huh?
The Sacred Jewel fragments!
Give them back or
I'll get mad!
Kagome!
Peel off the charm first!
Hey!
Hey you!
If only I had a little
more hair.
Then I'd be popular
like Brother Hiten.
Huh?
He's not coming after me.
Hmm... What's this?
If it ain't the son of that
fox I killed!
Y-You!
Hah!
Your father's fur is
sooo warm!
Why you!
How dare you do that
to my father... Why!
WHY!!
Hey, those are Sacred
Jewel fragments!
You... Those are the fragments
of the Sacred Jewel.
Give them to me!
If you don't!
Darn!
I did it.
What?
Hey, you!
Don't move!
I'll hit you right
in the brain next!
A monster!
Don't run!
I just asked you to
peel off the charm!
Kagome!
My nose hurts!
Don't move!
Shippo, come here.
Hurry!
Why you!
Leave the Sacred Jewel fragments!
Wait!
He has two fragments
in his forehead!
If I aim there,
I can bring him down!
Darn, I just grazed him!
Huh? What's wrong?
My hair!
How could you?!
Watch out! Run!
My father was killed
by that!
Did I strike them dead?
Kagome, hang on!
Why, it's only a woman!
Huh?
So... pretty!
Kagome!
You helped me, yet
I abandoned you and ran away!
D-Damn!
Ohh... It's not working!
Master Inuyasha, I can't
peel this charm off.
Damn that punk fox!
Hey!
I'm willing to help you.
But you must promise
NOT to hit me.
Hmm? You alone?
Where's Kagome?
Will you promise or not?!
I won't hit you, stupid!
Now listen quietly.
You promised not to hit me!
Oh yeah... One more.
Sacred Jewel fragments.
Good.
All intact.
Will you pay attention?!
Kagome's been captured
by the Thunder Brothers!
This is no time for that!
Huh? Thunder Brothers?
They're the ones that
killed your father?
You came across them?
Hmm... You don't look like
you avenged his death.
Did you hide and watch
Kagome being kidnapped?
Sh-Shut up!
Hurry and rescue her!
Isn't she your woman?!
Huh?!
No way!
Hey!
Well, I'll save her...
Huh?
Well, why don't you
grovel at my feet?
Then I'll let bygones
be bygones.
Why!!
Shippo, just do as
he says.
You need to act like
an adult now.
Grr... Why must I
stoop so low?!
But I can't save her
by myself.
Damn!
Please help me!
Get off your knees!
Let's go!
Huh?
Awake, are you?
Wh-Where am I?
Y-You intend to eat me?!
No!
The flesh and blood of pretty,
young women promote healthy hair.
I'm gonna boil you down into a potion
and apply it to my head.
Wh-hhat?!
I'd rather be eaten than
put on your head!!
Shhh!
Not so loud!
If Brother Hiten finds you here,
he'll really eat you!
Yo, Manten!
You're home.
Hmm... You don't look
alike at all!
Brother Hiten!
Who's that woman?
She's my prey!
Don't worry, I won't
lay claim on her.
I've got a better woman
right here!
He seems more human.
Maybe he'll be more receptive.
Hey, Manten.
Did you find a
new Sacred Jewel fragment?
Huh?
Errr... That's right.
Hmm?
Sorry, Brother!
I found one, but...
But what?
Don't tell me that you were more
interested in a woman...
and failed to get the
Sacred Jewel fragment?!
Brother! Sorry!
You're so hopeless!
If you weren't my kid brother...
you wouldn't have enough
lives to survive!
Who is he?!
He's so frightening!
What?!
That fox tyke has the
Sacred Jewel fragments?!
Are you gonna go for them,
Brother Hiten?
Of course!
Come on!
It's my chance to escape!
Wait!
What're you doing?!
What'm I doing?!
I'm gonna kill you so
you can't escape! What else?
I need you to make my
hair potion!
Wait! If you kill me, you won't...
Won't what?
Well...
Won't be able to get
the Sacred Jewel fragments!
What?!
I got it!
I can handle the stupid one.
The older brother may just
go for it.
Do you two know Inuyasha?
He's quite strong.
Strong?
I've heard of 'im.
But isn't he just a
half-demon?
He's strong!
He's defeated demons
from high and low...
and has most of the Sacred
Jewel fragments.
- Wha...
...at?!
Good! He bit it!
Hey! You'd better not
be lying!
Humph...
Inuyasha...
is in love with me.
Huh?
If you ask for an exchange...
I'm sure he'll gladly exchange
the fragments for me!
Brother Hiten, she's gotta
be lying!
I think I'll believe her.
Huh?
Woman!
Take us to this Inuyasha.
However...
If you've been lying, your pretty face
will end up black and charred.
He means it...
This arrogant oaf!
What's wrong, Shippo?
You're screaming your head off.
If you're scared, just go back.
Stupid! I'm going to avenge
my father!
You'd better be as strong
as you say you are!
The Thunder Brothers have used
the Sacred Jewel fragments...
to increase their power!
Whoa!
That makes beating them
even more fun!
Still, I'm worried about
Kagome!
That woman is fine! She's got
a tenacious streak in her.
I hope so...
According to rumors, those two brothers
devour pretty girls immediately!
Is that true?!
What'll we do?
Does that mean Kagome has already...
Stupid!
What's pretty about Kagome?
What?!
Are you totally blind?!
Yes, I think she's very pretty, too.
I'll bet she's already
been eaten!
It's all my fault!
"Pretty woman, short life."
What a wise saying.
Inuyasha!
How can you stand there
looking so blank?!
Kagome is a beauty! So she
may already have been eaten up!
So... Tell me what's pretty
about Kagome?
I've been thinking this from before...
but I think your perception of
beauty is a little off.
Aghhh! No wonder you look and
dress so weird!
I agree... A red outfit is
a bit troubling.
I think you should dress with
a little more refinement.
Aghh! Shut up!
How did the subject turn
to the way I dress?!
Humph, so you thwarted me!
For someone yapping out loud
in front of someone's front yard...
you move fast.
You must be the one...
Inuyasha the half-demon.
Master Inuyasha, that's the older
Thunder Brother, Hiten.
Hey you!
Where's Kagome?!
Relax, I haven't started
eating her yet.
Manten!
Yo! Tadah!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
She's still alive!
By your expression, looks like
the woman spoke the truth.
Hand over every fragment
of the Sacred Jewel!
If you want to save the
woman you love!
The woman I love?
W-wait!
Who said I love her?!
Don't be so embarrassed!
So you WERE lying!
Who'd hand over the precious
fragments just for you?!
What?! You intend to
abandon me?!
Abandon?!
You make it sound like you
and I are an item!
Which is more important?!
Me or the Sacred Jewel fragments?!
If you dare choose the fragments,
I'll rip your lips out!
Whatever!
One thing seems true... You have the
fragments of the Sacred Jewel.
I'm gonna kill you and take 'em all!
Hah! You'll be the sorry one!
Thunderbolt attack!
Hah! I wonder just how long you
can hold out against my strikes?
You've got brute strength,
at least.
This is gonna be fun!
Thunder Brothers, huh?
I'm getting tired of you!
Shippo, the fox tyke is seeking
revenge.
With Tetsusaiga, Inuyasha should have
an easy time...
defeating a Thunder Brother
or two.
Hiten has three fragments and
Manten has two.
Five Sacred Jewel fragments can be
won or lost in this match!
But when the five fragments get into
the hands of the enemy...
an even more frightening demon
confronts Inuyasha!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Phantom Showdown:
The Thunder Brothers vs. Tetsusaiga".
Don't miss it!