I'm Kagome Higurashi.
Born into an old and respected
family of shrine keepers,
I'm a third-yearstudent in
middle school living a normal life.
But on my 15th birthday,
I was dragged into the
Feudal Era
by a demon who suddenly
appeared from the shrine well.
That's how I met
the half-demon, Inuyasha.
The Shikon Jewel is a treasure which
increases the powerof a demon.
In orderto help Inuyasha
and some others
find the shards of
the shattered Shikon Jewel,
I've been going back and forth between
the real world and the feudal period.
But there's a greedy one trying to get
the Shikon Jewel for himself... Naraku.
Scheming to absorb the demon powers
of Sesshomaru, Inuyasha's olderbrother,
Naraku lures Sesshomaru to his castle.
And just as Naraku was about to
completely consume Sesshomaru's body,
Inuyasha broke through Naraku's barrier
and rushed into the castle.
Take this!
Wind Scar!
My barrier!
Die!
W- What?!
Inuyasha was ready to deliver
the finishing blow.
Fool!
Don't think you can escape
from me!
Naraku used Sango's youngerbrother,
Kohaku, in a dastardly trick
to make his escape.
Damn that Naraku!
He doesn't plan to return
to this castle.
You're probably right.
Afteryou broke through his barrier,
he had no choice but to leave.
Damn!
Naraku is probably vulnerable enough
to be killed right now.
I was almost there!
Damn!
I wonder if coming home
was the right thing to do?
I'm spending my time studying
in this safe world.
I feel bad about leaving
Inuyasha and the others.
I wonderwhat they're doing?
This formula will appear in
the test two days from now.
Rememberit.
Huh? Test?!
I can't be worrying about others.
I have to catch up
in two days.
Otherwise, I'll end up flunking!
Kagome, are you ready to leave?
Of course!
I'm begging you!
Please let me
borrow yournotes.
But...
Right?
We have to study for
the test, too.
So please...
ljust want to borrow it
for a short while.
Well... Kagome, we know you're
sickly and it's hard on you.
Yes! So please help me out.
ljust want to make a copy.
All right.
I guess it can't be helped.
Then!
I'll lend you my notes.
Ohh! Thank you!
But in return...
Huh?
Thanks so much!
Kagome?
Huh?
You're thinking again.
- About what?
- Whatelse?
Yourjealous, delinquent boyfriend.
I'm not! I really...
It's okay.
So how's itgoing?
Well...
What's the latest?
I recently met his olderbrother.
He has a brother?
Is he also a delinquent?
Is he strong, too?
Yes, he may be stronger.
The two of them only argue
when they see each other.
He's very dangerous.
Really, really dangerous.
Should we keep quiet?
I can just see it...
herunhappy future!
Where there's love,
there's hope!
Hang in there, Kagome!
- What's the matter?
- N-Nothing!
Can I borrow yournotes?
Huh?
Why?
It's exam week in college.
They all have the same plan
as you, Kagome.
What'll we do?
Stand in line?
We can make copies
somewhere else.
Fast and easy copies.
OUT OF ORDER
Somewhere else...
CLOSED FORTHE DAY
No way!
What's going on?!
W-Well, Kagome.
We have to go.
Hang in there.
W-Wait!
You can't leave!
You traitors!
She's late! Kagome's late!
I thought she was returning
right away?
She said she'd stay over
two or three days.
Don't be impatient, Inuyasha.
How can you stay so calm?!
It's not like we only started
hunting down Naraku.
Besides, Inuyasha...
You'd betterrest yourbody, too.
Huh?
What're you saying, Sango?!
I'm not like you humans.
I'm not a bit tired!
That's just it!
We can't keep up with
yourenergy.
You're the one who's tired.
You!
So...
I see.
Naraku's demonic aura
remains hidden.
I've had my Soul Collectors
look fortraces of him...
But there's not even a hint
of his barrier.
How has he hidden such
a strong demonic aura?
Geez!
Get the Sacred Jewel shard
from Kohaku's corpse.
I used to think this kid was
just a puppet...
But he didn't kill the hostage girl.
Nordid he allow himself to be
killed by Sesshomaru.
Kohaku, if you keep defying
Naraku,
you won't live long.
Although I shouldn't be
one to talk.
Naraku disappeared.
And Kohaku along with him.
Kohaku...
Where are you?
Sango...
Miroku.
So... Miroku went to
woo Sango?
That must be it.
Kagome even suggested that
Sango's been secretly waiting
forthis.
Kirara...
Do you mind?
You must be worried about
yourbrother.
Well... yes.
It's easier said than done,
but don't worry too much.
Uh-huh.
I understand what you're
going through.
Do you want to be alone,
after all?
Huh?
So...
is that all?
Huh?
Err... no...
After all, considering the
way you usually are...
I thought aftergiving me
the pep talk...
you'd do something lecherous.
Sango... you...
You should have told me sooner
if that's what you wanted.
Hmm?
Now that's a good one.
Damn! Everyone's crazy
around here!
I guess there's no other way
but to study.
I don't understand a thing!
At times like this...
Hello, Setsuko?
You ask someone else.
Okay, thanks!
All right. 'Bye.
Huh? Now why did I
call herin the first place?
Sis, your textbook...
I didn't do a thing last night.
Sis, hey...
- Sis...
- Don't talk to me!
I'll forgeteverything
I memorized.
I have to catch up today!
He's here... Inuyasha.
Yo!
W-Why?!
You're late, so I came
to get you.
Hey, let's go!
Are you kidding?!
I have a test tomorrow!
Why're you so mad?
I'm off!
Listen!
Do NOTgo outside.
Stay put in the house
and wait.
Understand?
Awright!
I'll be back this evening.
Huh? Where's Kagome?
She left.
Oh dear!
She forgot herlunch.
Lunch?
Can you take it to her?
Hmm?
Here.
If I follow Kagome's scent,
I'll catch up to herright away.
Someone! Catch him!
Hold it!
Hey, move outta there!
W-Wanna die?!
Kagome's world is
pretty dangerous, too.
What now?
What're you doing?!
C'mon!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Ears!
Cut it out!
See ya!
Hey! Thank you!
Man! What a dangerous world!
What's the matter, Kagome?
Err... nothing.
Oh no! What's Inuyasha doing here?!
Sit!
Sit, huh?
Well then, Higurashi,
you can stand.
Why'd she do this?!
What's wrong with you?!
Didn't I make it clear that
you were to stay home?!
Shaddup!
I couldn't help it!
Yourma asked me.
Asked you?
Here.
My lunch.
He came to bring
this to me.
Wait, Inuyasha.
Err... Huh?
Let's share.
It's all squished to one side...
I won't be able to
concentrate at home.
I'll stay in the library
until evening.
I have to study!
Higurashi!
Hojo!
Is yourneuralgia cured?
H-Hojo...
You're still young, so you
must take care of yourbody.
I made up this healthy menu
foryou.
Try it, will you?
T-Thank you!
See ya!
Hojo is so meticulous.
Oh! That's it!
Why didn't I think of it earlier?!
I can ask Hojo forthe notes!
Hojo, wait up!
Hojo!
Oh, I just remembered.
This is herbal medicine,
but it's supposed to work
on all kinds of ailments.
Huh?
Oh, thank you.
Listen, Higurashi.
Health is a matter
of the mind.
Live a wholesome life,
eat three meals daily.
A-All right.
Bye!
Oh...
Higurashi, eat properly!
Hey, wait!
Hojo!
Hojo...
I'm home.
I couldn't borrow any notes.
Sis, take a look!
Huh?
What's the matter?
A strange-looking youth
in a red outfit
captured a bank robber.
What's this story about?
On top of that,
this youth rescued a child
trapped in a fire.
Inuyasha, you're so cool!
Here is a drawing of his likeness
done by the rescued child.
Hey, that's the cap I was wearing!
You're right!
What did you do on the
way to school?
Say, what's this box?
Can't you see I'm busy?
Sit!
Sota, come here!
What is it, Sis?
Keep Inuyasha company.
Sure.
Inuyasha, let's take a bath.
Thanks!
Now then.
It's sooo hot!
What is this?!
C'mon, you have to rinse
off the suds.
Shaddup!
Enough!
Get out of here!
Go!
Hey! Kagome...
Oh no...
I've forgotten everything!
Would you like to eat?
It's quieted down.
Huh?
What IS this?!
My tongue is burning!
I gave him curry.
I guess it was too hot.
This coming from a guy that normally
grins and bears a hole in his gut...
Say...
What is it?
I'm being quiet.
But it's disconcerting to
be stared at.
Why don't you lie down?
As if!
Hurry up and get back
to your studies!
We're goin' back tomorrow!
All right!
Does he intend to watch over
me all night?
I wouldn't put it past him.
He's a fireball of energy.
H-He's asleep!
Geez! What a guy!
Afterbothering me with my studies
all this time!
But I've neverseen Inuyasha
sleeping so soundly.
I guess...
He's more exhausted
than any one of us.
Sleep peacefully...
at least on this night.
Oh, they're back!
Oh!
So you spent the night
at Kagome's house?
What's wrong, Kagome?
You have no energy!
You monopolized my bed
last night!
On top of which,
the test was a killer.
It's the pits!
What a clear day!
Here's a question.
Besides the ones Naraku
has in his possession,
who has Sacred Jewel shards
and how many?
Well... Kohaku has one.
Kagome has three.
And...
Time's up!
Koga of the Wolf-Demon Tribe
has one in each leg.
That means Naraku will
go after Koga, too.
However, Naraku has
disappeared from sight.
Then what's that?
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Female Wolf-Demon
and the Lunar Rainbow Promise."
Afemale wolf-demon?
That Koga is quite
the ladies' man!