Looks like the village where
I lived with Pa.
C'mon, Shippo!
'Kay!
Who suggested coming here anyway?
Doubt if we'll find a shard
in a place like this.
Kagome... are you picking up
any vibes from a Jewel Shard?
None at all.
Well, let's split up and look around.
Catch you later!
Huh? What is it?
Are you going off alone
to pick up some woman, Monk?
Huh! I sense a demon!
How can you be so callous?!
Huh? What is it?
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
We haven't even started.
If there's a demon around,
I'll smell it!
He plans to goof off!
Ahh... such nice weather.
Huh? Shippo's gone.
Huh? He probably went off to play.
He's just a kid, after all.
Boy, the pains I go through!
We've been in a lot of battles lately.
They deserve to be alone
for a change.
Now then...
Wait up!
Stop!
Catch me if you can!
Brat!
Get her!
Liar! You stole the dried
persimmon from my house!
Did not! Did you see me?!
Shaddup! You liar!
Why you! When my brother
comes home, you'll all get it!
Stupid! Your brother died long ago
in the war!
My pa was with him when
he died.
My brother's NOT dead!
Oww!
Why you!
You lying thief!
W-Wha!
You kids!
Arghhh! A ghost!
Wait up!
That'll show 'em!
It's safe now.
T-Thank you, raccoon-dog.
I'm a fox.
For saving me... want half?
Huh?
The dried persimmon I stole.
It's yummy.
S- She was the culprit, after all.
You're strong, aren't you?
I'm Satsuki.
What's your name?
l-I'm Shippo.
Shippo?
Hmm... cool name.
My pa named me.
Yeah? So your pa is a
raccoon-dog demon?
No, a fox.
Just teasing.
Satsuki, don't you have parents?
They died right after I was born.
I see...
But I have a big brother.
He's gonna prove himself in battle
and become a samurai...
then he's coming for me.
Huh? Were those kids lying then?
Didn't your brother...
He'll come home.
Even if he dies, he'll come back alive.
Huh?
I'll show only you.
It's my treasure.
Anything I wish on it
will come true.
Isn't it pretty? It's a piece
of something called...
the Jewel of Four Souls.
T- The Jewel of Four Souls?
Brother, what is it?
It's a shard from the Jewel of Four Souls
which grants any wish.
I'll become a samurai
without fail.
Uh-huh!
Brother wouldn't lie to me.
Are you really sure?
Is my home possessed
by some demon?
Yes, we must exorcise it immediately.
This is my duty as a monk.
I expect no payment, Headman.
Oh no...
I shall provide meals and a place to sleep
for you all this night.
That Miroku... lying through
his teeth again!
Sh...!
Huh?!
What's up?
Sh...!
E-Earthquake!
So... there was a demon.
It was true.
So you weren't lying?
Excuse me!
Big news!
Huh?
Kagome!
Shippo, how did you find us?
I figured Miroku would be
performing an exorcism at
the finest-looking house in
the village.
l-I found it...
the Sacred Jewel Shard!
What?
That girl?
Oh, it's Satsuki.
Listen, will you show me
your shard?
You won't take it, will you?
We will!
If it's real.
Inuyasha, sit!
Don't worry.
ljust want to see.
Oh no! If it's real, we'll have
to take it from her!
Then Satsuki's wish won't...
Oh, stupid me! What have I done?!
Stupid! Stupid me!
Kagome...
That's enough.
I'm goin' home.
Thank you.
Be careful now.
Is it okay to let her go?
Satsuki! Have you changed
your mind about living here?
No! Brother will come home
some day.
Kagome... that shard...
Hmm...
Shippo, that was
a stone flower.
Stone flower?
In other words, a quartz.
You can dig it up in
the mountains.
It's not a Sacred Jewel Shard.
l-It's a fake?
Satsuki...
Satsuki is a pitiful child.
Her brother really is dead,
but she won't believe it.
Oh...
Please bring Brother
back home soon.
I've told her to come live with us,
but she refuses to move from that hut
she shared with her brother.
I was chased out of the
headman's house,
but I can use that little girl.
I'll teach them!
The Sacred Jewel has the power to
create incarnations of Naraku.
So if a wish is made on
a real Sacred Jewel Shard,
will Satsuki's brother be resurrected
and return home?
Geometry scares me!
Forgive me, Kagome!
Hey!
Oh, Inuyasha!
I thought you were sleeping.
Please let me go!
It's to help someone!
Snap out of it!
Shippo, you know just
how frightening the Sacred Jewel is.
It's not something you give
to humans.
Besides, why are you taking pity
on that little girl?
He's smitten with her.
She was quite cute.
Is that all?!
Shaddup!
So what if I'm in love with her!
Look at you! Flitting back
and forth between Kikyo and Kagome!
Go to sleep!
Sorry...
Satsuki...
I'm home.
B-Brother!
You've waited a long time.
How have you been?
Brother!
I believed in you!
I knew... I knew that you would
come home!
I'll say good-bye at least.
I wonder if Satsuki will keep
wishing on that fake shard?
But I can't tell her the truth!
Oh, Shippo!
Satsuki!
My wish came true!
Brother is home!
Huh?
Inuyasha, where's Shippo?
Huh? Isn't he with that girl, Satsuki?
He was very worried about her.
Satsuki's brother is dead,
but she has faith in that shard
and keeps waiting.
I'm going.
Butting in again?
Wait, Kagome.
I'll come with you.
See? He's hurt, but Brother's back.
Satsuki... It's all thanks to you
and the Sacred Jewel Shard.
A demon...
Brother, hurry and get well.
Yeah... I made you suffer
a long time.
I'll make up for it now.
Uh-huh!
S-Satsuki...
Come here.
Oh, you're with the group staying
at the headman's house.
Satsuki, hurry!
Shippo?
Won't you bring it to me...
the real Sacred Jewel Shard?
Let Satsuki go!
What're you doing, Brother?!
I have the Sacred Jewel Shard
right here.
See?
Can't you tell... this is junk!
It's totally useless!
Satsuki cherished that shard!
Now kid... go and get me
the real Sacred Jewel Shard.
Or else... I'll break Satsuki's neck!
W-Who... are you?
Your brother, who else?
Show your true self, demon!
Fox Fire!
You're so cruel.
You coulda let her believe
I was her brother.
Satsuki!
Why you!
I'll teach you!
Satsuki, hurry!
W-Why... you!
Dang! He figured it out!
You won't get away!
I'll use this!
Satsuki, get away now!
Huh? No way!
I can't leave you!
This takes only one passenger!
Shippo!
Found you!
Is this Satsuki's hut?
See this? It's a crawling,
big-bellied demon.
Looks like it got away.
Let's go, Miroku!
We've gotta go after Shippo!
Stay alive, both of you!
That's Shippo's fox magic!
It's Satsuki!
Good job, Kirara!
Shippo's being attacked!
We know!
Let's go, Kagome!
Satsuki, I hope you got away!
You may've let the girl go,
but it's useless.
I'll do the same thing.
I'll use you as a hostage
to get a Sacred Jewel Shard.
Then why didn't you come after
me from the start?
You dashed Satsuki's hopes!
I won't forgive you!
Interesting... Want to fight?
You bet!
Get a taste of my stomach acid!
Multiply!
Take that!
Bombs away!
Now!
Why you...
I've had enough!
Is my powertoo weak?
Can't I fight like the others?
Playtime's over!
What?! Turned yourself into
something weird again?!
Huh? Got a gripe with me?
That's fine.
I can test the Backlash Wave
which I've just mastered!
Just what are you up to now?
Locate the demonic aura,
twist it around the Wind Scar...
then reverse the flow-
my new ultimate technique!
Backlash Wave...
Huh?
Damn! This opponent's demonic energy
is too weak...
I can't use the Backlash Wave!
What're you mumbling about?!
You're just too weak, that's all!
He's for real!
Huh? This is the demon I exorcised
from the headman's house last night.
l-Inuyasha...
Hey, Shippo...
you did well.
Shippo, are you all right?
Kagome!
Shippo, you beat the demon!
It wasn't me. Inuyasha...
When I arrived, the demon
was already beaten to a pulp.
Inuyasha...
This demon figured he didn't have
a chance with us, so he used Satsuki.
Everyone who tries to use
the Sacred Jewel encounters unhappiness.
I forgot that... and Satsuki suffered
for it.
Satsuki, I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Satsuki...
I've decided... to go live with
the headman.
I knew all along
that my brother was dead.
Take care, Satsuki!
Thank you, Shippo!
I'm glad I met you!
Satsuki, find happiness.
I don't have a Ma or Pa either.
But I'm not alone. That's why
I can go on living.
Was Shippo really in love
with that girl?
I guess so.
Hah! Acting like a grown-up!
He's little, but he's a man.
First love...
Shippo, let's go!
Hey Shippo! If you lag behind
we'll leave you!
I know!
All the men in a village are bewitched
by a demon princess and won't return.
Miroku sets out alone
to rescue them,
but his one weakness is...
a beautiful woman.
This may be dangerous!
Worried, Sango decides to
follow him.
But deep in that mountain
was a sad legend.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Temptress in the Mist"
Don't miss it!