Possession of the Sacred Jewel
bestows tremendous power...
upon demons and others
with evil in their hearts.
My sister Kikyo had died trying to
seal its powers.
However, she was reincarnated
as a young woman named Kagome...
and returned to this world.
And now, the journey begins for...
Inuyasha, a half-demon with
a human mother...
and this young woman from
the modern age.
All right... Now!
Hold it, Kagome!
Huh?!
Are you trying to escape?!
What about the Sacred Jewel?!
Move!
I have a test tomorrow!
I'm in the 9th grade!
I've been missing all my cram classes
for high school, too!
At this rate, I'll miss too many
classes to graduate!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Without this well, you can't
return to that strange other world!
I'll destroy it!
Sit!
Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit!
SIT!
I'll be back in three days.
So don't you dare follow me!
Come home! Return to us!
Gramps, will your chants really work?
It will!
This chant is an ancient one
that has been passed...
down through generations
of Higurashi priests!
But you've been at it
for three days...
and Sis still hasn't returned.
Good! I'm back!
Oh, sacred rice wine!
Bring her back!
What's this?!
Smells like sake!
Kagome!
My prayers have worked!
Gramps, I appreciate your
concern for me, but...
Sota, do you believe me now?
Oh, yeah!
You are amazing, Gramps!
Then you must train hard as
the next in line!
I'm the next in line?!
Naturally!
No way! I'm going to
become a soccer player!
"Socker" player?
You're going to punch people?!
Never mind that!
I have lots of things to
bring up... Help me!
- Mom wants me to become a doctor.
- A doctor?
A surgeon or a physician?
I would recommend you to become...
What's the matter, Buyo?
You're sneezing!
Do I still reek of liquor?
Here's your new school uniform.
I'll put it in your room.
Thanks, Mom.
Sis, didn't you bring that
dog fellow?
Of course not!
It was difficult enough trying
to lose him!
Difficult enough...
Yup... Life has become
quite difficult.
I've lived at this
Higurashi Shrine...
from the day I was born.
Gramps, my mom,
my younger brother, Sota...
and me, an average ninth grader.
We have a secret well on
our premises.
And demons are after
the Sacred Jewel.
And suddenly, I've had this
totally "unaverage"life.
Even today, I wake up wondering
if this is all a dream.
This is reality...
All right!
'Morning!
Good morning!
Kagome!
Is it okay for you
to be in school?
Huh?
You've been absent
a lot lately...
so we called your house.
This time, it was a strained back.
And before that, you had gone to
the doctor for a diabetes test.
Are you okay?
Gramps... If you have to lie,
make it believable!
Higurashi!
Huh?
Are you feeling better?
Huh?!
It's Hojo from B-section!
You're going through an awful
lot for someone so young.
You have gout?
No...!
I can't do much, but here.
What is it?
Therapeutic sandals!
Wear them, okay?
Hey, Kagome!
Have you been seeing Hojo?
As if I have the time!
But he seems to really
like you.
What a shock!!
Are you the least bit
interested?
Well!
Kagome, do you?
Do you have a
boyfriend already?!
No way!
Really? You really don't have one?
Then what kind of guys
do you like?
Well...
Someone who's not rough...
who's not spoiled...
who's not short-tempered...
who's kind...and understanding...
Yes...
Perhaps I'd like someone who's
the complete opposite of Inuyasha...
What's the matter with Kagome?
I think she still has
a fever.
Inuyasha, stop lying around.
Go out and get information
on the Sacred Jewel.
Shut up!
All that "sit" from her has
given me a sore back!
Damn that Kagome!
Hurry back so I can
teach you a lesson!
Oww!
Huh?! A fire!
What's happening?!
Why... You've burned the
talismans that have...
been in place for
generations!
Give me... a body...
That mask!
My predecessor several
generations back was...
asked to exorcise this mask
by a Noh actor!
It was named the
"Flesh-Eating Mask"!
I did not know it had
such enormous power!
A body...
Give me... a body!
A body... A body...
Is it looking for living flesh?!
A body... Give me a body!
Damn!
A body!
Hey, the fire's at
Higurashi Shrine!
Let's go!
Huh?!
The fire is under control!
Please do not worry!
This road is closed!
Do not push!
Excuse me!
Please let me through!
Hey, you!
You can go there!
Thank you very much!
Mom!
Kagome!
Mom, what happened?!
The storeroom caught fire.
Grandpa was surrounded
by the smoke.
Gramps?!
He's all right.
He was slightly injured...
then fainted before he
could inhale too much smoke.
I'm going to the hospital now.
Me, too!
Sota's not home yet.
Please stay home.
All right.
A fire in the storeroom?
There's no way a fire
could start in there.
The fire started inside, huh?
Watch out!
There are holes in the floor.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Sis!
It's all right!
We're all safe!
- Don't worry.
- Un-huh.
Stop!
Hurry!
Contact Headquarters!
There's an out-of-control truck!
And next on the news...
A runaway fire truck
on the streets...
has been involved in
many accidents.
There appears to be
several injured...
but that has not been
confirmed at this time.
It is unthinkable, but
at every accident site...
people have disappeared.
It is totally
incomprehensible!
The flesh keeps rotting away.
Rotting away!
If I can absorb a little more...
I'll be able to mold
a complete body.
A little more...
Oh, if only I had a fragment
of the Sacred Jewel!
Mom, how's Grandpa?
The doctor says
he's out of danger...
but Grandpa is still
unconscious.
Huh?
I don't think we need
to be overly concerned...
but he is getting on
in age.
Mom, what's all that?
When they rescued him...
he had these plastered all
over his face.
He had even stuffed some
in his mouth.
The Flesh-Eating Mask...
The Mask... The Flesh-Eating...
And so, Mom's going to stay
at the hospital another night...
to watch over Gramps.
Huh?
Sis, can I stay in here
tonight again?
What are you saying?!
You're a boy, aren't you?
But...
You're such a weakling!
Sleep in your own
room tonight!
I have another test
tomorrow!
Gramps had talismans in his mouth and
even sacred rice wine all over him.
I'll bet something happened
in the storeroom!
The Flesh-Eating Mask...
Something's different.
Until now, everything
was normal.
So has something...changed?
This!
Is it because of the
Sacred Jewel fragments?
Watch out... for...
the Flesh-Eating Mask!
A Noh mask?
The Flesh-Eating Mask that
Gramps was mumbling about...
The Jewel... The Sacred Jewel...
The Jewel... The Sacred Jewel!
Sota, don't just stand there!
Run!
I must... I must get Inuyasha!
Sis! You're bleeding!
Don't cry!
I just cut myself on the glass.
Give it to me... Give it to me...
It...has a Sacred Jewel fragment
in its forehead!
It's after this bottle
of fragments...
Sota will be safer
away from me.
Sota, run to the
hidden well...
and get Inuyasha!
Tell him there are Sacred Jewel
fragments in this world and...
he'll gladly come running!
What?! All by myself?!
Understand? Hurry!
The well is linked to the
Feudal States Era.
Jump and throw yourself in.
Let's go, Buyo!
Owweee!
I couldn't go through!
Why?!
Please... take me!
I have to... or Sis will...
Sis will die!
The... dog fellow...
What's up?
You look troubled.
Don't fall off!
I couldn't get through
the well.
You should be glad.
On the other side, there
are dozens of demons...
who love to eat little
boys like you.
Huh?!
Do you know where
Sis is?
My nose works real good.
I just have to follow
Kagome's blood scent.
Sis cut her hand...
I could smell her
from the well.
I'll find Kagome and
save her without fail.
This Inuyasha is rough
and spoiled...
and he isn't kind at all!
It's such a chore keeping
up with him.
I wonder...
He seems much kinder and
dependable...
than Sis made him out to be.
Not yet? Isn't Inuyasha
here yet?
Give it to me... The Sacred Jewel!
Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
Inuyasha!
Sis!
Sota!
Huh? Kagome!
You look just fine to me!
We'll be okay now.
Inuyasha will destroy
the demon for us!
I don't mind helping you...
But first, apologize for
the other day.
What're you talking about?
Sit!
I won't let you say
you've forgotten!
You shout incantations to
your heart's content...
and now you want me
to save you?!
Oh that...
Sorry, sorry!
I remember and
I apologize!
Damn... You don't sound
repentant at all!
Maybe I'll just go home.
What're you saying?!
That mask has a fragment
of the Sacred Jewel!
What'll you do?!
Hah!
I'm not sure if I'm
imagining it...
but he's smitten...
I'll bet he's smitten
in love!
Inuyasha!
Why you... How dare you
take my body!
Inuyasha, the core of the
demon is the Noh mask!
I am the Flesh-Eating Mask.
Several centuries ago...
I was carved out of a giant
katsura tree...
which had a fragment of the
Sacred Jewel imbedded in it.
Since then, I have craved flesh
and devoured humans.
Now, I want a good body
that will not rot!
And for that, it needs more power
from the Sacred Jewel.
I don't know how many humans
you've eaten to date...
but you're definitely too fat!
What?!
You fell into my trap.
Now you won't be able
to escape!
- Huh?!
- Inuyasha!
What a rotten trick!
Huh?!
Sis!
If I don't do something,
the fragments will...!
Sota, take this and run!
Hurry!
Yeah...
Sota, run!
That mask is after this bottle.
I know! If I throw it away...!
No!
It can't have this bottle!
Listen!
Don't move!
You did it!
Yeah! Are the Sacred Jewel
fragments safe?
Uh-huh!
Inuyasha...
Kagome, not hurt?
Huh?
No.
Huh... He's sorta nice.
What's happening?
It's just a little...but Inuyasha
seems sorta dashing.
Huh?! It's morning?!
Oh no!
I have a test today!
Hey, Kagome!
Oh... See you, Inuyasha!
Make sure you return
to the other dimension!
Sota!
Pick up those fragments
and bring them home!
Inuyasha!
Don't take them!
Umm... You were real cool!
Think so?
Yup... Scout's honor.
We know that the Sacred
Jewel fragments...
exist even in the modern world.
The search for the fragments
has become more complicated.
Huh?! Accompany Sota to
the next town?
Inuyasha is enough of a headache!
Please spare me!
But there's a little soul there
that I cannot ignore.
And I'm going to keep her
from going to hell!
Next on Inuyasha: "The Soul Piper
and the Mischievous Little Soul".
Don't miss it!