Even a large castle can be
difficult to find.
Since we have no clues
to its whereabouts.
Look, you're fully recovered,
aren't you?
Your goal is also to
beat Naraku.
Why don't you keep us
company for awhile?
You sure don't look
enthusiastic!
We know much more about
Naraku than you!
You'll only benefit from
coming along.
Yes...
So let us take it
one step at a time...
For now, we'll gather
the Sacred Jewel fragments.
If we keep gathering them...
Naraku will come for them
eventually.
I understand that you want
vengeance now.
But you must be patient.
All right.
I do understand how
you feel.
Thank you.
But Monk... why do you keep
stroking me as you speak?
Owee!
He was holding back until
you were better, Sango.
Miroku, control yourself!
Did you find something, Shippo?
Just over yonder is
a large lake...
and there's a huge shrine
smack in the middle of it.
A huge shrine?
Is it Naraku's castle?!
A flood?
How terrible...
Huh?
It's the procession of
the human sacrifice.
It was a bad flood this time.
Whose child is it this time?
A child for a human sacrifice?!
How disturbing.
Headman, please reconsider!
What are you saying?
To protect the village...
it's only natural to
give up our children.
What's natural about that?!
Some water god, huh?
I'll bet it's just
some weird demon.
A demon who's gotten stronger
from a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Don't hide it from us.
Who are you?!
Doesn't look familiar.
Look at his ears!
A demon?!
This is a peaceful village
protected by the Water God!
Demons, be gone!
What?! You old fart!
Stop it.
What're you doing, Miroku?!
We are not suspicious folk.
We travel around the country...
coming to the aid of
those in need.
We heard of your misfortune.
If you will allow me, I will
exorcise this village.
Huh?! Can you really do that?
I think that's a good idea...
No, do not be deceived!
They are fakes!
But headman... Just listen to them...
If we rely on shady characters...
and raise the ire of the Water God...
who knows what will
happen to our village?
Besides, how can I approve
an exorcism now...
when it's my own son's
turn to be sacrificed?
How will I answer to the other
children who went before him?
Is that the child to be sacrificed?
Before the sun sets, we must
deliver the sacrifice!
Now hurry!
That headman is fishy.
He acts like he wants his
son to be sacrificed!
He was quite upset with
our interference.
Well, what'll we do?
Leave em' alone?
What are you saying!?
We're going to save him!
Right?
Yes.
Are you serious?
Then come with me!
Hey! Wanna be left behind?
What's with that kid?
You can have 'em.
Take your pick.
What're these?
Oh... quite valuable.
Fine silk, too.
You chosen?
Good, you are hired!
Hired?
You were telling the village
men just now...
helping people
is your business.
So I wanna hire you...
to defeat the Water God.
Got it?
What're you doing?!
Inuyasha, he's just a boy!
He needs to be taught
who's stronger.
Hey, apologize even if you
won't mean it.
Inuyasha can be just
like a kid.
The human sacrifice is taken to
the shrine in a boat.
So we'll follow the boat...
and attack just when the Water God
appears to devour the sacrifice.
Got that?
These are stolen goods.
I just know it.
Oh, that's okay.
It's not okay!
Are you listening?!
Just whose child are you?
Humph! It's none of
your business.
I'll bet you're the real son
of the headman.
Oops!
Now that you mention it...
the eyebrows look
just like that headman's.
Even his cocky manner.
Then the one in the palanquin
was a stand-in?
Yes... I am Taromaru,
the headman's heir.
I thought so.
Why is the headman's son
so eager to do this?
The Water God began demanding
human sacrifices half a year ago.
Heavy rains...flooding...
He said in order to lift
the curse...
human sacrifice was necessary.
When a child from the village
was selected...
Please bear it... for the village's sake.
Yet when the white arrow landed
upon our roof...
he told me to hide.
And he found another child
to take your place?
Such a foolish, doting parent.
Foolish, period!
That's why you want to
save him...
He and I grew up together.
I won't let him take
my place.
And? I hope you have a boat.
If this human-devouring Water God
is allowed to live...
my reputation as a
Demon Slayer is mud.
I'll take care of him alone.
Alone?
You're still recovering,
so stop acting so tough.
I'll bet you can't even wield
that heavy weapon yet.
Want to try me?
Anytime!
Inuyasha!
Oh well... We received payment
for our services.
So we must work hard.
Inuyasha, stop alienating people!
Tell her that!
She doesn't want to
be part of us!
That's...
The Water God's shrine gate!
It's the shrine that I saw
this afternoon.
The human sacrifice has entered.
Hide! Gate guards!
Why should we hide?
You're in the way... move!
Hurry up!
We're goin' in!
He's strong!
My master, we brought
the human sacrifice.
Come closer.
Look at those dirty, calloused hands!
You are not the headman's child.
What is the meaning of this?
You dare deceive the Water God?
Please, oh mighty God!
Please eat me!
You have dishonored me!
I will tear you from limb to limb...
and send you back to
the village with the rains.
Hey! Move, move!
How dare you!
This is a sacred house!
Shaddup!
A crab!
They're all bewitched
fishes and crabs!
There you are!
So you're the Water God
that devours humans.
T-Taromaru!
Suekichi!
Calm down!
Aha... You appear dirty, but
you're actually the headman's son.
Yes! Now that you know,
release Suekichi!
I am your human sacrifice!
Hey, why'd you hire us then?
You talk big as Water God...
but you stink!
You reek of demon!
The Tetsusaiga's power
has been thwarted!
A demon's sword like yours
is no match...
for my sacred weapon,
the Trident of Amakoi.
You have committed a grave
crime in defacing my shrine!
You will pay with your lives!
I'm underwater!
Kagome!
Inuyasha!
He intends to eat the boy!
I must do something!
Now's my chance!
Hit the mark!
l-impossible... How can this body
succumb to a human arrow?!
Will you snap out of it?!
Thanks... Are you all right?
Yes!
- Suekichi!
- Young Master Taromaru!
Hurry!
Keep running until Inuyasha
comes for us.
How dare a young wench like
you injure my arm!
I shall impale you!
Sango... Sango!
Get a hold of yourself!
She's swallowed too much water.
I must breathe air
into her.
You misunderstood
my intentions.
W-where am I?!
Outside the Water God's shrine.
When I came to, I found
myself here, too.
Is that Inuyasha?
Thanks...
Did you save us, too?
Yes.
From your appearance...
you seem to be in the service
of the Water God.
The Water God is an imposter!
He used to be a water sprite like us
that lived in the lake.
But he resorted to trickery...
sealed the true one in the crag
over yonder...
And he took the sacred weapon,
the Trident of Amakoi...
and declared himself
the Water God!
I understand now.
We must rescue the
real Water God.
Fool!
How can you be
so easygoing!
I'm goin' back to the shrine!
Saving Kagome comes first!
The footsteps have ceased!
I will kill you first!
Are you going to leave Inuyasha
to deal with the Water God alone?
Inuyasha alone will be
more than enough.
Is he that strong?
He's also very shrewd.
Knowing the state of
your emotions right now...
he normally wouldn't
act so hostile.
But Inuyasha knows that fighting...
is what will ease your pain
right now.
That's why he's acting the part
of the vengeance seeker.
But maybe I'm reading too much
into his behavior.
Inuyasha!
Damn!
Kagome... Is everyone safe?
Yes!
The Water God is escaping!
Where are you, Water God?!
Inuyasha!
So you've shown your true self!
Fake Water God!
Without that trident,
you're just a lowly creature!
Why you!
Where is the cave in which the
real Water God is held captive?
I believe around here...
Is someone there?
Huh?!
A young woman's voice.
Who is there?
Could it be... the Water God is
a goddess!
Hurry and unseal this cave
and free me!
Right away!
Goddess?
Here.
Huh?
So... beautiful... but...
you are so tiny...
I couldn't even if
I wanted to...
Wanted to what?!
Nothing.
All is vanity.
Damn!
I can't breathe...!
Inuyasha!
He's not coming up!
Kagome!
You're all okay?!
Inuyasha was dragged underwater!
Let me down!
I shall subdue this fake Water God.
Yes, Water Goddess!
Water Goddess?
Parting Waters!
Hmmm? What?
T-that's!
The waters have parted!
There's Inuyasha!
Watch out!
To think you freed the Goddess!
Well now, I'm the real Water God!
Without her sacred trident, even the
real Water Goddess is powerless!
Now you shall all die!
Why you!
Kirara!
Fool!
Now you shall feel the power
of the Trident of Amakoi!
The sacred trident is calling
forth rain clouds!
Now!
Sango!
Die!
Are you all right?!
Inuyasha!
I'm sick and tired of you,
Fake Water God!
Inuyasha!
Enough is enough!
The twister is heading
for the village!
The village will be hit!
Calming a twister is
a simple matter.
Really?
Then please... hurry!
I shall...
so hurry and retrieve
my trident!
Inuyasha!
Don't worry!
I won't get killed
by the likes of him!
Stop bragging!
Hurry and get the trident!
Dang it... I thought she'd worry
at least a little about me.
Awright! Take it!
I got it!
Taromaru!
I am the headman's son!
I must save the village now!
Or I won't be able to face all those
killed by the fake God.
Young Master Taromaru!
Pretty fancy stuff, Sango.
It's nothing.
I'll aim for its head.
All right.
Let's go, Inuyasha!
Leave it to me!
Eat this! Tetsusaiga!
I shall deliver the
final blow.
Here you go!
Water Goddess, please.
She's grown!
Dispersing Clouds!
Have they all gone?
Yup.
I couldn't even thank
them properly.
They risked their lives
to save the village.
Cripes! We went and fought
a stupid snake...
who didn't even have
a Sacred Jewel fragment!
So what? We came to the
aid of the needy.
What's all this anyway?
Well... that is...
When I mentioned to the headman...
perhaps we should tell the villagers
about his son's brave deeds...
for some reason, he gave us all...
That's blackmail!
Does he always do such things?
Sometimes...
When I grow up, I wanna be
like them.
We'll sell these off
and celebrate!
Ahhh! I'll never help
humans again!
Funny. Miroku is gone
since this morning.
Old Myoga says he was staring at the
Wind Tunnel in his right hand last night.
Those Poison Insects appear again!
It's Naraku's trap!
The Wind Tunnel is damaged, and he's
surrounded by hundreds of demons!
Hurry, Inuyasha!
Miroku intends to give up his life!
Next, "Miroku Falls
Into a Dangerous Trap".
Look forward to it!