Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
The demon graveyard,
where Inuyasha's father also sleeps,
is the border between this
world and the next.
In order to obtain that last
remaining Sacred Jewel shard,
once again, we must find
the path that leads to that graveyard.
That place that the river otter's
father saw....
I wonder if Hakudoshi
already knows about it?
Yeah.
But where is this place
that's covered in white mist
and strewn with giant bones?
I may've been there once.
Inuyasha is thinking the same thing.
White mist and giant bones...
The border between this world
and the next...
The grave of Inuyasha's father...
This is...
That's right.
I've been here before.
Father....
Huh?
You're happy, Tetsusaiga?
I suppose so.... It's been a long time
since you've seen him.
Father, I've been using
Tetsusaiga to its fullest!
Huh?
It was a dream.
The border between this
world and the next...
If that's where the
last shard is,
then that's where I'll go.
He wants me to
visit his grave, huh?
Where could Inuyasha have gone?
Maybe he went in
search of Old Myoga.
Old Myoga?
How'll he find such
a teeny-tiny one?
Hmm... That's true.
But why would he be
looking for Myoga?
I'm not sure,
but it's probably
regarding the black pearl.
Black pearl?
Hey! You there, Totosai?
Totosai!
You're there, aren't you?
Answer!
What do you want,
showing up so unexpectedly?
I don't have business
with you.
Where's Old Myoga?
You are always so rude.
Since you've actually
come looking for me,
it must be something
troublesome.
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
This black pearl is the entryway
to Inuyasha's father's grave
and the border?
Yes.
Inuyasha's Tetsusaiga was to be
found at his father's grave.
When we went to get
the sword,
a space opened up
from the black pearl
which connected to
the other world.
Hey! Sesshomaru's
at the grave!
After he took possession
of Tetsusaiga,
we returned to this world...
But the black pearl fell back
into Inuyasha's right eye.
Oh....
I see, a way to remove the
black pearl from your eye?
Yeah, there's a way, right?
Well....
When the black pearl allowed you
passage into the other world,
it served its purpose.
Now, it has become a part
of your eye,
and it no longer has
demon power.
I can't use it anymore?
No, you cannot.
Then how do I get
to my old man's grave?!
Your father's grave?!
Yeah!
Good! Good boy, Inuyasha!
So you've finally realized how
great your father was
and decided to pay your respects
at his grave!
Don't you ever hit
me like that!
You always hit me, though.
What a surprise...
that you're showing
such respect.
Hah! It's nothing like that!
The last Sacred Jewel shard
may be found there.
In order to get it before Naraku,
we have to go ourselves
and beat him to it.
The Sacred Jewel shard?
If we can't use the black pearl,
any other method will do.
How can I get to
the other world?
Let's see....
Stupid!
Who're you calling "stupid"?
Think hard for a minute.
That demon graveyard is
in a separate world,
reached only by
traveling through a special path.
How could a Sacred Jewel shard
have gotten there?
He's right, Master Inuyasha.
And besides, Kagome was
with you then.
Yet she didn't sense a Sacred
Jewel shard at all.
T-That was then....
I think it'd be the same
this time, too.
Shaddup! Do you intend to
take me to the grave or not?!
In order to go to the graveyard,
you must see H-Hosenki.
Hosenki?
Who the hell is that?
An old friend of your father.
Hosenki cultivates many kinds
of precious jewels.
And each one of them can serve as
an entryway to the demon graveyard.
Hmm.... So he made
Inuyasha's black pearl, too?
Yes!
It was given to Inuyasha's
father by Hosenki.
Still....
The demon graveyard is
the final resting place of the dead.
It is no place for the living
to be visiting indiscriminately.
If that's where the Sacred Jewel
shard is, that's where we go.
That Inuyasha....
He's finally making his move.
I've just about had it!
How long must I baby-sit
this kid?!
If I kill him right here and now,
I'll be free...
Huh?
Kagura....
I know your thoughts
like the back of my hand.
You shouldn't think
foolish thoughts.
All right, I got you.
Damn kid!
Err...
Lord Sesshomaru,
where are we headed?
My lord! Lord Sesshomaru!
Do not ask me.
Huh?
Then who should I ask?
You, A-un?
It couldn't be Rin, could it?
That kid's scent...
and this scent that
I smell beyond him...
Naraku.
And this time, for sure....
- Huh?
I shall kill him.
Master Jaken....
Better not ask him
unnecessary questions.
Or else, he said that
he'll kill you.
Yeah, I'll do just that.
Dammit!
How much further, Myoga?
Just a bit more.
Once we pass this valley,
we'll reach the marsh where
Hosenki lives.
The sun's almost setting
and we're still not there!
Would you like to rest
around here?
Hah! Like we have
the luxury to rest!
Wait, Inuyasha!
As always, he sure has
a lot of energy.
Master Inuyasha,
this is impossible, even for you.
Let's wait for Kirara.
You've gotta be kidding!
If anything stands in my way,
I'll just blast it!
Outta my way!
Wind Scar!
The rocks!
Hah! How's that?!
You are amazing, Master Inuyasha!
I knew you could do it!
Liar!
Err, you're right.
Watch out!
Inuyasha is so reckless!
He's gone.
Shippo, keep at it!
O-Okay....
W- What...?
Why you...!
Hakudoshi!
You were careless,
Inuyasha.
So you came up ahead
of us and waited for this moment?
Hah! Go right ahead
and attack.
But I'm not gonna
die so easily!
I have no intention
of killing you.
I just wanted to see if
you were going to make it
to Hosenki's place.
Dammit! You know about
Hosenki?
But it's such a shame....
You won't be able
to see him.
W-What?!
Why you...!
You're not....!
Don't worry needlessly,
Inuyasha.
I won't interfere
with you people.
After all, I don't want
the entertainment to end.
Whaddya say?!
I'm looking forward to it,
Inuyasha.
You and your friends, or me....
Who will be the first to reach the
border between this world and the next?
Quit kidding!
Why you...!
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
There's nothing here.
Hosenki!
Aren't you here?
Huh?
Kirara, get back.
Oh! It's you, Hosenki!
Who is it?
There are no jewels here.
Hosenki! It's me, Myoga!
Huh?
It's me!
Oh!
Master Myoga!
He's Hosenki?
No, I am Hosenki's son.
Hosenki is dead.
W-Wha...!
Died?
W-Who....
Who killed him?!
No, he died just recently
from old age.
Old age?!
He died peacefully.
I am Hosenki II.
Umm....
You said earlier that there are no jewels
that can lead us to the grave...
That's right.
Oh?
My father used all the jewels
before he passed away.
And I am in the process of
making new jewels.
Then let us have those jewels!
Master Inuyasha, at least
say, "please."
Shaddup! I'll take 'em by force
if I have to.
Now, now....
This may not work.
Please, Master Hosenki!
We really need those
precious jewels.
Well, I don't mind
giving them to you....
But you'll have to
wait a bit.
We'll wait!
How long'll it take?
A hundred years.
What'd ya say?!
I'm still in training
to master jewel-making.
Demons sure have patience.
Perhaps this is futile.
Dammit!
Isn't there any other way?!
While we're wasting
time here,
Naraku or that kid Hakudoshi
could get the shard!
And? Did you find it?
The way to the border between
this world and the next....?
Yes.
Although there's only one path
at this time.
Hmm....
Then let's go.
What's wrong?
There's only one way...
Break open the gate.
Hey, Hakudoshi!
Hmm....interesting.
Kagura!
Huh?
Go on an errand.
Errand?
The scent disappeared...
Did I let him slip away?
Err....Lord Sesshomaru?
Oh, it's nothing!
Nothing.
It's been so stressful
for me lately...
Master Jaken!
You should train and learn
to turn your sighs into flowers.
Then there would be
flowers everywhere!
Silence!
- Huh?
Oh! Please wait,
Lord Sesshomaru!
We're at a dead-end.
It can't be helped.
We can't wait a hundred years.
Hey, Myoga!
Are you sure you don't know
any other way?
No! There is no other way
to reach the graveyard.
Wanna know....
where the entrance is?
Kagura?!
Hakudoshi is headed towards
the Mountain in the Realm of Fire.
There's supposed to be a gate there
that leads to the border between
this world and the next.
The Mountain in the Realm of Fire?
What is the meaning of this, Kagura?
Why have you come to
tell us this?
Well....
You'd have to ask Hakudoshi that.
What does this mean?
Is that a message from
Hakudoshi?
It could be a trap.
Hah! Even if it is a trap....
No, Master Inuyasha!
You must not go!
The Mountain in the Realm of Fire
is much too dangerous!
That is one place you must
not go!
Judging from your reaction,
I guess this thing about a gate
is no lie.
Err....no....
Then we have to go!
Regardless of what that
Hakudoshi has planned for us.
This is turning out to be
quite entertaining.
Inuyasha, I shall let you pass
through the gate first...
in exchange for your life.
The gate at the Realm of Fire is
the border between this life and the next.
The statues that we find
there begin to move!
They are Mezu and Gozu,
the gatekeepers.
They allow only the dead to pass.
They shall slay all those
who wish to pass.
Wha...?! My Wind Scar won't work!
Blades of this world have
no effect on them.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Bizarre Guards at the Border
of the Afterlife"
You'll die and the gate
will open.