Damn! I can't move!
Fool! You can jump or run...
but you can't escape my wind!
Blades!
My Sacred Jewel shards!
Now is the time
to escape...
Now when Naraku's barrier
is weak.
But... Naraku has...
Yes!
That one!
He has the power to sever the bond
between me and Naraku!
W-What is this?!
Yo!
"Yo"?! Why you!
Wind Sorceress Kagura, I recall?
I'm glad you remembered me.
Take your hand off your sword.
I didn't come here to fight.
Sesshomaru, I want to make
a deal with you.
A deal?
You know what these are.
I'll give these
Sacred Jewel shards to you.
In return... kill Naraku.
What?!
Free me from his grip.
You have the power to do it.
When you kill Naraku,
all the Sacred Jewel shards
he has gathered will be yours.
Let's use these shards and
have some fun.
You intend to betray Naraku?
It's not like I ever wanted
to be under his command.
Well, Sesshomaru?
I don't think it's a
bad idea to team up with me.
Unfortunately, I have no interest
in the Sacred Jewel.
If you wish to become free,
use those shards yourself
and destroy Naraku.
Are you afraid of Naraku?
I'm just saying I'm under no
obligation to help you.
If you don't have the resolve
to go it alone,
don't even think about betrayal.
Why you coward!
You still call yourself a man?!
W-What?!
Hah! I misjudged you!
Fool!
Why, that woman!
I wonder if she really intended
to make you her protector?
Talk about gall... the nerve of her!
Apart of Naraku...
That's all she is!
Lord Sesshomaru is so strong!
You don't need the power of
the Sacred Jewel!
Kagura... the Wind Sorceress
I wonder if she can use the Sacred Jewel
and defeat Naraku by herself?
But however it turns out...
It doesn't matter to me.
Lord Sesshomaru, leaving already?
Oops... I forgot.
Now come.
Lord Sesshomaru...
I am not lonely anymore.
But I wonder if she was
lonely because she was all alone?
Lord Sesshomaru!
What shall we do about dinner?
Oww!
Oh, maybe I wound it too tight.
No.
Thanks.
Because of your gentleness,
I don't feel the pain anymore.
Leave that half-dead wolf
demon alone, Kagome!
What?!
If it doesn't hurt anymore,
just go on home!
You runt!
What about you?!
Standing there weak and mortal!
You should talk?!
Hah! I'm not like this because
I wanna be!
Wanna fight?!
With pleasure!
Hey... Aren't we going to
take back the Sacred Jewel shards?
Why must you come along?!
Shaddup! They belong to me!
Why would I let you have them?!
Then Kagura hasn't returned
to the castle?
No.
Instead, I feel as though the
Sacred Jewel shards are going...
farther and farther away
from Naraku's castle.
What's going on?!
Kagura is an offshoot of
Naraku himself.
Isn't she acting according
to Naraku's will?
Does that mean Kagura is
stealing the shards?
It's not impossible.
Don't you think it's strange, Inuyasha?
Even the barrier.
Why did you and Koga pick up
the scent of the castle?
The barrier is weakened.
Isn't that because
Naraku's own powers are weak?
Powers are weak?
That's like!
Yes! Naraku is also a half-demon!
He used the body of a human
named Onigumo,
and gathered the powers of
countless demons.
That's Naraku!
Naraku is a half-demon, huh?
In the same way that Inuyasha loses
his powers on the night of the new moon,
perhaps Naraku has a day when
his powers wane.
Naraku has a weakness, too?!
Kagura... It's useless to run.
That cocky bastard...
How dare he say those things to me?!
Damn!
If you don't have the resolve
to go it alone,
don't even think of betrayal.
Hah! Use it myself?
And kill Naraku?
I've caught the scent!
It's Kagura!
Thanks for taking care of me!
I'm going on ahead!
Koga!
Why, that!
Koga, what about your wound?
I'm fine now.
Unlike that twerp, I'm a REAL demon!
What?!
See ya!
Who's the twerp! Hey!
Sango, Koga doesn't have his
Sacred Jewel shards anymore.
He doesn't have a chance!
I understand. Kirara!
Let Inuyasha down!
Inuyasha, lay low for a bit longer.
Damn! Cut out the jokes!
I'm coming!
Don't be hasty, Inuyasha!
Poison insects are out!
Naraku's making his move.
Inuyasha must not be seen
in his state.
Kagura!
Kagura, you!
What? Koga?
What do you want now?
Shaddup!
I'm taking back the shards
you took from me!
And you're relying on help
from Inuyasha and his gang?
Without these, you're too scared
to fight alone?
I'll beat Kagura alone!
Don't interfere!
What?!
Don't forget!
I still have my claws and fangs!
Try it!
Dance of Blades!
Damn! Dodging's about
all I can do!
I can't get close!
Just hurry up and die!
I don't have the time
to bother with YOU!
Koga!
Don't come!
You're a pesky one!
If you want to be free,
use the Sacred Jewel shards
and destroy Naraku yourself.
Humph! All right...
Damn!
I will use them.
What? It's not even a fight!
Naraku's demons!
Naraku...
He always sends so many!
Naraku hasn't realized that
I tried to betray him?
Or...
Does he intend to get rid
of me?
What're you standing in
a daze for?!
Die!
The Sacred Jewel shards!
Mine!
Dance of the Dragon!
That Koga! He can't even fight!
He'll be killed
unless we help him!
Hey, Miroku!
Don't try to stop me!
You want to save Koga?
Don't be silly! l just want
the Sacred Jewel shards!
If Koga is killed and this
battle ends,
Kagura will make her
escape again!
I can't just stand around
and watch!
Wait! No, Inuyasha!
Stop, Inuyasha!
Inuyasha? Why?!
Day is breaking! Inuyasha will
return to his half-demon state!
But if he's seen before that...
Kagome... Miroku... Sango!
You're all mere mortals,
yet you've fought hard!
Isn't that because you believed
in your own power?
Well, as if I can hold back!
Koga, you're a glutton for
punishment, aren't you?
Why don't you just
give up?
Koga!
It's done.
Huh?!
Kagura...
It's really not much fun killing
a half-dead wolf, is it?
Inuyasha?
I'll take you on now!
I know I saw it.
For a moment, I saw Inuyasha...
Do you think Kagura saw
Inuyasha in his human state?
Uh-huh...
That Inuyasha!
Is he crazy? Bursting in like that?
A second later, and Koga,
you'd've been killed by Kagura's wind.
What a laugh!
He came to save me...
knowing that his secret
would be revealed.
I see! There was no moon
last night.
Hah! Inuyasha...
So you lose your powers
on a moonless night?
So what?
I'm back so it doesn't matter!
It sure doesn't matter.
'Cuz you're gonna die right here
and now!
Dance of the Dragon!
Wind Scar!
What?! He cut through
my whirlpool!
Amazing!
I cannot dodge him!
He's going to get me!
Naraku's demons!
They acted as shields.
That Kagura! She escaped!
Hey, you puny wolf!
I hope this teaches you never to
interfere in my fight with Naraku!
Found it! My Sacred Jewel shards!
Hey! Give it here!
No way!
Remember this, mutt!
I've sworn to avenge my
comrades against Naraku!
I'll be the one to take Naraku's head!
Don't forget that!
Wait, Koga!
What you saw last night...
About Inuyasha...
Please don't tell!
Don't worry.
I could care less what
shape that mutt takes.
Does that mean he won't tell?
I think we can count
on Koga.
The problem is Kagura.
Naraku doesn't know about
my treachery.
That's why he used the demons
to save me.
Kanna... Where is she going?
A cellar beneath the cellar?
Kagura... Was it fun outside?
These bodies...
Naraku nourishes his body
with these demons...
I see!
Like Inuyasha, Naraku
is a half-demon!
Kagura...
While I slept,
you left the castle, didn't you?
Kagura... You are a part of me.
Would you like to return
to my flesh again?
W-Wait!
I promise I won't do it again!
There is no second time.
I cannot escape
from Naraku alone.
Inuyasha... I'll let you live
for a bit longer.
You're my precious trump card.
It'll get harder now.
Since Kagura knows the secret,
Sango and I must get even stronger,
Hah! Thanks, but no thanks
for worrying about me!
Besides, I'm the one who comes
through in a clutch.
You know?
He's just saying that.
I mean, before Inuyasha
met you all,
he'd never let anyone
see his human form.
He really depends on you.
Who said anything about
depending on anyone?!
Inuyasha, don't be embarrassed.
Who's embarrassed?!
- I think you are!
- I think so, too!
Cut it out, will ya?!
You can depend on us
anytime, Inuyasha!
Hey!
He's always fighting.
But he trusts us all.
That's why he wasn't discouraged
on the night of the new moon.
And that could be the secret
to his strength.
I am Shippo,
the child fox-demon of justice!
And I received a letter
of challenge!
And my opponents are...
Survivors of the Raijuu Tribe?!
Hah! Coming after me, huh?
T-They're pretty gutsy...
Next on Inuyasha:
"Shippo Gets An Angry Challenge!"
l-I'd better shape up.