Master Hiten is very handsome...
but Master Manten is
so dashing, too!
Those black locks...
irresistible!
With thick locks of hair...
I'm just as popular as
Brother Hiten.
Huh?!
Oh dear!
What's the matter, everyone?!
Where're you going?
If only I had hair...
a thick head of hair!
Huh?!
Ever since I reached puberty...
all my dreams have
been the same.
If only I had lots
and lots of hair...
I may not be
Brother Hiten's equal...
but I'd be quite popular.
Someday, I wish I could
be like Brother Hiten...
with lots of hair and
lots of girls...
It's time to hunt, Manten!
Coming, Brother Hiten!
Thunderbolt Attack!
Watch what we can do!
If I aim for there,
I can bring him down!
Huh?!
What?
My hair!
How could you?!
One thing seems true... You have the
fragments of the Sacred Jewel.
I'm gonna kill you and take 'em all!
You'll be the sorry one!
Hah! I wonder just how long you can
hold out against my strikes?
You have brute strength, at least.
This is gonna be fun!
Thunder Brothers, huh?
I'm getting tired of you!
Hmm... You want me to make
sport of you, huh?
Well, it's gonna be fun!
Hah! Of all the fools who
said the same thing...
none are alive today!
Fine! Get a taste of my
thunderbolt attack!
Take that!
Dodge it well
or you'll die!
Hiten's thunderbolt sword attack...
I can't let it touch my body
or I'm dead!
Inuyasha... Finish Hiten for me.
I'm gonna save Kagome!
Inuyasha!
Go for it, Brother Hiten!
I'll support you!
Two against one is cowardly!
Huh?!
I did it!
Kagome!
You can't afford to
worry about a woman now!
Kagome!
Hang tough until
I get there!
How am I to hang
onto anything?!
Oww!!
But I'm alive!
You bitch!
He's alive!
Wait!
Fox magic!
Spinning screw top!
Kagome, hurry over here!
Shippo!
Shippo, you know
such great magic!
Well...
You can't let your guard down yet.
I know...
Fox magic is actually
trickery.
Trickery?
Then what's that?
Owweee!!
It's all an illusion.
Damn! That fox tyke!
Huh?!
N-no!
Gone! It's gone!
My hair!
How dare you take my
last strand of hair?!
It's as though we added
fuel to the fire...
Damn!
Where are you?!
My hair potion candidate...
and that fox tyke!
Where'd they go?!
What'll we do? If we're found,
we'll be killed.
I know... that arrow!
Perhaps I can use it again.
Shippo, c'mere!
Are you here?!
Huh?
You bitch! Did you think
you could elude me?!
Shut up, you skinhead!
What?!
Look, hair that you love!
Two women?!
I'm taking back
my arrow!
Why you're... a fox!
I'm gonna avenge my
father's death!
Shippo, hold him down!
If I hit the Scared Jewel fragments
in the forehead...
I can beat him!
Why you!
I'll choke you to death!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Stop looking away!
Hah! You're not what
they said about you.
I expected more of
a fight!
Weakling!
How about I kill you slowly,
one limb at a time?
I can't concentrate on him.
I have to take care of
Kagome first.
Look, Manten... at this half-demon!
He's given up!
I'm having fun here, too, Brother!
A woman on the verge of
death is irresistible!
Damn!
Cut it out!
Shut up!
Angry, fox tyke?
Well, just wait.
After I kill her, I'll fleece you.
Just like I did your old man.
Maybe I'll turn you into
a hood.
I'll use father and son until
both their fur fall off!
Manten, you're becoming
pretty clever with words!
Brother praised me!
Unforgivable!
Hmmm? You fool!
I won't let go even if
it kills me!
Fox tyke... Release me!
Release me!
Or I'm gonna beat your
head to a pulp!
Manten... Watch out or
you'll soil his fur with blood.
Then he won't even make a hood.
All righty, Brother!
Damn! I may not be
the nicest guy around...
but you two are making
me sick!
Blades of Blood!
Fun! Keep attacking!
Fool! Where're you aiming?
I did it!
What?!
M-Manten!
Shippo!
Tetsusaiga! I must get it
to Inuyasha!
Father...
Yes... I must get
Shippo's father's body.
Manten!
Kagome! Hurry and
get away from there!
Damn!
Manten!
Brother Hiten...
My hair's all gone!
It's no use living.
What're you saying?!
Hang on and be strong!
Your locks are just
like Dad's.
I wish I inherited
Dad's looks.
If only Mom was a little
prettier with more hair.
I wonder what Dad saw in Mom
when he married her...
Huh, Brother Hiten?
It doesn't matter how
you look!
You're my dear, little brother!
Thanks, Brother Hiten.
When I'm reborn, I thought
I'd wanna be a fuzzy caterpillar.
With hair all over my body.
But I don't think so.
When I'm reincarnated...
even if I don't have
any hair at all...
I still wanna be born as
your kid brother.
Is that all right, Brother?
Manten! Manten?!
Hey, are you alive?
Sorry, Inuyasha...
I couldn't get Tetsusaiga.
Is that what took
you so long?
Sorry... After you rescued me.
Fool! Don't worry about
such a thing!
Even without a sword, no way would
I lose to that beast!
Manten...
Manten is dead!
Poor thing!
I'll always be with you!
Is he eating his brother?
No.
Hiten is synthesizing the Sacred Jewel
fragments into his own body.
Master Inuyasha, you must
be very careful.
He now has the power of
five Jewel fragments.
I got that, Myoga.
But where were you until now?
Err...
Probably hiding out in
a safe place.
You only appear when
it's convenient!
I've been thinking about
smashing you one day!
Oh... Stop quibbling about
minor matters.
Watch out!
You... dared... to kill
my dear kid brother.
I won't let you get away
with it!
The power in the thunderbolt
sword is increasing!
Five fragments combined
into one is a formidable force!
Kagome, take Shippo and
get as far as possible!
Inuyasha!
Hurry!
'Kay!
I'll avenge my kid brother!
Prepare yourself!
It's too powerful!
I can't repel it!
Master Inuyasha, use the
sheathe of Tetsusaiga!
The sheathe of Tetsusaiga?!
It will repel the bolt
without fail! Now use it!
Are you sure?!
What?!
Th-this is...
Just as I thought.
This is a sheathe that keeps
Tetsusaiga's power in check.
It should be able to repel
thunderbolt power.
My hunch was right.
You mean, you weren't sure?!
Well... That was a close call for me
since I couldn't get away.
Look, we got away with
our lives intact.
Let's make our escape!
Don't be ridiculous!
I can use this!
Die!
If I attack right to the core,
I can beat him!
Who's core?!
Inuyasha!
Father's fur...
Shippo, you're conscious.
Kagome... Where's Manten?
Inuyasha killed him.
But now, his brother Hiten...
Wanna be burned
to a crisp...
Or chopped up like salad!?
Inuyasha is tired.
His opponent can move
through the air with ease.
Hiten has wheels...
That's it!
Due to the Sacred Jewel
fragments...
even his speed is
picking up!
If only I had a bow...
Leave it to me!
I must repay my debts
or my father will scold me.
You can transform into
a bow!
Or are you a snail?
A bow!
What's the matter?
Shoot quickly!
I only have one arrow and...
my shots haven't hit
too often.
I'll lend you my power, too.
Thanks, Shippo!
Die!
I got him!
Now!
Are you stupid?!
Impossible...
No matter how strong
Master Inuyasha is...
what can he do by grabbing
hold of the thunderbolt sword?!
Myoga, when'd you come here?
Oh goodness, let go, fool!
This sheathe is only...
in the way!
No! You stupid fool!
Who told you to let
go of the sheathe?!
This way's better!
Did you feel that,
you imbecile?!
He slugged the guy?!
Simple, but amazing!
Leave it to Master Inuyasha!
Now it's a duel of
physical strength!
Give 'im the one-two punch!
Weren't you just calling
him a fool?
It's the first time someone's
hit me in the face!
- He's about to explode!
- He's in such a passion!
This is the end, you!
The sheathe has a crack!
Just because this half-demon
caused so much trouble!
No! If the sheathe breaks
in half...
even the powerful Master Inuyasha...
Will lose?!
I must get Tetsusaiga to
Inuyasha!
All right! I'll go!
Shippo, don't move!
It's too dangerous!
Wait, Shippo!
Dang it... He can use Manten's
power as well...!
Watch out! Run!
Kagome!
Serves you right!
Kagome!!
Looks like they're dead,
both the kid and the woman.
Why you!
Unforgivable!
You're just a half-demon!
Yet he's fighting like a
real demon!
I refuse to die
until I kill you!
Has the blood gone to your
head since...
the woman has been killed?
Stop acting so stupid over
some silly woman!
I'll teach you the
pain and sorrow...
of one who has lost
his only dear, little brother!
It's going to break!
I've won!
Tetsusaiga!
The sheathe has
summoned the sword!
Tetsusaiga!
I've lost...!
To a half-demon... Lost...
Master Inuyasha...
The Sacred Jewel fragments.
Damn...
If only I had defeated Hiten earlier...
Inuyasha...
Kagome...
Inuyasha... Thanks for
everything.
I'm happy that my father's
murder has been avenged.
Ohh... Those are the souls
of Kagome and Shippo.
They've come to bid
a final farewell.
What?!
Wait!
Don't go!
Kagome!
Huh?!
Yes?
You're alive?
Go where?
Father... He protected us with
fox fire.
Hmm... From what I saw...
that was undoubtedly fox fire
that shot out from the fur.
They weren't the souls?
Well, err...
That was that and...
Umm...
Besides, why'd you get
so sappy on me?!
If you're gonna die, die!
If you're not, don't die!
Just be clear!
Inuyasha... What's the matter?
Why're you so angry?
He's embarrassed that he
misunderstood something...
in the heat of passion.
Master Inuyasha is still
very naive.
Oww...
Shippo, why don't you
go home already?!
What?! Why can't
I stay with you?!
Let him stay, Inuyasha.
Shippo is all alone.
Yes, yes! I'm actually
a very cute kid.
Hah! You only act the good kid
when it's convenient.
Shippo, when're you going home?!
Kagome, he's being mean!
- Inuyasha, be nice!
- Ha!
Sit!
Still so young!
Higurashi Shrine where I live
is very, very old.
I never took Grandpa's omens
and exorcisms seriously.
But the old hidden well...
rumored to lead to another dimension
to the Feudal States Era...
is full of old stickers and
charms to ward off the spirits.
But an old Noh mask that had been
locked up in the storeroom...
burns through the charms
and comes after us!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Terror of the Ancient Noh Mask"
Don't miss it!