Sesshomaru had denounced
the half-demon Inuyasha
as a disgrace to his clan
and despised the human race...
But Jaken, Sesshomaru's henchman,
definitely had a human girl with him.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Rin has been kidnapped!
One of Naraku's incarnations
named Kagura appeared...
out of the blue...
Let me reassure you, Lord Sesshomaru.
If you heed my request,
I shall return Rin in
one piece.
Y-You are Naraku!
Just a little more...
Soon you will be absorbed...
and become one with my flesh!
We follow the trail of
the Sacred Jewel shards.
That's right!
Kohaku, Sango's youngerbrother,
has a single shard
which was imbedded in his back
by Naraku.
Inuyasha headed out alone
forNaraku's castle.
Miasma and toxic fumes...
this has gotta be it!
This is Naraku's barrier!
Tetsusaiga!
I can see it!
Naraku's castle!
He's coming.
That Kagura... She must have failed.
Naraku, you seem preoccupied
with what's beyond the castle walls.
Lord Sesshomaru, I no longerhave time
to dally with you.
Yourpower...
Every bit of
yourdemon power...
shall be wholly consumed by me.
L-Lord Sesshomaru!
T-This is terrible!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Staff ofTwo Heads...!
Huh?! Why is this happening?!
S-Stop!
Will he be all right?
This can't be happening!
Lord Sesshomaru has been!
Lord Sesshomaru...
I've finally obtained the powers
of a full-fledged demon!
Naraku!
Is that yourtrue form?!
Inuyasha!
Take this! Wind Scar!
I think not!
My barrier!?
I've found you, Naraku!
Today, I shall kill you!
Hmph! Don't make me laugh!
Kill me, you say?
Yes! Right now, Inuyasha can
defeat Naraku.
Huh?
That's!
So Naraku has already engulfed
Sesshomaru's body.
That means...
Naraku must be destroyed before
he has a chance
to absorb the demon power.
It'll be too late once Naraku
totally absorbs it, Inuyasha!
I miscalculated.
I did not expect Inuyasha
to come this far.
Inuyasha!
So you're able to break
through my barrier.
Naraku, you bastard!
You won't get away this time!
Prepare to die!
You seem to have become
a bit stronger.
But you're still no match
forme.
Take this!
No problem!
I'm not done yet!
Why you...!
Naraku!
W-What?!
What's this?
I'll engulf you, just like
I did Sesshomaru.
W-What?!
Sesshomaru?
Naraku's still too much forhim.
You're too late, Inuyasha.
Sesshomaru is already part
of my flesh.
I don't know whatgood your
half-demon powerwill do.
But I'll absorb you into me
as well.
Don't put me in the same
class as that Sesshomaru!
Wha...!
This is it!
No mercy!
Take this!
What?!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Sesshomaru!
Huh?!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Naraku...
Such irony.
That the flesh which bound me
would shield me against
Inuyasha's Wind Scar.
Move! Naraku's mine!
No, he is my prey.
Hah! Quit joking!
You're always!
I shall absorb the both of you!
What?!
Die!
You won't be able to
escape my attacks forever.
You're one persistent bastard!
Take this and... die!
What?!
Finishing blow!
I said he's mine!
What?!
A miasma!
Lord Sesshomaru.
I shall retreat tonight.
Fool!
Don't think you can escape
from me!
Lord Sesshomaru...
Instead of transforming
and coming after me,
you should hurry to
yourlittle girl companion.
Kohaku?
What's the matter?
Girl companion?
What's he talking about?
Rin is currently with
one named Kohaku.
Kohaku?!
Inuyasha, you should know
what that means.
Kohaku...
Sesshomaru's full-fledged
demon power...
I was within grasp of it all!
But I miscalculated Inuyasha!
I didn't expect him to become
this strong.
That Naraku... He's a tough one
to deal with.
It's gone.
Every scent, every clue of Naraku
is gone.
Even though he's badly injured.
Where could he have gone?
Hey Sesshomaru!
Did Naraku take a hostage?
Is this Rin a friend of yours?
So Rin was abducted in order
to buy time to escape.
Naraku...
He's becoming more
and more cunning.
H-Hey!
L-Lord Sesshomaru!
Don't leave me...!
Hey!
l-Inuyasha!
Damn right!
Jaken, explain.
What happened between
Naraku and Sesshomaru?
Hah! I'm underno obligation to
tell you, a half-demon!
If I tell you, it's a long story.
So make it short.
They're coming!
Hiraikotsu!
I see... They don't want us
to get nearthat mansion.
That's...
It IS Kohaku!
With a little girl!
That girl...
I've seen her before.
Kohaku!
Damn! Get out of my way!
We have to go after them!
Kagome!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Kohaku was here, wasn't he?
We can still catch him.
I can sense the Sacred Jewel
shard close by.
Inuyasha!
I'm going ahead!
The fasterthe better!
Kohaku's mind is controlled
by Naraku.
Yeah! Naraku probably made a
hypnotic suggestion to him...
to kill the hostage.
In orderto buy time
to escape from Sesshomaru,
Naraku had the girl kidnapped.
Then...
the child with Kohaku is
Sesshomaru's?
He considers humans no better
than worms.
So I can't believe that he'd
have a mortal at his side.
But there's no way he'd
let Kohaku live...
not afterwhat Naraku did.
Sesshomaru will kill Kohaku!
Sango's younger brother...
Killed by your olderbrother?
Whatever the case, it'll only
end up in tragedy.
We have to reach Kohaku
before Sesshomaru.
Right!
I'm the only one who can
stop Sesshomaru.
Tell me, why did we run away?
Someone was outside
the mansion.
Where are we going?
Tell me, Kohaku!
Huh?
Kill her!
K-Kohaku...
W-What's wrong with you, Kohaku?!
Kill her!
So... You turn yourblade
towards me now?
Kohaku!
Why you...!
What're you doing, fool?!
She's all right.
She just fainted.
We made it in time!
You heard her, Sesshomaru.
So don't lay a hand
on Kohaku.
It's useless, Inuyasha.
Even if you intervene,
that boy seems compelled
to die by my hands.
This must be anotherhypnotic
suggestion by Naraku...
to attack Sesshomaru and be killed.
You disarmed the boy.
Inuyasha, I didn't think you had such
strong feelings forme, your brother.
In yourdreams!
If you don't let him go,
I'll kill you!
Stop, Sesshomaru!
Enough, Sesshomaru!
This boy...
He has no suffering... has no fear.
I don't like... his eyes.
Oh, you're conscious.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Huh?
Kohaku...
Aren't you going afterhim?
Kagura?!
Um... thank you...
forforgiving Kohaku.
That boy tried to die at my hands.
Sesshomaru, you... knew?
I don't want to play into Naraku's
treacherous hands. That's all.
Good bye!
She went with him.
I see...
So Kohaku went away again.
Forgive me!
If I had killed Naraku,
Kohaku would also...
No, if we had stopped him...
It can't be helped.
As long as he's alive.
That Naraku...
Where'd he disappearto?
With a wound that serious,
he can't be able to
put up a strong barrier.
Just where?
Did Naraku lift the barrier,
leaving the castle visible?
That means... that this castle
has been abandoned.
That he is hiding himself
somewhere else.
Strange...
No matterwhere he moved to,
I was always able to
sense his barrier.
Yet...
As though he disappeared
into thin air,
there's no trace of Naraku.
There's something to this.
Damn that Naraku!
Afterwe almost had him cornered!
Is it really okay to
return to the present age?
Hey! Kagome!
Haven't we changed places?
You're right!
How'll we do the preview?
We've got no choice, just do it.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Gap Between the Ages"
Look forward to it!
Hey, I ain't taking no test!
Oh, we're back to normal.