Come on out, Tsubaki!
It IS that Tsubaki, after all.
Which Tsubaki?
A priestess, 50 years ago,
just like my sister, Kikyo.
Sister, who is that priestess?
That is Tsubaki.
I never imagined she would turn
to the Dark side.
Who cares about the past?!
Where is she now?!
What's the matter, Kagome?
Way inside...
I sense the Sacred Jewel.
All right!
But this area is...
What's the matter, Kaede?
Stories have been passed down,
that in this area a demon
was sealed away.
A demon?
That's!
So it's appeared!
Move, you!
Hiraikotsu!
You've come to?
You are!
Calm down!
I don't intend to hurt you.
Just...
Just?
Listen... Will you bear my child?
Well? Will you bear my child?
Will just anyone do?!
No, it's not that.
Oh, you're conscious.
Yes.
You appeared, Demon!
Stay away!
You're mistaken!
Shippo has taken care of
you all this time.
This demon?
I was ordered by Kagome and
the others, not to touch you.
So Shippo has been taking
care of you.
Maybe it was unnecessary.
He's not a bad demon?
I never hurt humans.
Really?
It can't be helped that priestesses
like yourselves
would consider all demons bad.
However...
What's the matter?
- So cute!!!
- What?!
Tail! A tail!
Ears, ears!
M-Miroku!
Hey, Miroku!
Please help me!
Just put up with it in order to
prove that you're not a bad demon.
I'm so envious!
However...
Why do you go after
Priestess Tsubaki?
Yes, isn't that Inuyasha
a bad demon?
Tsubaki tried to curse Kagome
to death.
- Impossible!
- That can't be!
I don't know what
Tsubaki has told you.
However, she is a dark priestess
now, who curses people.
Hah! Some enemy!
Yes, that Shikigami was not
all that powerful.
Does that mean Tsubaki's power
is weakening?
But she has the Sacred Jewel.
She probably can't use it
properly.
Let's go!
Here?
Uh-huh.
What is this pagoda?
The place where you'll die.
Why, you... Kagura!
So Naraku and Tsubaki
are in cahoots!
Naraku's with her, huh?
Couldn't be better!
I'll kill you both along
with Tsubaki!
Not so fast.
Your fight's not with me.
l just came to witness
your deaths.
No problem!
This one's just another puppet!
Inuyasha!
Hah! I guess he can fight a little.
Then take this!
Dance of Blades!
I guess you're not just
a witness! Hiraikotsu!
Just to keep
from getting bored.
Fujin!
Inuyasha!
Dance of the Dragon!
Go my blades!
Why, you!
Here goes!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
Next, it's your turn!
Hold it!
Tsubaki's first!
Damn!
Inuyasha, I sense the Sacred Jewel!
There was a barrier here to
keep something sealed within.
But the seal has been broken.
You mean the Shikikami earlier?
A seal this strong isn't necessary
for a Shikikami like that.
We'll find out inside!
C'mon!
Tsubaki is a Dark Priestess?
I can't believe such a thing!
You belong to the same
shrine as Tsubaki,
so I don't blame you for
not believing.
So why not go and
see for yourself?
Let's hurry!
Hang on tight.
He's having so much
fun with this!
Kirara, let's go!
Open, oh demon gates!
Come forth, oh golden god!
You dared to seal me within!
You shall not be forgiven!
Never!
I will give you power!
I have the power of the
Sacred Jewel here!
Now, do you not desire
this power?
Give it to me! Give it!
Give it to me!
Demon!
Demon power!
This is amazing!
So there you are, Tsubaki!
It is you!
I have been waiting.
We want the Sacred Jewel back.
Sacred Jewel?
I see... This is amazing!
The Sacred Power is in
Tsubaki's right eye.
Right eye?
I never imagined it would
be this powerful!
If only this Jewel had become
mine fifty years ago!
Fifty years, you say?
Tsubaki! What happened between
you and Kikyo fifty years ago?
Kikyo?
You say Kikyo?
Aghhh!
It's all Kikyo's fault!
That cold, smug priestess!
Don't you say anything
against Kikyo!
Silence!
Inuyasha!
So what's after the demon?
Just what are you harboring
in that right eye?
Overflowing... I'm overflowing
with demon power!
It's coursing throughout my body!
Demon?
What happened to the pagoda?
Impossible!
The forbidden pagoda gates
can't be open!
Forbidden?
But who?
What's that?!
It's!
Inuyasha!
This is the power of
the Sacred Jewel!
the demon!
What's the matter?
Does my power make
you speechless?
The seal has been broken!
That's Tsubaki!
She couldn't have
broken the seal!
With this power, I shall
have eternal life!
Stay back!
This power is amazing!
Inuyasha!
Why, you!
Damn!
It countered Tetsusaiga's thrust!
It won't work!
Don't act so smug!
Take my Wind Scar!
Why, you!
My Wind Scar didn't work!
You fool!
Inuyasha!
That leaves... my Wind Tunnel!
Why, that!
You may be Kikyo's reincarnation,
but you're nothing much.
Kikyo was just a priestess who
wasted the power of the Sacred Jewel!
What are you saying?!
I, Tsubaki, am the perfect match
for the Sacred Jewel.
Sister, what is that?
The Sacred Jewel.
I have been entrusted
with the duty
to keep the Jewel clean
and pure.
Fifty years have passed.
And at last, the power of the
Sacred Jewel is mine!
Why, you!
You won't get your way!
Hiraikotsu!
More! Even more!
The Sacred Jewel can take on
even more power!
There are countless demons who
desire the power of this Jewel!
I will devour them all
and I will grasp power
and eternal life!
She intends to use the power
of the Sacred Jewel
to consume the power of
demons.
I won't let her!
Half-demon, you will also
become mine!
What?!
Inuyasha, aren't you the one?
Who made Kikyo lose her heart?
Why, you!
The half-demon that Kikyo
could not have...
I shall devour whole!
Now then, give up your heart
to the Sacred Jewel!
This power...
Why, half-demon!
Why do you not give yourself
up to the Power?
Because you make the
Sacred Jewel filthy!
Which Kikyo never did!
How dare you!
Inuyasha!
I gave up everything in order
to posses the Sacred Jewel!
Wait, Tsubaki! Wait!
No, Master!
I am not satisfied!
Why did you entrust the Sacred Jewel
to Kikyo and not me?!
Well...
Why can't it be me?
Tsubaki!
I, Tsubaki, will not take
second place to Kikyo!
Know the wrath of
my power!
This is bad!
Inuyasha!
You're too easy!
That miasma will be
your downfall!
Take this! Backlash Wave!
The demon!?
The demon is disappearing!
Why?!
Not yet!
As long as I possess
the Sacred Jewel!
My Sacred Jewel!
You won't get away!
Why, you! Hold it!
So long.
Damn!
Damn it!
My youth is being
sucked out of me.
I can't hang on to my youth!
She aged so suddenly.
Tsubaki has lost the demon powers
as well as the power of the Sacred Jewel.
She has no choice but to go
back to her original form.
Oh, where did I go wrong?
Was it that half-demon?
Or that Kagome?
Or was it because I accepted
Naraku's offer?
Where did I?
Tsubaki!
I will not take
second place to Kikyo!
I should have the Sacred Jewel,
not Kikyo!
I, Tsubaki!
I, Tsubaki, am the ultimate
priestess!
It's the end of the Dark Priestess.
Tsubaki...
Please forgive us for
our errors.
Don't worry about it.
It wasn't your fault.
So then...
Take care, Shippo.
You, too.
It turns out that we were
victims of Naraku's treachery.
Who?
Tsubaki as well as us.
And the Sacred Jewel is still
in Naraku's hands.
I'll get it back without fail!
Yes, you're right, Inuyasha.
I'm so tired.
Shall we return?
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
It's nothing.
Just my imagination.
Tsubaki was so obsessed with
the Sacred Jewel...
But there was no way she
would win...
Obsessed... Who am I to talk?
What's the matter, Myoga?
You usually try to avoid us,
but today, you've actually
come to us!
Miroku is attacking Sango!
What's going on?!
Even Inuyasha is acting funny!
Could this be the curse of the
giant centipede?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Farewell Days of My Youth!"
Whose youth anyway?