Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The sacred ground of Mt. Hakurei
overflows with demonic aura.
Naraku's presence seems
ever so close.
In order to reach him,
Inuyasha must face a final
confrontation with Bankotsu,
the leader of the Band of Seven!
It's up to us and Miroku, Sango,
Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Humph!
I am none other than Bankotsu,
the leader of the Band of Seven!
I lose to no one!
Miroku, are you all right?!
Yes, more or less.
The remains of demons!
Sango, lower me down!
Is this Naraku's doing?
I didn't become the leader of
the Band of Seven for nothing!
Before I was resurrected with
the Shikon Jewel,
I controlled that gang of
murderers with my power!
Hmph! You're so pathetic!
You have a Sacred Jewel shard
imbedded in your left arm, too.
Such a simple method of
using your shards....
considering how twisted you are.
So you let me hit you on purpose,
just to check me out?
Will you get my shards?
Or will I pull your head off?
Who'll be first?!
Take that! And that!
How's that?!
Master Jaken! Look at the sky!
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru!
They're making their escape!
Um, aren't you going after them?
I have no interest
in the insignificant.
Did Naraku set them free
on purpose?
Or has he no use for
them anymore?
In any case, I shall go and see.
Kagome, is this the place?
Where Naraku is hiding?
Yes. I sense the presence of
Sacred Jewel shards
from inside this cave.
Do we have to go in?
Yes, we have to...
But....
Oh yeah, don't we have to wait
for Hakkaku and Ginta?
We can't be waiting
around for them.
You're right.
We must hurry!
Yeah!
Hey! I haven't prepared myself
for this!
We have to hurry.
I sense the shards steadily
becoming tainted.
So many of them!
It seems without a doubt
that Naraku was
rebuilding himself in here.
Then these demons....
They were probably used to
create parts of Naraku's body.
Huh?
What is that?
It's moving!
Not just one of them!
This is....
They aren't demons.
They're like clumps of flesh.
Yes. It's as though they're about
to spawn something....
Spawn?
But what?
I don't know.
Where did Naraku escape to?
Why you...!
He countered my attack?!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
I'm making it easy for you
to take my shards
by punching with this hand!
So is this battle over?
Man, what a disappointment!
I thought you'd put up
more of a fight.
Don't worry, Inuyasha.
I don't toy with the weak.
Because I have no interest
in weaklings.
So die.
Why you...!
I'm not like the others
you've killed.
I can take a lot of damage.
I've got five of them.
Once I get the shard
in your left arm,
it'll be over for you, Bankotsu.
Silence!
I'll never die!
I'll kill you and take back
the shards you stole from me!
It's useless!
Besides, even if you get
outta here,
Naraku would never let you stay
alive with the Sacred Jewel shards!
You're the one who
Naraku wants to kill, aren't you?
Look!
They're not guards.
They intend to go after
the one who survives.
That Naraku....
I don't know what kind
of promise you made with Naraku....
Awaken, Bankotsu.
Awaken.
I grant you life once more.
Work for me.
And I shall give you
life eternal.
Go forth with your comrades.
And destroy all my enemies.
You and the Band of Seven were
just used by Naraku
to provide a shield for himself.
Hah! So what of it?
What?!
The Band of Seven were originally
mercenaries hired by clan lords
who didn't give a damn
about us.
And when we became
too strong and dangerous,
they pursued us and
chopped off our heads!
I never trusted Naraku.
But now that I'm resurrected,
I can do as I please.
I'll kill anyone who gets
in my way, including Naraku!
Geez! Naraku revived
one hell of a guy!
Silence!
What about you? How did you
awaken from your seal?
None of your business.
It's greed, Inuyasha.
You're all the same.
That dried-up old Saint....
The dead priestess....
And even you who
broke free from your seal.
You're all greedy for life,
so you live!
Don't make us the only villains.
You're evil villains
who killed countless people!
Yeah, and we've killed
our share of demons too!
Damn!
There are Sacred Jewel shards
imbedded in Banryu!
Huh?!
Nine hundred ninety-one!
What the...!!
Nine hundred ninety-two!
Nine hundred ninety-three!
What the hell are you doing?!
Come and get me!
Nine hundred ninety-four!
Nine hundred ninety-five!
Nine hundred ninety-six!
What the...!?
Nine hundred ninety-seven!
Nine hundred ninety-eight!
Nine hundred ninety-nine!
A thousand!!
I don't need any more!
What...?!
If you decide to get outta here,
I won't get in your way.
Only after I kill you and
avenge my brothers.
Hah! Just because your
blade transformed a little!
I wanted to cut your head off
to complete the transformation.
But it wouldn't have been enough;
you being only a half-demon.
Whaddya mean?!
Just this!
What is this?!
The power from that sword!
It's just like Sesshomaru's
sword, Tokijin!
When I first met Naraku,
he told me about the existence
of the Shikon Jewel.
About a jewel that could empower
both humans and demons.
Humans can't possess
demon powers.
And I didn't care for
spiritual powers!
And I wasn't born
with the power of the divine!
I always thought that in order
to become strong,
you had to make
yourself strong.
But there was one other way.
To put power into an object.
So I made a wish
on this Banryu....
And I've cut off the heads
of a thousand warlords.
Wind Scar!
And just now, I killed
a thousand demons!
My Wind Scar....
Besides the wish
I made on Banryu,
it has Sacred Jewel shards
inside it.
One thousand humans,
one thousand demons.
This is a demon sword that has
absorbed the wrath of two thousand lives.
You wield a demon sword, too....
But can it beat my Banryu?!
You were resurrected
by Sacred Jewel shards,
but you're still human!
That sword is covered
by a demonic aura!
Get rid of it,
for your own good!
Go to hell!
A demon wouldn't understand!
Or because you're half-demon,
you think you understand?!
How can you understand
this world of man
where you're nothing
if you're not strong!
It's over!
Demonic aura?!
With this power,
I'll lose to no one!
Bankotsu is not a demon.
But if Banryu's producing
this demonic aura,
I can use the Backlash Wave!
Backlash Wave!
Huh?!
Whaa...!
Why....?!
Bankotsu, you were
too greedy.
You were strong,
just with your bare hands.
What's this?!
Miroku!
What is it?!
Run!
What's happening?
Keep going and we'll find out.
The demonic aura is
growing stronger.
Rin....
Yes?
Get away from the mountain
with A-Un.
But.... What about you,
Lord Sesshomaru?
It's goes without saying.
Naraku is in there.
Pardon me....
What is it?
Naraku has kept himself
hidden until now
in order to recoup his strength.
He is most probably much stronger
than he was before.
So?
Huh?
Err.... Well....
I guess I'm getting a
little weak with age....
Lord Sesshomaru!
Good luck to you!
Damn!
What's with this ground?!
It's trying to draw me in.
Not only the ground.
This entire cave looks like
a giant wall of flesh!
It's getting noisier in here.
Let's hurry, Kagome.
Huh?!
What's going on?!
Koga!
Damn! What's happening?!
Take my hand, Koga!
Hang on, Koga!
Don't give up!
Let go, Kagome!
Huh?
I'm not gonna put
you in danger....
Koga...
Don't! This is definitely....!
Koga!
What is this?
It's not stone.
K-Kagome....
This entire cave....
It's like being inside
a belly of a living being.
Kagome, will we be
devoured, too?
I don't know.
But if so, why haven't we
been eaten up already?
In any case, let's go
after Koga.
We can't leave him!
But we don't even know
where he's buried!
I can sense them....
The Sacred Jewel shards
in Koga's legs.
They're moving along these
fleshy walls
and heading straight towards
the presence of Naraku's
tainted presence.
Why this...!
We made it out!
Yes.
But where are we?
Kagome, what's that?
Demons?
I think they're a little different.
Whatever they are,
they give me the creeps.
Those voices....
Is that Kagome and Shippo?
Miroku! Sango!
Kagome!
Is it just the two of you?
Where's Inuyasha?
What about Inuyasha?
He went after you and
entered Mt. Hakurei
ahead of us.
We haven't crossed paths.
Where could he have gone?
Inuyasha....
Arghh!
Kirara, go!
Thank you, Kirara.
Where's Kagome?!
I've got you, Kagome.
I know.
Something's coming
up from the bottom.
This is....
Inuyasha!
What happened to you, Inuyasha?
The Sacred Jewel shards
of the Band of Seven
have been taken
by Naraku.
So you've finally made
your move, Naraku!
It has begun....
But it will end quickly.
That's....!
Naraku's new body.
Inuyasha and his friends
will die here.
And I now possess
a new body.
Naraku has appeared at last!
But what is his true aim?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Beyond the Darkness-Naraku Reborn!"
Only one thing remains.... Kikyo.