Master!
Tsubaki, the Dark Priestess.
A priestess on the dark side
specializing in curses.
Tsubaki who desires
eternal youth...
agrees to lend Naraku
her skills of malediction...
in exchange
for the Sacred Jewel.
Using her messenger demon,
Shikigami, she places a curse on me...
and takes control of my body.
The Shikon Jewel Shards have
entered my body.
Kagome!
G-get away...
What can I do?!
Suffer... Inuyasha.
Get away!
Inuyasha!
How interesting.
How does it feel, Inuyasha?
To, once again, have the woman you love
aim an arrow at you.
Inuyasha!
K- Kikyo...
Why you!
Just like the time Kikyo
shot and killed you...
you can re-experience
that moment 50 years ago,
this time,
through Kagome's hands.
Feel the pain
to the fullest, Inuyasha!
Damn! This is such
a strong barrier.
Does that mean
the Dark Priestess is inside?
After coming all this way...
Miroku, can't we break
the barrier?
Kirara, go!
I hate to admit it, but this barrier
is too much for me.
Miroku, look!
This is...
I can feel it...
This miasma full of evil.
Kikyo!
What is she doing here?
They are...
Inuyasha's friends.
What does that mean?
What's going on inside?
She went inside!
Choose whichever you like, Inuyasha!
Will you be killed by Kagome?
Or will you run
and save yourself?
But if you run,
Kagome will die...
From the curse
of the Dark Priestess.
Please! Run!
Kagome!
You fool!
As if I'd leave you and run!
Kill Inuyasha!
Inuyasha seems to have chosen death
at the hands of the woman.
Naraku... You are truly evil.
To make the reincarnation of Kikyo
kill the man she loves... yet again.
Kikyo?!
...You are?
Kikyo appeared.
Kikyo?
Don't underestimate the power
of that priestess.
Are you sure that Tsubaki
can manage?
Let her.
There's time after we see
what she's up to.
Kagome...
Kagome!
Inu... yasha...
Are you all right?
Uh-huh...
The voice in my head is gone.
Kagome...
Take me! I can sense it!
The presence
of the Sacred Jewel!
Kagome!
Don't try to get up!
The voice stopped.
So this is my chance.
You're going to look for it?
The Dark Priestess
is dangerous!
The curse isn't lifted yet.
I'll protect Kagome!
Inuyasha!
Will Kagome be all right?
She seems to be in such pain.
She will be okay. Kagome is a strong girl.
Besides, Inuyasha is with her.
Let us wait until they return safely.
Kagome, hang in there!
She's desperately enduring the pain.
Inuyasha, do not let Kagome die!
You must find a way to break
the curse and save Kagome!
Inuyasha... I'm sorry.
You didn't shoot that arrow!
Don't worry about it!
Damn! The enemy is so close!
Even while
we waste time here,
the Dark Priestess's curse
is doing its evil.
If it lasts much longer,
Kagome won't be able to endure it.
It may be difficult to break through
this barrier, but...
...it's better than doing nothing!
Let's go, Miroku!
Yes!
Kirara!
What's going on?
This girl, Kagome...
Isn't she your reincarnation, Kikyo?
Tsubaki...
So you've put a curse
on Kagome.
It's useless with the power
that you have.
Humph! Don't take me lightly, Kikyo.
I'm not the same person you
defeated last time.
I don't even need to be told that.
A glance at you tells me everything.
Tsubaki, you sold your soul to a demon
in exchange for youth.
For youth AND beauty.
Ahh... this youth and beauty.
Someday, I shall lose them.
Is that the fate of one
who is not a God?
No... If I can get a hold of the
Sacred Jewel that Kikyo guards...
This beauty will be eternal.
Me? A human?
You can become one!
You are, after all, half-human.
In the hands of evil, the Sacred Jewel
increases the power of evil.
But if it is used
to make you human,
the Jewel will be purified and
eventually, disintegrate.
At that time, Kikyo...
What'll happen to you?
I am the guardian of the Jewel.
If there is no Jewel,
I become an ordinary woman.
I can defeat Kikyo now... while she
is infatuated with a half-demon!
Arise, my Shikigami!
Kill Kikyo and
steal the Sacred Jewel!
Now go!
That day, fifty years ago...
Kikyo, you reversed the curse
unto me!
My face... My face!
I wasn't able to steal
the Sacred Jewel from you.
But I linked up with demons,
and gained eternal youth and beauty.
As well as demon power!
How foolish!
You should talk!
How can you appear here
looking exactly the same as before?
Kikyo... You!
Dead souls?
That body is neither
mortal nor demon.
It's a fake.
Kikyo...
You are using dead souls, yet you
dare lecture me?
l just came here to ascertain the
cause of the miasma.
I care not what happens to you.
It's coming closer.
Huh?
What?!
Inuyasha, why didn't you run away?
I already told you!
I wouldn't leave you!
One wrong move...
And it would've ended up
like the time with Kikyo.
Even if that did happen,
I wouldn't have run!
I'm gonna stay by you!
So don't bring it up again!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Inside that barrier... is the enemy!
The Sacred Jewel is being purified!
Is this the work... of that woman...
Kagome?!
I told you, Tsubaki.
A curse by the likes of you
won't work on Kagome.
Be quiet!
You are to blame for appearing
when unwanted!
This barrier!
The barrier is broken!
My barrier...
That's!
Inuyasha!
That Kagome! She missed!
Kikyo!
What are you doing?!
What did you just say?!
You tried to have Inuyasha killed...
by Kagome's arrow?!
Humph!
What's the matter, Kikyo?
Some unpleasant memories maybe?
Yes, I made Kagome shoot
the arrow.
Kikyo...
In just the same way that you
killed Inuyasha back then.
Huh?!
Tsubaki...
I have no intention of interfering with
whatever you do to Kagome.
However, if you ever
harm Inuyasha...
I will personally kill you.
Why you!
As if I would fear you!
Heed my words.
It is no idle threat.
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
So you're here, too?
Inside... is the Sacred Jewel.
As well as the one who put the curse
on me and manipulated me.
Are you the Dark Priestess?
I am known as Tsubaki.
Are you Inuyasha...
Kikyo's lover?
W-What!
Tsubaki, where is Kikyo?
I know she was in here!
Kikyo?
I saw her, too!
I saw Kikyo coming here.
Humph! That woman!
Inuyasha, she came to beg
for your life.
Kikyo still has feelings
for Inuyasha...
She borrows her body
from dead souls...
She cannot come to terms with
death because of her love for a man.
Miroku! Sango!
Watch over Kagome!
Are you all right, Kagome?
Yes...
Hey you!
You seem to know an awful
lot about us.
On top of which,
you used a dirty curse to manipulate
Kagome to make her kill me.
I'll bet the one pulling the
strings is Naraku!
And what of it?
Then, I won't stand for it!
I'll kill you!
Tetsusai!
If you draw your sword,
Kagome will die!
Huh?!
Fool!
My curse has not been broken yet!
As long as the Sacred Jewel
is in my hand,
Kagome's life is mine to control!
Why that!
Kagome!
The evil is back.
That young twit...
She can't even thwart
the Jewel's powers.
So silly.
The purification of the Jewel...
the breaking of the barrier...
It was all because
Kikyo interfered
and distracted my concentration
on the curse.
A curse by the likes of you
won't work on Kagome.
That Kikyo thinks quite highly
of Kagome...
You dirty, conniving!
I will do anything in order to possess
the Sacred Jewel whole.
Inuyasha... you will die first!
That's!
That woman!
She harbors demons inside
her body!
Do not draw your sword, Inuyasha!
If you do,
I will curse Kagome to death!
Fight miserably and be killed
by my demons!
It's so maddening!
I must do something about
this curse!
Inuyasha is totally helpless like this!
What can we do?!
Do it! Kill her!
Kagome!
Kill him!
Oh, demons within me!
Iron-reaver Soul-stealer!
...Inuyasha...
Without your sword,
you can do nothing!
Let yourself become
fodder for my demons!
Inuyasha!
Why you!
It's so maddening.
I must do something about this curse!
Who are you?
Huh? What happened?
Why am I back in the present?
Where's Sango?
And Miroku?
Are you... me?
I'm...
As it is, you'll end up killing
Inuyasha again.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Tsubaki's Unrelenting Evil Spell!"
I am... Kagome!