Naraku had dispelled the barrier
around his castle.
In otherwords, he had abandoned
his castle
and hid himself somewhere else.
In the past, no matterwhere
he hid,
I could sense the presence
of his barrier.
But now, as though he
had disappeared from this world,
there is absolutely no sign
of Naraku.
There is something behind this.
I have had my soul collectors
search forhis demonic aura.
But they cannot detect a barrier.
A demonic aura of such size...
how did he hide it?
Say, let's rest somewhere.
Not again?!
We just stopped to rest
awhile ago!
But it's raining.
What're you, made of paper
or somethin'?
You can't call this "rain"!
It's not only that.
Besides! You're riding that
weird contraption.
You've got it easy!
But!
If you ride this for a long time,
yourbutt starts to hurt!
Geez!
Why'd you make me
say it, stupid?!
Huh?
Inuyasha!
What if Kagome's butt
gets deformed!?
S-Shippo...
Oh well...
But understand this.
We start up again as soon as
Kagome's butt returns to normal.
Got it?
Inuyasha!
Sit!
It's turning into a downpour.
Let's look for shelter.
Hey! Don't leave me! Hey!
An evil apparition?
Yes.
Several villagers have already
been killed.
Priestess, please put a
spell on the apparition.
- Please!
The apparition lives in the misty swamp
at the top of the mountain.
Please, Priestess!
I understand.
The misty swamp, you say?
So this is the place...
I see...
There's an uncommon air
about this place.
What?
This isn't the place.
I have been traveling around looking
forareas with a demonic aura...
but I have not come across...
any sign of Naraku.
With Naraku's disappearance,
the numberof demons and
apparitions has grown.
Simply searching forplaces
with a demonic aura
is not the answerto
capturing Naraku.
Hey!
A human?
He has a serious illness.
He does not have long to live.
The villagers gave you a fat reward
forexterminating the demon, huh?
Reward?
No such thing.
Any amount will do.
Leave all yourmoney.
I don't have money.
There's no temple or shrine
hereabouts.
You're traveling without
a farthing?
If you think I lie,
go ahead and search me.
Don't tell me you eat
mist to survive?
Hmph... you could say that.
Never mind then.
Disappearfrom here.
What're you looking at?
Go!
A Sacred Jewel shard?
That shard is what
keeps you alive.
Isn't that so?
I'll be seventy next year.
If the average man lives 50 years,
I've lived too long.
But I can't die yet.
As long as I have this
Sacred Jewel shard...
What do you intend to do
in that condition?
Find my death place...
Drink this.
It'll ease the pain.
Why do you help a
man like me?
You didn't finish
your story.
I went searching for a suitable
place to die.
Suitable place to die?
Yes...
From the days of my youth,
I've committed all
kinds of evil.
Kansuke, the Mad Killer Rasetsu
was quite notorious.
I killed... stole... burned...
I did whatever I felt like doing.
I figured I was gonna end up
dead soon anyway.
So I lived as I pleased.
But I was a stubborn guy.
I got to be old like this...
and I'm still living.
What's the matter?
I hate growing old.
I keep forgetting things
these days.
But I suddenly recall silly things.
When I first saw you,
I was thinking...
that you look like her.
Look like who?
Long ago, I came upon a priestess
who looked exactly like you.
Hername was...
Kikyo, I think.
Pure coincidence.
Naturally. I'm talking
about fifty years ago.
If she were still alive,
she'd be an old woman.
If she lived...
Well... I heard through the grapevine
that she died.
And that the Sacred Jewel was
interred with her.
I don't know how this thing came
to exist in this world.
But I got it at the very last moment.
Were you seeking the Sacred Jewel
fifty years ago?
Yeah... Along with a fellow named
Onigumo.
Onigumo?
He had a burn scarthat
was shaped like a spider.
Now he was a true villain...
I couldn't compare with him.
It'll grant any wish?
Sure.
That's amazing!
And it's called the Shikon Jewel?
In the village overyonder...
A priestess named Kikyo
has possession of it.
Then we'll attack this village
tomorrow.
No, Rasetsu... go alone.
Why?
Kikyo has sharp senses.
If we go in numbers,
she'll escape.
Damn! Then what'll I do?
With your bow and arrow,
you can get herfrom a distance
with one shot.
Isn't that so?
Well...
Won't you try it, Rasetsu?
Whatever I want, huh?
I'll be able to drink all
the sake I want.
And next, I'll conquer
the world!
I found you! Die!
What?!
Who are you?!
Hah! Just a human!
What?!
A human like you... trying
to take Kikyo's life...
You've got some nerve!
Are you after the Sacred Jewel?
Shut up, demon!
Unfortunately, I'm no demon!
Now prepare to die!
Inuyasha!
Damn! You're a lucky dog!
Did something happen?
Huh! It was nothing.
Don't do anything rough
when I'm around.
Where?
Where did they go?!
Damn that Onigumo!
He planned to take
my men from the start!
So this is where...
B-Boss!
You're alive!
Boss!
We didn't mean to
betray you!
Shut up!
If you come back to me,
I'll spare your lives!
However...
Where is he?
Where is that Onigumo?!
Damn him!
I won't let him go!
Didn't that half-demon
kill you?!
Hah! Look at this eye!
How dare you set me up
like that!
Now I'll return the favor!
Rasetsu!
So long, Onigumo!
Burn! Burn!
Burn!
R-Rasetsu!
Stubborn fellow!
Here...
Hey! Throw him over.
Onigumo, this time you
can go get it...
The Sacred Jewel.
Say hello to Kikyo!
So you threw him over?
Yeah. To the infernal abyss.
Infernal abyss... Naraku.
And? What happened afterthat?
That was the end.
I stole this Sacred Jewel shard
recently from a dying demon.
But it won'tgrant my wish.
It just prolongs my life...
and tempts demons to
constantly attack me.
Onigumo continues to
betray me even in death.
Although, this shard helps
to ward off those demons.
What's the matter?
It's come.
Most probably, to get
that shard.
Ademon?
This demonic aura...
It couldn't be... Naraku!
No, it's not.
This is...
Give it to me...
Give me the Sacred Jewel shard!
You...
Just what are you to Naraku?!
Naraku?
That unforgivable Naraku?!
Naraku severed me from him!
Looking like this!
It's a portion of Naraku's body...
which was abandoned?
The Sacred Jewel shard.
If I have the shard,
I'll be able to secure myself
a properbody.
Give it here!
Damn demon!
Die!
A human dares defy me?!
Give me... the bow and arrow!
Hand overthe Sacred Jewel shard!
You want this so much?
That arrow-!
Are you all right?
How pitiful... saved by a woman!
However, you're some woman.
I got it back foryou.
I have no need forthat.
I'll give it to you.
However, I have just
one request.
Request?
I've lived the way I wanted.
However, afterexperiencing
old age and sickness,
I've become afraid of falling
to Hell.
You want to be saved?
I heard thateven villains like
me can find salvation.
And I've traveled in search
of it as a place forme to die.
But I guess I won't find it.
So?
Take this...
Iock of hair and bury it.
Woman...
What's yourname?
It's Kikyo.
That's a bad joke.
The wheel of fortune is
everin motion...so they say.
Put this on so
you won't catch a cold.
You've already caught one!
No, someone's gossiping
about me.
Dummy! Who'd gossip about you?
Good, no fever.
Thank you forbeing concerned.
Huh... you're starting to get warm.
It's okay, don't worry.
Came all this way
with his remains?
Thank you so much
for all yourtrouble.
It was his dying wish.
I've heard about this
place of purification.
I believe the priest's name
was Hakushin.
Yes, yes!
There's a temple started
by this Priest Hakushin.
And if the soul is returned there,
he can cleanse any sin.
Where is this temple?
Mount Hakurei.
Mount Hakurei?
Beyond this forest,
there's a valley
overwhich looms Mount Hakurei.
So that is Mount Hakurei.
I'm getting a strange feeling...
All the fields have been ruined!
It's time to act, Inuyasha!
I'm no Dog God!
What's so hard about
catching monkeys?
Why do I have to take
care of monkeys?!
There! Oh, how cute?!
Say, do you want some treats?
What's this?!
Those baby monkeys have
used some kind of magic!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Three Sprites of the Monkey God!"
Miroku, stop it!
Don't use your Wind Tunnel!