It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
for our dreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
The bird master Princess Abi
betrays Naraku
and thus begins
a three-way battle.
Furthermore, Kikyo has healed
and her reunion with Inuyasha
draws near!
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new dayawaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
I smell the birds!
Are we close to the nest?
Huh?!
They are Kikyo's shikigami!
You two....
Kikyo....
is waiting.
Huh?!
Hey! Wait up!
Those lights...
Kikyo!
Those are....!
Soul Collectors!
Kikyo....
Inuyasha....
Are you all right now?
You must have heard.
Naraku's miasma which
was eating through my body
was purified by Kagome.
Uh-huh....
Kikyo...
still looks like she's in pain.
She's not completely healed yet.
Inuyasha....
You must have noticed it, too.
The barrier around the birds' nest
is gone.
I get it now!
That's why I could smell the birds.
Inuyasha, what is Naraku
trying to do?
He's trying to get to the border
between this world
and the next.
In order to get the Sacred Jewel shard.
That's why he used the birds to
gather human blood.
Which means....
that the road that connects this
world to the afterlife will soon open.
Huh?
Inuyasha did....?
Yes, he went after
two young children.
Two young children...?
Those two!
Inuyasha...
went to Kikyo.
Inuyasha....
you and your friends intend to go to
the border between this world and the next?
'Course!
We're not gonna let someone like Naraku
get his hands on the Sacred Jewel shard!
- Then...
- Huh?!
do not take Kagome.
Huh?
Whaddya mean?
The reason Naraku removed the
barrier around the birds' nest
was to lure you into his trap.
What?!
Naraku's goal is Kagome's eyes.
Her power to see
the Sacred Jewel shards?
Naraku wants to lure you
to the border
between this world and
the afterlife
and then force Kagome
to locate the shard.
Huh....?
Kikyo?
I will go!
Wha...!
Kikyo!
You're not completely healed yet!
It's impossible in your condition.
I can do it.
My spiritual powers have
not weakened.
Don't be ridiculous!
You'll only end up
as Naraku's prey!
You know, right?
Naraku is after your life!
Kikyo....
Back then, I....
When you were attacked
at Mt. Hakurei....
I wasn't able to protect you!
I refuse to give Naraku
a second chance at your life....
I never want to go
through something like that again!
I'll only be a burden....
Are you trying to tell me that?
I'm begging you!
Just wait here!
Kikyo!
The arrows...
Here....
Huh?
Give this to Kagome.
But whether she can use it
depends on her.
There's something weird
about the sky.
Yes. Look closely.
Those are....
Naraku's demons.
They seem to be
headed somewhere.
Now where did Inuyasha go
at a time like this?
On top of which, it's morning
and he's still not back.
Say, the shikigami that
Inuyasha went after....
I know. Most likely,
they were Kikyo's.
Goodness! Of all the times....!
It's a problem.
Yes.
A real problem.
Something scares me
about Kagome....
I have to stay sharp.
After all...
he wanted to see her alone.
But still, what's the matter
with him?!
Sneaking around like that!
Kagome....
W-What?
Inuyasha....
Uh-oh, they're gonna
start fighting!
I hope he doesn't say
something he shouldn't.
I went to see Kikyo.
Huh?
He just came out and said it,
without any hesitation.
Although, we know already.
What a fool!
So?
She told me to give this
to you.
This is Kikyo's....
It's been rubbed with dirt
from Onigumo's cave.
She said it should be
effective against Naraku.
And?
Well....
What Kagome wants to know
is what happened between
you and Kikyo!
Don't try to fool us!
I'm not trying to fool anyone!
All I did was see her!
I just....
wanted to see for myself that
she was okay.
That's all.
Is that really all?
Are you upset, Kagome?
Not really.
I trust you, Inuyasha.
Kagome....
And so....
And so what?
Tell me honestly
what happened.
She doesn't believe me
and she's angry.
I have to stay sharp.
Are they Naraku's demons?
I smell it...
Although it's very faint.
Mixed into the smell of the birds...
Naraku's evil aura.
I'm going.
Yes!
I, Jaken, will follow you any-
Oh, wait! Please wait!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Naraku removed the barrier
around the birds' nest?
Yeah! It reeks with
the smell of the birds!
Naraku wants Kagome's eyes.
Kagome....
Huh?
When we get to the
other side of the world,
you may face a bit of danger.
Why are you telling
me such a thing now?
Without me, you can't locate
the Sacred Jewel shard, right?
The reason Naraku removed the
barrier around the birds' nest
was to lure you into his trap.
Even if it is Naraku's trap,
I won't let it go his way!
Don't worry, Kagome!
I'm right beside you!
I'll protect you without fail!
'Kay. I believe in you.
This is....!
Naraku's smell!
Then he's close by!
I sense a Sacred Jewel shard!
Damn Naraku!
He's in the birds' nest!
Why Naraku....
I never thought you'd
come looking for a fight.
Is it payback time because
I destroyed your castle?
Princess Abi....
Your birds sucked out every drop
of human blood at the castle.
They sure did.
And thanks to them, my mother
has been completely cured.
I see.
Naraku, my mother says
she wants to greet you.
It is finally opening....
The road that leads to the border
between this world and the next.
Naraku....
I don't know what you are scheming,
using us in this way.
However, we no longer
have use for you.
Naraku, it seems you chose
the wrong people to manipulate!
Die!
So easy!
Where are you aiming?
Huh?!
Don't take me lightly, Naraku!
Such attacks won't
work on us!
This will finish you!
Such puny flames won't
bring down my barrier.
I'll devour both you and your barrier!
I'll swallow you in one gulp!
Naraku....
is that the extent
of your strength?
What?!
Naraku's already at the nest?
I'm sure of it!
It's his scent!
Naraku removed the barrier
around the nest,
and didn't send Kagura or Hakudoshi,
but went himself!
Something is....
No, the path that leads to the border
between this world and the next
is about to open!
That's what one would conclude.
Who cares what Naraku
is scheming?!
If we defeat him, it's all over!
Master Inuyasha!
Old Myoga!
Inuyasha, is it true that
Naraku is at Princess Abi's nest?
There's no mistake!
This is not good.
Tekkei will be at the nest.
Who the hell is that?
Myoga, who is Tekkei?
Tekkei belongs to a group
of birds which live in hell.
More precisely, she's a demon
connected to the other world.
That's perfect!
But Tekkei is brutal, so
you must be extremely careful.
Remember, you have been warned.
And with that....
Hold it!
So tell me, how do I
get to the other side?
Huh?!
Inuyasha, look!
What is that huge bird?!
Is that....
Tekkei?!
Inuyasha, have you all
come to die, too?
Princess Abi....
What happened to Naraku?!
Naraku's already dead!
What?!
Dead? Not that Naraku?!
Yes, that Naraku!
He's in my belly.
S-So you ate him?
He's probably hard to digest....
I can't believe that Naraku
would be beaten so easily.
Now then, stay still and
be eaten by me!
You've gotta be kidding!
Go!
Hiraikotsu!
As long as there aren't
any saimyosho,
I can use my Wind Tunnel freely!
No way!
Wind Scar!
That's useless!
Wha...!
Die, Inuyasha!
A half-demon thinks he can
defy me and my daughter?!
Huh?!
W-What is this....?!
Huh?
M-Mother!
Y-You!
Naraku!
You're late, Inuyasha.
Naraku, how dare you!
Princess Abi, well done.
I'll never forgive you!
What the...!
The trident!
Have you forgotten?
That trident was a part
of my body.
You have worked hard for me.
Damn you!
This is your reward. You shall not
suffer when I kill you.
Naraku!
He takes every advantage
of them, then....
Dammit!
This is nothing new,
but your methods are disgusting!
Well, weren't you planning
to defeat Princess Abi, too?
You should be grateful.
Thanks to me, you all are....
now able to go to the border
between this world and the next.
We chase after Naraku and cross
a river of blood
and find ourselves at the border
between this world and the afterlife.
But suddenly, we're attacked
by a spear of light!
Dammit! The spear came
from my old man's grave!
Grave robbers who seek
the Sacred Jewel shard!
This eloquent voice....
could it be Hosenki?
The shard chose to come
with me!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Demon Protector of
the Sacred Jewel Shard!"
Whoever comes, I will not hand it over!