At times, he'll use his spiritual
powers to help people.
At others, he'll use his Wind Tunnel
to subjugate demons.
In orderto destroy our
arch-enemy Naraku,
Miroku journeys
togetherwith us.
He seems to love women
and making money,
but at critical times,
he's very dependable.
I shall be off now.
MasterMonk, thank you so
much for everything.
Now we can live in peace.
You saved ourvillage.
No such thing! I only did what
had to be done.
Good-bye.
MasterMonk! Please tell us your
name at least!
My name is Miroku.
Miroku is my name.
Lately, we only sleep
in the open fields.
How I long for a good night's sleep with
a roof over ourheads.
- Look! Avillage!
- Huh?
Really?
I'm so glad!
We'll be able to sleep
indoors tonight!
Perhaps we'll get news
about Naraku.
Well then, let's go!
Yeah!
All nice and clean now.
Huh?! T-That's!
Miroku!
It's Miroku!
Miroku is coming!
He's coming!
Get inside!
- Huh?
- "Miroku is coming"?
You corrupt monk!
How dare you deceive us!
J-Just a minute!
Just what did I do?
Don't act innocent!
No need fortalk!
Get him!
What's going on, Miroku?!
Well, that's a difficult question
to answer.
What'll we do?
There're so many of them.
I agree...
At times like this, before
anyone is injured...
the only thing to do
is run away!
Hold it!
I wonder what that was
all about?
It concerns Miroku, after all.
He probably did some mischief
in the past there.
But they sure were angry.
What did you do, Miroku?
I have no idea.
Sure about that?
Hmm...
Oh well...
No sense thinking about it.
You probably can't remember
all the bad things you've done.
Surrounded by beautiful women
and partying it up...
Now that's a memory
I wouldn't forget.
Listen here!
Will you bear my child?
Yes, yes!
I'll bearyour child,
so drink up, MasterMonk!
Drink it all up, monk.
Okay then... I'll down it all.
How wonderful!
Oww!
Oh! Anothervillage!
Tonight for sure...
I'll get a good night's sleep!
MasterMonk!
- Huh?!
- What now?
Oh dear...
What is going on here?
Where have you been?
You promised I could bear
your child.
What're you saying?
I'm going to bear his child!
Oh, I see... I see.
Well then, let's take turns.
Hey Miroku!
You have some nerve
coming back here, you fake monk!
Don't think you'll get away
scot-free!
Oh dear... This doesn't look
good at all.
Anyway, let's get away
from here, everyone.
W-Why're you looking at me like that?
Why must we run away, too?
I think you should humbly apologize.
Don't be so heartless.
Look, you sowed these seeds
in the first place.
So you'd bettertake
responsibility.
I told you, I!
Hey, Shippo!
You understand, don't you?
Please help me.
Huh? I'm just a kid. I don't understand
this grown-up stuff.
Forgive me, Miroku!
Capture him!
Yeah!
Please hearme out!
I have to keep it together.
Women are frightening creatures.
Yeah.
Did you say something?
- No, nothing.
So just what did Miroku do
in this village?
You'd have to hearit to believe it.
Yeah...
And so, this person
built a fine storehouse.
However, he had so many worries...
Would robbers break in? Would
a fire break out?
And thus, this sutra charm.
Wards off evil spirits,
promotes good health,
protects the home,
ensures safe birth.
This sutra charm will take care
of every need and concern.
Furthermore!
For a limited time only,
I'll give you two
forthe price of one!
I'm a little suspicious
about this charm.
Usually, a safe-delivery charm
is for childbirth only.
What are you saying?
That's what makes this charm
so wonderful!
That anyone would complain
about its multiple benefits!
What if an evil spirit has
a safe delivery?
Can't have it get healthy.
This despicable monk tricked us
into buying worthless charms
at exorbitant prices!
So you ended up buying them?
And there's more!
Uh... Monk...
What is it?
Won't you stop eating and
begin the exorcism?
Oh... That's right.
Evil spirit begone!
Huh?
Okay, done.
T- That's all?
At my house, he made us feel beholden
with his fake exorcism,
then ate and slept like there
was no tomorrow!
Not only that!
There's more?
Every time he came to the village,
he flirted with the girls!
MasterMonk!
- How nice! How nice!
- This way! This way!
Hurry, come this way!
Is he really a high-ranking monk?
Thanks to him,
all the girls are... Look foryourself!
Oh Miroku... Even under arrest,
you're so divine!
Hurry and release Miroku!
Oh well... It's no different from
how Miroku always acts.
But he's neverbeen
this popular.
You're wrong about that, Sango.
Wrong about what?
Well, you're wrong about
me not being so popular.
But it's even more wrong
that I'm tied up.
Whaddya mean?
Well... because...
This is the first time
I've been to this village.
Stop your lying!
How can you look so smug
and lie before all these witnesses?!
But it's the truth, so I can't help it.
Yesterday and now today...
all lies!
How can you tell such bold-faced lies?
Huh?
Let's throw him in the river!
Just a minute!
What's the matter?
He just said,
"yesterday and now today."
What about it?
Yesterday and today... Miroku has
been with us all along.
Huh? Oh yeah!
Then...
You finally understand?
Then just who was
this other Miroku?
Oh, so you are the famous
MasterMiroku.
Yes... Well...
So, MasterMiroku...
What are you doing in
a village like ours?
Well...
I was passing nearthis village
during my journey
and I felt a very
suspicious aura.
Ohh!
So you did, after all?
Huh?
You are amazing, Miroku.
That you would sense the presence
of the demon from the outskirts.
Then we must ask you to
exterminate the demon immediately.
Huh? It looked for a second that
you grew bigger.
Uh... err... it must be
yourimagination.
Afake?!
Yes.
Someone is using my identity and
is up to no good in this region.
Why must you look at me
like that?!
Think about it...
That's the only explanation!
- But...
- I'll say!
What good does it do
to impersonate you?
I'd pick someone else to
impersonate.
That's why I'm suggesting
that we check this out!
What are you all babbling about?!
Throw him in the river!
J-Just a minute!
We understand how you feel,
but this man denies it.
Hey, hey!
You can throw him in the river
afterwe learn the truth.
Well whatever! Just untie me!
Don't try to talk your way
outta this!
I'm not!
If you're someone else,
show us proof!
Proof?
Geez! Will you cut
all this racket?!
Hey you!
If you insist that Miroku
is guilty...
then YOU show us proof!
W-Why's he so rough?
I knew you'd say that!
Then we'll show you.
Here's...
The proof!
Huh?!
What's the matter, Miroku?
Has he finally lost it?
I see. So that's what it is.
Huh?
I have unraveled the mystery.
But... in that position...
He doesn't look too convincing.
That's why I keep asking you...
to untie me!
Let's hurry!
The impostor is heading
forthe next village!
And?
Just who is this impostor, Miroku?
You'll see when we get there.
He knows me well
and can imitate me.
That leaf gave him away.
Now then, MasterMiroku.
Oh yes...
There's a shrine deep
in this cave.
A raccoon dog demon now
haunts the interior of the shrine.
Oh well... A raccoon dog should
listen to reason.
It'd be okay if it kept to
feeding on mountain prey.
But now it attacks our
livestock and fields.
With the illustrious Miroku here,
we're not too worried.
But please do be careful.
Yes, just leave it to me.
Hey, raccoon dog!
If you're here, show yourself!
Huh?!
That must be the shrine.
What do you want?!
No need to worry.
It's just a raccoon dog, too.
Are you the demon?!
What does a mortal want with me?
So you ARE a raccoon dog.
I'm a weasel!
Huh? You look like a raccoon dog to me.
We're totally different!
Although, I love eating raccoon dogs.
Huh?
Are you really human?
Uhh!
You smell like a vermin.
Oh no...
What are you saying?!
My name is Miroku!
And if I do say so myself,
I am a famous monk!
Miroku?
The one that uses the Wind Tunnel?!
Precisely!
If you apologize now,
I shall forgive you!
This is an opportune time!
I shall devour you and become
the most powerful demon in the world!
No-o!
Huh? Why's Miroku here?!
Miroku is supposed
to be in the cave...
- Let's hurry!
- Yeah!
What is this?!
So you ARE a raccoon dog!
I'll turn you into stew!
S-Stay away!
Come any closer, and I'll
uncovermy Wind Tunnel!
Y-You're bluffing!
Shall I show you then?
Well... But you're...
...back to being... a raccoon dog.
Huh?!
No-o-o-o-!
Stupid raccoon dog.
Say your prayers!
Please forgive me!
I promise to stop this!
Never forget those words.
Huh?
Who's there?!
MasterMiroku!
It's been a long time, Hachi.
Hah! You're the raccoon dog's partner?
Hey you... raccoon dog!
I said I'm a weasel!
I don't care about that.
Justgo back quietly
to yourmountain.
I hate violence.
So let's be civil about this.
Hah! You're all raccoon dogs!
Don't talk big!
I'll make stew outta all of you!
I guess he doesn't understand reason.
Wind Tunnel!
What?!
Damn it! He's the REAL Miroku,
after all!
I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
Please forgive me!
- Please, oh please, stop!
- As long as you understand.
What? It's all over?
That was quick.
Must be a weak raccoon dog.
Not a raccoon dog, a weasel.
Hey raccoon dog!
I said I'm a weasel!
Who cares about that!
In any case, don't try anything
bad from now on.
Yesss!
As long as you understand.
Now go back to your mountain.
Yes! I will!
Excuse me!
Now then!
I want a full explanation.
Please forgive me!
Why did you impersonate
Miroku?
ljust decided on the
spur of the moment...
I was so hungry,
I couldn't bearit.
And so...
I impersonated Miroku
just for one time.
And it went well?
Oh yes! It went
unbelievably well.
And you started liking it?
Just as you say...
Listen here, Hachi.
Yes?
If you've learned yourlesson,
don't try anything foolish
like this ever again.
Yes!
The trouble I went through
all because of you!
Yes...
But it's strange.
Huh?
I really did impersonate you,
but I neverdid anything
to disparage you.
How disrespectful of you!
Is that how you see me?!
You say that...
but I really tried my utmost
to pretend to be you.
Now that you mention it...
How you acted wasn't any different
from how Miroku would act.
How rude of you!
The only thing different is that
Hachiemon was more
the lady's man.
Hey, Hachi!
Y-Yes?
Sorry, but can you teach me?
Teach you what?
The secret to being popular
with the girls... What else?!
Well sir... Indifference ensures success.
Indifference?
Miroku! What are you two
whispering about?
Err... nothing.
You probably have
lecherous ideas again.
What are you saying?
Does my face look like I have
such thoughts?
Yes.
W-What?!
Huh?!
- Let's go!
- Yes!
Hey! Wait up!
Miroku!
He's the real Miroku.
You can talk to him!
What're you saying?!
He's the real one!
Stop fooling around,
you trickstermonk!
You womanizer!
You lecher!
You crook! You fool!
Oh dear...
Just what are you up to?!
Indifference, sir!
That's impossible for me!
Why did that demon have
a fake Sacred Jewel?
Someone gave it to him.
- Who?
- Ademon.
You picking a fight?!
Calm down, Inuyasha!
Demons are trying to create
a real Sacred Jewel.
Izumo the scholar
was attacked.
And people are being kidnapped
in nearby villages.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Sacred Jewel Maker, Part l"
Can you really make another
Sacred Jewel?