Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gatherall the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
We're on a journey in search of
Naraku who has disappeared.
Together, we've managed to
overcome many hardships,
but a dark shadow will cast over
the hearts of my friends.
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Well, Inuyasha?
Have you found the way out?
Shaddup! I'm trying to concentrate!
You've been at it since morning
and it's getting dark.
Why're you shaking?
Miroku, this forest must be...
Yes, there's no doubt about it.
This is a demon's nest.
Shucks! Did it again!
Damn! Get rid of a useless
thing like that!
No way! My motherbought it forme.
It's coming... something evil.
At last! The master of this forest
makes his appearance.
Ademon or an apparition?
If I can see it,
I can get rid of it!
Quit stalling and show yourself!
Welcome to my Forest of Sorrow.
T-That's!
Kagome, that demon is!
Yes, it's Gatenmaru.
Oh? You know Gatenmaru?
He's the bane of my tribe.
I hearhe banded togetherwith
lowly humans,
then got himself killed
by a half-demon.
Now that's a sharp sword.
That half-demon... was me.
That was such a stupid ending
to the fight.
Why?
The smell of demon blood?
You pesky moth!
If you wanna avenge Gatenmaru's death,
I'll gladly take you on!
Avenge?
Whateverfor?
He deserved to die!
I could care less about him.
Whatever!
I hate moth demons like you
and him!
Inuyasha!
W-What?!
What is this?!
I was careless!
It won't come off!
It's entering my body!
My power...
...is being sucked out!
Damn!
Kagome!
Tetsusaiga isn't working!
It's so uncouth to suck out
human blood...
These days, my tribe likes
to devour
the heart and soul, shaking
in fear and despair.
Dammit!
Miroku!
Hey! Don't be so weak!
Hey Miroku!
Sango!
Hang in there!
Whateveryou shout,
they cannot hear anymore.
Shippo!
Hey! Answerme!
By morning, a part of me shall
take hold of theirhearts and bodies.
Wind Scar!
Shall I test it?
It's useless!
The only way to break this curse
is to defeat him!
Now then...
I shall create nightmares foryou...
And you shall pour out your
ultimate fear and despairforme!
Hey! K-Kirara!
Are you all right, Kohaku?
If Kirara can handle him like that,
maybe it's too early
forhim to face battle.
No such thing, Father.
Kohaku is very skilled
with his sickle and chain.
If you say so...
He'll be fine!
And if anything should happen,
I'll be with him.
Kohaku!
K-Kohaku!
S-Sister!
I'm scared...
It's okay.
I'm with you!
Kohaku...
How fun! How fun!
Well, Miroku?
Don't you forget all your cares
when you're here?
MasterMushin, why isn't
my fatherhere?
MasterMushin?
Yourfatherdid not want you to
see him part from this life.
Part from this life?
By now...
Father!
F-Father...
Pa!
Look, Pa!
See?
So many acorns.
Pa!
What's the matter, Sota?
Buyo went in here.
This place is creepy.
It's too late to say that.
Sis!
This miasma...
No! No way!
Sota, run! Hurry!
Sota! Snap out of it!
What's the matter, Kagome?
What's all the fuss?
Don't come!
Suffer!
Beyond that suffering awaits
unfathomable despair.
I shall get an ample taste of
yourfear and hopelessness.
What'd you do to those guys?!
Just letting them dream.
Dream?!
Humans and demons alike...
all have fears that they suppress
deep down in theirhearts
which dreams can release.
We feed on that.
You bastard!
Release Kagome and the others now!
Ahalf-demon!
I can see yourfear
so clearly.
What?!
Without your comrades,
you're so lonely,
you can't bearit.
Shaddup!
I can fight alone!
However...
ljust don't like you making
my friends yourfodder!
All talk.
The unbearable fear of
being alone...
I shall devourit!
Shaddup! Take this!
Wind Scar!
He's the one who's all talk.
Think you won?
What?!
Even if you destroy me,
I'll devourtheir souls
and with theirbodies...
I shall grow another self.
And that will spell YOURend!
Being devoured by your
formerfriends...
that is the fate that awaits you.
And at that moment,
you will be truly released
from the fear of loneliness.
The cocoon won't disappear...
What can I do?!
Just what?!
Dammit!
Why you...!
Kagome!
Shippo!
Miroku! Sango!
Kohaku!
Sis! Rejoice forme!
I did it!
I exterminated demons
all by myself!
Exterminated demons?
You!
Fatherwill praise me, won't he?
Sister!
Kohaku!
It's yourfault, Sis.
You didn't praise me.
MasterMushin!
Let me go!
Please let me go!
Miroku!
Your Wind Tunnel has
reached its limit.
Don'tgo anywhere!
I'll find Naraku!
One more step...
Miroku, what's the matter?
Don't come near!
Miroku?
Miroku!
Don't come!
l-Impossible!
It's notexposed!
Monk... did you want so much
to be saved?
At the expense of
yourfriends' lives?
It's all yourdoing!
Cursing my grandfather
with the Wind Tunnel...
Help!
Oh... I've been dreaming.
What's the matter, Kagome?
It's unlike you to be dozing off.
You were sleeping so soundly.
You've been cramming too hard.
No such thing...
This can't be!
Everyone, run!
It's dangerous to stay here!
Damn!
Blades of Blood!
Kagome!
Is that all there is
to yourpowers?!
Was it so weak that a mere dream
could devourit?!
I misjudged you!
If you're gonna give up
so easily,
I'll defeat Naraku alone!
Don't come crying later!
Wake up!
Don't let a moth demon
eat yourheart!
Kagome!
You're not a weak girl
like that!
Tell me...
To Sit!
Kohaku!
Forgive me!
I must kill you,
oryou can't return to me.
Why?
Why is that, Sis?
I'll kill you, then kill myself.
This is the only way to get
you back from Naraku!
I'm sorry, Kohaku!
Don't kill Kohaku.
We mustget him back alive!
But... with me around...
It only causes everyone trouble.
Quit rambling!
It's betterto stay together!
You're good at fighting.
Inuyasha!
What're you afraid of!?
If you expose that hand once more,
I'll cut it off!
Don't you want to defeat Naraku
and break the curse of the Wind Tunnel?!
This is no place to be
wasting time!
You're absolutely right, Inuyasha.
Hang in there, Shippo!
Fox fire!
All right!
Hey Shippo, you've been
trying hard.
Yeah!
Kagome!
Inuyasha!
You smell nice.
What a thing to say
at a time like this...
Run, Inuyasha!
You can't win in your
human form.
Fool!
As if I'd go without you!
I'll...
...I'll protect you!
That's right.
I have Inuyasha.
As long as I'm with Inuyasha...
As long as I'm with everyone...
I can overcome any adversity!
Guys!
Atta way, everyone!
That's what MYfriends
are made of!
Inuyasha!
Hey!
We're leaving this forest now!
Overthere!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
The forest disappeared.
So it was all an illusion
created by Garamaru.
We wasted so much time
because of him.
I'll say!
Uh-huh...
But y'know...
Without me around,
you guys are nothing!
What? Any complaints.
Well, that's exactly true.
At least today,
we'll let itgo.
What a way to put it!
Nevermind, Inuyasha.
Everyone acknowledges what you did.
No, I DO mind!
If you really believe I saved you,
at least say, "thank you."
Well then, Kagome, as ourrepresentative,
please say a word.
All right.
What?!
Tell me... to SIT!
Inuyasha...
Th-ank you!
Whoa... it wasn't "sit."
Well now, shall we proceed?
Yes.
I'm hungry.
Hey! Hey Kagome!
What'd you just say?
Say it once more!
Not anymore!
C'mon! Say it!
Such a bother!
What?! Kagome!
Say it!
Sit!
Afterlosing my father, I had
continued my training.
Powdery snow fell steadily
and my body sank deeperand deeper
into the ground.
But there was someone who saved me.
That was his encounterwith
Koyuki seven years ago?
She resembles that
woman of my memories.
Did yourtears freeze into snow?
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Snow from Seven Years Past"
Wait, she's not human!