Now then...
let's check out the
state of the world...
Hmm...
What's this?
Foot-and-mouth disease
is an infantile illness?
Can't use this.
Hmm...
Have I used up all the illnesses
as excuses...
when Kagome is in
the other time?
Hello Gramps!
Mommy, are you all right?
This year's colds are nasty.
I should've worn
a mask today.
Huh? That's it!
'Bye Gramps!
Okay... watch out for cars.
Huh?! Hey Kagome!
Where are you off to?!
School... where else?
Dang it! I thought up
a good illness!
Impertinent child!
What is Grandpa talking about?
Oh no! I forgot my math book!
What're you doing, Kagome?
Hurry and borrow a book from
the class next door.
I forgot my language, science
and history books too!
You finally come to class
and you're a mess!
My writing instruments
are in the Feudal Era!
Is Higurashi here?
Kagome, they're things
you forgot!
Your younger brother
just dropped them off.
He said to pardon you for
being so hopeless.
Your younger brother
is such a capable kid!
It's been quite some time since...
I, an average middle-school student,
began...
going to the Feudal Era.
In the Feudal Era...
I have Inuyasha, Miroku
and old Kaede to help me.
But here, with high school
entrance exams looming...
I have to manage on my own.
Well...not quite.
I've been getting help
in this world, too.
Eri, thanks for the notes.
They were a big help!
Your brother Sota
asked me to keep notes.
He said you tend to fall
behind in math.
Huh? Sota said that?
My sister forgot this.
May I ask you to
give this to her?
What?! There's a test
coming up?
Oh no! I'd better tell Sis!
Thank you! Please keep
me informed!
That Sota!
Good Sota!
I see.
Inuyasha killed them with
one swing of Tetsusaiga?
Rather than sending
100 demons...
send one he cannot kill.
Well, kill or miss...
I intend to use you.
Are you agreeable?
Are you able to move
your body now?
Yes, Master Naraku.
Can you kill them?
Inuyasha, Miroku...
and Sango.
Yes, Master Naraku.
Ready!
Huh? Damn!
How do I extract
Tetsusaiga's ultimate power?
Don't be disheartened.
Even if it was sheer luck,
you saved us all.
Next time, just get lucky again.
Tetsusaiga!
Hey Inuyasha!
Do you want to kill me?!
Is it luck, after all?
Are you listening to me?
Don't get lucky now!
Shut up!
And quit calling it luck!
Naraku took the offensive.
If he's keeping a watch on us
from somewhere...
it'll be hard to make a move.
It'll save us time looking for him.
That bastard, let him come
and attack anytime, anywhere!
Miroku, what're you laughing about?!
Sorry...
I won't be able to use
my Wind Tunnel for a while.
Hearing you talk with such
confidence is gratifying.
Well, sit back and relax.
I'll slice Naraku in two
with Tetsusaiga.
I don't care if it's
luck or whatever.
If I have Tetsusaiga's
true power, I can beat Naraku.
I swear to master this sword...
the Tetsusaiga.
Well Shippo?
They're in deep conversation.
Really?
Let's go and bathe
in the hot springs now.
I understand about the monk...
but will Inuyasha take a peek, too?
No way! He's so standoffish!
Do you want him to look?
Those scars...
Yeah... they didn't heal completely.
Were they from the demons?
No...
I got these scars...
from my dead younger brother.
If only I had realized it sooner,
I could have prevented it all.
Kohaku was a weak,
gentle boy.
Perhaps, he wasn't suited
to be a slayer.
I'm sorry to make you
remember such sad memories.
It's all right.
Before he died, Kohaku had
reverted to his old self.
I'm sad, but that has somewhat
eased the pain.
I'm a Demon Slayer.
It can't be helped.
Everyone else has a reason
for being here, right?
Kagome, why are you gathering
Sacred Jewel fragments?
Huh?
Err... well, I feel bad about
my involvement...
You broke the Jewel?!
I'm sorry.
I really did something horrible.
But you were trying to take it
back from a demon...
so it couldn't be helped.
But you're the reincarnation
of a priestess? Amazing!
I don't even understand
that part.
I can see the fragments
of the Sacred Jewel.
So we've joined forces to
collect the fragments.
With Naraku's appearance,
things have gotten more complicated.
In order to break the curse
of the Sacred Jewel...
we must first destroy Naraku.
Do you understand that...
you over there?!
- Huh?!
- A monkey?
Hey! What's the ruckus?!
For once, you were really
talking seriously.
Why'd they have to
suspect me, too?!
So what? That was a
wonderful sight we just saw.
Everyone has been drawn into
the curse of the Sacred Jewel...
but I feel most sorry for Sango...
who watched as her father and
younger brother were killed.
Now then, time to go.
Kagome, what did you bring?!
It's much heavier than before!
Uh-huh... I have a test next week...
so I brought as many
books as I could carry.
You have it rough, huh?
Miroku says you should just
"flunk" or something like that.
Not Miroku, too?!
My brother Sota, who's only
in grade school, says...
"If you repeat grades six times...
I'll be in the same grade as you
and I'll help you study."
What a cocky young brother,
don't you think?
Oh...
He acts tough and he's cocky.
Yet he cries easily and
gets Ionely.
Isn't he a good boy,
this brother of yours?
Uh-huh...
Hey, someone's coming.
Huh?
Inuyasha! Hurry!
He's not breathing.
Seems like an ordinary villager.
These scars...aren't from
a sword.
He's not the only one
who was killed.
Huh?
The wind is carrying
the smell of blood.
Not just a few...
Many have been killed.
The entire village?
Hey! Anyone here?!
We must find out what happened.
Let's split up and search.
Good idea.
Hold it!
Don't move!
Traps are everywhere!
If you make a move,
your legs may be blown off!
What?!
Even underground?!
Then even around
the bodies?
Probably.
What a cruel thing to do?!
Someone tries to help,
and they're also blown up.
So heartless!
Well, let's find out what
this guy is planning?!
Inuyasha! It's dangerous to move!
As if I know how...
to stay still!
Is he the one?!
A mere child... killed all
the villagers?!
Impossible!
That chain... and on his body...
there's blood splattered all over!
He's a vicious kid!
Why'd you do this?!
What're you up to?!
Kohaku!
That attire...
is the same as Sango's...
a slayer's.
Kirara is... But how... ?!
Kohaku... are you?!
Sango...what did you just say?!
Halt!
Damn!
Kirara!
W-what?!
A barrier!
Kohaku...
I thought you were dead!
Damn! We're here!
Hurry and get off!
The two of them went through
this barrier?
Yeah...
Kagome, what you said earlier...
is that really true?
No mistake about it.
Sango called him Kohaku.
Sango told me that her
younger brother...
was killed in that castle
occupied by Naraku.
And he had a Sacred Jewel
fragment imbedded in his back.
We've heard that one before.
It's Naraku's same old trick...
forcing Sango to fight when
she was in total anguish.
Then Naraku is manipulating
Kohaku this time?
Sango is probably aware of it.
The barrier allowed only Sango
to go through.
I have bad feelings about this.
Let me see your face.
Kohaku...
You are alive! Kohaku!
Are you happy to see
your brother alive?
It's been quite some time, Sango.
Naraku!
Aren't you going to thank me?
What?!
I salvaged your brother's life.
When he was killed by
those arrows at the castle...
Kohaku's life should've ended.
But I saved him.
You should know this well...
the power of a Sacred Jewel fragment.
When you had it inside you...
you fought Inuyasha
better than evenly matched.
Shut up!
So it is now with Kohaku.
He is able to stand before you
because of the Sacred Jewel.
If it is extracted, he will die.
Understand, Sango?
Kohaku's life is in your hands.
Bring me the Tetsusaiga,
Inuyasha's sword.
Then I shall let Kohaku
have eternal life.
Don't underestimate me!
Kohaku, Why?!
Why protect Naraku?!
I've made him forget...
I've erased all memories of
you and of himself.
A fighting machine has no need
of feelings.
He slaughtered an entire village.
Kohaku has become
a fine slayer.
Why you!
Miasma!
You will bring me the Tetsusaiga.
I will be waiting... Sango.
Sango!
That boy... your brother...
He wasn't Kohaku!
Sango...
Well, the main thing is that
you returned unharmed.
Sango... The one who laid
this trap...
the one behind the barrier...
was it Naraku?
Uh-huh.
Then you must be exhausted.
Let us return to the village
and get some rest.
Monk...
Please...
hold a service for the villagers.
This is the last.
Amazing Kirara...
her experience in a village
of slayers paid off.
She sniffed out all the traps.
We'll have Sango destroy
all of these later.
Now then, let's go tell everyone
about Kirara's good work.
Huh?! Kirara... Where are you?
Kirara!
What do you think, Miroku?
About what?
She said she met Naraku.
I wonder what happened to Sango
behind the barrier.
Probably that Naraku is the one
manipulating her brother, Kohaku.
He tried to get Sango
to fight Kohaku!
Naraku is unforgivable!
Sango can't slay her own brother.
Let's leave her alone for a while.
Until she's ready to talk
to us about it.
How can you be so nonchalant?!
He may be Naraku's puppet with
a Sacred Jewel fragment...
Kohaku's the one who slaughtered
this entire village!
If Sango can't kill him,
I'll do it in one swing!
Hey Sango!
Any complaints?!
Inuyasha! You are sooo insensitive!
Sango, wait!
But, pratically speaking,
what will we do?
Kill him?
Of course!
No matter what?
Think about it!
Naraku sent Sango's brother...
believing that we wouldn't be able
to kill him.
No way will I fall for that!
Don't try too hard.
Shaddup, will ya!? Damn!
I hate my role...
but I'll have to do it.
Though I feel sorry for Sango...
I did it!
Weakling! Look at you!
Stop it! You!
How's the wound?
Sister!
Rough, huh?
Can't be helped.
I have such a long way to go.
But Father said that you're
getting better and better.
Really?
Really.
It's the first time
Father praised me!
Feels kinda awkward.
I made him forget...
I erased all his memories.
Kohaku didn't react at all
when he saw me.
Has he truly forgotten
all about me?
No...
He doesn't even know that
Naraku is our sworn enemy...
and it vexes me that Naraku
manipulates Kohaku!
I want to take Kohaku back...
away from Naraku's evil grip!
Bring me Tetsusaiga,
Inuyasha's sword.
Then I will give Kohaku
eternal life.
Steal Tetsusaiga...
In order to save Kohaku!
Steal Inuyasha's sword in
exchange for her brother's life?!
That Naraku is so rotten!
Kohaku is being
thoroughly manipulated!
But we can't fight and
risk killing him!
We have no choice but to attack
the castle shrouded in miasma...
and destroy Naraku once
and for all!
Even I... even I'm hopping mad!
Next on Inuyasha...
"Tetsusaiga is Stolen!
Showdown at Naraku's Castle!"
Don't miss it!