Wh... - why!
Lord Sesshomaru!
- Is it here?
- Yes.
The stake pointed in this direction,
then lodged itself by this tomb.
We'll check it immediately.
Why would beasts respect
a tomb?
Lord Sesshomaru!
This is it!
There's no mistake!
The fang...
I search for the fang.
Once I possess it, I will be able
to transform myself...
into an even greater power!
It seems my power is still
insufficient, I'm still too naive.
Am I unsure of myself?
No... I just don't know
my limits.
I presume too much
about my power...
The fang...
I want the fang...
Jaken... the Human Head Staff.
Yes, my lord.
The female's face is screaming.
Does that mean this is not
the tomb you seek?
Lord Sesshomaru, please wait!
Dangerous, so dangerous!
Just who is he anyway?!
Hurry!
I must report this without delay!
To Master Inuyasha!
We'll meet up with the main
troops tomorrow.
Men! Eat boar's meat tonight
and energize yourselves!
Yo!
Such a man of strength and power
is our lord and master!
What an amazing man!
I'll take an enemy general's head!
Who goes there?!
- What's the matter?
- My Lord!
Why you... who are you?!
A boat...
A boat?
Who has the luxury to lend you a boat
in the middle of war!?
I want a boat.
What?!
Why you!
Lord Sesshomaru!
I can't find any boats
in this area!
Huh? Oh! So many boats!
Leave it to Lord Sesshomaru!
Wh... - what?
You're not mortal, are you?
Beast! We'll kill you!
Surround him!
Jaken... I'll let you deal with them.
Yes, my lord.
Feel the full power of
my Human Head Staff!
Hah! Not a piece left of them! Fools!
If they hadn't resisted us,
they would still be alive.
Wherever Lord Sesshomaru goes...
the powerholds of the samurai
go astray.
It's over and done with, my lord.
Huh? Err...
Please wait, my lord!
This is?!
The staff changed directions?
Is the location of the fang moving?
Lord Sesshomaru...
What is it?
The location of the tomb.
I believe that
Inuyasha knows where it is.
Inuyasha?
It's a name I'd rather
not remember...
Please forgive me!
Besides, he is not alive.
I heard that a spell was cast
upon him fifty years ago.
Yes... but I have heard that the spell
was undone only recently.
Also, my staff has been pointing
in a different direction.
I believe this has something to do
with Inuyasha's awakening.
By the way, my lord...
Won't you release the staff?
I can't... breathe!
Huh... I'm exhausted.
How could an average
middle-school girl like me...
get hurled into the
Warring States period?
My family are the protectors of
an ancient shrine...
We have a sacred thousand-year-old
tree on the premises...
a mysterious, secret well...
I guess thinking back...
it was a pretty strange shrine.
The time warp to the Warring States
period is connected to the secret well.
And now all kinds of phantoms are
after the Sacred Jewel...
which was hidden inside my body.
The old priestess, Kaede, and the
rest of the villagers are very kind...
so I've been able to
manage somehow.
But it's too frightening to think...
about all the demons that may come
in pursuit of the Sacred Jewel.
Let's go, Kagome.
What?
It's the first time you
said my name.
So what?
Maybe you've decided to be
a bit nicer to me?
Hey! Don't get cheeky!
Who'd be chums with
a girl like you?!
What?! And who was it
that just saved you?
Look... if it hurts, just
speak up and say so!
Shut up!
Although he's rough and rude
and mean...
in order to find the fragments
of the Sacred Jewel...
I hope Inuyasha and I
can get along.
I've been walking continuously
for three days.
Perhaps I will rest a bit.
Huh? What's that sound?
What was that?
My imagination, maybe?
Tending to my wound?
Forget it!
No! It's a serious wound.
Get down.
Nope!
Come down, I said!
Hah!
Sit!
Why you... What're you doing?!
Tending to your wound!
What else?
You've just been through
the mill and...
you're cut up, beat up
and mangled up!
Get one thing clear...
I was the winner!
Don't you forget that!
Priestess Kaede, how is your injury?
It's much better now.
I hope the fragments of
the Sacred Jewel can be found soon!
You children need not worry
your heads about it.
But if Inuyasha and Kagome could
get along for a while longer...
that would be a big help.
Looks like they're getting
along fine.
Just undress!
Cut it out!
Undress!
Do not look!
Huh?!
It seems as though you're
starting to get along.
Huh?!
You!
Can't you understand that
my body is different?!
Huh?! It's already healed.
That terrible injury is healed...
And not even a scar!
Amazing!
Don't compare me mortals!
I ain't flattered at all
by your amazement!
He's not human, but he's
not a demon.
So what is a half-demon... ?
Oww!
Greetings, Master Inuyasha!
Huh?
Why if it ain't ol' Myoga the Flea!
Flea?
What's up, Myoga?
It has been so long!
So long... Master Inuyasha...
What'd you do?
Shouldn't I have?
Men are trying to violate
my old man's tomb?
I, Myoga, protector of
the tomb...
could bear it no longer
and here I am.
You abandoned the tomb
and ran away?!
But that tomb was just stone.
The urn itself is in
another location.
Then where is it?
Well, I do not know myself.
And you call yourself
a tomb protector?!
Inuyasha, I have heard that
your father...
phantom dog that once ruled
over the western region.
I don't remember much
about 'im.
He was a magnificent and
powerful demon.
And his blood was so flavorful.
Master Inuyasha has inherited
the tasty blood from his father.
Hmmm... and his mother?
His mother was very beautiful.
Inuyasha! Don't be so rough!
My mother died a long time ago!
Why? Did I say something
to anger him?
Hmmm... I do not know.
All I did was ask about
his mother.
Master Inuyasha is
always like that...
when the subject turns
to his mother.
His father was a full-fledged demon.
And Inuyasha is a half-demon.
Half demon...does that mean the
other half is human?
Is that why... ?
You're just half-demon
with half the power.
Pitiful thing.
You wanted this in order to become
a full-fledged demon, huh?
Half of him is mortal.
He's not a whole demon.
That's the cause of
Inuyasha's complex.
So Inuyasha's mother was human?
My mother died a long time ago!
His mother is human.
Is that why he hates her?
I'm off!
Kagome, wait!
What? I must hurry to
the other side!
It's something extra
to carry, but take it.
I already have so much.
Didn't you say your friends
there have gotten injured?
Make sure you sterilize their
wounds and treat them.
All right!
I wonder if Inuyasha really
despises his mother?
Wh-what?!
Get down!
Inuyasha!
Can you feel it? There's something
weird coming.
A noble's palenquin?
There's a lady inside.
Inuyasha!
What's the matter?
M-my mother?
You are... Inuyasha!
Agh!
Mom!
What's happening?
I thought you said your
mother was dead!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha, your mother!
You...
Damn!
Jaken...
Yes, my lord?
We kill him after our business
is done.
Yes, my lord.
You... Sesshomaru!
Admirable... so you remember your
older brother?
You... Sesshomaru!
Admirable... so you remember your
older brother?
Older brother?
Your brother?
A mortal girl?
Wh-What?
Inuyasha...
It suits you to stick to
humans.
Disgusting beasts called humans.
To be a half-demon...
whose mother is a human
is a disgrace to all our kind!
So Inuyasha's mother is
human, after all!
Sesshomaru... you!
Did you come all this way
just to tell me that?
Fool!
I am not so idle as that!
I came to ask you the location
of our father's grave.
Grave? Who knows?!
Visible, but invisible...
The true protector of the grave
cannot see it.
That is the clue to
the gravesite.
I don't know what you're talking about!
Besides, even if I knew, I wouldn't
tell you! That's for sure!
I see... Then it can't be helped.
Your mother will suffer for it.
Inuyasha!
Are you stupid?!
My mother died a long time ago!
As if I'd fall for such a trick!
Trick, huh?
Do you not understand?
Bringing dead spirits from
the netherworld...
is a simple task for someone
as great as Lord Sesshomaru.
He was even so kind as to
give her flesh!
Her own son won't believe
that it's her.
How mortifying it must
be for your mother!
Inuyasha!
It's not some trick... ?!
I am returned from the dead...
Damn!
Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
Are you all right, Mother?!
Kagome! Take my mother
and go!
You will not escape.
You hopeless imbecile!
Mother!
Inuyasha!
What a nuisance.
It's going well, my lord.
Just leave everything
to Jaken!
You made me go along with
this silly scheme...
If it fails...
You will die.
Oh... Please leave it to me.
Where is this?
We are at the border of the
spirit world.
I must now return.
The spirit world?
Yes... You are dead, after all.
Inuyasha... How you have grown.
Of course! I was just a little
kid when you died.
It was a violent age.
And I left you... all alone with
no one to care for you.
Forgive me.
How you must have suffered.
It wasn't your fault.
Inuyasha...
Huh?!
Inuyasha and his mother...
They're okay.
Wh-what... My body...
I can't move!
Huh?! There's no face
in the reflection!
Inuyasha!
My voice... I can't speak!
Mother...
Parting is so sad... Inuyasha.
Yes...
Have you realized it, Inuyasha?
She doesn't have a face!
She's not your mother!
Inuyasha sacrifices himself
to save his mother.
Inuyasha must be
a child of an upper classmen...
if his mother is wearing a ceremonial
robe of a Japanese court lady.
Never would have guessed
with his rough speeches.
Sesshomaru sets a trap using
Inuyasha's feeling toward his mother.
Inuyasha!
She is not your real mother!
Next time, Inuyasha "Tetsusaiga,
the Phantom Sword" See you then.