Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
In the castle where
Naraku's baby sleeps,
Sango reunites with
her younger brother, Kohaku.
Guilt that cannot be erased,
as well as tragic memories and heartache
are about to be reawakened.
The birds are dwindling.
My lady, please bear it
for just a bit longer.
Thank goodness!
My lady, we will be saved, won't we?
Kohaku, it is because
of you that we were saved.
And this child is without
a single scratch.
You're just a kid, but you did
a fine job, Kohaku.
You will be rewarded later!
Huh?
Kohaku, is something wrong?
K-Kohaku!
My lady!
This way!
What's going on?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Kohaku...
take the child.
And kill everyone around you.
Answer! Kohaku!
Why must I kill these people?
Why you...!
Have you gone mad?!
I don't want to.
What is this terrible feeling
I have?
Take the child.
And kill everyone around you.
No... I don't want to.
Why are you doing this?
Why?!
I don't want to.
Kohaku....
I don't want to...
Who.... Who is controlling
your heart?
My heart?
Kohaku!
It's that lady...
They...
weren't killed by the birds.
Kanna? You were in
this castle?
Huh? That's...
That's Hakudoshi's counterpart.
What? You're telling me
to get Kohaku?
Huh?
Kanna's gone.
Half-demon! I'll put an end to you!
Hah! I'm gonna kill you on this spot
and put an end to your evil!
Take this!
Is her barrier just as strong
as Naraku's?!
If even Inuyasha's Tetsusaiga
can't break through it,
it must be.
Well, we have to do something!
Silly girl!
Kagome!
Save me, too!
Stay back!
I can handle her by myself!
The birds are starting to gather!
It must mean that
they've sucked all the blood
from the humans in that castle.
I expected more resistance
from a castle
that is connected
with Naraku.
But it seems it was
just an ordinary human castle.
Ordinary human castle?
But Kohaku is in this castle...
No doubt under Naraku's orders.
I'm withdrawing for now.
Your life has been extended
for a while, half-demon.
What the...!
Quit fooling around!
Shut up! Taking the human blood
back to the nest is more important!
I'm not letting you get away!
Get lost!
Wind....
Scar!
Wha...!
Dammit!
She got away....
Where's Sango?!
Kohaku....
You did it again, didn't you?
Again?
What does she mean?
Kohaku....
Again?
W- What was that just now?
What...
Kohaku....?
Who? Who is she?
Who am I?!
l- I...
Kohaku!
That's right...
I killed my father and
everyone else...
with these hands.
Sister!
Hey!
I remember... everything!
I killed my father and
the rest of the demon slayers...
with my own hands.
And I even hurt Sister.
I'm supposed to have
died on that day.
But he...
Naraku...
Kohaku, you're trembling?
You want to forget
the terrible thing you've done?
Forget then. Forget everything.
And work for me.
Why you...!
Cripes! What do you think
you're doing?!
Do you want to die?
I don't care if I die.
What?
Naraku....!
Even if we both die,
I'll get him!
Kohaku...
- Sango!
W-What happened?!
This is....
It's not the work
of the birds.
Kohaku....
did this.
Sango....
Did Kohaku go away again?
Yes.
But I couldn't go after him.
Sango....
Kohaku...
You were covered in blood...
Even if I did take Kohaku away
from Naraku...
I don't know how to free his heart
from Naraku's grasp...
I could...
I could... with my very own hands...
kill Kohaku...
Huh?
The birds are gone!
Are we saved?
There are survivors!
Kohaku!
- Kohaku, where are you?!
- Hey!
You know Kohaku?
Oh yes.... He worked with us.
We were saved by Kohaku.
Huh?
He protected us and
fought off the demon-birds.
He looked like such an innocent.
Thanks to him, we're alive.
Kohaku....
You know Kohaku?
What happened to Kohaku?
Is he okay?
Huh?
Kohaku is a kind boy.
He really isn't one who
could do something like that....
You....?
It's okay.
Kohaku is alive.
Sango, I know it's difficult,
but can you describe
exactly what you saw?
Since Kohaku was there,
Naraku must be connected
in some way to that castle.
Yes....
When I rushed to him,
Kohaku was about to kill
a woman holding a baby.
A baby?
Huh?!
That baby....
Iooked like Naraku's child.
What?!
That's right! That baby looked
just like Naraku's infant!
So that's the connection
between Naraku and the castle.
But why?
What were you doing
at that castle?
Why was that baby
So was Naraku hiding his baby
at a human castle?
Whatever the case,
one thing is certain.
That baby is very special
to Naraku.
Kohaku, weren't you given
even a clue
about who that baby is?
No....
I see....
Who is that?
Huh? Don't you know anything?
That's Hakudoshi.
The counterpart of that
baby you were with.
Hold it!
But why was the baby
split in two?
With one hidden in
a human castle?
I remember!
This one doesn't have a heart!
That baby is Hakudoshi's heart.
Or maybe...
Naraku's heart?
What's the matter, Kagura?
Is there something on my face?
Is this the right way?
This is the direction that
Princess Abi went.
But I don't even pick up
the scent of the birds.
There's no sign of them
in this village.
Let's keep going.
Yes, the sun is still high
in the sky.
Let us go a bit further.
Yeah!
Sango....
Let us go.
Y-Yeah!
Right.
What will we do from now, Inuyasha?
Huh?
If Princess Abi has turned traitor,
even if we find the nest, there's
no guarantee that it'll lead to Naraku.
Sure it will.
Naraku is after the human blood
that Princess Abi is collecting.
You're right.
Naraku intends to use human blood
to cross into the other world
where the Sacred Jewel fragment is.
We still don't know how
he's going to do that, though....
Say Inuyasha....
Is it okay to leave
Sango alone?
Huh?
Sango's been so down.
She must be worried about Kohaku.
The next time I see Kohaku...
If he has committed more sins...
what will I do?
Can I save Kohaku?
Miroku....
Sango.... Can I stay by you?
I don't want to see you suffer.
Is there something I can do for you?
Can you....
just stay here with me?
Sure thing.
Oh, he casually put his arm
around her shoulders.
Shoulders?
He's not stroking her butt?
Nope, her shoulders.
You are so ignorant, Inuyasha!
Miroku may be a lecher,
but even he knows
there's a time and place.
But didn't they promise
to marry?
Sango wouldn't get
mad any more.
You are really dense!
Why?
Even if you love someone,
you fall out of love if that person
keeps being insensitive!
Hah! But if Miroku stops
acting like a lecher, what's left?
Maybe just his Wind Tunnel.
Don't worry, Sango.
I won't stroke your butt.
Yes, keep your hands
off for now.
Mother, I attacked the castle,
but Naraku did not appear.
So instead, the birds sucked
all the blood out of the humans there.
Yes, thanks to you, the poison
in my body has been diluted.
But do not let your
guard down, Princess Abi.
I'm certain that the castle you attacked
is connected to Naraku.
And the proof of that is....
the barrier around this nest
is gone.
Barrier?
Yes, Naraku had hidden this nest
by putting up a barrier.
Even though we never asked him
to do it.
You think he's going to try something?
That half-demon?
Sister...
Kohaku...
I smell the birds!
Are we close to the nest?
They are Kikyo's shikigami!
You two....
Kikyo....
is waiting.
Huh?!
I reunite with Kikyo,
but she has not completely healed yet.
That's impossible!
You wait here!
Then give this to Kagome....
But whether she can use it
depends on her.
One arrow is entrusted to me.
But what does it mean?
And Naraku battles
Princess Abi's mother, Tekkei,
and opens the path that connects
this world to the next!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Demon Linked
with the Netherworld"
The broken barrier...
is a trap laid by Naraku!