Who are you?
Like you, I despise Inuyasha.
Tell me your name.
It is Naruku.
I'm not afraid!
Naraku is an awful demon!
We must destroy him!
Trying to gain time?!
I was scared.
What're you doing, Inuyasha?!
Shut up!
If you destroy the well, Kagome
won't be able to return!
Don't you care if you never
see her again?!
When she's around, I can't
fight the way I want.
Let's go, Miroku.
Where to?
Isn't it obvious?
To find Naraku and beat the
hell out of him!
Well, Shippo?
Forget it!
I hate Inuyasha!
Awright! Please yourself!
I think you were a bit
too rough.
Although I understand that you
don't want her to get hurt.
If you understand, shut up!
So you're going to look for Naraku...
but how will you find him?
You have any ideas?
Well...
You don't?
Shaddup!
You sent her back.
Just because Kagome isn't here now,
don't take it out on me!
You!
Oh well... Let's just calm down
and think things through!
We don't have the time!
I, too!
I, too, want to find him quickly
and slay him with these hands!
Fifty years ago, he opened the
Wind Tunnel in my grandfather's hand.
The curse has carried over
generation after generation to me!
Miroku...
I'm not good at thinking.
You think of something.
These things must be taken
in order.
Inuyasha, you said you fell
into Naraku's trap 50 years ago...
in this village.
Yeah.
So you've met Naraku then?
Well...
Inuyasha, you can become
a mortal.
If you use the Sacred Jewel.
Tomorrow at dawn,
right here...
I will bring the Sacred Jewel.
Die, Inuyasha!
Even if I met him, he was
disguised as Kikyo.
I don't know what
he looks like.
That's the strange part.
You don't know Naraku...
yet he disguised himself as
Kikyo and shot an arrow at you.
Did you do something
that embittered him?
I've never seen his face!
How would I know?!
In any case,
Kikyo was a priestess.
It could be that Naraku...
had something to do with Kikyo
rather than you.
Kikyo and Naraku?!
Kagome!
It's been so long! Is your
rheumatism better?
Not! She had beriberi!
Huh? You're not in uniform.
What happened?
My uniform was dirty...
with blood all over.
Huh?! Now it's hemorrhaging?!
My illness is going from
bad to worse.
Inuyasha's bleeding hadn't stopped.
I was so worried for him...
When he embraced me...
I'll hold onto this!
What if he did that on purpose
to get the Sacred Jewel?
If so, I'll never forgive him!
Higurashi...
Go stand in the hallway.
I had never been held like
that by a boy...
I guess he passes for a boy.
Since he's half-human.
Inuyasha, with these injuries,
you won't be able to fight for a while.
Shaddup! It'll be better
in a few days.
Hah! Trying to act brave!
Well, I'm done.
What're you doing?!
With that kind of energy, you
may recover quickly.
But I've been thinking...
ever since that time my sister
Kikyo was resurrected from mud.
My sister said that her Sacred Jewel
was stolen by you.
Don't you think it strange?
This man who disguised himself
as you...
Why, he could have made his
escape with the Jewel.
Yet...
He tricked you into
terrorizing the village...
and going after the
Sacred Jewel.
And then...
Kikyo sealed you to
the tree.
Did he want to make
you despise each other?
Or was he trying to fill Kikyo's heart
with hate and bitterness?
What?
In Kikyo's possession, the
Sacred Jewel remained pure.
But when her heart became
unclean and hateful...
the Jewel also became unclean
and filled with evil strength.
And at that time, only one person
would have hoped for that.
Do you want to go there...
where this man lived?
My sister had decided so...
But she harbored
a thief?
Because he was unable to move at all.
He called himself Onigumo.
He had terrible burn scars over
his entire body.
His face, especially, was
badly burned.
He probably fell from a cliff...
both his legs were broken.
Still, Onigumo lived.
He was unable to move...
but he slowly healed and
was able to speak.
However...
His true self...
Hey kid...
I'm Kaede.
Your sister has something
called the Sacred Jewel.
How do you know
about that?
All bad men are after it.
You, too?
I understand that the more
evil this Jewel absorbs...
the more evil it becomes.
How nice...
My sister has it under control.
It will not go bad.
Kikyo is always so smug.
I'd like to see her
worried and scared.
Now that would give
me a rush.
I see...
So Onigumo said that?
Sister, I don't like him.
Forgive him.
He will probably never be able
to move from there.
Shortly thereafter...
Sister sealed you to the tree
and died.
Several days later when
I went there...
the cave was burned down.
The flames must have
been huge...
Onigumo was
unable to escape...
and perished... leaving no bones...
not a sign.
Or so I thought.
C'mon, Old Woman!
Wasn't he human?
The Naraku I seek is
a demon!
Absolutely.
No matter how weak and evil,
he was still human.
No mistake about that.
Shall we go inside
this cave?
It won't budge!
Unless the well is fixed,
Kagome can't return.
Will I ever see her again?
When she's around, I can't
fight the way I want!
He's so willful!
I'll never speak to
Inuyasha ever again!
Inuyasha?
Did you say Inuyasha?
Priestess Kaede, what is this?
No grass... not even moss
grows on this one spot.
This is where the paralyzed
Onigumo rested!
I feel the spirit
of a demon!
The spirit which was
left here decades ago!
What?!
Can it be that the one
who left the evil here...
so that no grass grows...
is actually human?
No, it's not human.
It's from a demon!
How can a human
like Onigumo...
possess such evil as
would belong to a demon?
Help!
Inuyasha!
Shippo!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha... blood!
Damn!
My wound has reopened!
Are you Inuyasha?
Who are you?!
I am the guardian of Hell,
Royakan!
Royakan? Are you the demon that
guards that forest?
I am reborn!
Inuyasha, I come to kill you!
Kill me?!
He knows that Inuyasha
is in no condition to fight.
It's useless to fight me!
There's only one thing
to use here!
Inuyasha, come over this way!
No way!
What a brilliant idea it was...
to imbed a Sacred Jewel fragment
in Royakan.
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Inuyasha!
My vision's getting blurry...
Monk, Inuyasha's in danger!
Yes... There's only one way...
If I can swallow up Royakan!
We can win!
He escaped...
I should've made Royakan
a bit stronger.
Are you all right, Inuyasha?
Where's Royakan?
He escaped.
Inuyasha, Naraku is near.
What?!
Royakan is probably
under control...
by Naraku, who has a
Sacred Jewel fragment.
No wonder such a gentle
demon like Royakan...
has turned so evil.
Naraku! Where are you?!
If you're here, come out
and fight!
Inuyasha!
Monk, Royakan may
come again.
We should return to
the village.
Inuyasha!
It's been three days.
Why doesn't he come for me?
Kagome!
Hojo from Group E
wants to talk to you.
Higurashi, how've you
been feeling these days?
I'm okay.
Really? Then will you go to
the movies with me on Saturday?
On Saturday?
Yeah.
It'll be a nice change
from studying.
Or do you have other plans?
Plans... err...
Inuyasha might've come
for me by then...
Go, Kagome.
You already stood him up once.
- How'd you know?!
- Excuse us.
- Give us a moment.
What?
Do you have someone
else you like?
You're always sighing.
It's not the look of one
who's worried about school.
Well, that's...
After he hugged me
like that...
I'll bet it's
unrequited love!
W-what?
Are you kidding?!
Who'd like a selfish and
rough guy like that!
- Who's she talking about?
- Well...
Hojo! I'll go to the movies with you.
Really? Yes!
Besides, why should I be manipulated
by that stubborn Inuyasha!?
Didn't work.
I wonder what Inuyasha
is doing now.
Open! Open!
Open up!
It's useless, Inuyasha.
This hut is plastered with
charms to keep demons out.
Why must I be
sealed in?!
Open!
Please Inuyasha.
Be still and rest.
Your wound isn't
healed yet.
Kagome!
Eh-heh-heh... Would you like
me to sleep with you?
Shippo... Why you!
Don't you dare disguise
yourself like that again?!
Don't get so mad?!!
Inuyasha, are you still
banging around?
Miroku! You!
Charms are no use if
you act like this.
Lemme outta here!
Priestess Kaede, please seal
the door with the charm.
All right.
You're not ready yet.
I know how eager
you are...
but first, the wound must
heal completely.
He's right.
You can't underestimate
that Naraku.
Isn't that why you made
Kagome go through the well?
Inuyasha... So that's why
you sent her away.
I don't want to die in vain.
And that's why...
I need you to get well
quickly.
Stop talking like a weakling!
I'm ready to fight
anytime!
Inuyasha, just stay still and
get some sleep.
How many times must
I repeat myself?!
You dog!
Hey! His wound will
reopen.
Say, Inuyasha...
What is it?
I wonder how Kagome
is doing?
Not again! Look, just forget
about Kagome already.
As long as she's alive
and well somewhere, that's all.
I don't want to see anymore
women I know die.
I looked for you, Royakan.
Naraku!
Go back! I refuse to
fight Inuyasha again!
You're trembling.
I don't want to be sucked
into the Wind Tunnel.
Just go away!
I will take away the fear
that is making you tremble.
S-stop!
A sinister wind...
Priestess Kaede, take care.
It's coming.
Yes.
He will not take
a step further!
Inuyasha!
Where are you?!
What happened?! He's grown
much bigger!
Where are you, Inuyasha!
As long as our spell
is active...
that hut where Inuyasha lies
will be invisible!
But what has happened to this
demon? He's different.
I'll wager another Sacred Jewel
fragment has been imbedded in him.
Such a pitiful defense.
Priestess Kaede!
Don't move!
I must!
I can see you now!
Inuyasha, there you are!
- Inuyasha!
Thanks for releasing me,
Royakan.
That old hag and monk
had me sealed up.
We were protecting him!
Such an ingrate!
Die quietly!
Shaddup!
Inuyasha's been thrown!
Inuyasha's all talk... His strength
isn't back yet.
How'd he get so strong?!
It's a giant fragment of
Sacred Jewel.
Damn!
You can't have 'em!
Shippo!
You won't get away!
Shippo! I'll take over.
I'll use my Wind Tunnel!
That's!
Naraku's poison bugs!
Damn!
What'll I do?!
50 years ago,
Inuyasha and Kikyo were...
tricked into hating and
killing each other.
It was all engineered by
a demon, Naraku.
Why did he do it?
What was his purpose?
What is his true identity?
Inuyasha's fury and
love for Kikyo...
cut through the evil
and corner Naraku.
Next, Inuyasha:
"Naraku's True Identity Revealed".
Look forward to it!