Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
In our search for clues to
Naraku's whereabouts,
we head towards the sacred
land of Mt. Hakurei.
Blocking our way is Bankotsu,
the leader of the Band of Seven,
who finally makes himself
known to us.
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time.
To a Feudal Fairytale...
Inuyasha!
Let's see....
Agh! No good!
I know....
Wash your face....
Huh?
No!
Damn!
Oh....
Bankotsu....
Huh?
I brought your friends.
Bankotsu!
Yo!
Big Brother!
We're all here.
Good.
But say....
Big Brother....
Kyokotsu and Mukotsu were....
Can't be helped
if they were killed.
You knew?!
But Renkotsu....
Huh?
You're smart.
So you can write.
Yes.
But what?
Let's see....
"We're coming to
settle old scores.
"Wash your face....
I mean neck, and wait."
Or something like that.
It's payback time!
Yeah.
That castle.
That one!
Yeah....
The bastards in that castle
chopped our heads off.
That last battle was
a lot of fun.
He was such a stupid lord.
Hope this fight is fun, too.
Big Brother, what do you think?
Will it be fun?
Yeah, I think it will be.
Look, there it is.
Huh?
Who is that?
The general of the samurai
of this castle.
What? Isn't the lord himself
gonna appear?
I want you to attack
the eastern lands.
An advance guard?
If you're the rumored Band of Seven,
it should be easy work.
As long as the money is right.
Our lord has instructed me to
pay whatever you demand.
Then, we'll accept.
Thank goodness other daimyo lords
hadn't defeated him.
Yeah. My companion is there, too.
You mean....?
Yeah.
They had some nerve.
Big Brother. Will this do?
Huh?
Kohaku!
Take this to that castle.
Hand it to the clan lord.
Me?
You're a ninja, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Then what are you?
Well....
Never mind, I'll go.
Be careful, Kohaku!
Here!
Didn't you want to eat it?
Was I wrong?
Big Brother!
Huh?
What about preparations
to attack?
Why'd you think I sent that letter?
I want to take my time and
watch those guys squirm.
Humph....
I'll let them keep my companion
a while longer.
It's just as Kikyo said.
She was right.
This Mt. Hakurei
is so serene.
What's the matter, Kirara?
Kirara!
Shippo, too?
Miroku, what does this mean?
They've been exposed to
the ki of the Mountain.
After all, Shippo and Kirara
are real demons.
Even half-demon Inuyasha
must feel it, too.
Inuyasha!
Huh?
This is a barrier!
It's probably to protect
this sacred place.
In fact, it's a powerful barrier
strong enough to instantly purify
evil and demons.
I'm human,
and even for me,
this immaculate purity
is uncomfortable.
Huh?
We're fine, right?
Uh-huh.
Maybe you're impure....
Whaa...!
Huh?
No! Don't do that! Don't!
Please stop!
Stop!
You ARE impure!
And you're a monk!
Now it's clear to me.
I thought that, perhaps....
Naraku was taking advantage of
this barrier to hide himself.
Well, it's impossible.
Naraku's a mass of evil.
He takes one step into the mountain
and he'll be purified immediately.
Yes.
There's no way Naraku
could survive in there.
The barrier of Mt. Hakurei
is amazing.
Yes.
Well....
Inuyasha, what'll we do
from now?
What do you mean?
Naraku's whereabouts.
He's not here.
The Band of Seven.
We'll look for them.
Without a doubt, Naraku
is connected to them somehow.
We'll capture them
and make them confess
where Naraku is!
Well then, let's descend
this mountain quickly.
Shippo and Kirara
seem to be in pain.
I don't think so!
Hmm.... He's the one
who's in pain.
He really must be impure.
Huh?
Hey, you!
If young ones like you
wander around here,
the men from the castle
will capture you!
Huh?
The young ones in this area
were all forcibly taken away to the castle.
Regardless of if they were
just traveling through.
Is there a big battle coming up?
I dunno.
But it seems a warning was
sent to the castle.
Warning?
That the castle treasure
would be seized.
Castle treasure?
Like what?
We don't know.
In any case, you'd better
hide out somewhere.
Oh, no!
No what?
The general from the castle!
You there!
Identify yourselves!
We're just travelers.
Don't take me for a fool.
Huh?
Demons wandering in
our borders in broad daylight?!
You got a problem with me?!
What're you doing?!
You're lucky this time.
But there won't be a second chance.
Leave our fief immediately!
Why that...!
Stop! Stop!
He's nothing!
Do you know
about the Band of Seven?
The Band of Seven?!
Old man, you know something
about them?
At one time, the Band of Seven were
mercenaries who wreaked havoc.
That's old news!
The one who killed the
Band of Seven
is rumored to be that
samurai general.
Huh?
Him?
That one is a devil!
What'll we do?
Should we go and
talk to him?
Better not.
If you approach the castle,
you'll only get in trouble.
Inuyasha....
Look! There it is.
Makes me sick.
You got that right!
Damn, we really got it
that time.
Take that!
That was easy!
Such a disappointment!
No kidding.
He may be a daimyo,
but he's no match
for the Band of Seven!
Big Brother...
Isn't it time we find a castle
to lord over?
I mean, you could even
become Shogun.
That'll be a pain!
Do you want to?
Become a daimyo lord
or Shogun?
No...
I'd never overstep you,
Big Brother.
If you want, I'll help you.
Who knows how many men
we'll have to kill first.
Makes me excited!
Me, too!
What a turn-on!
We can kill until we're bored,
and there'll still be more.
Hah! Haven't learned
their lesson yet?
Let's go kill some more!
Okay! Let's get to work!
Huh?
Hey! I thought we were
the advance guard!
The Band of Seven
has gotten too notorious.
Changed your mind
about paying us?
You kill too much.
Whether you are friend orfoe,
the daimyo lords believe
the Band of Seven are too strong.
Brother!
Big Brother!
And you think you can
defeat us?
There is nowhere you can escape.
Consider every daimyo
in the surrounding region your enemy.
Huh?
Big Brother!
Run!
You are too dangerous
even in this age of wars!
Hah!
Before I died the first time,
I killed 999 men.
Now I can make it a thousand.
Don't fail, guys!
If it's a real fight,
we won't lose!
Damn right!
I wonder when we'll be able
to return to the village?
I wanna go home!
Hey!
Huh?
Get back to your positions!
Yessir!
My lord....
Reinforcements will
arrive shortly.
We've gathered the villagers
to take up arms
and the castle is completely secure.
Hah! You're overreacting.
Huh?
You!
Stop!
Who are you?!
But my lord....
Calamities thought to be the work
of the specters of the Band of Seven
have caused panic
in various regions.
And Banryu,
our clan's treasured halberd....
Hey!
I'm here to take back
my companion.
H-He's here!
After him!
Yes.
This is the proof of our killing of
Bankotsu, the leader of the Band of Seven.
If he attacks again,
we'll just beat him.... Huh?
W-What's happening?!
Do not retreat!
Do not allow them to enter
the castle grounds!
Don't panic!
Take that!
Lord!
Stay calm!
They will not attack
any further.
There you are.
Did you read the letter?
W-Why you...!
Where are the guards?
Huh? Oh them?
I don't think they'll be coming.
T-That's....!
Now then.
W-Wait!
You desire this....halberd, right?
Hey, there's my Banryu!
Here. You can have it back....
Huh?! That huge halberd required
three men to carry it!
That young brat is holding
it in one hand!
Wow! It's so shiny!
You polished it, huh?
Y-Yes.
It doesn't matter if you are a ghost.
Will you serve me?
My lord!
I shall make you a vassal!
And together in this feudal age,
we shall....
Hey you! Did you read the
letter carefully?
Huh? Letter?
Your neck.
Neck?
Didn't it say to "wash your neck
and wait"?
Huh?
You'll be....
Number 1000!
I guess it's all over.
Yeah.
Huh?
Reinforcements have arrived.
Well, shall we live it up
some more?
You guys, move aside.
You got it back, Big Brother!
This will be a good warm-up.
The castle!
That's....!
Stop!
It's been awhile.
Why you...!
What did you do
to our lord?!
His head....
Head?
Our heads were chopped off.
So we just paid him back.
Why you...!
Did you wash your neck?
Kill them!
Hah! This feels better than
when I was alive.
Huh?! I sense
a Sacred Jewel shard!
Not only that!
I smell gunpowder and
lots of blood!
No mistake!
The Band of Seven are up ahead!
A slaughter?
Damn it!
Jakotsu, this is your doing.
Couldn't you keep one woman
alive to pour sake?
Forget that, Bankotsu!
This isn't the time to be
drinking sake!
I can't wait to see Inuyasha!
Don't be so rash, Jakotsu.
Inuyasha has a keen
sense of smell.
Yeah, we just have to wait here.
He'll come following the
scent of blood.
Really? I guess we wait then.
Still.... Big Brother....
Hmm?
Doesn't Naraku worry you?
Why?
Why did he bring us back
from the dead?
He wanted us to get rid of
those pests....
like Inuyasha and Koga.
Big Brother....
You're the only one who's
met Naraku.
Can you tell us more about him?
Listen Renkotsu....
We've been resurrected.
And we can wreak havoc
just like old times.
Isn't that good enough?
Yeah....
Once he makes up his mind,
Big Brother never changes it.
I wish Inuyasha would come!
Huh?
A whirlwind!
You must be the Band of Seven!
Huh? Yo, Koga!
So the wolf comes
before the dog.
Quit acting so smug!
I know that you're in cahoots
with Naraku!
Tell me where Naraku is!
Gee, this Naraku has made enemies
of a lot of people.
Where is he?!
Makes me wonder.
Can he be trusted?
Don't ask me.
You're the only one who's
met him, Bankotsu.
If you try to keep it secret....
I'll kill you!
That's right! We still have
a match to finish.
Fool!
I've already seen through your....
weird sword!
He avoided it.
Hey, you're pretty nimble.
Must be the Shikon Jewel shards
in your legs.
Why you...!
Naraku asked me....
to take them, too.
Why that...!
Hah!
What?!
This guy isn't like the rest of them...
Everyone!
Don't let him get away!
Stay still!
Move it, you wimpy wolf!
Huh?
I found you.... Band of Seven!
I'm going to avenge the deaths
of Mukotsu and Kyokotsu!
So you're the leader of
the Band of Seven?!
Be careful, Inuyasha!
That Bankotsu has three
Sacred Jewel shards around his neck.
If you want to know
Naraku's hideout,
ask my Banryu.
In the midst of the vicious
attack by the Band of Seven,
Naraku makes his appearance.
Sesshomaru?!
Kill him, too?
Next on Inuyasha:
The Big Clash:
Banryu versus the Wind Scar!
Water and the smell of flowers....
What do they mean?!