Hello, Higurashi residence.
Oh, Kagome's grandpa!
Hello!
Is that you, Yuka?
Why hello.
Umm... Is Kagome home?
Well... Kagome pulled her
back again and took to her bed.
Pulled her back?
Oh...
Who pulled her back?!
Give it to me!
May I speak to Kagome please?
Well, Kagome's diabetes
came back and...
Huh?! Has she been
hospitalized again for tests?
Oh...
Beriberi and rheumatism
and neuralgia?
She's such a sickly
grandchild...
Oh...
Will you cut it out, Grandpa?
Why would a girl my age
get neuralgia and rheumatism?!
I don't want to tell lies, either!
I'm just helping to explain
your absence...
when you go off
to the Feudal Era!
And what I'm saying is valid!
No way! I'm right here today!
Huh?
Oh yes... Kagome, what's the matter?
You usually rush off over to
the other side on weekends.
That's why I made up
those illnesses.
W-what's wrong with staying here?
This world is where I really belong.
Hmm...
Sota! Playing games
from morning again?
The weather's great, so
go outside to play.
Will you go to the movies
with me on Saturday?
On Saturday?
It'll be a nice change
from studying.
You're in love with someone else,
aren't you?
How could I?
Game over!
l- I didn't come here because
I was worried about Inuyasha...
Inuyasha... I'm going on a date!
You okay with that?
Die!
Shaddup!
Inuyasha's been thrown!
Inuyasha denied it, but he's not
back to full strength.
How come he's so strong?!
A huge Sacred Jewel fragment!
Damn!
You can't have it!
Shippo!
You won't get away!
Time to show them my...
Split Image!
Now's my chance!
You fools!
What is that?
It's slight, but
I feel the presence of the Jewel.
Inuyasha!
What's going on?!
No one's here!
After I came back all
the way here!
Oh no! The time!
I'll be late!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
- Inuyasha!
- He usually fights back so easily!
His slow movements aren't
simply due to his injury.
It's Kagome.
Without Kagome, he's unable to
realize his true power.
Royakan definitely is
using the power of the Sacred Jewel.
What?!
Find where it is,
and you can defeat it!
Kagome would know
its weak spot...
where the fragment is hidden.
Forget about her.
Kagome's not here anymore!
I closed up the well which
connected her world to ours.
Sh-she will never return
here again!
We cannot...
involve Kagome in
these dangerous battles!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Cripes...he gets me so mad!
He always interfered when I
had a test and was cramming.
Higurashi, what's the matter?
You look so angry.
Huh? l-I'm sorry.
That's right. I'm on a date.
Why am I thinking of that
fool at such a time?
Err... What were we talking about?
Higurashi?
Aren't you forcing yourself?
Forcing myself?
I keep thinking about him...
am I being too proud?
Oh no... no such thing!
I can sorta tell.
Hojo... I don't...
I don't think anything of him.
I'll bet you don't feel well,
but you forced yourself to come.
Your grandfather said you had gout.
Not even to Hojo too...!
Do I look sick at all?!
That's right... Maybe Inuyasha's
wound hasn't healed.
Oh no... What if he's dead?!
Sorry, Hojo! Ask me out again.
Good bye!
Higurashi!
I feel it!
I feel the Sacred Jewel.
I can't see it.
Where? Where is it?
They found me!
I want to go back!
Inuyasha, are you all right?!
This is...
The fragment of the
Sacred Jewel!
Shippo!
Kagome!
Kagome! Kagome!
I was able to return!
I smell Kagome!
I'm sure of it!
Kagome is here!
You won't get away!
Shaddup!
Don't... get in my way!
He's suddenly much stronger!
Hey! At least deliver the
fatal blow!
What's going on?
Inuyasha's wound isn't
fully healed.
The enemy is taking
advantage of that to attack.
I knew it... He's in danger.
They're here!
I'll teach...
you!
Inuyasha...
Silly fool!
W-why'd you come back?
Inuyasha!
I thought you died... because
you didn't come for me!
I told you not to come anymore!
I can't help it!
I longed to see you!
Longed to see me? Me?
I...l...
What's that look?
Didn't you want to see me, too?
How dare you?! I was so worried
about you... What a fool I was!
You don't understand a thing!
H-hey! Are you crying, Kagome?
Don't cry over such a trifle!
I'm not crying out of sadness!
It's frustration!
They fight the minute they set
eyes on each other.
But thank goodness it's all over!
Kagome has returned!
Priestess Kaede, it's Kagome!
Priestess Kaede?
Monk, don't you think it strange?
Yes?
The droves of poison insects have
disappeared.
You're right.
That girl...
Kikyo?
No, it can't be.
Kikyo... That woman died
fifty years ago.
W- what is this presence?
Someone's here... who possesses
the Sacred Jewel fragment.
Lots of them!
I knew you were nearby.
You are Naraku!
I've got you now!
So...he is Naraku!
Before I kill you, I must ask
you one thing...
What grudge do you have
against me?
Grudge, huh?
I guess you can't
die in peace...
not knowing why someone
hates you so much.
You are...
Huh?
Kaede, huh?
My, my... How old you've grown.
You know me?
I knew it... You are... Onigumo!
Onigumo... Such a nostalgic name.
I, Naraku, am not Onigumo.
But it is true... that fifty years ago,
I was borne out of Onigumo.
Onigumo was a foolish man.
He began to desire the kind-hearted
young priestess who nursed him.
He succumbed to his weakness
and called forth the demons...
Even my rotting soul is
worth something...
Want a taste of me?
Hungry for me, aren't you?
I want a body that moves freely...
in order to possess the
Sacred Jewel and Kikyo.
Now eat me! Devour me!
And in return, give me power!
That is how...many demons
became one...into Naraku.
Creating my body took
countless demons.
Because the priestess had been
reduced to a powerless girl...
this region teemed with demons.
All because the priestess...Kikyo...
had fallen in love with
a worthless half-demon.
She gave in to childish desires...
tried to use the power
of the Sacred Jewel...
and was punished.
Inuyasha...
you experienced the
punishment yourself.
Die, Inuyasha!
Stupid fool! I have no desire
to become human!
Thanks for the Sacred Jewel!
How dare you?!
You tricked us!
You tricked Kikyo and me
into trying to kill each other!
Then let me ask you...
Was the trust you had in each
other so easy to destroy?
W-what?!
The truth is that anger...
Bitter anger set you against
each other.
That is the true legacy of
the trust you had for each other.
Kikyo could not understand.
Instead of choosing death...
she should have clung on to
her life...
and used the Sacred Jewel.
Had she pleaded for her life...
her wretched wish would have
been easily granted...
and she would have understood
the ultimate truth of darkness.
Such a foolish woman.
The Sacred Jewel grows even more
beautiful when it is tainted.
Kagome!
How many fragments do you see
inside him?
Sacred Jewel fragments...
Ten... No, twenty...
No, much more!
Hey, Naraku... I'll show you
what tainted is!
I'll make that tainted blood
of yours flow!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
A miasma! Get away!
Inuyasha!
So you've sunken into
my miasma.
Tetsusaiga!
You've...
cut through the miasma!
He escaped...
That damned Naraku got away!
Damn it!
Stay and fight!
A spider on his back...
Yes. According to Inuyasha...
a spider-shaped burn mark
on his back.
The robber Onigumo had
terrible burns.
Perhaps that is proof that
it is Onigumo.
A spider on his back...
That will also be the
telltale sign of Naraku.
We are asked to protect the souls
of the dead people at a mansion.
A demon gathers numbers of souls
and carries them away to somewhere.
The demon is controlled by a priestess
with an awful vengeance.
A priestess?
Could she be?
Nobody can sooth her
anger and sorrow...
where are they taking her to?
Next on Inuyasha: "A Wicked smile;
Kikyo's Wandering Soul."
Look forward to it!