Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
Bird Master Princess Abi, who has
allied herself with Naraku
sends her demon birds to
attack the village.
The people worship a mysterious
figure in hopes of salvation...
But that figure can't be...!
Princess Abi, the Bird Master.
Who are you?
Create a path for me.
How dare you order me around like that!
It's not an order. It's a trade.
Without any interruption
from anyone.
That is made from my bones.
I shall lend it to you.
Huh?!
What's going on?!
Huh?! They're attacking!
Wind Scar!
There're more of them coming!
T-They're on fire!
Grandpa!
Why you...!
Hiraikotsu!
They're coming again!
What a nuisance!
Wind Tunnel!
Saimyosho!
That's....!
Just who are you?
Why'd you interfere?!
I could say the same thing!
Are you one of Naraku's minions?
Naraku?
The Saimyosho flying around
you are proof!
I know nothing.
I don't know what's going on
between you and Naraku,
but you killed my birds.
I'll kill every one of you and
drain every drop of your blood!
Now die!
Watch out!
Take this!
Damn you!
Inuyasha!
Curse you!
Damn!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
Who is this half-demon?!
His aura is stronger than I thought.
A barrier!
Hold it!
Naraku is trying to find a way to
get to the border
between this life and the next, in order
to get the Sacred Jewel shard.
And is collecting human blood
somehow connected to that?
Well, it's the only thing
we have to go on.
Whatever the connection....
The path that leads to the border
between this world and the next.
It will soon open.
W-What's happening?!
Demon birds!
Please stop!
Pa! Ma!
Don't cry!
Let's go.
Go where?
To St. Hijiri.
Huh?
Are you two going too?
Uh-huh.
Then let's travel together.
Come with us.
Is this also the work
of the demon birds?
I'm sure of it.
They seem to be attacking
every village in the area.
But that demon who called
herself Princess Abi....
What is her purpose?
Say, Inuyasha....
What could she be up to....
gathering so much human blood?
I dunno....
Let's go, everyone.
Huh?
We'll find the nest.
Nest? You mean the nest
of the demon birds?
Uh-huh.
She's right.
We have nothing else
to go on.
Right.
Master Jaken....
Why, oh why, are you green?
How should I know?
I guess we have to stay
back again today.
Isn't it boring, Master Jaken?
It really is boring.
If I didn't have to baby-sit
this kid,
I could accompany
Lord Sesshomaru.
Huh?
Huh?!
What the...?!
Master Jaken!
Kagura!
You're not here to
abduct Rin again, are you?!
Huh? Did I ever do that?
Don't you dare deny it!
Isn't Sesshomaru around?
You fool! If Lord Sesshomaru
were here,
your head would be
rolling on the ground by now!
I guess....
She's gone.
What did she want anyway?
Guess he was right...
If I come empty-handed,
all I could expect is
to be killed.
What should I do?
Don't mess with me, brat!
Are you in pain, Kagura?
I wasn't able to kill that brat
Hakudoshi with my Dance of Blades.
Still, in order to become free,
I must kill Naraku and
Hakudoshi.
Hold it...!
Back then, when that infant
broke apart into two...
This was meant to happen.
Was there a purpose for
that other half, too?
I'm sure of it!
And a purpose more important
than Hakudoshi.
That's why it was put into
the care of Kanna,
who is trusted more than me.
There has to be some secret.
Maybe something...
That could put an end
to Naraku's life.
What is the matter?
Why can I not hear
the baby's first cries?
Hurry and let me hold him.
My lady....
Regretfully....the young lord was....
the heir was stillborn.
What?! Are you saying
he's dead?!
Yes. He was not breathing
when he was born....
It can't be!
My lady....
I am so sorry....
Huh?!
The infant is not dead.
The infant....
is here.
Dammit!
How frustrating....
Not a single clue.
Demon birds would likely
nest in a high place.
Princess Abi has Naraku's
protection.
Maybe the nest is hidden
by a barrier.
Hah! I'll rip through
any damn barrier!
Excuse me, but we have
to find the barrier first!
Shaddup! I know that!
This is not funny!
It's like Naraku's leading
us by the nose!
- Inuyasha, look!
- Huh?
I can't go any further.
You go on without me.
Hang on, woman!
You escaped from the village?
Yes, it was so frightening.
We never knew when the
demon birds would attack....
Everyone in the region
is packing up and leaving.
You are a godsend.
It always ends up like this.
And you're used to it, right?
Do you have a place to go?
Yes.
If we appeal to St. Hijiri, the holy man
who lives beyond the pass,
perhaps he can protect us
from the demon birds.
St. Hijiri?
Is he a priest?
Well, no one knows
for sure.
We've only heard
rumors about him.
It seems no one has
actually seen him.
Huh? What's that mean?
His face is always
hidden,
and no one has ever
heard his voice.
It is said that communication
between the holy man and the people
is conducted by his
attendants.
So no one knows whether he is
old or young,
or even if he is male or female.
Geez! You traveled this far relying
on rumors?
Wait up! So everyone else is
going there
because of these rumors?
Yes.
Miroku, I think we'd better hurry.
I agree.
Why is that?
Because the birds appear
wherever there are a lot of people.
Kagome, hang on.
Uh-huh!
T-Thank you for carrying me.
When we reach a safe place,
I'll put you down.
Everyone, beyond this pass
is the holy man's village!
We're almost there!
Hey, Hakudoshi!
What're you up to this time?
Kagura, look
at the bird food.
Huh?
Their blood, each drop of it,
will create the road between
this world and the afterlife.
Huh?
It seems they've come.
Huh?!
H-Help!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
This can't be!
Hiraikotsu!
Are you all right?!
Kagura's Blades!
It's been a while, Inuyasha.
Huh?!
Hakudoshi! Why you...!
What're you doing here?!
Inuyasha....
While you blabber,
humans will die.
Huh?!
Stay together!
Don't scatter!
Okay!
Wind Scar!
He did it!
Dammit! They keep coming!
Is there no end?!
This is bad.
As long as we're protecting
the villagers,
we can't act freely.
Miroku, something is strange.
I know. Hakudoshi and
Kagura are merely watching.
And the birds' actions seem
as though they're just buying time.
It can't be that....!
You're right! There are probably
more people gathered
at St. Hijiri's village!
So you finally
figured it out.
Well, it's too late.
By now, Abi and
her main force of demon birds
have begun their attack
on this so-called holy man's village.
Then did you spread the rumors
about St. Hijiri?!
I wouldn't do such a
tiresome thing.
There is a holy man.
Probably just another
exorcist.
Because they were so
afraid of the demon birds,
they raised him to god-like status
and worshipped him.
We learned about him
and we came to feast.
That's all there is to it.
Well, you can cut it out,
you bastard!
Countering your
Wind Scar takes no effort.
Damn!
Master, I can see them.
The same demon birds are
attacking the village.
Give it up and just watch...
the foolish humans
become bird fodder.
Your stupid barrier....
will be broken by me!
It's the Red Tetsusaiga
that breaks through barriers!
He did it!
Whaa...!
Impossible!
Even the Red Tetsusaiga
could not break the barrier?!
So even Inuyasha can't
break through.
Damn!
Damn Hakudoshi,
what does it take to kill you?!
Humph!
Huh?!
What was that just now?
The barrier is gone!
That's....not...!
Wind Scar!
Why...!
It worked!
It's over now!
What the...!
Kagura!
We leave!
Hold you!
Dammit!
He's too fast!
Leave this to me
and go!
Uh-huh!
This way, everyone!
Hurry!
Inuyasha!
Kirara!
Why you...!
It's not working.
The horse's too fast.
He's too fast.
Even if we met head-on,
he'll just dodge my attacks.
Huh?
Might as well try it.
Kirara, over there!
All right....
Follow me!
This is the end of the road,
wild horse.
You may move with
lightning speed,
but this space is
too small for you now!
That's the way!
Just what I've been waiting for!
Now!
Backlash Wave!
Inuyasha!
That's...
The Sacred Arrow that
broke through Hakudoshi's barrier...
This arrow...
came from over there.
No one's there.
Naraku's demons!
It's as though they're
looking for something.
Are they looking for
the holy man?
I heard he decimated
Princess Abi's huge army of birds
with a single arrow.
And it broke through
Hakudoshi's barrier.
And Naraku noticed this?
Does he intend to find out
if this holy man is actually Kikyo....
and if so, kill her once more?!
Well, he's definitely a
hindrance to Naraku.
Next on Inuyash
"The Mysterious Light that
Guides the Saint"
Soul Collectors?
Is Kikyo still alive?!