So many kinds of weapons!
All made from the bones and
hides of demons!
With these arms, the people of
this village slew demons.
So there are strong humans, too.
That's why demons despised
this village.
And Naraku took advantage
of that hatred...
Precisely, he set the demons
upon this village.
On our journey in search of
Sacred Jewel fragments...
we came upon a village
of Demon Slayers...
said to be the birthplace of
the Sacred Jewel.
Naraku's treachery had reached
this spot as well...
and the entire village had been
annihilated.
Every Slayer except Sango
was killed.
The Sacred Jewel which Kikyo had
tried to hide from the world...
The Sacred Jewel which eons later
burst forth from my body...
In this village, everything
would become clear.
Damn it! What's going on anyway?!
Hey, Miroku!
Is that Sango still in bed?
I believe so.
Well, get her up!
She knows Naraku's whereabouts!
She says she can't remember the
castle where Naraku is staying!
But if we keep looking, she's
bound to remember!
It's probably Naraku's doing.
He probably put a spell on her...
which made her forget everything...
So what?! We've been waiting
now for ten days!
A wound like that... I'd be up
and around in three days!
I would probably take to bed
for a month.
Besides, Sango suffers not only
from physical injuries.
She lost her entire family...
the wound to her heart
goes deep.
A wounded heart, huh?
The best cure for that
is vengeance!
And for that, we have to find the
castle where Naraku is staying!
Awright! I'll go and ask her!
Owwee! What're you doing?!
Let her be for a while.
That's the best medicine.
Huh?
She's gone.
Sango!
Should you be up?
You still need to rest.
The graves...
Huh?
You buried everyone and
marked their graves.
Uh-huh...
Umm... Uh...
I can't tell her to cheer up.
In one short day, she became
all alone in the world.
When your wound heals,
won't you come with us?
Inuyasha and Miroku are
basically good people.
What do you think?
You... had a fragment of
the Sacred Jewel.
Huh?
The fragment of the Sacred Jewel
energizes the power of evil...
It's far from its original shape.
Naraku will come after it.
All right, I'll come with you.
You intend to avenge
your family and village?
I guess...
Plus the Sacred Jewel was...
Born in this region.
We came to this village wanting
to know more about that.
Everyone who comes in contact
with the Sacred Jewel fragment...
becomes unhappy.
Just what is the Sacred Jewel?
What is it, Kirara?
Call your friends.
You helped bury the dead.
I'll tell you...
how the Sacred Jewel came to be.
At last, we'll be able to enter
this limestone cave...
where the Sacred Jewel came to be.
So Sango...
just how do we get rid of
this barrier?
Precisely... We must say the
age-old incantation...
and the barrier will be broken...
There's no such incantation.
Huh?
Then how?!
Myoga...
This is a graveyard.
Graveyard?
It's useless to just look
for ways in.
At first, we all thought that
the demons had placed a curse...
to keep anyone from entering.
But it seems that she is the one
who keeps intruders out.
She?
The person from whom the
Sacred Jewel was born.
Her sadness and regret keep
people from entering.
That's what I sense.
It'll be easier to understand
if we go in.
Go ahead, enter.
Ahh...
Are you sure?
Until now, countless people have
become victims of the Sacred Jewel.
You sympathize with them...
so I'm sure she will allow you to enter.
She's right. We got through.
We did it! Now we can meet
this person...
who gave birth to the Sacred Jewel!
Enter Myoga!
W-why?!
What IS this?!
Demons, dragons and spiders
all merged into one to wage a battle...
against one single human.
There's a mummy inside
the stalagmite!
The demon has her in
its jaws...
An ancient armor...
A warrior of long ago?
It's a woman.
A priestess from
several centuries ago.
A priestess?
But look at the number of
demons surrounding her.
This priestess must have
had immense spiritual power.
The court nobles controlled
power at that time.
Wars and famine dragged
on and on...
and countless people perished.
By devouring the dead and
the near-dead...
demons grew in number.
Many priests and warriors
set out to saly them...
but one priestess known
as Midoriko...
was able to purify demons' souls
and render them harmless.
She ranked the strongest
of them all.
She was able to purify the
souls and weaken the demons?
Yes...
In this world...
humans, animals, trees,
and stones alike...
all are created through
four souls.
Four souls?
Shikon?
I've come across it in
my readings.
The four souls are namely.
Aramitama, Nigimitama...
Kushimitama and Sakimitama.
Combined they become the
soul of one person...
housed inside the heart.
Aramitama governs courage.
Nigimitama governs friendship.
Kushimitama governs wisdom.
Sakimitama governs love.
When the four souls work
properly in harmony...
it is called Naobi...
and the human heart
is filled with good.
Inuyasha, do you follow me?
W-what?!
I don't understand at all!
When one does bad deeds...
the four spirits energize evil...
and the human loses
his way.
In other words, with both
humans and demons...
the soul can turn good
or bad.
Midoriko must've been
a formidable foe to the demons.
She was able to purify the souls
of demons and make them powerless.
She fought off an army of demons,
but her power didn't last.
Just means that this Midoriko wasn't
much of a priestess.
She hasn't lost the battle yet.
Not yet?
What's that... ?
After battling for seven days
and seven nights...
a demon got its fangs
into Midoriko.
With the last ounce of her energy...
Midoriko seized the demon's soul...
took it into her own soul, and
forced it out of her body.
The spot where she forced
out her soul...
is that the hole in her chest?
What she forced out...
was the Sacred Jewel.
She wasn't able to purify
the demon's soul.
All she could manage was to
seize the demon's soul.
Although the flesh is gone...
inside the Sacred Jewel...
a battle still wages between the
souls of Midoriko and the demons.
That is why this fight isn't over yet.
Inside the Sacred Jewel...
a war still rages on?
Hah! In any case...
it's all because Naraku came
for the fragments...
that the story's become
so complicated.
I'm gonna take possession
of the Sacred Jewel...
and use it to become a
full-fledged demon!
Then Midoriko can
rest in peace!
W-what!
What's going on?!
People who think like that...
will be thrown out
of the cave... like that.
It's Midoriko's version of "sit!"
It's gotten so late.
A priestess inside
a stalagmite?
Tell me in detail, Shippo.
The priestess thrust the
Sacred Jewel from her body...
the demon had her in its jaws...
and they are set in stone.
Hmm... Covered in stalagmite...
Then as Sango mentioned,
several hundred years have passed.
I believe it has something
to do with Midoriko...
but the villagers worked as
Slayers for generations.
Over the centuries, the Sacred
Jewel passed through...
the hands of various humans
and demons.
And it returned here, during
my grandfather's time.
It came out of a demon that he slew.
But his life and many others
were sacrificed in the fight.
The Sacred Jewel which was
removed from the demon...
was horribly defiled...
and beyond the abilities of the
Slayers to handle.
So they put in Kikyo's care...
Kikyo...
I heard of a priestess
so named...
who was able to purify
the Jewel.
Naraku learned about her
and killer her.
When demons and evil men possess it,
the Jewel becomes defiled.
When a pure-hearted human
possesses it...
the Jewel becomes pure.
It's very complicated.
A Sacred Jewel has the power
for good or evil.
However, I've never heard of
an instance...
where the Jewel has been
used for good.
As long as Naraku is after it...
there will be more
and more bloodshed.
This karma of the Sacred Jewel.
We must put an end to it.
Inuyasha!
Do not think about using the
Sacred Jewel...
to become a great demon!
Hah!
First, I'll kill that Naraku!
That's first and foremost.
Good!
Kirara... my thanks.
We made good time coming here.
Midoriko...
I, too, feel compassion
for humans.
However, when one lives long
and sees so much death...
one becomes accustomed to it.
Forgive me.
This afternoon, I was too eager
in my pursuit of truth.
Since you've allowed me
past the barrier...
I guess you understand.
Oh, sorry, sorry!
I will be finished here soon.
Namu amida butsu...
So many demons...
A single priestess took on
this many demons?
Unbelievable.
Many of the demons merged
with others into huge ones.
So that's the hole in the chest...
where the Sacred Jewel
was thrust out.
Judging from the size...
it's quite possible that the
Jewel was thrust out from that spot.
W-what?!
I have this ominous feeling...
Damn! It's the power of
the Sacred Jewel!
Demons who were not
completely subdued...
are trying to revive!
Damn! It's the power of
the Sacred Jewel!
Demons who were not
completely subdued...
are trying to revive!
What was that tremor?!
Inuyasha! The Sacred Jewel
is gone!
Something's happening in
Midoriko's cave!
Old Myoga is missing.
Kagome, where's he, you know?
Maybe he went with Inuyasha?
No way!
The old one wouldn't stick
his nose into danger!
Old Myoga, where are you?!
Kirara?
Kirara! Run!
Call Inuyasha and Miroku!
What's the matter, Kirara?
I see! We must get the
Jewel fragment back!
Kirara!
Demon spirits!
They're transforming into
fierce ones!
Hang on, Kirara!
Just won't do at all!
T-that's!
Midoriko!
Hurry, Miroku!
Found it!
I cannot linger here with
the Jewel fragment!
- I'm going out of the cave!
- Go!
Now then...
I know of only one creature
who would do something so stupid...
Oh, Master Inuyasha!
Oh dear... Thank goodness
nothing happened.
Cut it out, will ya!
Why'd you bring the Jewel
fragment into a place like this?!
Well, Kirara wanted to...
Iook inside the cave again...
Lying again?!
Err... no...
The souls which still lingered...
reacted to the light
from the Sacred Jewel...
and tried to revive.
I kind of expected it.
How can you brush it off
so lightly when you almost died?
You're so smooth with your talk!
I shouldn't have saved you.
W-what? When was I
saved by you?
Wake up!
And don't act dumb!
I'm not acting dumb!
I was saved by
Priestess Midoriko!
You can sleep talk
in your sleep!
Old Myoga who investigated
the story of the Sacred Jewel feels...
it was impossible for one priestess
to battle so many demons...
no matter how strong her
spiritual power.
Perhaps, Midoriko had a
brilliant vassal at her side...
The Demon Slayer Sango
has decided to join us!
Is it me, or does Miroku look happy?
A village suffers from flood...
and their Water God demands
a sacrifice.
What kind of god would say...
he'd prevent disaster only if the
village people gave up their children?
This could be a demon with
a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Next, "The Lake of the
Evil Water God".
Don't miss it!