It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
forourdreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
At the border between this world
and the next,
Naraku plots to take possession
of the shard.
And Sesshomaru also appears
at the scene of the final battle.
And now, in front of theirfather's grave,
the two brothers face each other.
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
In pursuit of Naraku,
we came to the borderbetween
this world and the next.
And here we met Hosenki,
who had been dwelling
inside Inuyasha's father.
There's no mistake that Hosenki
possesses the Sacred Jewel shard,
but it seems he has no intention
of giving it to us.
And not only that, influenced by
the shards that Naraku possesses,
the shard Hosenki has inside him is
beginning to turn black.
What are we to do?!
Wind Scar!
I know!
If I can purify that shard...
My arrow will probably work...
Go!
I got it!
Hmm.... That was pointless...
Huh?!
It didn't purify the shard!
Kagome, aim for that spot
once more!
B-But....!
Hurry up and shoot!
A-All right!
Just because Kagome's arrow
didn't reach the shard,
doesn't mean it had
no effect at all.
I'lljust cut it here!
Wind Scar!
It broke open!
Awright!
Now I can get the shard!
You....fools!
Huh?
Inuyasha!
You and I....
All of us were just made
to dance by the black jewel.
Inuyasha....
Inuyasha!
In this Land of Fire is a gate that
connects to the "other side".
Overhere.
By "here," do you mean here?
Lord Sesshomaru, can we really
trust that Kagura?
She may be luring you into
a trap again.
Settle down.
Huh?
Not you.
I mean, Tenseiga.
Huh?
T-Tenseiga?
Let us go.
H-Huh?
P-Please wait, Lord Sesshomaru!
Inuyasha!
He's come!
The one who possesses
the black jewel.
Inuyasha!
Go down a bit.
I'm going to look for Inuyasha.
Please!
Go after Inuyasha!
Kagome....!
Kagome!
Kagome! I sense an evil aura!
Huh?
The Sacred Jewel shard....
is coming!
So have you met yourend, Inuyasha?
I witnessed it all.
What?
Naraku!
Uh-oh....this is awful!
Even if I'm brave,
I don't think it'll help.
Naraku!
If you've been watching all this time,
you should know.
Inuyasha was not killed!
Humph!
No way!
It didn't have any effect at all!
Even Kagome's sacred arrow
cannot break through the barrier.
So you are the one who
possesses the black jewel.
What is this rock?
It's very stifling in here, isn't it?
Okay....
That's as far as I go.
I don't want to get involved
in this.
Huh? What do you mean, Kagura?
Is it dangerous up ahead?
Will you shut up?!
You're the one who asked
me to show you the way.
H-Huh?!
And I told you,
I wouldn't guarantee
your safety.
L-Lord Sesshomaru....!
The gate which connects
this world with the next....
Do you wish to pass?
Huh?! Huh? Huh?!
D-Did the stone statue speak?!
Do you wish to pass?
Or do you not wish to pass?
O-Of course we want to pass!
That's why we're here!
Then you shall pass.
The only way to pass this gate is
to allow yourself to be killed
by the guardians Gozu and Mezu
and become dead.
Go!
Even if Gozu and Mezu
are beaten...
If you force the gate open,
you will be bathed in a strange light
that will turn you to stone.
What?!
Now what will you do, Sesshomaru?
L-Lord Sesshomaru....
Dammit!
Tetsusaiga....
Be quiet!
I can still fight!
Naraku, I won'tgive in until
I destroy you!
Hosenki....
It seems you are
quite weakened.
He went right through the barrier
and Naraku!
I see....
I understand you were a great
demon when you were alive.
I'm quite impressed,
that you still have the power
to resist me.
The Sacred Jewel shard will
be taken!
I won't let you!
- Huh?!
- Kagome!
Hiraikotsu!
Kagome, are you okay?
Y-Yeah....
Thank you!
The light from the shard
is jet black!
The impurity from the shard
is spreading through Hosenki's body!
It's all due to yourhard work.
The Sacred Jewel shard
that was hidden
deep within the adamantine armor
and protected by demon powers
was too much for even me,
Naraku, to corrupt.
Are you saying that it's because
we shattered Hosenki's body?!
You broke open Hosenki....
and Hosenki wounded Inuyasha.
In reaction to that hatred,
the Sacred Jewel shard became
even more tainted.
So you're trying to tell us that
this is exactly what you planned?
Yes, and indeed, it has come to pass.
Hmmm....
The Sacred Jewel shard wants
to become whole.
Just now....wasn't that
the Wind Scar?
Did you say Wind Scar?!
Inuyasha!
- Oh, Inuyasha!
- Thank goodness... he's all right!
Naraku!
Humph! So you're still alive, Inuyasha?
Although from the looks of you,
Hosenki battered you
quite a bit.
Hah! Naraku, you were too rash.
Got overconfident and
came crawling out of yourhiding place.
This is the moment I've been
waiting for!
The Red Tetsusaiga!
He plans to draw Naraku
out of his barrier.
Prepare to die!
Master Inuyasha....
Is there any chance
of victory with that attack?
That's right...
I'll cut you down!
Even the Red Tetsusaiga...
It's the barrier-breaking Red Tetsusaiga!
He did it!
He couldn't break through
Hakudoshi's barrier.
You don't get any
stronger, do you, Inuyasha?
And you still don't understand that
even the Tetsusaiga has
no effect on me?
That dull sword is totally useless!
Huh?
Shaddup!
Wind Scar!
Don't you understand
that it's futile?
He used that technique
on Mt. Hakurei....
The one that bounces back
the Wind Scar!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
Kagome!
Inuyasha, you fool!
Letting Naraku's taunts get to him!
This is bad!
Everyone, get away from here!
You can be sliced to bits by
the Wind Scaryou produced!
I've still got one more trick
I haven't tried!
Feel the swirling
of the demonic aura!
Take this!
Backlash Wave!
Did I get him?!
Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha!
Master Inuyasha!
lmpossible! The Backlash Wave
didn't work?!
Inuyasha, it's all over for you.
D-Dammit!
Only the dead can pass through
this gate.
Those who wish to pass shall
first die at ourhands.
Humph.... Interesting.
H-He did it!
Leave it to Lord Sesshomaru.
Huh?
It's futile.
l-It can't be...!
So not even Sesshomaru...
can pass.
We cannot be killed by a sword
of this world.
Tenseiga...
Humph.... Is that how it is?
Then I should use Tenseiga
to destroy them...
Huh? He's in danger!
If he's bathed in the light
of the gate, he'll turn to stone.
Pass....
Ye who wields the sword
of the otherworld.
T-They're kneeling.
That is a sword that cuts down
those who do not belong in this world.
It is as if we have been cut....
So you will notengage in
a needless fight? Very admirable.
I knew it!
Only Sesshomaru can kill Naraku.
Inuyasha....
Your Wind Scar, the barrier-breaking
Red Tetsusaiga,
and even your Backlash Wave
were all useless against me.
You have nothing else
you can use.
You cannot kill me with
yourTetsusaiga.
Hah! Quit sleep-talking!
This match ain't over yet!
Huh?!
He's trying to get the
Sacred Jewel shard.
Hiraikotsu!
You did it!
Great job, Sango!
So he's vulnerable
outside the barrier!
Wha...?! A miasma!
Did he say miasma?!
This is notgood!
The toxic fumes of a miasma will
be especially bad for Inuyasha right now!
It is finally within my grasp!
The last shard of the Sacred Jewel!
L- Last shard?!
I have no use for you anymore.
We won't let you get away!
Saimyosho!
Miroku, you cannot use
the Wind Tunnel.
Hah! You can choose....
Will it be a quick death from
sucking in the Saimyosho?
Or will you choose the stay here
in this graveyard and live for eternity?
Foreternity?
In this graveyard?!
What do you mean, Naraku?!
The river of blood which you and
I crossed has already stopped.
There is no way foryou to
return to the world of man.
Huh?!
Didn't I tell you that
you may not be able to get back?!
If the path is closed,
then Naraku, you cannot go back either!
But, I shall. I alone.
It worries me...
Naraku's smug demeanor.
Naraku! Don't think you're gonna
get away!
Don't you understand, Inuyasha?
It's all over.
Huh?
What?
What is that?
Sesshomaru....
Sesshomaru!
Wha...!
How the hell did he get here?
Humph! Sesshomaru....
Did you rush overto
save your little brother?
Such a kind brotheryou are.
Sesshomaru! Why'd he come here?!
Huh?!
Inuyasha!
Why you...! What the hell
do you think you're doing?!
How dare you, a worthless half-demon,
taint Father's resting place!
Vermin!
Lord Sesshomaru....
Dammit!
Hey....kid....
Huh?
Do you still have the strength to fight?
Each time you cut me, the miasma
will increase.
And eventually, everyone who is
here will die.
I am not so sentimental as to
hold back my sword
forthe sake of humans.
I guess not!
The miasma is coming!
Cut me!
Hosenki!
You will cut me, in order to
break through Naraku's barrier.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Destroy Naraku
with the Adamant Barrage!"
With this one blow,
I'll put an end to all this!