Damn!
Found some sake, Chief.
Hey! Come over here and pour!
Half-demon,
you've weakened considerably.
Serves you right.
Siding with humans
and attacking like that.
No...the barrier isn't going
to hold much longer.
Damn!
Hurry and serve the Chief!
Are you afraid, woman?
I like your face.
He is a demon.
Every woman the Chief had
disappeared mysteriously.
We used to wonder about that.
Why you... bastard!
Are you all right, Inuyasha?!
Hang on!
The poison has traveled
throughout your body.
You can watch me until you die,
half-demon!
As I devour these women...
one by one.
If he gets the sword,
we will all be saved.
Huh?!
Hey, old man!
Tetsusaiga!
Please... save the women!
Huh?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Stupid old fool!
It's over for all of you!
Damn...!
Old geezer... trying to act smart.
Gramps!
Huh?
Noisy kid!
Gramps!
The sword...
Huh?
Please give it to him!
Tetsusaiga?
Where is Inuyasha?!
Where is he?!
Hmm... a delicious-Iooking woman.
Get her.
Yes sir!
You bandits!
Don't resist!
Are you all right, Inuyasha?!
No! The barrier is!
What's with you?!
It's the Chief's orders!
Come here!
No way! You won't touch a
hair on Kagome's head!
Sango!
You ain't getting away!
Darn... there's too many of them!
Get 'em!
The barrier won't hold... anymore.
Inuyasha, are you all right?!
Hang on!
Inuyasha... what's?!
What's this?!
Inuyasha!
He ripped through my poison cocoon.
Inuyasha...
Inuyasha's face!
He's transformed!
Kid...
Don't make me laugh!
You're only a half-demon.
No way can you beat
the demon Gatenmaru!
Take this, kid!
Why does he carry the
scent of demon blood?
So he's melted.
After all, he was just a half-demon.
Did you say something?!
You pesky moth!
You ain't getting away!
Inuyasha...
Lord Sesshomaru...
Lord Sesshomaru,
have you gone away again?
where are you?
Lord Sesshomaru...
How could you leave
your vassal and go?!
It's all because of that Rin!
Damn! He should just abandon
that human child somewhere.
Huh?! Could it be that...
Lord Sesshomaru...
in order to confirm
what Bokusen-Oh said...
has gone to Inuyasha!
Hmm? What kind of person
is Inuyasha?
Hmm, thanks for asking.
It's a long story, but one which
must be told in order to understand.
Ahem!
Inuyasha is Lord Sesshomaru's
younger brother.
However, in demon rank...
in demon dignity...
there's no comparison.
And that is because...
Huh?!
What?
Hey!
Wait! Where are you going?
It sounds like a long story.
Let's go, A-Un!
There's nice juicy grass
over there.
A-Un?!
Why be so mean to me?
You ain't getting away!
Kagome!
Kirara! Protect those people!
Inuyasha!
H-help!
W-we were just following
the Chief's orders!
Spare us!
Stop, Inuyasha!
They're begging for mercy!
Even Kagome can't reach him.
He's laughing...
as he's about to kill!
Kagome, give Tetsusaiga
to Inuyasha...
and calm him down.
I can't stand to see
his face like that!
Uh-huh...
Inuyasha, take Tetsusaiga!
Return to your old self, Inuyasha!
- Huh?!
- Sesshomaru!
Why is he?!
Hmm... A monster
who only knows to fight.
But...
the pure demon blood of his father
is too strong for a half-demon.
After repeated transformation...
Inuyasha will eventually lose
his soul...
Come at me, Inuyasha.
I'll test you...
to see just how strong you are
when you transform.
Inuyasha!
No, Inuyasha!
Sesshomaru's Tokijin can slay
an enemy with the slightest pressure.
You will be killed before
you even reach him!
He punched away the sword!
Huh... Pointless!
He's full of lacerations!
Stop already!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha...
you feel no fear...
nor even pain.
The demon blood has
devoured your soul.
You don't even recognize
who you are.
You will continue fighting
until you die.
Just to make sure if
Bokusen-Oh's words were true...
I have come after you...
Pathetic...
I understand fully now.
You are not a full-fledged demon.
All you are...is a half-demon.
So know your place!
Inuyasha, a half-demon should
act like a half-demon...
and crawl on the ground!
Inuyasha!
Please stop!
He finally stopped moving.
Stay away, stupid!
Watch out!
Kagome, you'll be!
If you want him to stop, use Tetsusaiga
to undo the transformation.
Huh?!
If he revives as is,
he will fight again.
Doesn't he intend to kill... ?
If you wanted to, you had a chance
to bisect Inuyasha earlier.
But you only threw Inuyasha off
with the sword.
Why did you stop there?
You despise Inuyasha.
I can't believe you suddenly
found brotherly love.
I will kill him, in time.
But now... when he doesn't
even know himself...
there's no point in killing him.
It's as if...he came to stop Inuyasha
running out of control.
Huh?
Inuyasha!
You've come to!
Lord Sesshomaru!
You're back!
Rin, have you been good?
Uh-huh!
Rin and A-Un were
very good.
But Jaken seems a bit
depressed over there.
Huh?!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Lord Sesshomaru, why did you
go off alone after Inuyasha?!
Err... Oh!
I'm sorry. That was uncalled for.
Hmmm?
Lord Sesshomaru...
Inuyasha, you mustn't move.
Did I do all this?
Huh?
He doesn't remember?
Huh? My claws... reek of
the bandits' blood.
Inuyasha...
Inuyasha, you did it to
save everyone...
That's why you did it.
Uhh...
He's a monster!
If you get close, he'll kill you!
T-that's not!
I don't care if he's a monster!
He... he saved Gramps!
He defeated all the bad men!
No...all I did was hunt men.
The demon that I wanted
to become...
the power that I desired...
isn't like this!
Each time Inuyasha transforms
into a demon, he loses himself.
Today, not even
Kagome's voice could...
Miroku... even if Inuyasha
fully transforms into a demon...
I want to stay with him.
Sango...
Though I caused so much trouble
over Kohaku...
all of you stood by me,
like it was the natural thing to do.
That's why, I...
Uh-huh...
Damn! I can't wash away
the smell of blood!
It's sickening!
Here, a towel.
No thanks.
You don't have to force yourself
to stay by me.
What?!
Everyone's been tiptoeing
around me!
Now get this!
It doesn't bother me!
I don't give a damn
what I did!
Inuyasha...
It must be hard.
Inuyasha... I understand.
Kagome...
I don't remember a thing
while I was transformed.
This has never happened before.
The next time I transform...
I may use these claws, Kagome...
to tear you up.
Inuyasha cannot suppress his
violent demon blood!
But he doesn't want to become
a monster who only kills.
There must be a solution!
If he defeats Ryukotsusei,
Tetsusaiga will become light.
Inuyasha bravely faces the challenge
posed by Totosai...
but that Naraku is up
to no good again!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Father's Old Enemy: Ryukotsusei".
Don't miss it!