You've gotta be kidding!
Even if it is Feudal Japan...
There's no hot baths?!
C-C-Cuh-Cuh...
Cold!
Kagome, don't force it.
Come on out.
No! I'm all bloody and dirty.
And I can't stand my filthy hair!
The Sacred Jewel...
My name is Kagome Higurashi.
I'm just your average school kid...
but, through some strange,
weird situation...
I've ended up here, in the
"Warring States"era.
Rejoice! My power is coming back!
My body is being restored!
You have it...
I know you have it!!
Let me go! You're disgusting!
Let me go!
I've also become the target
of demons...
all after a jewel in my body.
This "Jewel of Four Souls," which
belonged to some "Kikyo"person...
How did it end up in ME?
Now I have to team up with a
half-demon called "Inuyasha"...
who wants Jewel's power...
and who intends to keep the
fragments for himself.
Am I dreaming?
But it's NOTa dream!
What's going on?!
Stop barking, Inuyasha.
What happened to the Jewel?!
The arrow to which Kagome
attached the crow's feet...
hit the Corpse Crow
and destroyed it...
but it also shattered
the Sacred Jewel.
In other words, fragments of
the Sacred Jewel...
have been scattered throughout
the world.
Who knows whether there were
one hundred fragments...
or a thousand.
Should even one fragment
fall into evil hands, however...
the destruction will be incalculable.
It wasn't my fault...
was it?
I feel sort of responsible.
Kagome, Inuyasha...
You must use your combined
strength to gather the fragments...
and restore the Sacred Jewel!
Huh?
Listen up, old hag!
I'm one of the "evil-doers"
looking for the Jewel!
It cannot be helped...
But... I have to go home.
Besides, I don't have
such powers.
And Inuyasha is so selfish.
Sit!!
So you are here, Inuyasha.
Rrragh!
I'd forgotten about the
subjugawhatchamacallit.
Shame on you!
Spying like that!
Huh?!
Yeah, right!
All I was doing was...
...trying to steal the Sacred
Jewel. Yes, I know.
If you knew, why'd you ask?
The future looks very bleak...
Inuyasha, unless you join forces...
with Kagome, who has the
ability to "see" the Jewel...
there is no way all of the fragments
will be found.
And I'm tellin' you that if it's
for the sake of the Sacred Jewel...
I'll put up with the dumb girl,
so stop worryin'!
Do you really dislike me
that much, huh?
Kikyo...
What's that expression on
your face, Inuyasha?
Well, well!
The Sacred Jewel I thought
lost over fifty years ago...
has appeared once more.
It's going to be very interesting...
Priestess Kaede...
Yes?
My daughter...
I see. I will be right there.
I must return.
Do not fight.
Hey.
"Hey" what.
Get undressed.
Oww! Why, you...
Why did you...?!
Pervert!
I didn't mean undress undress!
"Put your own weird stuff
back on," is what I meant.
Because this makes me
look like Kikyo?
Whatever.
Oh, please... It's like
he's in middle-school.
Look! I can't work with someone
who's always picking a fight!
That's fine with me!
I prefer to go it alone.
I see! You don't need me
along then?
Hey. Where you goin'.
I've made up my mind.
I'm going home.
Goodbye, Inuyasha.
"Going home"? Hey!
My name is Kagome.
Please address me
as such.
Hey! Wait!
It's not "hey," either.
Wait, I said! Hey...!
What?! It's useless to
try and stop me.
You got that Jewel piece, right?
Leave it.
You mean this?
Sit!
Why, you!
You can't have it.
I can't believe that guy!
Inuyasha has never once
addressed me by my name!
This way, Priestess Kaede...
She suddenly collapsed?
Yes.
She was just fine
this morning.
Let's see...
Hmm?!
Stay back!
Huh?
She's... floating.
Hair?!
That's how I got here,
thru the Dry Well.
I'm sure I can go back
from here.
Bones...
That dry well is nicknamed
the "bone-devouring well."
It is where the corpses of
the dead demons are discarded.
After several days,
the corpses disappear.
Those are the bones of the
Centipede-Monster.
Great. Now I'm afraid to go in.
Now what?
Ouch!
It can't be.
That's hair!
Oh, my!
You can see it, then...
my web of hair.
But being able to "see" it
isn't enough...
Who're you?!
I'm going home.
Goodbye, Inuyasha.
Let her go, who cares?
What's with you all?
Interesting!
Wanna take me on, huh?
They call me
"Yura of the Demon-Hair"...
though you needn't bother
remembering it.
Your time's about to run out!
I'm helping myself to the Jewel!
Now look
what you've done to it.
Where are the other fragments?
Give it back!
Answer my question!
Where are the remaining fragments!?
I... I don't know.
I see.
In that case...
you may as well die!
I see.
In that case...
you may as well die!
It's useless to try
and escape!
Gone...
Who was that girl?
Wait a minute!
They're all girls
from the village.
What's going on?
Planning to tie me up again?
Well, I'm not giving in.
Inuyasha, don't do it!
Do not harm the girls!
Old Kaede!
Wow, look at you.
You're a bloody mess.
Have you nothing nicer to say?
So why shouldn't I hurt 'em, huh?
They're sure tryin' to hurt me.
They're all under a spell.
Kagome? Where's Kagome?
She went back to her own land.
Not that it matters or nothin'.
I don't need her to handle this.
You mustn't!
Do not touch the village girls!
Will you quit flappin'
your gums already?
Or have you forgotten
they're after you, too.
Don't you understand, Inuyasha?
We must get to the one who
is controlling them.
Now you've completely lost it.
Then Inuyasha, please...
Cut the hair!
Just cut the hair and the
trance will be broken!
The what?
I don't see anything.
Now, then...
Time to draw close this prey.
No!
Inuyasha, run!
They're not too smart,
whoever's behind this...
I may be tangled up...
but even if I can't see
who's doing it...
I can cut down whoever's
in front of me!
Ohh, so sorry!
I suppose I've teased
you long enough.
Inuyasha!
Nnyaah!
The tension's gone.
The head must not have
been severed.
Oh, man...
I thought I was done for.
If you'd been a mere human,
it would have come clean off.
The village men!
More human puppets?
It's gettin' kinda old.
Inuyasha, leave this to me and
make your escape.
Aw man, would you quit
bein' such a martyr an'...
Old Kaede!
Inu... yasha...
Can't be helped.
Ooh! Such pretty, silver hair.
Hang in there, old woman!
Be careful, Inuyasha!
The hair...
You say somethin', old woman?
Never mind.
Such a stubborn one.
This is fun.
And this silver hair...
I must have it!
Old woman, you said you can see
the strands!
Tell me where it's being
pulled from, then.
Don't be ridiculous!
With me in this condition...
and even with my
seeing powers...
Hurry... Kagome can...
So she can see it, too?
Yes.
For this foe...
Kagome...
Kagome is necessary
for victory...
Where is this?
The bottom of the well.
That's right...
That girl came after me...
and pushed me into the well.
We've looked in this well
over and over again.
But I already told you,
it's where she fell in!
You must've been dreaming.
It's the truth!
Gramps!
Sota!
I'm back...
Back to my own time.
Kagome, you've been gone
for three days...
We've been so worried.
Sis, what happened to you?
I'm not dreaming!
I'm really home!
Gramps!
I was so scared!
Kagome...
What happened?!
Okay...
This is it, old woman.
Givin' you a decent burial's
the least I can do.
Fine. Only...
I'm not dead yet.
What I meant was,
bury you to hide here.
I'll even come back an'
dig you out, if I don't forget.
Are you sure?
You had better not forget.
Do not forget, Inuyasha!
I know! I know!
Curse that stupid girl!
Where'd she run off to,
at a time like this??
Happiness at last.
Wherever she went,
she won't get away!
It feels so good.
It seems Inuyasha can't
even SEE Yura's hair!
What hope can he have
of defeating her?
In order to help Kaede, we
have to defeat Yura...and fast.
Nothing Inuyasha does
seems to have any effect!
She's GOT to have a
weakness...SOMEWHERE.
Next time.
"Yura of the Demon-Hair"
See you soon!