Sacred Jewel shards...
We were in search of Naraku,
when a ghastly demon
came afterus.
Just then...
Koga saved me.
But a young girl from the
Wolf-Demon Tribe appeared.
You promised me...
Don't overdo it.
If itgets too hard,
I'll make you my wife, Ayame.
l-Is that true?
D-Did I really say that?
That demon...
Did Naraku send that
as a decoy?
We'll find out once
we capture it.
It may know Naraku's
whereabouts, too.
That's afterwe save Kagome!
Be safe, Kagome!
Then the elder of the Wolf-Demon Tribe
is yourgrandfather?
I call him Gramps.
But there must be a reason
for coming down
the mountain like this?
It's only recently...
but a strange demonic aura came
down from the northern mountain.
Strange demonic aura?
Gramps said it smells
of a demon.
Demon?
Uh-huh...
And around that time,
in-fighting among the
Wolf-Demon Tribes
in the east and north,
and south and west increased.
So Gramps decided to marry me
off to one of the strong young ones
to build up an alliance.
Huh?! Apolitical marriage?
Luckily, Koga and I were
already promised.
I said I don't remember!
Gramps thought that Koga would
be able to get followers.
And I didn't mind marrying,
if it's to Koga.
So it wasn't just a
political marriage.
Damn!
Getting all worked up
over a stupid demonic aura!
Yourrole may be to
make peace...
but all you gotta do is
crack theirheads together
and make them see some sense!
It's not thateasy!
In orderto bring the tribes together,
we need their trust!
You have to get married
and be settled.
Then I'm not suited forthat.
Koga!
What I want to do more
than anything right now,
is to get Naraku's head!
I don't have time for
anything else!
No matter what?
Shut up!
Go back to the mountain!
Koga!
Ayame...
Stop listening only to
what the elder says.
Do what you want to do.
Huh?
Ayame... That's the end
of this subject.
Say, Koga!
This demonic aura?!
Demonic aura?
That Inuyasha!
He must have let the demon go!
I can smell it...
it's real close.
Huh?
Koga, let's go back
to Inuyasha and the others.
Don't worry, Kagome.
I'll protect you.
I appreciate your words...
But this isn't the time for such words!
Huh? Koga keeps saying
he loves her.
But this Kagome, could she?
Hey demon!
I'll take you on.
Besides, I need to
ask you a question!
Which way?!
Overthere?
Huh?!
The Hair is attacking!
To stall us?
It doesn't want to
let us pass.
Inuyasha!
Go to Kagome!
Awright!
Kagome, wait for me!
You won't get away now!
I'll devour you all...
Sacred Jewel shards and all!
Ayame... I don't have any right
to ask you this.
But I'll leave Kagome
in your care.
In my care?
Me?
Kagome, wait there with
Ayame.
Koga!
You're just huge, that's all!
Just watch!
Take this!
Now that you've caught
up with me...
Now you can tell me!
Where is Naraku?!
The hair's falling out!
Why you!
Koga!
Strike him!
A sacred arrow?
Is Kagome... a priestess?
D-Damn!
Are you all right, Ayame?
This demon!
Why don't you get away?
What?
Koga is doing his best
to protect you.
Koga isn't like that.
Koga is fighting to protect
both you and me.
Huh?!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Inuyasha!
You're all right, Kagome?
I'm okay.
Inuyasha?
He's with Kagome?
Koga, what're you doing?!
Putting Kagome in danger
like this!
Shaddup!
It's only because you stupidly
let the demon escape!
I'll protect Kagome!
So stay outta this, Wolf!
But you can't!
Koga, Inuyasha is here.
Don't overexert yourself.
K-Kagome!
Huh?
Is Koga...
Watch out, Inuyasha.
Don't get tangled up
in that demon's hair.
Hah! Don't worry, Kagome.
Just watch me.
I'll destroy him in one blow
with my Wind Scar.
Damn mutt!
Coming into the picture like this!
I'm gonna get the demon!
Koga... Could this be...
an unrequited love?
I'll devour you,
shard and all!
Hurry, Inuyasha!
We have to save him!
Me?
You're the only one who can!
Hurry before he's eaten!
Hurry!
I don't care what happens
to Koga.
But I can't let you have
the Sacred Jewel shard!
Huh? The hair only scattered away!
What?!
Inuyasha!
No one will get in
my way now!
I've finally been...
Damn!
freed from Naraku!
Wha?!
I'll use the Sacred Jewel's power...
and get back my former self.
What?
Kagome!
You're all right?
Everyone!
Who is thatgirl?
She's Ayame.
Koga's fiancée.
Huh? Fiancée?!
We can talk later.
But what is that demon?
That demon said that he had
been freed from Naraku.
Huh?
You!
Just what do you mean?
That Naraku... he abandoned me
and the castle.
He wasn't an incarnation that Naraku
created out of his body?
Naraku didn't need him anymore?
Well... he certainly doesn't
look very useful.
I shoulda known...
You're too ugly even for
Naraku's demon.
What a pity, Koga.
You mean all this time,
you've been fooling around with
trash like this?
Damn it all.
Ayame!
Can't be helped.
I'll protect you, too.
So stay there and watch.
Mutt, I'll play with you later.
W-What!
Hey, Demon!
You cried about being
abandoned, huh?
Does that mean...
you don't know where
Naraku is?!
Huh?!
Koga!
Don't be hasty, Koga!
We still have questions.
Hah! Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
Now then, Demon...
Tell us all you know.
Or else...
It's useless to search.
Naraku has escaped to
a place
where no one can touch him.
Huh?!
Where no one can touch him?!
Too bad.
That's all I know.
Huh?!
Naraku cut me off
in the midst of things.
I don't know Naraku's
plans beyond that.
Serves you right!
It seems he's telling the truth.
Damn! He's no help!
Huh!
Can't be helped if you don't know.
However...
There's one thing this trash of a
demon is good for.
Why you!
Koga!
Ayame!
She purified the demonic aura!
It's the spiritual power of the iris.
I'll devour you!
- Koga!
- Ayame!
They've both been devoured!
Koga! Ayame!
Damn, I can't use the Wind Scar!
I've eaten the
Sacred Jewel shards!
As if you can kill me!
Koga! Your arm!
All because I jumped in.
Hah! This is just a scratch.
It's nothing.
Hey!
Koga!
So you finally caught up.
You two, rememberthe scent.
And make sure all the wolves
rememberit.
So you'll use all the wolves to
track the scent?
And search for Naraku
high and low?
Hah! As if that'll work!
If wolves were able to
sniff that Naraku out,
I'd have done it long ago!
Huh?!
Koga!
Hey!
Kagome, I have to go now.
But...
When we next meet, I'll have
Naraku's head as a gift.
That Koga...
She doesn't love him!
Yet he's trying so hard.
N- No... thanks!
Don't look like that, Kagome.
You're the woman who's
gonna be my wife.
What?!
Ahh! Hey wait, Koga!
You promised long, long before
you met me...
that you'd marry Ayame.
And yet you're telling me this?
That's something... I don't remember.
But look...
The night of the lunarrainbow...
Don't you remember anything?!
A rainbow...
Huh?!
I'll make you my wife...
when you come
down from the mountain.
Look!
A lunarrainbow...
Sorry, but I still don't remember.
Koga, you saw the rainbow, didn't you?
I said I don't remember
any rainbow.
Ayame was...
still really... young, right?
Never mind about the past.
I understand now that you have
to go afterthis Naraku.
Is Kagome part of a love
triangle with Koga and Ayame?
I don't think so...
I think Ayame came to
get Koga.
But Koga loves only Kagome.
Unlike some otherguy,
he's sticking to one and only one.
What're you doing, Inuyasha?!
Shaddup!
Until you complete your vendetta,
I'll manage something
with the elder.
Okay.
But, I don't plan to
give you up.
Rememberthat!
Huh?!
I'm the only one
who can be your wife.
M-My woman has to be able
to sense the Sacred Jewel shards!
Kagome can see it!
See it?
The Sacred Jewel shards?
Then I'll make myself
be able to see it, too!
Make yourself able to see it?
As if you can!
- I can!
- You can't!
I can!
You can't, I said!
W-What?
You just wait and see.
H-Hey!
See ya!
Hey, Miroku...
If you train, can you make yourself
see the Sacred Jewel shards like Kagome?
Impossible, I think.
But I think she's going to do it.
She's full of confidence, too.
That fool Ayame!
Hey Koga!
Now that that's settled...
Why don't you leave those shards that
are in yourlegs here?!
No way!
See ya, Kagome!
Good bye!
Wait, Koga!
Damn!
But Inuyasha...
I think Koga's idea about
using his wolves makes sense.
It's too simple!
If the scent was a problem,
why did Naraku leave his trash?
The source of his scent!
Isn't that too careless?
Oh, you're right.
In otherwords, Naraku...
is confident that he'll
never be located.
Isn't that so?
That makes a lot of sense.
And?
Huh?
Not "huh."
Where do you think
Naraku went?
Tell us yourthoughts.
You figure the rest out yourself.
So he didn't figure it
out yet.
I gotta keep it together...
But... Inuyasha is right.
The place where Naraku escaped to...
The place where no one
can touch him...
How do we locate such a place?
We were close to the river
on that night, too.
I don't feel like I'll lose
to Naraku.
But there's no guarantee that
I'll be alive
afterl take my revenge.
Ayame, forget about the
night of the lunar rainbow.
I won't forget.
I won't everforget that
you protected me.
Even if the rainbow fades.
Damn it all!
Just when I'm able to
break through Naraku's barrier...
Uh-huh...
But we'll find Naraku.
If we all search together.
All?!
Are you still gonna
rely on Koga?
Hah!
Even his fiancée from the
Wolf-Demon Tribe left him.
And you're gonna depend on
a guy like that?!
Huh? Are you stilljealous?
l-I'm not jealous!
You're not jealous?
Who cares about that?
You're the one who
started it!
Come on... Just continue
what you were saying.
Forget it!
I won't!
If only Inuyasha could
be a bit more forthright...
like Ayame who loves Koga.
A lunarrainbow...
Huh?
Ain't no such thing as a
rainbow at night.
There is.
To people who can see it.
Really?
Ever since Naraku disappeared,
all these demons who've lain low
have begun to act up.
Thanks to them, Demon Slayers
have lots of work.
But that means more competition.
How can that old woman exorcist
endure this demonic aura?
She must be really powerful...
or really dense.
Let's clean this up
and go home.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Evil Within Demon's Head Castle"
A beautiful princess!
Leave her to me.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay!