Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
The Demon Ninja Hoshiyomi captured
Kagome and used her spiritual powers
to restore the frightening power
of the Naginata of Kenkon.
Damn! What're we gonna do?!
We're being sucked in.
We're gonna save Kagome
from the hands of that monster
no matter what we have to do!
But Tetsusaiga still isn't....
Anything is possible if
you put your spirit into it!
Everything in the universe
disappears eventually.
Sadness and happiness,
all fade with time.
Nothing lasts forever.
Even this world will
someday be destroyed.
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
So you should give up
your senseless struggle
and die quietly!
I don't think so!
Sango!
Why, you!
You do not understand, do you?
Against the Naginata of Kenkon,
you cannot win!
l-Impossible!
The Naginata of Kenkon
is invincible!
Miroku!
Blades of Blood!
You want this girl back
so badly?
You love this girl that much?
I love Kagome!
I will gladly trade my life for hers!
Please return Kagome!
Huh?!
You said that nothing
lasts forever.
But....
Even with the passing
of time....
There is something called
love which never dies!
Akitoki....
He's so impulsive!
At times like these,
he should just keep quiet.
Just as you said, it is true that
I am but a weak human being.
But....
But, because we are so weak,
humans can understand the
pain of others,
and can show kindness
and compassion!
And I believe that such
feelings last forever!
Hmph! Feelings?
Don't make me laugh!
If humans had kindness,
if they understood pain,
why did Tsukiyomi
seal me away?!
I cannot forgive you!
What humans did to me,
I will repay with death!
So die knowing how I feel-!
W-What is happening?!
You are...!
l-It's impossible!
W-What's happening?!
That's....!
Kagome!
Hoshiyomi....
Tsukiyomi....
We are finally able
to meet once again,
Hoshiyomi....
Tsukiyomi, what do you want now?
I wanted you to remember
once again....
the feelings you once felt
towards humans.
The kindness you showed me....
The days we once shared together.
Are you hurt, Tsukiyomi?
Save your worries for yourself.
I do not want to hold you back!
So like you.
Do you really think you can
run away from us, you fool?!
You're not even worth fearing!
You go through such
pains....for a lone woman!
Letting a lowly human....
Letting Tsukiyomi....
steal your heart....
Yes, I even changed my
name to Hoshiyomi...
That's how much
I cared about Tsukiyomi...
Abiraunken Sowaka!
Tsukiyomi!
You've used too much
of your strength.
If we continue hunting down
demons like this....
your life will be....
It's too late to give up fighting.
The demons who begrudge us
will keep coming after us.
No! There must be a place where
we need not fight!
Somewhere we can live
in peace.
Here are the corpses of
the demons you spoke of....
There are 222 of them in all.
I gathered them all.
Now you have everything
to complete
the ultimate weapon which
possesses the power of yin and yang.
Yes....
Tsukiyomi....
That time, in order to find a place for
you and me where there would be no fighting,
I asked Kaijinbo to forge this
Naginata of Kenkon.
I needed a weapon that equaled
the power you possessed.
So that you would not need to
expend any more of your powers.
I did it all for you.
Hoshiyomi....
So why?!
Why did you betray me?!
Amazing!
This naginata is truly amazing!
Hoshiyomi!
Behold, Tsukiyomi!
As long as I have this Naginata of Kenkon,
you need not use your powers.
With this, we need not worry.
Even if a hundred, a thousand
demons attack us,
I shall be able to protect you.
Hoshiyomi....
That Naginata of Kenkon
is very dangerous.
We must seal it immediately.
What are you saying?!
In order to live in peace,
without having to fight....
I must have absolute power!
Hoshiyomi is becoming possessed
by the Naginata of Kenkon.
If nothing is done...
Forgive me!
Rin! Pyo! To! Sha! Kai! Chin!
- Retsu! Zai!
- Tsukiyomi!
Zen!
Why?!
Why are you doing this to me?!
Tsukiyomi!
Why? Why?!
Such frightening demonic power!
Evil powers.... Begone!
The calamity has been sealed.
Hoshiyomi....
I will release you from
the seal now.
Huh?!
My strength....
Ho-shi....yomi....
Tsukiyomi....
You were just a human, after all.
There was no way you could love
me, a demon.
T-That's ridiculous!
Are you telling me the truth?!
I am not saying that I
did not betray you.
But I wanted to save you!
From the spell of the
Naginata of Kenkon.
I wanted to release you!
Was it all because of
my own weakness?!
Was it because my heart
did not have faith in Tsukiyomi,
that this darkness was born?!
Hoshiyomi....
My body may no longer exist,
but my feelings are
yours eternally.
I have no regrets!
Ridiculous!
It's way too late!
It's all much too late!
The Naginata of Kenkon has
returned to this world!
And it thirsts for blood even now!
Kagome!
She's all right.
The blade didn't touch her.
Kagome!
Inuyasha?
Huh?! Let me down.
I'm all right.
'Kay.
Kagome....
I now possess absolute power!
I have no regrets whatsoever!
I shall rid the world of humans
with the Naginata of Kenkon!
Are you still going on about that?!
Tsukiyomi died for your sake!
How can you ignore her sacrifice?!
Kagome!
My Tetsusaiga....!
Tsukiyomi was human,
but she was not weak!
She possessed a much
stronger heart than you!
You're the one who
betrayed yourself!
You became bewitched by the
Naginata of Kenkon
because your own heart
was weak!
Silence, wench!
What would you know?!
Die!
Don't you dare lay a hand on her!
I'll....
protect Kagome!
Don't you dare lay a hand on her!
Inuyasha....?
Prepare to die, Hoshiyomi!
Wind Scar!
You impudent half-demon!
What?!
My power....
My power hasn't returned.
Your spiritual powers have all
been absorbed by the Naginata of Kenkon.
It's useless.
Kagome!
Isn't there something we can do?!
Hmm.... If we take the naginata
away from him,
something may be possible....
That's impossible!
We'll be killed before
we can steal it.
Kagome....!
Kagome, whom I care for deeply,
is fighting, while I....
Die!
Inuyasha!
K-Kagome....
I....
I love you, Kagome!
Why, you....!
A-Akitoki....
That damn fool!
Humans are weak, after all.
If you want to rush to death,
so be it.
Lend me your strength, Tsukiyomi....
Die!
Stop! Hoshiyomi!
What?!
T-Tsukiyomi!
Yes! My power has returned!
Be grateful to Akitoki.
It's all because of him.
I know! Thank you, Hojo!
You're welcome.
Now then,
let's put an end to this.
Okay!
W-What's that?!
Hah! What can you do?!
Everything is powerless against
the Naginata of Kenkon!
It's coming!
I know!
Begone!
Take this! Backlash Wave!
Go!
It's better this way....
It's better like this,
right, Tsukiyomi?
Kagome!
Are you all right, Kagome?!
Uh-huh....
That was a fine joint effort.
You were in perfect sync.
Yes!
He is....me.
Huh?
He was the same as me.
You mean, Hoshiyomi?
Yeah....
There was a time when I was
possessed by demonic power,
and I couldn't control myself.
Damn! It's exactly the same.
Inuyasha....
However, you had Kagome.
Kagome embraced you with kindness
and saved you.
Yes, many times.
The first time was
with "sit."
Shippo, hush!
Looking back, he's right!
You're not kind at all!
Well, I'm sorry!
- You should be! You little pipsqueak!
- What did you say?!
Now, now.... There are
different forms of kindness.
Kagome....
- please take care of yourself.
- Shut up! You fake, lecherous monk!
Don't call me a fake. I won't argue
about being a lecher, though.
What was that?!
I had deep feelings for Kagome.
Even if they would never be reciprocated,
my feelings will never fade.
Please wait!
You're speaking to me?
Yes!
What is your name?
It's Suzaku.
Suzaku?!
Oh, you should change
such a name.
It does not suit someone
as beautiful as you!
Huh?
Change it to Kagome.
It's a lovely name.
How about we continue the
journey together?
But you were going that way.
No, no.... Don't worry about that.
Let us be on our way.
All right.
My name is Akitoki Hojo.
And let me tell you that I
have had many adventures.
Why just the other day....
Higurashi....
What's the matter, Hojo?
You're daydreaming.
Keep sighing and
happiness will run away.
Never mind this silly family tree.
Huh?!
What have you done?!
Be quiet. It'll be over quickly.
Are you the ones killing
monks and shrine-keepers?
I heard the demon was a
female with an infant.
But this infant.... Could it be
more frightening than the woman?
A priest like you should be able
to see the border
between this life and the next.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Entei, The Demon Horse Unleashed!"
That's just a stupid horse!