Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
We learned that the remaining
Sacred Jewel shard
was to be found at the border
between this world and the netherworld.
Then Sesshomaru appeared
before us.
What will his father's sword,
Tenseiga, divulge?
I am Hakudoshi.
As you've guessed,
I am one of Naraku's
incarnations.
Hakudoshi?!
So you're Naraku's....
Would you like to search
for it, too?
The Sacred Jewel shard?
Sacred Jewel shard?!
Hah! I don't give a damn about
the next world or whatever,
but if there's a shard to be
found there,
you can go there yourself!
Why you.!
This brat... just what is he thinking?
Let's go.
- Huh?
- Oh....
- I wonder what's going on?
- Yeah....
I shall go and ask.
Miss, will you bear my child?
M-O-N-K!
Owwwee!
What an idiot.
It was just a greeting!
Umm.... Did something happen?
Our village was attacked by
a headless demon.
It tore up the village....
I was scared out of my wits.
And you're sure that this
demon was headless?
Yes. It used to be the man-eating demon
who lived in the mountains.
We don't know who ripped
its head off,
but a number of villagers have
already been injured.
Leave it to us!
We shall exterminate
this demon!
You think it's wise to let that
monk handle this problem?
Just earlier, he flirted with our women.
I don't trust him.
Oh well, shall we go?
Inuyasha, please follow
the demon's scent.
I really don't need to....
It's pretty obvious
which way he went.
You're right.
And there it is!
That girl....is in danger!
- I must....do something!
- You fool! It's too dangerous!
Damn! Git outta here!
Stop!
Huh?
What're you doing?!
Please! Make him stop!
But why?
Huh?!
It's a baby raccoon dog!
That's my father!
Please don't hurt him!
- Hey raccoon dog!
- I'm an otter.
Whatever!
You sure don't look like
you're related!
Huh?! No, that's not my father!
I don't know how you can
make a mistake like that,
but you can explain after
I take care of this bastard!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
My name is Kanta.
As you can see, I'm a....
Raccoon dog!
I'm an otter!
Why did you take on the appearance
of a human girl?
Pa told me to.
He said if I disguise myself
as a human village girl
whenever I leave the mountain,
some idiot will always
come to my rescue.
Your father is very shrewd.
Earlier, you called that
demon "father."
Actually, inside this bundle
is Pa's head.
What?!
It happened three days ago....
Pa and I were catching fish
in the river.
You're fantastic, Pa!
It's easy once you get
the hang of it.
Wanna try it?
Yeah!
Huh?
You okay?
You have to be aware
of the depth.
Can't have an otter drowning
in a river.
'Kay, Pa!
Just then, a white child
riding a demon horse appeared.
Go and hide!
- Pa?
- Just go! Quickly!
Uh-huh....
Who are you?
Not from hereabouts.
Huh?
So, you dodged my first blow.
You brat! Don't underestimate me!
Hmph!
This will be more fun
than I expected.
Pa!
Kanta! Run!
With that life energy,
you'll last awhile.
Pa's head was carried away
by the current
and swallowed up
by a waterfall.
Damn! Oh well....
The child went away
after that,
but by the time I retrieved
Pa's head and returned,
his body was nowhere
to be found!
Use this....
Thanks.
So the one hunting down
all the demons....
Has to be Hakudoshi.
But for what purpose?
While in his infant stage,
Hakudoshi killed numerous
monks and shrine keepers.
In order to get a glimpse of the
border between this world and the next.
Maybe he's still trying
to do the same thing....
Using the demons....
That's right!
He looks into the human heart.
Sounds possible to me.
Unlike humans, demons
don't die easily.
So if you find your pa's body and
stick his head back on....
It may not be too late!
Ohh?
You mean he'll revive?
Your father must be
very robust.
Idiot!
But it's already been three days....
And if his body has been
exterminated, it'll be too late for him!
Don't despair!
Inuyasha will help you.
I'll what?
Inuyasha helped me avenge
my pa in the past, too.
Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha is very strong!
Shippo....
He's that strong?
Right!
He's so strong, it makes up
for the fact that
he's also stupid, childish
and eccentric.
I see....
So you lost your pa, too....
Let's be friends, raccoon dog!
I'm a fox!
- No, you're a raccoon dog.
- I'm a fox!
I'm sure it's over this way....
I sense a terrible
demonic aura approaching.
Shh! Quiet!
You'll let them know
where we are!
What?
You're asking me
what I'm doing?
Well, I guess I should tell you.
Actually, there are rumors of
stronger demons being stalked
and decapitated.
Small fry like you need not worry.
"Stronger" demons means
I, Chokyukai, will be targeted next.
Nah... nah...
Oh... there he is.
Damn!
Brat! I'll tear you to shreds!
Quiet!
Huh?
l-I'm not afraid, you know.
I may be heartless,
but I wouldn't pick a fight
with a kid like that.
Huh? Hmm?
How dare a mere horse....!
Entei's making a fuss.
Probably just some monkeys
or boars.
Hmm....
By the way, have you seen anything?
They're all basically the same.
A world of white mist...
And those things scattered
beneath the mist are...
Master Jaken....
What is it?
Where did Lord Sesshomaru go?
I have no idea.
He's never talkative
to begin with...
But since he failed to defeat
Naraku at Mt. Hakurei,
he's been even more silent.
Still, he could at least tell me
where he's going!
Master Jaken, when you sigh,
happiness runs away.
Here you are!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Tenseiga...
What is exciting you?
A demon!
A headless demon!
T-There it is!
- It's getting away!
- After him!
Huh?
Did you catch the scent
of Kanta's father?
Yeah.
R-Really?
But I also smell blood.
I wonder if someone
injured him?
Will we make it in time?!
Women and children, go inside!
The headless demon may return!
A headless demon?
Could it be Kanta's pa?
This is terrible!
If his body is exterminated,
he won't be able to resurrect!
Hurry, Inuyasha!
Yeah!
The scent isn't far!
But there's a troublesome guy
near Kanta's old man.
Huh?!
That's....!
Sesshomaru!
Why's he...!
Huh?
Pa!
Hang on, Pa!
Kanta, the head!
Okay!
It didn't work....
Pa!
Kanta....
Hey, Sesshomaru!
Why're you here?
I can't believe you're just
passing by.
I don't owe you any
explanations.
Please wait, Sesshomaru!
Your sword....
Tenseiga is the sword
that brings back life.
Please....
Use Tenseiga....
to bring his father back....
This has nothing to do with me.
Pa!
Umm....
C-Can you save him?
Shippo....
lf... lf his pa dies....
Kanta will be all alone.
Move.
Please!
I beg you!
Please!!
Shippo....
But....!
It's useless, Shippo.
It's too bad....
But Sesshomaru isn't the
type to come to anyone's aid.
And besides, that Tenseiga....
isn't something Sesshomaru
can use.
That's true.
Unless its bearer has a caring heart,
Tenseiga cannot be wielded.
Precisely.
Tenseiga is stirring...
Is it telling me to save
that demon?
Why?
Huh? Sesshomaru...!
Move!
I can see...
the messengers
of the afterlife.
He cut something!
Huh?!
P-Pa....
Pa!
Pa! Pa!
I'm so glad!
I'm so glad for you!
Geez! I thought I'd never
be able to come back.
Umm.... Where were you?
Hmm.... A very strange place.
A world shrouded in white mist.
I was flying through this world
with only my head.
And I noticed numerous other
demon heads
all with terrible expressions
on their faces.
Demons who were beheaded
by Hakudoshi.
And when I dove under the mist....
there were giant bones.
Giant bones?
Yes, there was a giant skeleton
clad in magnificent armor.
And there were lots of other
skeletons, too.
I guess that's the world of
the afterlife.
Pa....
T-Thank you so much
for saving me.
Umm....Sesshomaru,
thank-
He left.
What was Tenseiga
trying to tell me?
Is it telling me to remember?
That it involves that place...?
Take care, Shippo.
Yeah. I'm glad it all worked out.
It's all because of you.
I'll never forget you.
Me neither.
Be happy with your pa.
Thanks for everything, boy.
Sure! You take care, Pa!
Shippo... is remembering
his father.
That place that Kanta's father
saw....
I wonder if Hakudoshi
already knows about it?
Yeah.
But where is this place
that's covered in white mist
and strewn with giant bones?
I may've been there once.
What?!
So you remember something
about it?
Yeah....
Inuyasha is thinking the same thing.
White mist and giant bones...
The border between this world
and the next...
The grave of Inuyasha's father...
The Sacred Jewel shard can be found
by Inuyasha's father's grave
at the border between
this life and the next.
Hah! He wants me to
visit his grave?
But the black pearl which is the
entrance to the grave
has already allowed us entry before
and fulfilled its purpose.
Isn't there any other way in?
What? A guy named Hosenki who
cultivates jewels knows the way?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Hosenki and the Last Shard!"
I'll get it by force if I have to!