Gathering shards of the Sacred Jewel,
we continue our journey to
battle our arch-enemy Naraku.
Inuyasha is so dense,
he hasn't noticed...
but it seems that Miroku the monk
and Sango the Demon Slayer
have feelings for each other.
However, they're both hesitant
about declaring their feelings
and the relationship hasn't
progressed at all.
There it is!
The beast!
Get it!
Shoot!
There's no other way.
But my young lord,
what about the other personage?
Stop whining!
Leave no stone unturned!
Find it!
Yes sire!
Damn!
You should use an umbrella, too,
Inuyasha.
Only kids and women use
that stuff!
Cling to pride and
you'll catch cold.
Hah! I'm not such a weakling!
You just don't understand.
Understand what?
Umbrellas are useful for
a number of reasons.
Like what?
Well...
What's the matter?
Something's coming.
I don't feel a demonic aura.
I think they're...
Humans.
Yeah... and a lot of 'em.
Are you Sango the Demon Slayer
and her travel party?
Huh?
Yes, we are they.
I am Takeda Clan vassal
Miwanosuke Asahi.
We have come to speak
to Sango.
Huh?
We have to request that you
destroy a demon
that has plagued our castle
night after night.
We will not question
your methods.
Minor damages to the castle
will be tolerated.
Here is an advance.
After the beast is destroyed,
you will receive an amount
equal to this.
What do you say?
It is not a bad offer?
It's way too much.
Ten times... Twenty times
what is normally charged.
Then you'll agree?
The terms are too good.
I'm sorry, but I must...
You cannot refuse!
It's been a long time, Sango.
Huh?
Who are you?
Sango, you don't remember?
You seem to have totally forgotten.
Uh-huh...
Well, I don't blame her
for not remembering.
It was a long time ago.
But we mustn't talk here.
Come to the castle.
W-What is this?
Wow! Amazing!
What a fine castle!
Pardon the late introduction.
I am Kuranosuke Takeda,
lord of this castle.
A clan lord?
No wonder he acts pompous.
Kuranosuke Takeda...
Oh, that time...
the runny-nosed kid!
I mean... Young lord.
So you remember.
Yes, it was six years ago.
My castle had been plagued
by a demon
and we had hired your group
to slay it.
Hah!
It was a magnificent sight.
Like a single lily in the
bloody battlefield.
You were so awe-inspiring!
Awe-inspiring?
Oh, let me come to the point!
Sango! Destroy the beast,
then marry me!
What?! This is so sudden!
I had decided the moment
I saw you.
The one who will become
my wife... is you, Sango, and only you!
Err... I...
I hope you will accept.
Men! Prepare rooms
for the guests!
Yes, sire!
What's happening anyway?
Huh?
It can't be helped.
Sango is a candidate
to become a lord's bride.
What'll I do?
How do I refuse?
Err... Miroku...
Will you bear my child?
Huh?
Surely you jest, Master Monk!
No, no.
It's no joke.
What a fool!
That man is so maddening!
Goodness! There was no need
to slap me.
You didn't have to flirt with
a girl like that!
Sango was so angry.
Miroku flirts all the time.
What's the big deal?
You don't understand a thing,
Inuyasha!
Understand what?
Sango wants Miroku to
stop her!
Stop what?!
He is so dense!
But this may be
just the chance!
Miroku has to be
concerned about Sango.
So if I just give him
a little push...
W-What's the matter?
I wonder...
And now that's decided...
Let's go for it!
Miroku, come with me!
Aghh! Kagome,
what's going on?!
Just come!
I have to be strong.
Okay.
What is the matter?
Must you ask?!
Do you realize Sango
might get married?
And what of it?
What of it?!
Is that all right with you?
Well... It's something
Sango must decide.
It's none of our business.
I guess.
After all, any woman would
do for you.
You... without fortune, home,
or status...
just a flirtatious, itinerant monk!
On the other hand, a clan lord who
is young, handsome and rich.
Earnest and focused and
unlikely to stray...
He's a huge catch!
I guess there's absolutely
no question who's better.
W-What? Well?
Are you nervous?
Is that all you want to say?
Huh?
Then I must go.
I want to check something.
Wait, Miroku!
Huh?
I knew it... You are concerned,
after all.
Oh, Miroku!
Why can't you come clean?
Actually, your sudden appearance
is what scared me.
What'll I do?
I don't want to hurt him.
How can I show her
how I feel?
Sango...
Yes, my lord?
Don't call me "lord."
Just call me Kuranosuke.
You can even call me
Runny-Nose.
Just jesting.
I... I really...
Sango...
You know the kind of
world we live in.
There are few I can trust.
Evil demons abound in
mountains and rivers.
And mortals resort to trickery
and betrayal.
We call this the world
above hell,
but I am not satisfied with
how things are.
That is why...
I swore that at least the woman
I spend my life with
will be someone I love.
Why did you choose me?
I AM the lord of a clan.
I know I am a good judge
of people.
Sango, I love you.
Thank you.
I'm happy to hear that.
Huh?
Miroku!
Then you will marry me?
No, I cannot.
Why is that?
There is something
I must do.
It will probably be very
difficult to accomplish.
However...
I must do this or I cannot
go forward in life.
That's why I must
continue my journey.
Please! You must find
someone more suitable!
Who do you think I am?
I have waited six years.
It matters not how many more
years I must wait.
Huh?
Sango, I understand how
you feel.
I will wait forever.
Err... no... but...
If you are ever in trouble,
come to me without hesitation.
I will do everything
in my power to help.
Wait, Miroku!
Why let her go?!
Sango is!
If I'm truly concerned about
Sango's happiness,
it's best that I let
her be.
Huh?
Her fate was shattered
by the evil Naraku
and she continues to fight.
Now she has a chance to
marry Lord Takeda and settle down.
Which will bring her happiness?
There's no need to even think
about it.
But!
Kagome, you will
understand someday, too.
Then what about Sango's feelings?!
Huh?
Be happy.
Huh?!
The demon!
So he's come!
Inuyasha!
You're late!
Still, it'll all be over
with a swing of my sword.
I'll do it!
You stay out of this, Inuyasha!
Why?!
I can handle this small fry!
This is my job!
Besides... I'm in a real bad mood,
right now!
Okay...
Did you say something to her,
Miroku?!
Huh? No... I...
Take this!
And this!
I've never seen Sango
looking so fierce.
Yeah... No one in this world
could take her on at this moment.
Don't come crying to me!
Ohh!
This is the finishing blow...
Hiraikotsu!
You did it, Sango!
Miroku!
You miscalculated, Sango.
I realized it after watching
you fight.
This demon is actually
a vengeful spirit.
It cannot be destroyed
the usual way.
Evil spirit exorcism!
Bear ornaments?
Then these bears' vengeful spirit?
No, that's not it.
Look at that.
A bear pelt?
That's the demon we exterminated
six years ago.
But we instructed the clan
to offer prayers,
then bury it in the ground.
I can explain.
We were following your
instructions...
and were about to bury it
when we were stopped
by the late lord.
Instead, in accordance
with his orders,
wood carvings were made and
designated clan treasures
to use as a way to restore
the clan's finances.
Furthermore, big-bear bean jam cakes,
big-bear towels and
big-bear coins were marketed.
But they didn't sell.
Yes... Well...
Kuranosuke...
Never mind. Say no more.
I understand well
how you feel.
Go. Your friends await.
Yes.
Sango, I haven't given up yet.
Miroku, what happened
to that hat?
Well, the strap broke.
Thank you.
Is your wound okay?
Yes.
Um... Miroku...
I'm glad.
Huh?
That we can continue
our journey together.
What are you smiling about?
Isn't it useful?
Thanks to that umbrella, those two
look pretty happy together.
Say, Inuyasha.
Do you know janken?
The one who's always
sticking around Sesshomaru.
That's Jaken. I meant
rock-paper-scissors!
Here we go,
jan, ken, scissors! ...I win!
Strange things're happening today.
Rock-paper-scissors!
I win again!
Wind Tunnel!
Isn't that Jaken?
Is he after the Tetsusaiga?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Jaken's Plan to Steal the Tetsusaiga"
Never Jaken...
just rock-paper-scissors!
No!