All right! I'm off!
Okay! Hurry back!
And don't forget
the ninja treats.
Did you see Inuyasha?
Inuyasha left on Kirara
early in the morning.
I think he went quite far.
Uh-huh... there's one place
I can think of.
Where?
The only one who knows
Tetsusaiga's true power
is the one who forged it.
You mean, Old Totosai?
He really intends to
break through Naraku's barrier.
To that old man's place?
Totosai!
You would know a way to
break through any barrier...
however strong it is.
However strong, huh?
It's not like there isn't a way...
Or that there is a way.
Which is it?!
I have to get stronger when
Naraku's out of commission!
Oh, it itches!
That's right.
I haven't bathed in a week.
Totosai! I doubt he's gonna
tell me so easily.
I have to be patient and
coax it outta him.
Please!
Oh... it itches!
My back, too.
Totosai! I know it's difficult!
But I need you to teach me
how to break the barrier!
Boy, I need... I need a bath!
Isn't there some way
I can train?!
A bath... in order to
get a bath ready...
Oh, I have to get the water.
Get water?
But that's so hard.
To haul enough water from the river
at the bottom of the valley
to fill the tub.
Then cut all the wood out back
into firewood.
Such humbug.
Getting a bath for one as old as I
is such a chore.
Cutting wood?
Is that training?
Training?
Master!
Huh?!
Oh, you're here again.
Master, I will not
go away today.
Who's this fox demon?
Wrong! I'm a Lynx Demon.
I've asked Master Totosai
to train me.
Train?
I want Master Totosai to train me
so I can break the barrier.
Err...
I'm itchy.
I can use them.
Ahem! You two...
I want you to fetch some water
and cut some wood.
I knew it!
That's special training!
You know nothing!
Fetching water builds up
essential muscles.
And cutting wood improves
your fighting posture.
And heating the bath water
builds up your lungs.
Every task has a meaning.
Pa told me that's been the
tradition on the continent
for four thousand years.
I see!
So you're willing to teach me
how to break the barrier!
No, l just wanted to...
Take a bath...
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Totosai, I guess
you need strength
to learn this special
technique, huh?
All right, then.
I'll stay and train.
Wait a minute!
I've been staying in that hut
over yonder for ten days!
I'm the senior apprentice!
Senior apprentice?
Don't you know?
In the human world, there's an
apprenticeship system!
The one who came first
is the senior apprentice.
Don't dawdle and follow me!
What?!
Hurry! Junior apprentice!
Hah! Ridiculous!
Hurry and follow me!
Shaddup! I'm coming!
They're under the wrong
impression...
But I think I'm going to
get my bath.
I left without saying a word
to Kagome and the others.
It's gonna take more time
than I expected.
Hey Meow!
That's impossible for you.
I'm not "Meow"! I'm Bunza!
Okay then, Bunza.
Don't overdo it.
Shut up!
I'm gonna train harder
than you,
and have the Master teach
me the method first!
What's with you?
Why do you need to learn
the method so badly?
Cripes!
Hey lemme go!
I said lemme go, Junior!
This isn't training!
Lemme go!
Just lemme go!
Are you listening?!
I said don't overdo it!
But I must learn the technique!
Watch out, fool!
You rest!
That's not training.
Damn! You're such a handful!
You're burning up!
What? You haven't even eaten?
S-Sorry...
And you've stayed here in this
hut for ten days?
No wonder you got sick.
I m-must train and learn
the technique to break the barrier.
First, get well.
I'll bring you something
good to eat later.
Why?
Why are you so kind?
Well... there's a kid about your age
among my companions.
What's the matter, Shippo?
I think I caught a cold.
Maybe someone's gossiping
about you.
This is great for
building up the lungs.
Hmm... such a nice bath!
Hey! Tell me if there's any
other way to train!
I'll do anything if it's to
master the technique.
Train?
Hey, you!
Huh?
Is it true that you're making
Inuyasha train?
Well, actually...
I wanted to take a bath.
When one is old, fetching water
is so difficult.
When I mentioned it, before I knew it,
he decided it was training!
He's the one who jumped to
the wrong conclusions.
I've never seen Inuyasha
looking so earnest.
If he learns the truth,
I fear what will happen!
What?!
All you wanted was bath water?!
How frightening!
It's making me shiver with fear!
Oh... I'm getting chicken skin.
Huh?
I came to wash your back.
If you're cold, I'd better
burn more wood.
Here, have mine.
You sure?
You're sick.
Don't question!
Sorry.
Why do you want to train?
Well, you don't have to
talk if you don't feel like it.
A demon named Nanafushi took
over the mountain where we,
the Lynx Demon tribe, lived.
And he built a barrier around it.
We weren't able to go into the
mountain, couldn't gather food...
our entire lives were disrupted.
According to Pa,
who's the tribe leader,
only Totosai can make a weapon
that would break the barrier.
And Totosai would know
a special technique.
But Totosai is an old eccentric,
who refuses to teach
just anyone.
The members of the tribe are beginning
to turn their backs on Pa.
I... I'm so mad!
I want everyone to recognize
Pa as their leader once more!
For Pa's sake, I must learn
and master the technique!
That's!
Torako!
Is that you, Torako?
Why've you come here?
What?!
Huh? What's wrong, Bunza?
Pa went to get Nanafushi!
He went inside the barrier
to take back the mountain...
even if he doesn't know
the technique!
Bunza!
Pa! Pa!
Huh?
I sensed something just now...
Sensed something?
Hey! Did Bunza come
this way?
Huh? Oh, that may've been
Bunza just now.
Which way'd he go?
Atta way.
That Bunza!
I'm not itchy at all.
Is it this way, Torako?
There!
Bunza!
Inuyasha?
We'll go together!
I'll help.
I refuse!
Why?
He's my Pa!
I'll rescue him myself.
It's got nothing to do with you.
You're under no obligation to help.
Cut it out!
Didn't you say we were
brother apprentices?!
The senior apprentice
and the junior.
Isn't that connection enough
to help?
Well, ain't it?!
Pa!
Wait!
Your Pa's inside the barrier!
Huh? You're right!
But how'd he get inside
the barrier?
Nanafushi opened the barrier
so he could kill Pa!
Pa knew it was a trap!
Still, in order to save
the others...
He chose to fight as the leader
of the Lynx tribe!
Wait!
I'll go.
He's my father! It's a son's duty
to save his father!
Then I'm coming along as
your junior!
That okay, senior?
Yeah... Brother.
Your father's okay. We made it
in time to save him.
Hey!
Don't be hasty!
It didn't work!
It didn't work at all.
I'm no good!
No such thing.
Your attack has Nanafushi scared.
It's him!
He's coming!
Quit hiding and
come on out!
Awright... perfect.
Taking up the safe spot
all for yourself.
You've got some nerve!
Wow!
It was a short time,
but I'll see what my training
with Totosai yields.
My training with you.
Although it was for
just a day.
But I'll put it all
into this sword!
Do it, Brother!
Gotcha!
Wind... Scar!
You did it!
Oh-oh-oh!
Why, you!
Not giving up?
That's fun.
Take this!
Amazing!
It... it was Master Totosai's
training, after all.
I guess!
I kinda feel like I'm stronger
than before.
Keep up with your training!
Yeah! You too.
You've saved your Pa. Now train
to become the leader of your tribe!
We'll meet again, won't we?
Yeah!
Come see us... Brother!
Oh, Inuyasha? Where've you been?
Well... just out.
But listen, your training worked.
I'm stronger.
Huh?
Sorry... I made you do those things.
Those things?
Hmm... It's hard to say...
But you mistakenly thought that
you would become stronger.
And if you had gone in search
of Naraku's barrier,
you may've been in
grave danger...
And so, that's...
So what?
Well, there's no way you've
gotten stronger...
T-Then the training?!
l just wanted to take a bath.
Huh?
Yes, yes! You jumped to
conclusions yet again.
Yes. You see, I haven't
bathed in a while...
Eek!
What?!
There's no technique to break
Naraku's barrier?
Well, it's not as though
there isn't...
And it's not as though
there is...
He's so useless!
I was just going to tell him!
He's so rash!
What do you mean?
Well, he had labored
hard and persevered.
I thought I'd teach him
the method
to become stronger to enable
him to break the barrier.
Is it THAT method?
Uh-huh. Can you tell
Inuyasha about it?
All right.
Still...
Be thankful you ended up
with just one lump on your head.
I was away a whole night
without telling them.
I guess everyone's worried.
Hey! I'm back.
Sorry I worried you.
Ninja food is always
so delicious!
This flavor, we just can't
duplicate it.
Where's mine?!
You weren't here,
so I ate them.
What?!
That's mine!
Inuyasha!
Sit!
Cripes! I brought you
special treats.
It's your fault for
not being here!
Why, you!
Can't you be more concerned?!
You're so hopeless.
I'll share just a little.
Shaddup!
It controls the seas and
hunts down humans and demons.
That's the Demon Bat?
Yes... and if he destroys it,
Tetsusaiga will gain the power
to break the barrier.
But there's a problem.
A half-demon, one just like
Master Inuyasha, protects the barrier.
But she's a girl... so I don't know if
Inuyasha can willingly kill her.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Shiori's Family and Inuyasha's Feelings"
Aah, a bath feels nice after all...