Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
At the border between this world
and the next, the shard sleeps.
At its only entrance, the Gate to the
Land of Fire,
giant sentries stand guard.
And even here,
Naraku's trap awaits us.
The spot where Inuyasha
and I first met...
Although that was actually during
the Feudal Age.
The Sacred Tree!
I'm so glad!
This must be close to home.
A....boy.
And it all began right here.
You have it, don't you?
You must have it....
Let me go, you disgusting thing!
Give me the Sacred Jewel!
Can't you even handle a weak
thing like the Centipede Demon?
You....just spoke!
You're alive?
Let....go....of....me!
Owweee!
Let go of ME!
- Hand it over!
- Let go!
Hey!
Can you pull out this arrow?
Huh?
I'm asking if you can pull out
this arrow!
I... I don't understand a thing
that's happening!
But I don't...
want to die!
You brat!
Shut up, old hag!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
If I hadn't been attacked
by that demon...
If I hadn't met Inuyasha
on that day...
I wouldn't have to stress
out during tests,
and Grandpa wouldn't have to
agonize over my feigned illnesses.
Sis, you're up early.
Yeah, I had something to do.
Before, she'd still be dead to the world.
Mom, is my lunch ready?
Yes, all done.
Thank you!
No problem.
Oh, Kagome....
Don't forget to ask everyone
how it all tasted, okay?
Sure.
Junior high students have it tough
enough with just their studies.
Hey, Kagome!
Huh?
Morning, Inuyasha!
Get with it! Let's go!
Okay.
Again today, I'm setting out
into the Feudal Age.
And again today...
Kagome! Welcome back!
I'm back!
Hey! Inuyasha! Hurry it up!
I'll do my best again to
find the Sacred Jewel shard
and continue our journey!
Have you noticed, Inuyasha?
Yeah.
Saimyosho are watching us.
Hah!
Just making sure that we're
heading towards the Realm of Fire.
Old Myoga, are you sure you
don't know
any other way to get there?
I do not know any other way
to get to the grave.
Wanna know....
where the entrance is?
Kagura?!
Hakudoshi is headed towards
the Mountain in the Realm of Fire.
There's supposed to be a gate there
that leads to the border between
this world and the next.
The Mountain in the Realm of Fire?
What is the meaning of this, Kagura?
Why have you come to
tell us this?
Well....
You'd have to ask Hakudoshi that.
It seems the Saimyosho plan to
lead us to the gate.
Yes, but if they've come to
show us the way....
Perhaps it means that Hakudoshi
doesn't have the power
to pass through the gate on his own.
If we're talking about the usual Naraku,
I'm sure he has something
up his sleeves.
But this is Hakudoshi, not Naraku.
Yes, Hakudoshi....who was created
by Naraku.
Geez! Who cares which it is!
All we have to do is get there first
and get a hold of the Sacred Jewel
shard that's at the border.
Such a simpleton.
And that's just like Inuyasha.
Inuyasha....
So this is the Realm of Fire?
Yes....
And it certainly looks
like the land of fire.
Those are....?
They're luring us.
Let's go after 'em!
Hachi, go down.
It's underground.
It's kinda creepy.
Uh-huh....
Hah, really feels like
the entrance to a grave.
Let's go.
Miroku....
Let us go.
Kagura, Inuyasha and his friends
made it to the gate.
You sure about letting them
go in first?
Isn't the Sacred Jewel shard
on the other side of that gate?
Of course, we'll get the shard first.
In order to do that, Kagura,
you'll have to do your job.
Humph.... So you want the last laugh, huh?
You're just like Naraku.
Hmmm....
It's huge.
Well, there must be
a huge gate in here.
K-Kagome....
What's wrong, Shippo?
D-Don't those rocks look
like the faces of demons?
You're right.
And they seem to be
increasing as we proceed....
Maybe they're just paving
stones to the gate.
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Look over there!
Hah! I think we've finally
made it.
This is....
There really is a gate.
So nice and simple.
And there aren't any guards around.
Everyone, get back.
I'll break apart the gate
with my Wind Scar.
You want to pass?
Huh?
l-Is someone there?
Answer! Do you want to pass?
Or not?
What was that?
You must not answer, Master Inuyasha!
Myoga?
So you followed us, Old Myoga?
I thought he ran away
a long time ago.
And so I shall after this!
It's not too late.
Turn back!
What are you babbling about?
Do you want to pass?
Or not?
'Course I want to pass!
That's why I came all the way here!
N-No, Master Inuyasha!
Then you may pass.
T-The stone statues....!
W-Wha...!
They are Gozu and Mezu,
the guards of this gate!
They weren't just stone decorations?
Only the dead can pass through
these gates.
We make certain all those who wish
to pass are dead.
So you won't let us pass
unless we die?
Now we know why Hakudoshi
lured us here!
Although....
That won't make me
turn back!
These guys are big, but
that makes 'em slow!
Wind Scar!
Did he succeed?
W-Wha...!
My Wind Scar didn't work!
It's useless.
We cannot be slain by
blades of this world.
Cannot be slain by
"blades of this world"?
That is because Gozu and Mezu
are not of this world.
Tetsusaiga is a sword that slays
demons of this world.
But it won't hurt Gozu or Mezu.
T-Then what are we going to do?!
Inuyasha is going to get killed!
She's right!
Isn't there a way to
stop Gozu and Mezu?
Once Gozu and Mezu
are awakened,
they will not become dormant until
the gate has been opened, then closed.
To be it bluntly, until Master Inuyasha
has passed through the gate as the dead.
T-That's crazy!
Pass....
After you die.
There's no point unless
I'm alive!
In order to pass through the gate
at the border of this world and the next,
one must battle the guards,
Gozu and Mezu.
Right now, Inuyasha should be
fighting them in my place.
Soon, the gate will open....
In whatever way.
Only the dead can pass
through this gate.
So die by our hands.
Hah! Are those the only
words you can speak?
Not even a crack!
Inuyasha!
We told you.
Swords of this world
will not harm us.
Inuyasha!
If swords won't work,
how about this?!
Wind Tunnel!
Do you want to pass through, too?
Wind Tunnel doesn't work either!
H-How can that be?!
Miroku! Hold that Wind Tunnel open!
He did it!
Inuyasha!
I just tripped 'em....
I'm all right!
Dammit!
Even after using the Wind Tunnel
to increase my speed,
it didn't faze 'em.
Master Inuyasha!
Myoga?
You're still here?
How can you say such a thing?
When I've stayed here without
running away!
'Kay, I get it!
So hurry and speak up!
Oh, yes....
Anyway, you just have to return
Mezu and Gozu to stone.
Huh?
Gozu and Mezu will return to stone
after the gate has opened and closed.
So aim for the chains holding
the gate shut with your Wind Scar.
And now, I shall take my leave!
Huh?
He's running away, after all!
Old Myoga is right, though.
If I blast those chains apart
and open the gate,
it'll be like killing two birds
with one stone!
My red Tetsusaiga
that breaks through barriers!
Awright!
Now go!
He did it!
Good job, Inuyasha.
I'm going on ahead.
Kagura, why you...!
Stop!
It opened!
Huh?!
Kagura, why you...!
Stop!
It opened!
Huh?!
Wha...?!
What's this?!
The demons have
become petrified....
T-They couldn't be....!
Hide or we'll turn to stone!
Inuyasha!
Hide!
There! Beyond the gate!
Do you want to pass?
Or not?
Dammit!
Who'd want to pass, idiot?!
Then....
We shall close the gate.
Are you all right, Kagome?
Uh-huh....
They've turned to stone again.
Where's Kagura?
It seems she ran away.
I wonder if Hakudoshi
knew about this?
That one turns to stone
once you pass the gate.
He was testing it....
by using us and Kagura.
Hakudoshi....you....!
What's the matter, Kagura?
You could care less if I died.
I heard that the living cannot
pass through the gate.
But I didn't know exactly
what that meant.
Don't mess around with me,
you brat!
Are you in pain?
Naraku just grasped your heart....
from somewhere.
Just remember this, Kagura.
Naraku and I are connected.
So think before you act
next time.
Although....
I'd never be killed
by the likes of you.
Is that true, Kagome?
I'm sure of it.
When the gate opened,
I sensed the presence of
the Sacred Jewel shard.
So it's there....
Somewhere over in that world....
the Sacred Jewel shard.
While we are in the Realm of Fire,
demons wreak havoc.
Someone is using birds
to attack people.
Are you another one
of Naraku's incarnations?!
The Saimyosho are proof!
I don't like to fight women,
but you're just too evil!
She seems to have something
to do with Naraku....
but I don't think she's
his slave.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Fiery Bird Master, Princess Abi"
Impossible!
She countered the Wind Scar!