I was so worried...
I thought you weren't coming
back anymore, Kagome.
I'm sorry, Shippo.
Hey you, Inuyasha!
Did you ask Kagome for forgiveness?!
Shaddup!
I wonder how those two made up?
Well... probably Kagome gave in.
What?!
You mean, she forgave Inuyasha's
indiscretion with Kikyo?
I can't believe it!
How can she endure it?
Inuyasha was quite depressed about it.
I guess she didn't want
to back him into a corner.
Well, he's usually in some tight spot.
What're you looking at?!
He seems to be repenting just a bit.
This is where Naraku's castle
used to be?
Traces of Naraku's miasma still remain.
So there's no mistake.
But... there's nary
a hint of the remains.
Was Naraku's castle really here?
You're right.
When you think about it, we've been
lured to a fake castle before.
Was what we saw just an illusion?
No, you're wrong.
Huh?
Sango!
There's no mistake.
Naraku's castle was here.
Huh? Sango, what's?
What's up? Found something?
My father's armor.
That day, we slayers were
lured to Naraku's castle.
Hiraikotsu!
Me, too!
And my father
and all the others were slain.
They were killed by
my younger brother, Kohaku.
His mind was being
controlled by Naraku.
Huh?!
Sister!
Kohaku!
Their bodies were buried
in the corner of the courtyard.
So this is...
Sango...
Miroku?
We must not leave your father
and the others in this tainted ground.
Miroku...
We will find another burial ground
for them and offer prayers.
Is that all right?
Yes, thank you.
Miroku.
So this is where Naraku's castle was...
But what of its occupants?
Sango's brother, Kohaku...
who was controlled by Naraku.
Did he perish with the castle?
Here, at least, wild dogs
won't dig up their graves.
Let this be
your resting place for now.
Someday, I promise to erect
proper graves for you in our village.
The village is abandoned now.
But Kohaku and I are still alive.
If we both watch over the graves...
But Kohaku is...
Here!
Ohh!
Kid, you're pretty good!
You're amazing!
I'll say!
You've totally entertained us.
On top of which,
you helped cut firewood.
Nothing to it!
You must be tired.
Come inside and rest.
Thanks.
Well? Did you remember anything?
Uh-uh... I don't know.
Where'd you come from?
Or at least your name?
Maybe, you...
used to live close to the castle?
Castle?
About ten days ago...
Lord Hitomi's castle
suddenly disappeared into thin air.
And we found you unconscious
the next day.
Maybe something terribly
frightening happened to you...
and you lost your memory.
Well, never mind.
No need to rush.
Yes, yes. Just stay as long
as you like, until you remember.
Look, there's lot more. Eat up.
Thank you.
Castle...
Yes, the castle.
I have a feeling I was there.
Huh?
Huh?!
Gramps! Granny!
Huh?
I have to go!
Go where?
I can't stay here!
It's dangerous, so don't go out!
Thanks for everything!
- Hey!
- Hey you!
That's it! I remember!
I ran away from the castle!
That night...
when the castle disappeared...
Kohaku, keeping you alive
is no longer necessary.
You can join your father
and the others.
Kohaku?
My name is Kohaku?
What's the matter, Kirara?
Demons nearby?
I sense a Sacred Jewel fragment!
What?!
Kagome, this way?!
It's near! Beyond this forest!
Naraku's poison insects!
Damn! So are they after the
Sacred Jewel fragment, too?!
Kohaku, you can't get away!
Huh!
Now, obey and return the Sacred
Jewel fragment in your back.
Sacred Jewel fragment?
Hand over the fragment!
Die!
Kohaku!
That demon is trying to get
the fragment in Kohaku's back!
What?!
The Sacred Jewel fragment
in Kohaku's back...
is his lifeline.
If the fragment is removed, he'll die!
Kohaku!
You were under Naraku's mind control...
and you were in Naraku's castle.
So why are you... ?
You... know me?
Huh?
You've hurt your arm. Let me see.
Ah...
Hmm?
Have we met before?
Uh-huh.
Kohaku... You really
don't remember anything about...
before you escaped from the castle?
No... I'm sorry.
Even about Naraku?
Naraku?
Kohaku...
Keeping you alive
is no longer necessary.
Join your father and the others.
Could that have been...Naraku?
I don't like it!
That kid is just putting on an act.
It doesn't look it.
You trust him?
No!
But the Kohaku
who appeared before us that time...
was like a puppet...
a human without a soul.
But now...
Huh?
Is it safe to leave them alone?
Sango wanted it that way.
The slayers' village?
Yes... that's where we used to live.
Then was I also a demon slayer?
You were an apprentice.
Rest a bit.
We have lots of work ahead.
All right.
Kohaku, be prepared, too.
Huh? Me?
You're eleven years old.
It's time you got some
real experience.
Uh-huh...
Sister...
Huh?
Do demons really spit fire
and poison?
Sometimes.
I see...
Kohaku, are you afraid?
N- no such thing! But...
Don't worry.
We only slay oversized
snakes and spiders.
Father always says...
the demons to fear most
are the ones pretending to be humans.
If such demons
get ahold of Sacred Jewel...
it'll be terrible.
Hmm...
And then that day
when we were summoned by Naraku...
that was Kohaku's
very first battle experience.
Say...
Tell me everything you know.
Huh?
I feel so empty...
I don't know why I'm like this.
He's just like the Kohaku of old.
Quiet...and a bit cowardly.
Huh?
Just try to remember little by little.
We'll be together from now on.
Huh? Ah...
Hmm?
This is embarrassing...
What're you so shy for?
We're siblings.
Kohaku has come back to me.
He's escaped from Naraku's grasp...
That's what I want to believe.
Give 'im a couple of knocks
and he'll show his real self!
Inuyasha, you!
It's not that simple.
Whether it's a trap or not,
her dear brother is back.
Yes... if this is a trap,
Sango will be so hurt.
Naraku loves to play
with people's feelings.
Inuyasha?
If you won't tell her, I will!
W-wait! Stop, Inuyasha!
What's the matter?
Say...
About Kohaku...
This has to be Naraku's trap!
I believe in Kohaku!
That's Naraku's aim.
What else can I do
except to trust him?!
It's a trick Naraku is likely to use!
If we hadn't come to his aid...
his Sacred Jewel fragment
would have been removed...
and he would really have died!
Listen... that's the trap!
It's not a trap!
I feel as though that kind woman will
become unhappy...all because of me.
I must not stay here.
You're being blinded by love
for your kid brother!
Shut up! What would you know?!
Open your eyes!
Farewell...
Inuyasha, you!
Shh!
They're coming...
A huge number of them!
Naraku's poison insects!
His advance guard.
They're... not after Kohaku?!
Sango, you!
Kohaku!
Sango, I sense
the Sacred Jewel fragment moving.
Let's go, Sango!
We must protect Kohaku!
Uh-huh!
Kagura! Whaddya want?!
You're hiding Kohaku, aren't you?
Let me have him.
What?!
Don't act innocent!
The kid Naraku's kept.
Kohaku ran off
amidst the confusion...
with the Sacred Jewel fragment
in his back.
And that's why you've come for him?
Naraku always goes overboard.
Just because he wants the fragment...
he sends out this army.
So you're after
the Sacred Jewel fragment?
Yes... although once that's removed,
Kohaku will die.
We're under orders
to let Sango have him after that.
W-why... you!
You're okay!
Why?
Why did you come?!
They're after me!
Huh?
Kohaku!
Don't go anywhere anymore.
Why?
Why go through all this for me?
You're my... brother.
You're my one and only little brother.
Kirara!
Kagome, watch Kohaku.
I'll stop those demons!
All right!
Kirara!
Kohaku! You must live!
Let's go!
Uh!
- If this keeps up...
- Don't worry!
I'm out of arrows.
We'll hide in that hole.
We'll wait until Inuyasha comes.
That woman...
Huh?
I wonder if she's all right.
Oh... Sango is really strong.
Don't worry about her.
Kohaku... You still don't remember?
That Sango is your older sister?
No...
But she... She seems so familiar.
Sango had always worried about you
while you two were apart.
She's always so cheerful...
but once in a while,
she looks very sad.
So I'm glad that you've returned.
Is it... Is it okay to stay with her?
Of course!
Then you'll start to remember
about Sango.
Uh-huh...
I want to remember...
about her and everything else.
But...what's this feeling?
I feel scared...
something I don't want to remember...
Kill her... Kill Kagome.
Inuyasha... He's so late.
You're all out of Sacred Arrows.
Huh?
Kohaku!
Kohaku, who has lost his memory,
is still being controlled by Naraku!
He is about to carry out
Naraku's order: "Kill Kagome!"
Sango finds out and resolves to
kill Kohaku, then herself.
Miroku realizes the trap
and uses his Wind Tunnel...
to suck in the demons,
poison insects and all!
Hurry, Inuyasha!
You must stop Sango!
Next on Inuyasha:
"That Unforgettable Face!"
Don't miss it!