I have to rescue Kagome!
So don't bother me
at a time like this!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
This woman is off limits!
I'll kill anyone who tries
to take a bite outta her!
Whoa... Scary!
Koga of the Wolf-Demon Tribe.
With Sacred Jewel fragments
in his right arm and both his legs...
he battles Inuyasha
with amazing speed.
The Wolf-Demon Tribe is fighting
the Birds of Paradise...
and are planning to steal
Sacred Jewel fragments...
which the Birds of Paradise
have in their possession.
I was kidnapped because
I'm able to see the Sacred Jewel.
But if this goes on...
some day,
both Shippo and I will be eaten.
If I could only help Shippo escape.
Huh? Shippo?
Stand!
Stand up please.
I mean, stand!
Hey, Koga. Where're you going?
I'm taking the woman out
for some fresh air.
This place smells like animals.
Wow! Great acting!
Hey, Ginta! Hakkaku!
Accompany Koga.
What're you saying?
Ginta and Hakkaku
went out on patrol.
With Koga.
What?!
Then who was...?!
Hey you!
You fooled us!
Shippo, hurry!
Hold it!
Ohh! We're trapped, Kagome!
Shippo, you can expand and fly,
can't you?
Yes, but I don't know
if I can fly with you!
You won't get away!
Shippo! Get Inuyasha! Hurry!
Tricky woman!
I'll devour you alive!
W-who did that?!
Hey! What did I say about eating her?!
Koga!
Koga, the little kid is way over there!
Let us go after him, Koga!
Let us make amends!
Awright?!
We're gonna be killed!
Just to let your friend escape, huh?
All right, decided!
You're gonna be my woman.
Koga! Weren't you gonna eat her
when you finished with her?
Besides, she's human!
Fools! This woman can see
the Sacred Jewel.
Not only the Birds of Paradise
have the fragments.
We can gather all the fragments
in this region.
All the fragments?
Then we'll be invincible!
That's right.
So she's much more useful to us
than some demon woman.
Kagome... that's what you're called?
From today, you're my woman.
Understood?
S-say... don't touch me, stupid!
She slapped Koga!
She's as good as dead.
Ou... ch...
H-hey... It's rude to claim
a girl as your "woman."
Besides, I already have
someone I'm seeing.
Seeing? Not that mutt-face.
Yes, that mutt-face...
No! His name is Inuyasha!
My sweetheart has a name, Inuyasha!
Stop calling him mutt-face!
Hmm... You and that guy, huh?
What am I saying?!
Inuyasha is in love with Kikyo!
I see, so that's it?
Well, it's just as well.
Next time I see him, I'll kill 'im!
And when this Inuyasha fella is dead,
there won't be a problem.
Sango! Are they allies
of the Wolf-Demon Tribe?
I'm not sure.
Hey, Miroku! Get to work, will ya?!
Inuyasha... get captured by these birds.
What?!
What're you thinking, Miroku?
If this area is the hunting ground
of these bird demons...
there should be bones
and skeletons of wolves.
But there's not a single one.
So they're in alliance
with the Wolf-Demon Tribe?
That's what I suspect.
And so...
If I get captured,
I'll get taken to their nest...
I'll be able to save Kagome
and we'll live happily ever after.
Awright!
Take care of the rest!
Just a minute.
Hey, Miroku... Why couldn't you
be the one who gets captured?
Hey Miroku!
You tricked me!
What are you saying?
You are built much more sturdily
than I am!
Miroku, aren't we going to follow?
We'll let some distance
build between us.
Miroku! Switch places with me!
I must hurry and get Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
Has Inuyasha been captured?!
I let him out of my sight
for just a while.
If only I had been
more diligent!
Stupid!
Hey Shippo! You're all right?
Miroku! Sango!
Look!
Inuyasha's been captured!
Strategy?
We wanted that bird to take him
to the den of the Wolf-Demon Tribe.
What are you saying?!
The Birds of Paradise and the
Wolf-Demon Tribe are bitter enemies.
Kagome is in the den of
the Wolf-Demon Tribe.
I see.
And there's a mountain of wolf bones.
So the Birds of Paradise and
the Wolf-Demon Tribe are enemies?!
Inuyasha... you heard?
Damn!
At this moment, I'm not angry at
Wolf-Demons or you birds!
Lemme go!
Ouch...
The one I wanna kill right now...
is you, Miroku!
Come down here and fight me, Miroku!
Did you hear him?
We must hurry and rescue Kagome.
Hey! Wait up! Miroku!
Don't you dare leave me!
Everyone, are you ready?
Yeah!
The Birds of Paradise
nest in this mountain?
Yeah.
Somewhere in this mountain is
one who has the Sacred Jewel.
You must find him.
All right.
There is a Sacred Jewel fragment
here in this mountain.
I must get the Jewel.
But Inuyasha...hurry!
Huh?!
They're on to us!
Hey guys!
I'm leaving the small fry to you!
Let's go, Kagome!
Kagome! Do you see the
Sacred Jewel fragment?
I can't look while you fight!
There!
I see it right before us!
We've been waiting,
Wolf-Demon brat.
You have Sacred Jewel fragments
on your body.
We brothers have sought
your fragments.
To think you'd come to us.
Hah! So we're both thinking
the same thing.
Kagome,
where's the Sacred Jewel fragment?
The fragment is inside its mouth.
Exactly!
If you want the Sacred Jewel fragment,
you must come inside our mouth!
Hey you!
Koga?
Protect Kagome!
But what're you gonna do, Koga?
I'll cut up its mouth with this!
You're going after the fragment
in its mouth? Impossible for you alone!
Only I can take on
that giant ugly bird!
Here I go!
Awright, Sis!
We'll get you to safety.
Sis? You mean me?
Of course! You're the boss's woman!
Hey! What are you thinking?!
Hey!
It's coming your way!
Sis, watch out!
Sis!
I have to save him!
It's too late! He'll be taken to
their nest and devoured!
Sis!
Please hit the mark!
Bull's eye!
I'm so glad! Are you all right?
- Amazing!
- Who is she anyway?!
Thanks... it's coming again!
Kagome!
Inu... yasha!
I was so scared!
Kagome, are you all right?
Sango! Miroku!
Kagome!
Shippo!
Kagome, what's going on?
The Wolf-Demons and
the Birds of Paradise...
are fighting an all-out war.
We have to do something about
the Birds of Paradise!
All right. I'll take care of them.
If you value your life... stand back!
- Amazing!
- What was that?!
That mutt-face...
what a time for him to show up.
I have no time
to take you on right now.
I'll let you go for today. So just go!
Shaddup!
You dared to kidnap Kagome
and you're gonna pay right now!
Kagome?
Hey, mutt-face.
You can run away, but keep your
hands off my woman.
Your woman?!
A woman who can see the Sacred
Jewel... Now she's perfect for me.
W-what?!
Kagome, did you hear what he said?
l-It's a lie!
He's just making it all up!
W-why you!
How dare you tell such lies?!
I'm not lying! Kagome is my woman!
I'm in love with Kagome!
Kagome is better off with me!
Much better than sticking
to some weak mutt!
So that she can make
a clean break from you...
I'm gonna kill you one day!
Then Kagome... you'll be free
to fall in love with me!
What a forceful guy!
Actually, I'm quite envious
of his personality.
Why you.
Calling her Kagome,
Kagome, Kagome...
Acting so familiar with her!
Fool! I'm too busy, I said.
Go away!
The Sacred Jewel fragment!
Koga! It's up higher!
W-what?!
She's calling out to him?!
Even higher? This is the peak!
Take that!
First, we'll tear off your right arm!
Damn!
The fragment on my right arm!
It's coming back!
It's after the fragments on my legs!
Hey you! What're you doing here?!
Shaddup and watch, you puny wolf!
Bear witness to my true strength!
Now we have two
Sacred Jewel fragments!
Brother!
Power, we'll soon have more power!
Now I draw out the true
power of Tetsusaiga!
The Wind Scar is... there!
He killed that giant demon in one swing!
You've mastered the Wind Scar!
Yeah well.
Now then.
We've gotten rid of the pesky birds.
So let's settle this once and for all!
She's hugging him!
Settle it once and for all?!
This is no time for that!
Koga is hurt!
This is nothing!
Koga, hang on!
Why is she taking his side?!
I can kill the likes of you
with just my left arm!
Are you still insulting me?!
Prepare yourself!
Inuyasha, sit!
Make your escape now! Hurry!
Oh... okay!
Koga.
Let's go!
Hold it! You!
Why'd you let him go?
Well, he was hurt and...
besides, he wasn't all that bad.
Not bad?!
Cut the jokes! Weren't you kidnapped
and almost killed?!
Well yes.
But he did protect me, too.
So you fell in love with him?
Well, after he declared his love
so boldly, how could she hate him?
Stupid! Forget it!
The Bird of Paradise
had one piece...
Koga had the other one
in his right arm.
Won't he come back for it?
Probably.
When Koga and Inuyasha meet
the next time...
will they start fighting again?
Kagome,
go and put Inuyasha's mind at ease.
He was so worried about you.
I pity him the way he is.
Oh Inuyasha.
I'm sorry I worried you.
Thank you so much for saving me.
Wouldn't you have preferred
that I didn't save you?
Taken in by his sweet words.
Sweet words?
Because he said he loved me?
Is that what's bothering you?
What're you saying?!
Nothing's bothering me!
It is bothering you.
Let me make one thing clear.
I don't feel anything for Koga!
Hah! I didn't ask that!
Forget it!
Let's not talk about it anymore!
Say.
What really happened
between you two?
Inuyasha.
Just what are you suspecting me of?!
Is that how you've been seeing me?!
W-what're you scolding me for?!
Because you've totally misunderstood!
Shaddup!
I don't wanna see your face anymore!
Just go away!
I see!
Sango!
What is it?
Can I borrow Kirara?
What're you going to do?
Hah! Planning to go to Koga?
I'm going back home!
Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid!
Kagome is scary when she's mad.
l-I'm not scared.
I'm not scared at all, stupid!
Since I started crossing between
the present and the Feudal Era...
this is the first time
I've gotten so angry.
I'll never forgive that Inuyasha!
But something's strange... as though
I've forgotten something valuable.
My... my youth as a ninth grader is
supposed to be in the present time.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Two Hearts, One Mind"
Don't miss it!