Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
From the time he was little,
Miroku has had no close kin.
He was taught everything,
both good and bad, by one man.
And now, Monk Mushin was about to
preside over one last feast.
Huh?
Wha...!
This is....!
Who's there?!
Serial murders at
popular temples?
Lately, highly spiritual monks
and head priests have been murdered.
Monks and priests?
What significance does that have?
Well, I'm not the one to ask....
It's a terrible story.
But does it have anything to do
with the remaining Sacred Jewel shards?
Would that Naraku go so far as
to kill ordinary humans?
I doubt it.
Then it's got nothing to do with us.
Besides, there aren't any highly
spiritual monks among us, or anything.
You're absolutely right.
Hey you.... That isn't funny.
Master Miroku!
Huh?
Huh? That's....
It's Hachiemon, the Raccoon Dog.
Master Mushin is going to die?!
It's regrettable, but I saw it!
Mushin is the monk who
raised you?
That's who we went to see
to treat your Wind Tunnel,
right, Miroku?
What's going on?
Tell me everything!
Y-Yes....
Well....for the past few days, I've been
staying at Master Mushin's temple.
Hyee!
Master Mushin!
l-It's nothing.
Still....!
Master Mushin!
I told you, it's nothing.
And that's why I rushed
over to get you.
It seems that Hachi
was not lying.
Miroku!
It's been a while, Master.
Is something wrong?
You shall die sometime tonight.
Just kidding.
This is no time to be joking.
Hmm?
Did Hachi speak the truth?
Hachi?
Hachi said that you
are going to die soon.
It's not a lie.
I am going to die very soon.
It's the path I've chosen.
I have no complaints.
But I'm glad I got to see you
one more time.
Look! We all eventually die.
No sense getting sentimental.
Inuyasha!
No, Inuyasha is right.
All living things eventually die.
Miroku....
But isn't there something
we can do?
Master....
Master Mushin!
I guess I dozed off.
Master Mushin is going to die...?
Um, Master Mushin....
Isn't there anything you'd
like to do?
Anything I'd like to do?
She means you'd better take care
of any unfinished business
before you go
to the other world.
Inuyasha?
What?
Sit!
Well, that's what she means.
Well, let's see....
I'd like to drink sake.
You're already drinking.
Well, then....
First, you can clean up
the temple.
First?!
Man!
Why do I....have to....do this?!
That's the way to go, Inuyasha.
After all, this is the last time.
But cleaning this huge temple
is a pain.
Hmm.... You're right.
Wind Tunnel.
If he could use the
Wind Tunnel freely...
Wind Tunnel!
Look! The dirt on the floor....
the trash in the bedrooms....
With my Wind Tunnel, you don't
need to use a broom.
See? Spic and span in no time!
The suction power is so strong!
Gotta hand it to Miroku, the
Human Vacuum Cleaner!
I can't say it out loud,
but I sure would like to!
Kagome?
All done?
Next, you can air out
the beddings.
Arghh! Tetsusaiga!
- Why me?! Why me?! Why me?!
- Not so hard, Inuyasha!
- Tetsusaiga! Tetsusaiga! Tetsusaiga!
- He's really into it.
He's the type who can't
sit still.
Next, cut the grass.
Hiraikotsu!
Now, the laundry.
Go!
- And that's it.
- All done!
We cleaned the temple,
aired out the beddings,
and did all the wash.
Anything else?
Shall we prepare dinner?
Yes, let's!
No need for that.
T-This is....?
Can't you tell by looking at it?
It's an inn....
and obviously expensive.
I've always wanted to drink
to my heart's content in a place like this.
Hey you, depraved monk!
You really are going to die,
aren't you?
Of course! Would I ask for these
things if I weren't?
Well anyway, come on,
let's go.
That old geezer!
Come on, Miroku.
It is his last wish.
Here you are.
Oh come on....snuggle up closer.
Stay calm.
It is his last wish.
Cleaning, washing....
then a feast.
Nothing special, huh?
Well, he's just a drunk monk,
after all.
This is the speed of
a country monk.
Master Mushin, isn't there
anything else you want to do?
Well.... I want to drink sake.
You're already drinking!!
What are you saying?
The sake I desire is
no ordinary sake.
Huh?
Then what kind of sake is it?
The legendary sake, the Mist of Sages!
Mist of Sages?
Beyond four mountains from here,
there is a sacred peak known
as Kasumidake.
A sage who lives there makes a
very rare sake
and that is known as
the Mist of Sages.
Those who drink this sake feel
as though they have climbed into Heaven.
Its taste is indescribably delicious.
So you want us to acquire
some of this sake?
I am not finished
with the story.
A countless many have set out to
acquire the sake,
but not one has ever
returned with it.
If I could drink this sake,
I would have no regrets.
I guess we have no choice.
Huh?
Miroku!
You'll go for me?
You said, if you drink it,
you would have no regrets.
You're such a great guy, Miroku.
And so are you, Inuyasha,
since you are coming along.
Stupid! I'm just....
Hmm?
Miroku, look!
That's....!
Yes, that is Kasumidake.
Well, we just have to
find this sage
and have him share
some of his sake with us.
I just hope he's willing
to share it.
Huh?!
Miroku....
I know. I sense it, too.
This is no sage.
This is the aura of a demon!
This is....?!
Mist?
This mist... what is it?
Everyone!
Don't let your guard down!
I'll be Number One!
I'm Kagome Higurashi
and I'm going to sing!
W-What?!
Next, I, Kagome Higurashi,
will now dance!
And Number Three,
Kagome Higurashi will laugh!
What's happened to me?!
It looks like there are
a bunch of me!
Oh well, let's sing!
W-What's happening?!
Everyone, don't inhale the mist!
This is the work of the demon.
I don't know just what it is exactly,
but it makes one intoxicated.
So do not inhale, no matter what!
It's too late!
The others are already drunk!
I meant the rest of us!
All right, one more song!
Kagome Higurashi, here goes!
Hey! Calm down, everyone!
Huh....!
S-Sango!
Inuyasha!
S-Sango, what're you doing?!
Forget 'im.... Let's just go.
Go?!
That flirtatious monk....
and Kagome... huh?
There's so many of her.
But let's just leave them.
Let's go, just the two of us....
Let's go defeat Naraku.
Okay?
Sit!
Sit! Sit! Sit!
Now she's crying.
Sango!
Oh.... The one who made her cry
is going to console her.
Miroku....
Miroku, you flirting cheat!
Now she's angry!
Go! Go!
Hiraikotsu!
Is this what the demon intends?
To intoxicate us with his demonic
power and make us fight?
Inuyasha! Scatter the mist
with your Wind Scar!
- Sit. Sit. Sit. Sit. Sit. Sit. Sit. Sit.
- L-Look b-before y-you s-speak!
Sorry.
At this rate....
I have no choice....
It's not manly to fear being
poisoned!
One must drink sake,
but not get drunk on sake!
Wind Tunnel!
Huh?!
Are you the sake sages?!
Huh? I'm out of sake.
All gone already?
Huh?
Ohh....
Here.
How does it taste?
It is superb.
Miroku....
Forgive me.
It's nothing.
It's been quite a while since
we sat and talked like this.
Yes....
Father! Father!
Let me go, Monk!
If I do, you will also be sucked
into your father's Wind Tunnel.
Father!
Does it bother you?
I guess it will bother you
even if I tell you not to let it.
Master Mushin....
Naraku is still alive, isn't he?
Yes.
The uncertainty of tomorrow
can only be understood
by those who don't know if
they will live another day.
Until Naraku is defeated,
you are not able to forget any of this
even when drunk.
That's not true.
I may not be able to forget,
but I can get drunk with the hope
of defeating Naraku.
Master Mushin!
Master Mushin....
Master Mushin....Master Mushin!
Master Mushin!
Master Mushin...!
Huh?!
Hey, you're not dead?!
What....?!
What does this mean?!
What do you mean,
"what does this mean"?
So....because all those high-ranking
monks and priests were being killed,
you figured you were going to
be murdered, too?!
Exactly!
There's nothing wrong
with your health?
Fool! I'm perfectly healthy!
Then what about the blood
Hachi saw you spit up?!
Oh that.... A piece of fish got
stuck in the wrong pipe.
N-No way....
T-This is so stupid....
Who else around here
is highly spiritual?!
The next victim is sure to be....
Believe us, you are safe!
W-What did I say wrong?
Geez! Didn't I tell you
not to bother with this?!
I'll say.... What a big mistake.
My head hurts.
But, well, it's okay.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Well, I just thought something
like this is nice sometimes. That's all.
We'll be on our way.
Yes....
Just what is this kid up to anyway?
Half-killing so many highly spiritual
monks and priests...
Is he looking into their hearts?
Kagura, I'm done.
Finish him.
I couldn't see anything.
Even if they're highly spiritual,
they're mere humans, that's all.
Just what are you trying to see?
The border between
this world and the next.
Where the final shard
of the Sacred Jewel lies.
Mysterious happenings occur
night after night...
Only the wealthy are targeted
and no matter how tight
the security,
the homes are broken into and
valuables are stolen.
It's too strange for it to be the
work of robbers.
A demon which can make
itself disappear?
Will they be able to work together
to slay the demon?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"A Strange, Invisible Demon Appears!"
Just leave it to me!
I'll slay it for sure!