Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The battalion of resurrected specters...
the Band of Seven appears
one after another.
Somewhere ahead is Naraku.
Then out of nowhere...
Sesshomaru appears!
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
So cold!
Shaddup!
Who gave you the Sacred Jewel shard?!
Confess now!
Yeah... he's at it.
That Jakotsu hasn't changed a bit.
This should be just about right.
Jakotsu!
Was it Naraku who
gave you the Sacred Jewel shard?
I dunno....never met him.
Why you...!
Enough of your quips!
Huh?!
Smoke?
Mukotsu, huh?
Interfering!
Inuyasha, better make your getaway.
What're you up to?!
H-Hot!
What is that?!
It's poison smoke.
We'll meet again, Inuyasha!
Damn him!
But where is this poison
coming from?
That Naraku....just you wait!
I'll smash you and send you to
the depths of hell!
I smell him.
This is...
Naraku's servant...
That boy's smell.
Lord Sesshomaru, why do
you seek Naraku?
Cripes!
It's because you were abducted by Naraku
that Lord Sesshomaru is so upset.
Huh?! All because of me?!
Don't get so conceited, silly fool!
Lord Sesshomaru is a man
of pride.
He seems very calm on
the outside....
but after being treated like that....
he's seething on the inside.
Huh?
He's got that scary look.
Do you despise me that much?
Are you all right?
Sango, does it hurt?
It's okay.
That Jakotsu!
He can't have gone far.
You'll go after him?
Of course!
He hasn't coughed up
any clues yet!
But Inuyasha....
What do you think
of that poison smoke?
Whaddya mean?
Jakotsu seemed to know
something.
Yeah....
Maybe it's another one of
the Band of Seven.
Huh? Another specter appeared?
Miroku, you stay and
protect Kagome and Sango.
All right!
There.
And mix well.
Huh?
It's you, Jakotsu.
It's been a long time.
Why you...!
You tried to melt me away, too,
huh Mukotsu?
Don't get angry.
Just my way of
saying hello.
Hah!
And what about the others?
Renkotsu is taking
care of Ginkotsu.
What happened to Ginkotsu?
He's....you know....
He needs all this new gunpowder
and guns....
Yeah....
And he needs to oil them well....
Right?
Huh?
What's going on?
What?!
Inuyasha's coming after me alone?
So... left behind are
the humans and a child-fox.
What's more....this girl Kagome
has Sacred Jewel shards.
I'll leave you to
deal with them.
What? You sure?
I'm gonna take the shards, you know?
In exchange, Inuyasha is mine.
Sure, I don't want him.
Can I have the woman?
Sure thing.
No thanks for me.
All right!
Hmm?
You have business at this shrine?
Let's see...
This temple will be perfect.
Yes?
This shrine will be taken over
by the Band of Seven.
Band of Seven?!
You're one of the specters?!
That raiment of yours
will suit me, too.
Oh! Kagome!
A well!
Uh-huh!
Let's replenish our water.
Huh? Someone's on the ground.
This is terrible!
Are you all right?
She's dead.
What's this?
Kagome! Let's hurry and
get away from here!
Uh-huh....
Huh?!
Poison smoke!
You can't get away from
Mukotsu's poison.
Kagome, hang on!
You're the one who
has the Sacred Jewel shard.
Kagome! Kagome!
Run away!
Shippo....
No, I won't!
Don't worry. I won't kill
you right away.
This poison will paralyze
your body,
but your mind will be
alert until the very end.
It's my special toxin.
Unfortunately, it has no effect
on demons.
Don't you dare lay a hand
on Kagome!
Fox magic! Smashing top!
How was that?!
Shippo!
Miroku, stay back.
It's poison.
So he's the one behind
the smoke.
Don't come, Sango!
Miroku!
Wait!
I'll call Inuyasha!
You must be one of
the Band of Seven!
Yeah, I'm Mukotsu
the Poison Master!
There must be someone who resurrected
you and sent you after us!
Is it Naraku who is behind all this?
Who knows?
You have to ask the Chief.
That's if you get to him.
Run away!
Melt!
Sango...
Miroku...
Now then, woman.
The intruders are gone.
It's just you and me now.
Inuyasha!
Where are you?!
It's getting closer...
Jakotsu's smell.
Wha...!
Hey!
Inuyasha!
What're you doing?
You followed my scent, didn't you?
So I made it easy to track me.
Here, get a whiff.
I'll kill you!
We're surrounded by
a poison barrier.
No one can come to help.
But what a beauty!
I'm so fortunate.
I get to marry
such a pretty girl.
What?! Marry?!
With my face....
girls don't come to me.
I'll dress you up pretty
like a bride.
Then we'll have
the ceremony.
Ceremony?!
He can't mean a marriage ceremony?!
Run some more!
Why you...!
Don't act cocky!
That angry face of yours
gets me excited!
His sword...
It's distorting the path
for Tetsusaiga's Wind Scar!
The fun is just beginning!
If I stop that sword of yours
from moving around,
it'll be all over!
Hmm....you think you can
stop my Jakotsu-Sword?
Come at me!
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Another one of the Band of Seven
has Kagome!
Kagome is in danger!
What?!
I'm your opponent!
Shaddup!
We're going, Shippo!
You won't get away!
Go, horse!
What?!
What IS this?!
Hey!
Wait, Inuyasha!
I'm not perfect,
but please be good to me!
Good, good.
Now then, dance for me
in celebration.
Just what is he up to?
If only I can get a hold of
that Sacred Jewel shard.
Such a fine bride.
Afine bride indeed!
Next, some sake...
Kagome!
Don't interrupt my ceremony!
Leave him to me!
Huh?!
A repellant mask won't work.
This also enters the body through
the eyes and skin.
Sango!
That was easy.
Although it doesn't affect
me at all.
I'm so used to the poison already.
I did it!
Stupid girl!
It didn't work.
You too?
Does my face repel you, too?
Is that why you reject me?!
What are you saying?
I despised you even before
I saw your face!
Unforgivable!
You hurt my feelings!
I don't want you for a wife anymore!
Kagome...
Damn! I can't move!
I'll just take the Sacred Jewel shard.
Inuyasha...
Now die!
Sesshomaru!
Sesshomaru saved me?
What's going on?
I thought the only opponents
of the Band of Seven
would be Inuyasha and his group,
and Koga of the Wolf-Demon tribe?
Is Inuyasha here?
Who are you?
That's my question to you.
You don't know me,
yet you'll....
I stabbed you with
my toxic claws....
and you're still moving around?
Die!
Serves you right!
Huh?!
Wait....! Please wait!
I....I was wrong!
Forgive me! Spare... spare me!
In order to...
In order to defy you....
I'd have to do this at least.
Learned your lesson?
Even demons will die with this...
Why won't you dissolve?
It's toxin made by
the Poison Master Mukotsu!
As if poison made for humans
will work on me, Sesshomaru.
Kagome!
Sesshomaru?!
Huh?!
Everyone's dead!
Why you...!
What'd you do to them?
No....
Huh?
Sesshomaru....saved us.
I didn't save you.
He didn't tell me what I needed to know,
so I got rid of him.
That's all.
Needed to know what?
I can smell that kid Kohaku
in the area.
Does that mean Naraku is near?
Damn that Inuyasha!
Totally ignoring me!
But who is that solemn guy?
Never heard about a guy like
that coming around!
Furthermore, he got rid
of Mukotsu like a bug.
I'd better not stick around
here long.
Answer me, Inuyasha.
Where is Naraku?
We haven't found him either.
Just....some specters possessing
Sacred Jewel shards have come after us.
I'm sure that Naraku is close by!
That's all I need to hear.
Sesshomaru!
Get a hold of yourself, Sango!
Miroku!
Wake up! Miroku!
It's the poison!
The poison got to them!
Kagome!
I'm all right!
Miroku and Sango... protected me.
I have medicine in
in my first-aid box....
Kagome!
Damn!
If I had only stayed with her!
Lord Sesshomaru is late.
I wish I had gone with him.
Silly! Where Lord Sesshomaru went,
there were signs of poison.
If you followed along,
you'd be dead!
Gee... how boring!
Huh?
That's... Kohaku!?
Why is he here of all places?
What's the matter, Rin?
Huh?
Nothing.
Lord Sesshomaru...
If you see him again,
will you kill Kohaku?
I see.
First Kyokotsu, and now Mukotsu is dead.
Yup.
And? Who was it that
killed Mukotsu?
He had really cold eyes.
Guess you could say
he was manly.
But I prefer a cuter one,
like Inuyasha.
Who's asking you for
your preferences?
But Renkotsu....
Aren't there too many things
we haven't been told?
Huh?
First, this Naraku who
revived us all.
Just who is he?
That, huh?
Brother, have you ever met him?
Only Big Brother has met Naraku.
Naraku handed him the shards
of the Sacred Jewels....
including ones for us.
The agreement was if we got rid of all who
sought Naraku,
the shards would become ours.
What an agreement.
Two are already dead.
From seven....there's four left.
Seven minus two is five!
Huh?
Wait....one, two, three....
Never mind that, Jakotsu...
You said Inuyasha's friends
were exposed to Mukotsu's poison?
Yeah....
Mukotsu's poison is
very persistent.
By nightfall, they may be dead.
We gave them the antidote,
but they need to rest!
Yeah....we have to find
a safe place for them.
This is getting interesting.
Actually, Ginkotsu is headed
towards their way.
Ginkotsu....a pretty formidable
foe for a demon.
Master Inuyasha! How did you travel so far
in my absence?!
This is the north country.
You're not going to a hot spring?
A rejuvenating spa!
It works on body chills, aches and pains
and ringworm!
We don't have time to waste
on stuff like this!
Miroku! There's more of 'em!
Damn it! I'll kill you!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Ghastly Steel Machine!
There's a Sacred Jewel shard
around the neck!
Could he be one of the
Band of Seven?!