Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled
by the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
Miroku, Sango, Inuyasha
and Kagome....
I command these brave warriors
and I'll defeat Naraku
with my Smashing Top!
Here I come!
It's time for the start of Shippo!
Meow!
Miaaow!
- We're tired, Brother!
- We're tired, Big Brother!
Shut up and walk.
Meow.
Miaaow.
- Let's take a break, Brother!
- Let's take a break, Big Brother!
- Meow.
- Miaaow.
Just for a minute!
A demon!!
- Why, you....!
- Wind Scar!
Well, now what do you think?!
That'll teach you to
try to eat me!
Is that....?!
You shouldn't take
me too lightly!
Hey! We're leaving, Shippo!
Ah!! Wait for me!
Don't leave me behind!
- Don't tell me....
- That's....?!
The Great Hero!
It's gotta be, Big Brother!
It's the Great Hero!
Meow!
Miaaow!
Yeah! That's the legendary
Great Hero!
You see, I lost both my
ma and my pa....
Poor Shippo....
But I'm okay. I've
got my friends with me.
They seem like good people.
I'm more worried about you.
The world of humans is
going through tough times.
I'll be fine.
Especially now that
I've met you....
S-Same here! Mizuki!
How is it that Shippo meets
girls at every town we visit?
It's probably due to the one
he's always hanging around with!
If you've been seeing a demon,
of course we'll get rid of it
for you right away.
It might take a while if it's
hiding up in the mountains.
Oh, we are very well aware of that.
So what about lodging
during that time....?
Feh!
You may stay here as
long as you wish!
And could we ask the young
ladies to take care of us....?
I can certainly ask some young
maidens over to help at dinner.
And through the night, as well?
You're asking a bit much
of our host, Miroku!
Well, well! If it isn't Sango!
Geez! I can't stand it!
From what I hear it's only a
stupid little small-fry demon.
It's got nothing to do with
the Jewel shards,
and I'm not interested.
Please don't say that!
Why should I care?!
Let's leave this dump of a
village and be on our way!
Inuyasha!
Huh?!
Sit! boy!
Ka....Kagome! Why, you....!
Kagome!!
Sit! boy!
Are your friends always
so violent....?
That's because they're
still children.
But don't worry!
I keep things together!
Oh?
Well, we'll be off!
I can't thank you enough!
And you look after things here,
you hear me, Inuyasha?
Yeah, yeah....
Aren't you going, Inuyasha?
They don't need me to go!
Besides, what happens if the
demon attacks the village?
We're placing all our
hopes in you!
Yeah, I know....
Well, I'll go take
a look around!
Sure. I'm counting on you.
There!
I wonder if
Mizuki will like it?
Of course she will!!
Master!
Miaaow.
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Master!
Mister!
Mustard!
- Meow.
- Miaaow.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
We're fox demons and we
had the good fortune
to come across our hero,
the Master Shippo!
Mister!
Mustard!
- Meow.
- Miaaow.
Huh? Master....?
These are the times when the
world of demons is in turmoil
with this demon Naraku showing up
and other demons are wreaking
havoc all they like!
Because of that, our family
of fox demons was attacked!
The five of us got separated
from our parents,
and now we're
looking for them.
- Meow.
- Miaaow.
And during all this we heard
rumors of the Master Shippo!
We heard there was a group who
battles with the evil Naraku!
And among them is a fox demon
who is a great hero!
- Meow!
- Miaaow!
Hm.... Well, I guess that
would be me....
Master! We'll work very hard!
Train us hard to be
strong like you!
Make us your disciples!
Your underlings!
Meow!
Miaaow!
I can't do that!
Oh, no! The stories
about you are legion!
Even though you're
a demon yourself,
you have among your
followers a priestess....
A demon slayer....
A holy monk....
Namu Namu Namu
And a half-demon....
You're the Great Shippo who
leads such illustrious warriors!
Me? I lead....a priestess....?
A demon slayer....?
A monk....?
And a half-demon....?
Why, you!
Inuyasha is my retainer!!
And the humans are my servants!!
Master! Teach us
one of your deadly moves!
You had a technique when you
fought with Naraku, didn't you?!
A deadly technique....?
Oh, yeah! You must mean this!!
Fox Magic, Smashing Top!
Well? Whacha think?
Master!
Mister!
Mustard!
Meow!
Miaoww!
What?
Please don't make fun of us.
Please!
You have a really
incredible one, don't you?!
An incredible one....?
A terrific one!
Something like, "Wink Star!"
"Think Hard!"
"Bean Curd!"
Incredible skills!
Incredible!
Are you talking about
the Wind Scar?
That's it!!
Yes, that's it!
Please teach us
that one, Master!
Mister!
Mustard!
Meow!
Miaaow!
But.... Um....You, see....!
Master! Please teach us!
All right. I get it.
Can you wait here a bit?
I'm capable, too!
Inuyasha!
What is it, Shippo?
Has the demon showed up?
Lend it to me!
It's....the WIND SCAR!!!
WIND SCAR....WIND SCAR....
WIND SCAR....!
What on earth are you doing?
Inuyasha! How do you
do the Wind Scar?
What's this all of a sudden?
I want to use the
Wind Scar, too!
Huh?!
I have to be a lot stronger....
No, no! You can't just
swing it around like that!
Listen, you have a sensitive nose
and can smell the flow of
the demonic aura, right?
So, that's where you go,
"Ga-ga-ga!!"
And then, like you're slicing
through it, go "Zu-ba-ba!!"
Ga-ga-ga? Zu-ba-ba?
Yeah! Ga-ga-ga and zu-ba-ba!
I don't get the "ga-ga-ga" and
the "zu-ba-ba" part!
If you don't get the "ga-ga-ga" or
the "zu-ba-ba" parts,
then you'll never get it!
Watch!
It's like this....
Ga-ga-ga!!! And zu-ba-ba!!!
Wind Scar!
See? Like that....Ack!!
Oh, this is bad!
I decimated it!
Shippo....! This....
Huh?! Where'd he go?
Shoot! I got carried away!
I was stupid to think Inuyasha
would teach it to me....
Shippo!
Hello!
Mizuki!
Where were you?
I....uh.... I was going to check
around for that demon.
Oh! And I thought I'd
give this to you....
Oh, my! It's lovely!
Thank you, Shippo!
Okay, so I'm going back
to look for the demon,
so you should go back.
Okay. Be careful now.
Sure.
Thank you!
Master!
H-How long have
you been standing there?
For a while.
Listen, about the Wind Scar....
I don't have it....
That was great, Master!
Hm?
Enchanting that human
girl so easily!
I wasn't exactly
enchanting her....
We fox demons have a long
tradition of bewitching folks!
And we can't let the
raccoon dog demons outdo us!
Right!
So, Master! Are you going to
do something awful to this girl?
Well, not really....
I'm sure Master Shippo has a
terrific technique for it!
I'm so excited!
We wanna watch!
J- Just what're these
fox demons thinking?!
Outta my way, you fox brats!
You creep! What do you
think you're doing?!
This must be the demon who is
terrorizing the village!
I have to get word to
Inuyasha right away!
Hold it! Do you know who
you're dealing with?!
Huh?
This is the master famous
throughout the fox demon world,
the one and only Master Shippo!
You're the one who should
get out of his way!
Yeah! You!
- Just be good and apologize!
- If you don't, he'll getcha!!
Wonder at the power
of Master Shippo!
Be amazed!!
Be amazed!
Hey....why are you holding onto me?
Oh, yeah? Well, I guess
I've gotta fight him!
Go get him, Master!
Go get him!
Miaaow!
Now that it's come to this....
Come on! I'm ready anytime!
Fox Magic! Anything to get away!
Run for it!
Now, you little squirts!
How dare you make a fool of me!
Ma....Master!!
Hah! Little twerps!
Wow.... It looks like I got
away from that one....
Uh-oh! I sense....
Master!
Mister!
Mustard!
Meow!
Miaoww!
Are you really the hero of the
fox demons, Master Shippo?
Well....yeah! I'm Shippo. No
two ways about that.
And you really are a
powerful demon, right?
Well....yeah.
And you really have a
deadly technique, right?
Uh....huh.
Then why did you run off?
Well, you see....
Why?!
Well....
Ah! Master!
Huh?
M-Mizuki!
That's the girl!
She's the one you'll
play a trick on, right?
Please show us how
well you do it!
We wanna see!
What's wrong, Master?
There really is no need
to enchant a human girl....
Master!!
Are you sure you're the hero of
the fox demons, Master Shippo?
Well, are you?
Yes, I am! I am Shippo!
No question about it!
What a lovely smell....
La-di-la-di-da!
Why's this happening?!
Ha, ha! Get ready!
- Take that!
Oww!! That hurts! Stop!
Hey, quit jumping around....!
Mi....Mizuki?!
Mizuki!
Mizuki....? Are you....are you....?
Shippo....
It was you?
He did it!
- Good job! Good job!
- Good job!
- Way to go!
- Wow, she's a mess!
- Hey! Human girl!
- Learned your lesson?!
Err....
You....
I hate you!
Way to go! Way to go!
Ah....M- Mizuki....!
Master!
Mister!
Mustard!
Meow!
Miaoww!
You were terrific!
Yay!!
This....wasn't much at all....
Once again....
my first love is over....
Good job! Way to go!
Did you see that, little girl?!
He's back!
A little while ago you made a
fool of me with that cheap trick
but this time we're gonna
settle things properly!
Master!
Mister!
Mustard!
Meow!
Miaoww!
Shut up! What's with
this "mustard" stuff?
Now, if you think you
want to apologize to me....
Huh?! What? What's this?!
If it hadn't been for you
showing up,
I'd....I'd....
Y-You're really going
to fight me?!
I'd never have had to do that!
And Mizuki wouldn't hate me!!
You little....!
Master!!
And next, I'll see to you guys....
I....!
You little twerp!!
I can see it!
A flow of demonic power!
It's the Master's
deadly technique!
Here it comes!
It's the Wind Scar!!
Meow!
Miaaow!
It's not the Wind Scar!
It's....
It's the Heart Scar!!!
It's even more incredible
than the Wind Scar!
Ow, ow! Let me go!
Hey, you little....!
The Heart Scar!
Wow.! Master!
You all join in!
Yeah! Come on, everybody!
Heart....!
No! No! I can't take it!!
You were terrific, Master!
Mister!
Mustard!
Meow!
Miaaow!
We've learned a great deal!
Your fox demon technique:
the Heart Scar.
I hope you'll allow us
to use it, too.
Sure, if you want.
Now we have much more
confidence in ourselves.
We can now go looking
for our mother and father.
It was a short friendship,
but we'll never forget you!
Thank you very much!
And so, we're off.
My first love!
Mizuki!
Why, that little brat!
The next time I see him,
I'll whomp him good!
Huh?
Wha...!
Ackkkk! That stings!
What happened?
Well, another one vanquished.
What's that?
Namu Amida Butsu....
Thank you so much! You've
done us a great service.
Not at all. It really wasn't
such a dangerous demon anyway.
I'm sorry we finished
so quickly....
Hey!
What's up, Shippo?
Something wrong?
Nothing.
Are you saying you're the one
who fixed that demon?
Who cares about that foolishness?!
Hm?
Um....Mizuki?
Bleh! Hmph!
Hey, Shippo! What've you done?
What's she so mad about, heh?
Why, you....!
Heart Scar!!
Yow, ow, ow! Hey!
Whadaya think you're doing?!
What's all that about?
Who knows?
Another test from the
great Buddha.
Heart Scar!!!
Mizuki!!!
We're supposed to find
the den of demon women...
but Miroku is flirting with
women again!
Say Sango....
Is there really nothing
between you and Miroku?
Huh? What do you mean?
When you two were alone at Mt. Hakurei,
nothing happened?
What a thing to ask, Kagome!
Miroku and I don't have
that kind of relationship.
I think Miroku likes you, Sango.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Trap of the Cursed Wall Hanging"
He's so reliable
in times of trouble.