It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
forourdreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
Sango is unaware that
Kohaku has regained his memory.
But Kirara knows just what both
of them are feeling.
In the village of the Demon Slayers
which holds so many memories,
a miracle occurs!
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Sango's younger brother, Kohaku,
is caught in Naraku's contemptible trap
and must beara heavy burden.
And even now, Kohaku continues
to be manipulated by him.
Sango feels an enormous guilt
that she is responsible,
and we want to do something
forher...
but it doesn't seem to be
that simple.
I wonderwhat Kirara
is thinking about Kohaku?
Yup, it's delicious!
I wonder where Kirara has gone?
Don't worry!
Kirara can manage alone.
But lately, Kirara goes off
on her own quite often.
This is close to Sango's
birthplace,
so she probably feels
very nostalgic.
Hmm....
Huh?
Hey Kohaku!
You won't find Kikyo
around here.
Try somewhere else.
Okay, I understand.
Just make sure you don't
get killed.
Same goes forme.
There!
It's going towards you, Kohaku!
Leave it to me!
Here!
Boy, it's begun to rain.
Here, you'll catch cold.
It's okay, Sister!
Never mind!
Here!
Hiraikotsu!
Sister!
Stay back, Kohaku!
Are you all right?
Uh-huh....
Try to bearit.
There you go.
Thank you, Sister.
No problem.
Sister!
Wait a sec!
Huh?
Sister!
Kohaku.... Are you okay?
Here!
Forme?
Yup.
They're beautiful.
Thank you!
Hot!
Hey Kagome, it's hot!
Oh, sorry.
Kirara....
Sango!
Sango, come have tea.
Hey Sango!
It's no use getting all fidgety!
Don't worry. Kirara is the most
reliable one among us.
But she's late.
I'm going to take a look!
Huh? Jeez!
Let's do it, Kirara!
Whaddya you know....
The demon slayer.
All alone today?
Kagura!
Here, Kirara.
It's been a long time, huh, Kirara?
Is Sisterwell?
I see.
You're worried about me?
Thank you.
But right now, I can't go back
to Sisteryet.
Hey Demon Slayer, do you
know where Kikyo....?
Is Kohaku with you?
He is, isn't he?
I wonder....
Where is he?
If you're that worried,
why don't you search for yourself?
Hold it!
What do you intend to do
when you see him?
It has nothing to do with you.
Even if you find him,
he's bound to Naraku until
he dies.
I said it has nothing to do
with you!
Kohaku...
Many people have died....
because of me.
That's why the least I can do
is avenge theirdeaths....
and kill Naraku.
And I will....
without fail.
I don't know if I'll succeed.
And I don't know if I deserve
to live.
Welcome home!
Hey!
Here we go!
We fought so hard
and now, we're exhausted!
Demon Slayers
are so strong...
Too bad forthe demons!
I'm sorry, Kirara.
Huh?
You're hurt!
Wait a sec.
Stay still....
All right, done.
Kohaku....
Hey Kirara....
Come!
I'll show you my secret place.
Not much time has passed.
He must be nearby.
What do you intend to do
when you see him?
But....!
Kohaku is still my little brother!
See?
Isn't this great?
This spot hasn't changed
a bit.
I wish I could have shown it
to Sister, too.
Kohaku... Kohaku... Kohaku!
Well then....
Say hello to Sister.
Good-bye, Kirara.
Kohaku!
Huh?
Sister!
Sister....
Kirara!
Kirara?
You want me to follow?
Kirara....
Just what....?
Agarden of lilies....
This injury....
You have medicine on it....
Kohaku?!
Sister, wait!
You were with him?
Kohaku!
Shippo falls underthe spell
of a parasite chrysalis!
He's become a violent prankster
and that's a problem.
Serves you right!
The villagers are seething mad!
We have to find him
before he gets exterminated!
Stupid! Your Fox-fire isn't hot at all!
I still have othertricks!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Possessed by a Parasite:
Shippo, Our Worst Enemy!"
Why do you keep pulling
yourfox pranks on me?!