The black pearl in the right eye...
Imagine, the gateway to the tomb was
hidden in Inuyasha's right eye.
No wonder Lord Sesshomaru
was not able to find it.
Now that the location of
the tomb is known...
the sacred sword, Tetsusaiga,
will belong to him.
Tetsusaiga, the sword known to slay
100 demons in a single stroke...!
Lord Sesshomaru, now take
hold of it!
And you say that Inuyasha can?
Sesshomaru couldn't do it!
Now, if you pull it
out with ease...
Sesshomaru's pride
will be in shreds!
How embarrassing for him!
Master Inuyasha is immune
to the spell...
which cast off Lord Sesshomaru!
I knew it! Tetsusaiga is destined
to belong to Master Inuyasha!
Draw it out, Inuyasha!
Enough of your antics!
Inuyasha!
Huh?!
Sorry! I pulled it out.
Im... impossible!
Inuyasha, let alone Lord Sesshomaru,
could not budge Tetsusaiga...
How could a mere mortal?
You shouldn't have looked away!
Huh?!
Just who are you?
Why were you able to
draw out the sword?
I guess he's no longer
interested in you...
and your life's been spared, huh?
Fool!
Sesshomaru! Leave her alone!
She has nothing to do with you!
Inuyasha!
Don't come near me
or I'll kill you!
Neither you nor I could
draw out Tetsusaiga.
Yet she had no trouble
against the spell.
You expect me to
let her go?
I don't know why the spell
had no effect on her!
But she's only a human girl!
Kagome!
Hand over Tetsusaiga
to Sesshomaru!
No!
He couldn't pull out
the sword!
That means he's not the
rightful owner!
I WILL NOT give
it to him.
Fool!
A mortal girl has nothing
to do with this!
Stop interfering!
Stop interfering, you say?!
Inuyasha...
You seem to be very interested
in the actions of a human.
Why protect her?
Why let her go?
Why love her?
I certainly did not inherit
from our father...
the feelings of compassion
towards humans that you have.
It was this feeling for a mortal
woman, your mother...
this weakness of the heart...
that caused our father to
end up here like this.
Tainted blood courses
through your body!
Is it this blood that endears
you to humans?
Well, I don't pay any heed
to such infinitely vulgar beings.
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
So totally useless,
right, Inuyasha?
Sesshomaru!
Humans, as well as half-demons.
Why!
Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
Wake up!
With tainted blood like yours,
you cannot touch me!
Damn!
What can half-demons do?!
You're just half a demon!
Half-demon, huh?
Go!
There!
Half-demon?
Mother!
What is a half-demon?
That's right...
I...remember.
At that time, my mother cried...
for my sake.
She thought of my future
and cried for me.
It doesn't matter whether one is
human or demon!
I can't forgive you for playing
with my mother's memory...
But for her sake, I will not
lose to you!
This one's for my mother!
And this one is for...
Kagome!
Wh-why?!
It was useless a minute ago...
Anger over a mere mortal woman?
You act in the heat of passion and
rush to your death...
You are a truly pitiful fellow.
Why you!
I'll slit you open and
cut out your guts!
For Kagome, who died
a senseless death!
Phew!
I thought I was a goner!
Wh-hat!?
Huh?!
Hey you! You actually
tried to kill me!
Well, you're going to regret it
now! Get ready!
- Here!
- Huh?
I think this sword has
special powers. Go for it!
How... how come you're
so energetic?
Huh?
Hmm?
I see... The sword's spell
protected you.
Amazing... This Tetsusaiga...
to thwart the deadly poisons
in Lord Sesshomaru's claws!
Master Inuyasha, do not fear!
Try out the Tetsusaiga on
Lord Sesshomaru himself!
Listen to you, prattling on!
What's happening?!
He's so mean and evil!
We'll see if a half-demon can
wield the Tetsusaiga!
I will bear witness!
He transformed!
Hah! Now he's shown
his true colors!
And just because he
coveted this Tetsusaiga...
Does this sword really have
such awesome powers?
Kagome! Hide nearby.
Nearby? Where?
Okay! Now show me,
Tetsusaiga, your power!
He pushed me back!
Hey, Myoga!
What's going on?!
This sword can't cut!
It didn't even leave a lump!
Err... well, Master Inuyasha...
That sword is your
father's heirloom.
You must believe in
its power.
And by no means must
you release it!
Now then, excuse me!
Wh-why you!
Turn Lord Sesshomaru
into fodder!
Why!
Kagome! A miasma!
Don't breathe it in!
Don't breathe it in?!
Up! Escape upwards!
Inuyasha!
Never mind, just escape!
Those toxic fumes can kill
any demon in an instant!
Lord Sesshomaru!
There!
What about Inuyasha?!
Hey! Will Inuyasha be okay?
Huh?
I wonder?
Huh?!
Just leave things to
Master Inuyasha for now!
We must concentrate
on escaping!
Inuyasha!
Strong poison...
I can't linger here much longer.
Damn! My arms and legs
are becoming numb!
Even a useless sword like this...
hasta be more irritating
than a mosquito bite!
Inuyasha!
Master Inuyasha, now do you
see the power of Tetsusaiga?
Now for the finishing blow!
Fool!
This sword is as useless
as a cane!
Are you saying this isn't
the treasured sword of your father?
Hah!
He escaped!
Damn!
Does this junk do anything?!
Hang in there, Inuyasha!
The first blow worked!
Hah! It didn't do a thing!
But that's YOUR sword!
I have faith in your power!
How can you keep talking
such rubbish?!
I'm hardy, so I'll survive.
But you may end up dead!
Is it really... hopeless?
Well...
Hey... Did I... Did I make you cry?
Don't cry!
You expect me to laugh?!
Shut up!
I'm saying I'll protect you!
Cripes! Just stay there and watch.
I didn't hear wrong, did I?
He said he'd protect me...
Inuyasha is crude...
but he's different
from Sesshomaru.
There's something
different.
Damn! What the heck anyway?
Come, beast dog!
Tetsusaiga is pulsing!
I can hear it...
Is this the lifebeat
of Tetsusaiga?
It's different...
something's changed!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Get that half-demon Inuyasha
and devour him, head first!
He hasn't lost yet!
Do your best, Inuyasha!
I can do it!
This... fang!
A fang!
What an heirloom the
old man left me!
Hey, Sesshomaru, listen up!
Here we are, two brothers,
fighting for our father's treasure...
compared to his magnificence,
we're nothing!
Do you understand?
We're battling it out now,
on top of our father's body!
We're nowhere near
his equal.
I don't have any memories
of being loved by my father!
But he chose to hide his
fang inside my eye!
And I ain't giving up this sword!
Not to anyone!
Not even to my "fine"
older brother!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Please wait!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha, are you all right?!
Thanks, old man...
You left me a pretty
handy heirloom.
Master Inuyasha, well done!
I, Myoga, had faith in you!
Please wait!
Look there!
I was arranging for transportation
to go home.
I certainly did not intend
to run away!
You understand?
Then you didn't run away?
Huh?
Well, when you ask
me so nicely...
I'm sorry!
I thought you had no chance
in a hundred...
against Lord Sesshomaru...
and I ran away.
I underestimated you,
Master Inuyasha.
I am so terribly
ashamed of myself.
Myoga...
Huh?!
Oh dear...
What a happy day!
Are you all right, Inuyasha?
I just returned to normal.
There's no tomb or
treasure here anymore.
My old man can finally
rest in peace.
But why were you able to
draw out this Tetsusaiga?
I must say, you have some
strange powers.
Uh-huh...
I believe that it was because
Kagome is a mortal.
In the first place, Tetsusaiga was
forged by Inuyasha's father...
in order to protect Inuyasha's
human mother.
It is a supernatural sword that
can only be wielded...
by one who feels love for and
protective towards a human being.
Shut up! I said I'll
protect you!
I see!
That's why the sword started to pulse.
Tetsusaiga is pulsing!
There was just no way...
someone like Sesshomaru,
who despises humans...
could control Tetsusaiga.
Such a strange story.
Inuyasha thinks that being a
half-demon is a weakness.
That's why he didn't want to
feel anything for his mother.
But it is necessary for Inuyasha
to have feelings for humans.
That is what his father wanted
to teach him.
Perhaps it is Inuyasha rather
than Sesshomaru...
who inherited the true traits
of their father.
Huh?!
What's this?!
It turned back into
a useless, old sword.
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Shall I tell you the secret
to controlling Tetsusaiga?
What?
Do you know?
Can you really protect me
with that sword?
Huh?!
What're you saying?
Are you sane?
You're the one who told me,
"I'll protect you always!"
I did not!
Now listen here, Kagome.
One day, I'm gonna become
a full-fledged demon...
a magnificent one at that!
And with this sword...
I'll be able to gather all
the fragments of the Sacred Jewel.
And that means...
I have no time to waste
on a girl like you!
Hey!
What?!
Sit!
I was such a fool...
for believing for an instant,
that he could be kinda nice!
Damn Kagome!
What'd you do that for?!
Wait!
Show me how to control
this sword!
Seriously injured, Sesshomaru
makes his escape.
His severed left arm is
buried in his father's tomb.
Inuyasha takes possession
of Tetsusaiga...
a sword forged from
his father's fang.
He sets out in search of
fragments of the Sacred Jewel.
He comes to a town...
where young women are
taken to a mysterious castle...
and meets a young samurai
determined to save the princess.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Toad Who Would Be Prince"
Don't miss it!