Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings
a group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled by
the few remaining shards of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
Demon Ninjas come after
the blade of the Naginata of Kenkon,
and I end up becoming separated
from Inuyasha and the others.
And thus, I begin a fierce struggle to
survive along with Hojo's ancestor.
I found something amazing.
My ancestor, Akitoki Hojo,
who lived 500 years ago
during the feudal age....
Look at his wife's name.
Wife?
Hojo's ancestor...
What if...
I couldn't return to the modern age and
ended up marrying
Hojo here?
No way!
The one after the blade is
the leader of the Demon Ninjas, Hoshiyomi.
And Hoshiyomi is the one who
made Kaijinbo forge the Naginata.
Hojo, hang on!
Kagome! Akitoki!
Kagome! Kagome!
Kagome!
I don't have time for
the likes of you!
Who the hell are you?!
Genbu of the Darkness.
Byakko of the Snow.
Seiryu of the Moon.
Suzaku of the Flower.
Let's see how you counter
our Demon Ninja doppleganger technique!
Why the hell are they circling us?!
Sango and I will handle them.
Inuyasha, go after Kagome.
Take care!
We'll fight you!
You're starting to annoy me!
Be safe... Kagome!
Huh?!
Master Hoshiyomi!
So you're Hoshiyomi, huh?
Move outta my way!
Too easy!
Huh?!
Demon Ninja technique....
Shadow Incarnation.
To be saved by the Ken blade....
Such fortune in the midst of misfortune!
Where's Kagome?
Kagome!
Hojo!
Grab onto this!
Kagome, we'll be all right now.
Thank you, Hojo.
Oh! Misfortune has brought
me even more fortune!
Could this mean the end
of all my misfortune?
Are you all right, Hojo?
Just another misfortune....
And I'm quite used to it.
Huh?!
The river is ending!
Why you...!
Stop already. It's useless.
I am immortal.
Just who the hell is he?
Master Hoshiyomi!
Why are you still here?
Go after the Ken blade!
Yes, Master!
Which is the real one?
Damn, this is such a nuisance!
It didn't work!
You don't learn, do you?
He seems quite strong.
I'll deal with Hoshiyomi.
Find Kagome and Hojo.
Understood.
Let's go, Miroku!
Kirara, take us!
I'm not letting you follow them!
Hoshiyomi!
I'm your opponent!
I once heard of a half-demon who
fought Kaijinbo and his sword, Tokijin.
His name was Inuyasha.
Oh, Kaijinbo....
I seem to remember a guy
with that name.
Why do you protect
the Naginata of Kenkon
which was forged by Kaijinbo?
You have no affinity for it.
If I let the likes you possess
a demonic blade,
nothing good will come of it.
So what will you do?
This!
Wind Scar!
So foolish!
Demon Ninja tricks don't
work on me!
Huh?!
The sword trick you used
to defeat Kaijinbo
lives up to its reputation indeed.
So there you are!
However, I'll prove to you....
that you are no match for me.
Shaddup!
I'll blow you and your shadow
outta here!
Demon Ninja technique....
Shadow Hold!
W-Wha...?!
W- What's going on?!
My body won't move!
Kagome and Hojo fell
from this waterfall?
Yes.... They probably were
swept away by the rapids.
If they fell from that distance,
there's no way
they could have survived!
Hey! Don't be so morbid!
Huh?!
This is Kagome's....
Shippo, use your Fox Fire!
Oh....all right.
Fox Fire!
Sango!
Miroku, I'm going to check
the bottom of the fall.
Be careful!
There are whirlpools in
the basin of these falls.
I know!
The aura of the Ken blade is
coming from over there!
You're giving me the creeps!
Stop acting like that, will ya?!
Aww. That's so mean!
Huh?
Huh?!
What is that?
Beats me.
Does your leg hurt, Kagome?
Thanks to the medicinal herbs
you applied, the pain's gone.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry. I'm such a burden.
Not at all!
I carry the weight of
the Hojo name on my shoulders.
So you're not that
heavy in comparison....
Err.... I didn't mean
it quite like that....
You're not heavy, Kagome....
Hojo, are you all right?
Just another slight misfortune....
S-Sorry....
Hojo!
J-Just another slight misfortune....
There's no sign of
being followed.
So let's stop here
to rest.
All right.
I hope we can meet up
with Inuyasha and the others.
But if worse comes to worst,
we'll have to go to Furai Shrine
by ourselves
and seal the Ken blade.
I'm definitely not as
strong as Inuyasha....
Huh?
But when the time comes
to step up,
I, Akitoki, can be of service!
Can't do a thing
on an empty stomach,
so I'll go find something
to eat!
Great! The contents of
my backpack weren't washed away.
Huh?!
It's not much, but here you are.
Wow!
I'm so honored to be able to
eat food that you prepared
in a place like this!
You don't have to compliment
me on instant noodles....
Oh.... You don't like it?
Not at all!
It's delicious! Such a delicacy!
When I think of the man who
gets to eat your cooking every day,
I'm so jealous, I can't stand it!
I don't....
Keh!
I don't have anyone like that.
Oh, I see....
Well, I know you're traveling
with a monk and a half-demon....
I can't say that they're
suitable for you.
Huh?
But somewhere under
this sky....
there exists a man who was
born to share his destiny with you.
Destiny, huh?
Hojo, is there someone?
Are you engaged?
No....
Especially since being the heir
of the Hojo family is
not without its problems....
I guess so.
So many things are
happening in this era,
and it must be hard to
find a bride.
No such thing!
Why, I'd jump at the chance
to marry you!
Huh?
Err....
F-Forget what I said....
Have mine.
Thanks....
Let's rest a bit longer,
then we should head for Furai Shrine....
KAGOME
No! Why am I remembering that?!
But...
The only ones who can handle
a demon sword
are demons or half-demons
like me.
It's impossible for you guys!
Huh?
It's impossible for humans!
You guys don't understand!
I wonder if there's a deep river
between demons and humans...
that simply can't be crossed...
Kagome....
Could the "Kagome" that was
written on that scroll be...
Look! Those humans
are defenseless.
It's our chance to attack them
and take the Ken blade!
Don't be hasty.
What?
Don't you sense it?
The aura emanating from
the blade is so strong,
we wouldn't be able to handle it,
let alone control it.
I thought I'd be able to
taste blood again!
We'll wait until
Master Hoshiyomi gets here....
Or....
Suzaku....
Huh?
That picture you found earlier....
This?
Hmm.... Maybe we can use it.
Damn!
This is the Kon blade.
Isn't the aura magnificent?
Why did you have Kaijinbo
make such a blade?
Why do you want
the other blade so badly?!
It's none of your business!
And I'll say it again.
While this blade means
everything to me,
it has absolutely no value
to you and your friends.
If you back off,
I'll spare the other humans, too.
Or....will you throw
away your life?
I can move!
Does the power of the Shadow Hold
fade as my shadow fades?
Now what will you do?
Hah! I ain't about to waste my life
over a demon blade!
You're smarter than I expected,
half-demon.
You are a fool, after all.
Wha...?!
Just what the hell does
the Naginata of Kenkon mean to you?!
I owe you no explanation!
Oh....
Kagome is as beautiful
as a Bodhisattva.
If she were to marry into
the Hojo family....
all would be well.
Kagome Hojo....
That has such a nice ring to it!
Huh?!
Err.... I was just....!
Huh?
Y-You're....?
We're from a nearby village.
This time, it's their ancestors?
What are you doing
at this hour?
We were picking firewood
for tomorrow morning,
and we sensed your presence.
You became lost in the forest?
Let us take you to the village.
Really? That would be
a great help.
But could it be...
Let me borrow this
for a second, Hojo.
I thought the Demon Ninja
had disguised themselves.
But I guess I'm being
too suspicious.
Even Inuyasha, a half-demon,
was nearly overcome
by the power of the aura
of the blade.
But these girls seem
to be fine.
Is something the matter?
No, it's nothing.
Now then... I'll carry you
to the village.
I'll carry your belongings.
Err.... No!
This is very valuable to me.
I'm okay, too.
Demon Ninja technique,
Darkness Puppet!
With this technique, the puppets
won't be affected by the aura
and they'll be able to
steal the blade.
I almost had it!
I mean, he was about to
hand it over to me!
I keep telling you to cut
out that act!
Don't be hasty.
We have lots of chances left.
We'll catch them off guard.
Then we'll steal the Ken blade
and tear those two apart!
Oh, how scary!
I said to stop it!
How can I concentrate?!
Is something wrong?
Err.... No....
Umm.... May I ask what kind
of relationship you have?
We really don't have
a relationship.
I'm sorry.
You make such a nice couple,
I thought you were married.
Really? We look good together, huh?
Yes.
Kagome and Akitoki....
you make a wonderful couple.
Really?
Hojo, put me down.
Huh? I'm sorry!
I got carried away there....
Please don't get upset.
That's not it!
Why do you know our names?
You fool!
It's your fault for acting weird
and making me lose my concentration!
We have no choice.
Hah! They're such a bother!
Let's kill them and get it over with.
Just a minute!
Don't be rash!
Our target is the Ken blade,
that's all!
We know that!
W-What's going on?!
Those are puppets.
That's why the aura of the blade
didn't affect them.
Go!
Hojo! Take the Ken blade
and run to Furai Shrine!
I cannot leave you by yourself!
Hojo!
Kagome, get away!
Don't move!
A-All right!
Hojo!
Kagome!
Haven't you figured it out yet?
All the power you throw
at me
is being absorbed by the blade.
What?!
Dammit!
What is that?
This aura is from Hoshiyomi's
Kon blade!
Master Hoshiyomi,
we captured the girl, Kagome,
who was with that group.
You're okay!
Where's Kagome?!
Kagome was....!
What about Kagome?!
Kagome!
What will you do now?
Do you want to protect the Ken blade
even if it means this woman's life?
Kagome!
If you want to save this woman,
come to Furai Shrine.
And make sure you don't
forget the Ken blade.
It's all my fault!
That Kagome got involved
in all this....
That she fell into
Hoshiyomi's hands!
We don't have time for that now!
We must save Kagome from that demon!
But how?!
Tetsusaiga still hasn't transformed!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Great Duel at Shoun Falls!"
As long as we have spirit,
we can do anything!