After him! He has a
Sacred Jewel fragment!
Damn!
Where is he?! Find him!
Get the Jewel fragment from him!
Demons!
Help!
These demons are thirsty
for blood!
Drink your fill!
Suck out their blood!
Huh?! What's this?!
Warriors defeated in battle?
Looks like they were slaughtered.
I really can't stand this...
Everywhere we go,
there's nothing but war.
No, this wasn't a battle.
Huh?
Strange... The smell...
I don't smell blood at all.
Probably the work of
some demon.
And no ordinary demon
at that.
Which means, it probably possesses
a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Miroku!
Let's get one thing straight!
I have no intention of
teaming up with you!
I'm not giving you
any Jewel fragments!
What you mean is...
first come, first serve. Right?
Absolutely!
Well then, I shall take my leave.
It's probably better
this way.
He seemed quite dependable.
Say, Inuyasha...
Miroku is going.
Huh? Where's Inuyasha?
Help!
I'm supposed to deliver that!
Is this the thing
I smell?
Sit!
Hey! What're you doing?!
He's just an ordinary person!
What's with you anyway?
At that last place, I got a whiff
of ink.
If I follow that scent of the ink,
I'll find the demon.
And you kept such information
from us?!
If we don't hurry it up...
Miroku will get the
Jewel fragment!
Oh dear... Do you dislike
him that much?
Don't tell me you like
his type!?
Very much!
Nah, just joking...
Oh... Is that how the
wind blows?
Listen to me, will you?!
He's so stupid!
What?! You killed all
the soldiers?
Alone?
If that is true, I will gladly
hire you.
Thank you!
I had heard that those
mercenary soldiers...
were becoming a nuisance
to you.
I thought it the perfect opportunity
to demonstrate my strength.
My lord...
What?
What "heir to a
powerful family"?!
You're just a wandering
artist from the capital!
Err... no!
I AM powerful and killed
those soldiers!
I am not an artist!
Please let me see
the lord again!
Fool!
One of our men remembered
you from yesterday...
when you tried to sell
your worthless paintings!
Damn!
You there! Do not be
so harsh!
Yes, Princess... But...
Damn... You're lucky
she saved your life.
So beautiful...
Good riddance!
Good luck!
Don't catch a cold!
Never come again!
Damn!
Damn them to hell!
I can summon my demon
brigade and...
defeat any and all enemies!
I deserve to become
a warlord!
No one should have
any complaints!
I WILL own a castle!
I will prosper!
And yes! I will wed
a princess!
There is nothing I can't accomplish!
Hey, I want a word with you!
Wh-what?!
Huh?! Not again!
That's the sixth one!
He never gives up!
Wh-what?! Who are you?!
I'm a powerful!
I'm just an ordinary artist!
An artist?!
Just what did you do?
You reek with the smell of
blood mixed with ink!
Lemme go!
Hey, wait!
What??!
A demon!
Hey, wait! You!
What's going on?!
Is he a demon?
No, he's human.
Hah! Just big in size!
Black blood!
That's blood and ink!
Hey!
His nose is too sensitive...
and the stench of the blood
and ink got to him.
Snap out of it, Inuyasha!
Who is he? He got the scent
of the blood and ink on me.
But there's nothing to fear...
Behind me, I have battalions
of demons under control.
An exorcism?
I can sense an evil shadow
over this mansion.
I can exorcise the demons
in one night.
Fool!
This mansion is blessed
each year...
by a priest of status
which you'll never attain!
Go on home!
Lately, we've been plagued by rogues
who seek access to the mansion!
Evil shadow! Hah!
I see...
Too bad, I spend the night in
the forest tonight.
Is that for real?!
Run!
The evil shadow is here!
What's going on now?
Is he still at it?!
- Huh?!
- Wh-what!
The bull-head demon and
the horse-head demon!
I've only seen them
in religious depictions of hell!
Someone! Save the princess!
Coming!
Princess...
Princess!
What is the matter?!
Your face?
Your blood...
I want your blood!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop!!
Wh-what is that?!
Please stop!
Black ink rain?!
So while I was asleep...
the ink took action
on its own?
Monk...
Pardon the rudeness of
my men earlier.
I am so glad that you
protected my daughter!
No need to thank me.
However, you must not
let down your guard yet.
I doubt if the attack by
the demons is over.
Now, let's see...
I think it's best if the
princess stays with me tonight.
Same bedroom...
one bedding.
Hey!
Whaddya intend to do when
you have her alone?! You lecher!
Oh! Kagome and Inuyasha!
Damn... We're late!
Miroku, did the ink demons
appear here, too?
Ink demons?
Were those demons made
of ink?
An artist who manipulates
the demons?
But he wasn't a demon.
I see... It could be that
this artist...
is using the power of
a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Then the one who attacked
this mansion just now...
Yes... I'm sure that they are
demons controlled by the artist.
Demon drawings by the artist
come alive?!
The power of the Jewel fragment
is amazing!
Huh? Inuyasha?
Are you part of
this conversation?
Hah!
How long are you going
to sulk?
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Shut up!
Why can't you depend on
Miroku just a bit?
He's so jealous!
Wh-what?!
Who's jealous!?
I see... Kagome, you do
accept me then?
Yes. After all, you have
a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Huh?
Two... No, you have three.
You have sharp eyes...
Sit!
Kagome!
These are fragments that
I accumulated.
Taking them will make
you a robber.
You should talk!
Who was that used that tanuki...
to try to steal Kagome's fragment?!
Oh...
You have such a sharp memory...
What?! That artist manipulated
the demons?
Yes, sire! I understand he possesses
a Sacred Jewel fragment.
A fragment of the Sacred Jewel?!
I've heard rumors...
One fragment can increase your
power many-fold!
A jewel to treasure, indeed!
We will take it from
that artist!
Also, that monk seems...
He possesses it, too?
When did you?!
What's going on?!
I have done nothing wrong
to warrant your attack!
At least, not yet.
Hand it over!
The Sacred Jewel fragment!
Miroku, what happened?!
Aren't these men of
this castle?
They mentioned something about
a Sacred Jewel fragment.
Now, start talking.
We just wanted your
Sacred Jewel fragment!
Our lord went to get the one
the artist possesses.
So you know where the
artist is?
Where is he?!
Answer me!
Kagome!
I'm going to borrow
your contraption!
Wait for me!
Me, too!
Hang on! We'll catch up!
The enemy is created by the
power of the Jewel fragment!
Mortal men won't be able to
defeat it!
Go forth!
I have an infinite number
of soldiers!
All I have to do is paint more
of them with that ink!
Come forth, ye demons of hell!
Wait!
Someone! Calm my horse!
If you slay them, the noxious odor
will overcome you.
What'll you do, Inuyasha?!
Shut up!
You saved me!
I will reward you later!
Ughh! This ink smells awful!
Inuyasha!
How long must you sleep, Inuyasha?!
Miroku!
Stay behind me at
all times!
I shall open my Wind Tunnel!
What's that?!
My demons are being sucked in?!
Miroku!
It's the first time I've sucked in
so much evil at once.
I'm a bit exhausted...
Damn! Being rescued
by this guy!
What now?
This is also an ink painting, isn't it?
I won't let you get away!
Kagome!
Where's the Jewel fragment?!
I see it! Inside the bamboo
container on the waist!
Got it!
Right! I almost forgot to tell you!
Hey, Miroku! Stop showing off
by yourself!
Stubborn punk!
Go! Kill him!
Create havoc, will you?!
Oh? What kind of trick is that?
He's just slugging them.
What?! Giving up?
Repent and turn over
the Jewel fragment!
The burning fires of Hell
will consume you...
bones and all!
Why you!
That's enough outta you!
Fool!
As if I'd let a human kill me!
I'll never let you have it!
I'm going to grasp happiness
with this Sacred Jewel fragment.
Enough, I said!
My ink!
I'm losing my ink!
Oh, ink of mine!
Here is blood!
Come and suck this blood!
Gather round this blood!
That fool!
I will not let it go...
no one shall have my ink!
Blood...
My blood is being devoured
by the ink!
Help me!
Help... me!
Stupid fool...
Devoured up by ink!
How did this happen?
The evil ambitions of the artist
turned the ink...
into evil blood-sucking ink.
He let his own blood be sucked up
before he'd part with the Jewel.
He went mad because of
the Jewel fragment.
The Sacred Jewel fragment that
I came in search for is evil.
It's too dangerous to touch.
Wh-what... ?
Who wants to hold it?
Why must we discuss it?!
Well, Miroku saved us.
Kagome, you hang on to it.
- Huh?!
- Are you sure?
Aren't you lucky?
Miroku is so mature.
Humph!
She purified that tainted jewel fragment
just by picking it up...
Huh? You're coming with us?
Yes!
I think it's much more fun in the
company of a pretty girl.
Oh dear!
Hah!
Besides, despite his
looks and manners...
Inuyasha seems to be
quite nice.
Huh?
By slaying the artist, Inuyasha
could have ended it all quickly.
But instead, Inuyasha tried only
to destroy the ink.
That's right... He just doesn't
realize it...
Inuyasha is quite a nice fellow.
Some time has passed since Inuyasha
took possession of the Tetsusaiga.
I thought he had learned all there was
to know about...
using this sword forged from
his father's fang.
But the words of his brother,
Sesshomaru, came to mind.
"The power to slay a hundred
demons in one stroke...
"That is the secret of the Tetsusaiga."
Sesshomaru reappears,
even more powerful that before!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Naraku and Sesshomaru Join Forces!"
Don't miss it!