A giant, centipede-like demon
pulled me...
into the depths of the Hidden Well
in the shrine.
I'm just a girl in her third year
in middle school...
and nothing this strange has
EVER happened to me before.
A youth was held fast to
the Sacred Tree with arrows...
Inuyasha was his name, I think...
An eternal spell to hold him there
had been cast.
But it was broken.
Demons now seek to possess
something known as the Sacred Jewel.
This Sacred Jewel has appeared once
again in the era of the Warring States.
Iron Reaver, Soul Stealer!
Why was it inside my body?
This jewel which can empower
such a demon?
If you don't want to feel
the pain of my claws...
just give me the Jewel
and get it over with.
You... Kagome!
Do not hand over the Jewel!
The Sacred Jewel increases
the power of these demons.
Could it be cursed?
I show no mercy!
Especially to women whose
scent I dislike!
Next it'll be you,
split down the middle!
You were serious just now,
weren't you.
Shoot!
Who you think I am, anyway?!
Don't you dare treat me like
some dumb Centipede Monster!
Priestess Kaede!
Perhaps that arrow sealing the
spell shouldn't've been removed...
Oh, for pity's sake...
That troublemaking hellion!
Prepare yourself!
Prepare myself?! How can I?
Now it's mine!
What's this?!
Kagome! Recite the Word to
hold Inuyasha's spirit!
Huh? What?
Just say something!
To subjugate the Inuyasha!
Subjugate me, will you?!
You fool!
Subjugate him?
But what do I say?
S... S...Sit!!
Sit!
It held him.
Wh-What's this?!
Damn!
It's useless, Inuyasha.
Your powers cannot remove
the rosary.
Shut up, old hag!
You're first in line!
Tho' you look half-dead already.
The Word...
Sit!
Now, then... Let us
return to the village.
How weird...
All I said was "Sit."
Let's see... I'll apply more salve
on the wound on your belly.
Oww!
They're fixing the houses destroyed
by that Centipede Monster.
So much work!
This does not bode well at all.
Now that the Sacred Jewel
has reappeared...
there will be others who
seek to possess it.
Like yesterday...
And not just demons...
but also humans, who have
evil in their hearts.
With all the violence
in the world...
it follows there will be those
who seek the Jewel's power...
to realize their greedy ambitions.
Huh.
Hey! Why are you here anyway?
Give me the Sacred Jewel!
It seems the holding power
of the rosary is quite effective.
Even if he gets near
the Sacred Jewel...
we do not have to worry.
Why do you want
the Sacred Jewel?
You're awfully strong right now.
You don't really need its
power, do you?
He is only half demon.
You old hag!
Who do you think
you are, anyway.
Don't talk as if you know
all about me!
Don't you understand?
I guess it can't be helped.
I am the younger sister of Kikyo...
the one who put the spell
on you. I am Kaede.
Kaede?
So... You're that kid?
Fifty years have passed.
And I have grown old.
And that means...
Kikyo must be really
old now, too.
Humans age so easily.
That's the way it goes.
My sister Kikyo died.
On the same day that she shot
the spellbound arrow at you.
Ah, so that's how it went.
She kicked the bucket, huh?
What a relief!
Inuyasha, it is too early to
breathe a sigh of relief.
Kagome...
You are the reincarnation
of my sister, Kikyo.
What?
It's not just your appearance
or psychic powers...
but the fact that you carried
the Jewel within yourself...
that is irrefutable proof.
You must protect the
Sacred Jewel, Kagome.
I must protect this Jewel... ?
That's ridiculous...
She's what?!
High Priestess Kikyo's??
When you think about it,
she does seem quite saintly...
What's up?
The kid's the reincarnation
of High Priestess Kikyo.
Watch your language!
Show some respect
for the young lady!
The "young lady" is
a reincarnation!
They're worshipping me!
So... She's dead.
Here! I'll share with you.
What?! What's with
all that food?
The villagers' offerings.
Say, can't you come down?
Let's eat together.
You're up to somethin',
I know it.
Am not.
Only...
You do hate me, don't you?
You've noooo idea how much!
Look...
The one you hate is not me,
but this lady named Kikyo.
I'm Kagome!
I'm not Kikyo!
So won't you be
a little nicer to me?
Are you stupid or what?!
I don't care who you are!
In order to get the Sacred Jewel,
I have to be merciless!
I see.
In case you should decide
to get violent, then...
all I have to do is
say "sit," and...
Oops, sorry!
I didn't mean that.
Nnyagh!
It's been two days since
I arrived here.
Gramps.
Sota... Mom...
They must be so worried.
I've gotta find a way
to get back home.
Great. They've followed
the scent of the Jewel.
Nasty vermin...
The Inuyasha Forest... The Dry Well...
I climbed out of there...
so shouldn't it have a clue
about how to get home?
Kagome?
Kagome!
She's nowhere to be found
in the village.
She couldn't have left
the village alone?
I ought to have explained
to her in more detail...
about the evil ones who
seek the Sacred Jewel.
Found it!
The Dry Well I came out of.
Oww!
Boss!
I captured her
just like you ordered!
She really has some
strange clothes on.
What's this flimsy
wrap-around?
Cut it out, you pervert!
Well, you asked for it!
Exposing yourself like that!
You wanna marry me?
Wh-Who are you guys?
Give me the Jewel!
Hey, wait!
Hey Boss! Slice 'er in half
in one swift stroke.
Let me go!
Start praying!
B-Boss!
Made a mistake...
Boss, where are you aiming?!
It's her!
Aren't you gonna
slay this girl?!
There's something wrong with
your boss.
Snap out of it or it'll be
your turn next.
Don't you get it?!
No!
Will somebody tell me...
why is it that...
me, who hasn't done a thing...
has to go through this??
Oh, great. That stupid girl!
Where'd she go with
the Jewel?!
Are you all right?!
The exit is blocked!
Can you stand?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
The Jewel... Give me
the Sacred Jewel...
He wants this Jewel.
If I get rid of it, he won't
come after me.
And not just demons...
but also humans, who have
evil in their hearts.
All will come seeking the Jewel.
But why me?!
Anyway, I have to
get out of here!
Hey-y-y!
Huh...
I know!
Take him!
The Jewel... The Sacred Jewel!
Now! Let's all push against
the wall!
Boss! It's no good!
I am not your boss!
Inuyasha!
Boss, we're going ahead.
Thanks again...
You came to rescue me?
Is it safe? The Sacred Jewel!
Huh?
I'm asking you if the Sacred Jewel
is safe!
Well...
What's that smell?!
That putrid smell!
What?!
His heart must've been torn apart
a couple of nights ago.
Then it nested there.
He was being manipulated?
I thought something was
strange about him.
Corpse Crows aren't too strong.
They use dead bodies to fight.
Disgusting!
It got away!
Aren't you going after it?
I can't go after every
stupid demon.
There's only one of me,
after all.
But...
Forget it!
I'm the one doing the fighting!
So I decide!
Now what about the Sacred Jewel?
Ahh!
Is that the Jewel in its beak?!
Why, you!
I never said anything about
having it on me.
Follow me!
No way it's gettin' away.
What're you doing?!
Hurry and shoot that thing down!
Are you crazy?!
I've never used a bow and
arrow in my life.
The Corpse Crow survives by
eating human flesh!
With the Sacred Jewel,
it might transform!
It just swallowed the Jewel!
I'll try it.
All right!
Heh!
Once that crow is shot down,
I won't need a girl like her.
Make it one shot!
Kikyo was a master archer!
I am Kagome!
But if it's okay, Kikyo,
please lend me your power...
Hit it!
You're not lying about her
being a master archer, are you?
Then you must be a klutz!
Look, now it's gettin' bigger!
Aim!
Oww!
Now I get it!
No way you're
Kikyo incarnated!
Now I know not to
expect nothin'.
Inuyasha!
My son!
Looking for food already?
Well, you'd better think about
running away from me first!
You can't hunt if you're
bein' hunted!
No! Save the child!
Yeah, right!
Iron Reaver, Soul Stealer!
Where is it?
Where's the Sacred Jewel!
My son! Shokichi!
I'm glad I went to
swimming classes.
How is she doin' that?!
So fast!
She must be a kappa!
A water-imp!
First time I saw one up-close!
Help!
Hang on!
Relax...
The kappa is swimmin' on its back!
IMPossible!
I'll kappa you, you stupid...
Hey girl!
Where's the Sacred Jewel?!
Shokichi!
Ma! I was so scared!
Wh-What?!
Thanks, lady!
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
It's okay, really.
Ahh! It's gettin' away!
I guess this is no time to
be fighting.
Aha!
May I use your bow and arrow?
Huh?
But it's so far away...
No way she can get it.
This time, for sure...
I'll get it!
She attached the foot
of the Corpse Crow...
The crow's foot will be drawn by
the power of the Sacred Jewel.
I did it!
She got it?
But... what's that light?
Priestess Kaede...
Up in the sky!
I've got a bad feeling about this...
Are you sure it's around here?
Yeah... I feel it...
But I wonder what it was...
that light?
Die!
Could this be?
"Could this be"...what.
A fragment of the
Sacred Jewel?
Wh... What did you say?!
The Sacred Jewel is in pieces!
Since even ONE piece can
make demons powerful...
it's up to us to get them back!
Of course Inuyasha will
want them for himself...
What am I gonna do?!
Isn't a girl who uses hair
like wires bad enough?
Next time.
"Down the Rabbit Hole and Back Again"
See you soon!