Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The saintly mummy of Hakushin
who saved so many people
has disappeared.
With the barrier broken
on the sacred island of Hijiri,
Inuyasha and Bankotsu are back at full
strength and locked in their final battle.
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Give me power, Father!
This is what created
the barrier.
But this ornament was
locked up in the temple.
Is Saint Hakushin lending
his powers to Naraku?!
That disgusting barrier
is finally gone.
Let's do it once and for all.
Thank goodness his
demonic powers are restored.
But Inuyasha is at a disadvantage.
He's hurt his left arm.
Inuyasha, will you be all right?
Bankotsu has two Sacred Jewel
shards in his halberd Banryu.
Let's see you do it right this time....
Let me see this Wind Scar.
I don't need advice from you!
Die!
Wind Scar!
Dragon Hammer!
Bankotsu stopped....
the Wind Scar!
I just need to look
for the miasmic whirlpool!
I've been waiting to use
my Backlash Wave!
Huh?! I don't see a demonic aura
around Bankotsu!
Then I can't use the Backlash Wave?
Don't stand there in a daze!
Inuyasha!
Ahh....
I feel like a weight's been
lifted off my shoulders....
You're conscious, Shippo?
All I remember is that
I started feeling sick.
You fainted from the sacred
barrier of this island.
It seems to have purified
your demonic powers.
Is that why?
Where's Inuyasha?
He's having a tough time
fighting off Bankotsu.
Damn!
I guess you were gonna
try something,
but it didn't work.
Damn!
Inuyasha, keep it together!
Inuyasha's arm has been injured.
Is it bad?
Kirara!
Yes, Kirara!
Help Inuyasha!
He won't last long
with that arm.
Bankotsu is a specter,
but he was once human.
But the scope of his strength means
he's using some kind of demon power.
Backlash Wave is a technique
that surrounds and reverses
the flow of an opponent's
demonic aura.
But since Bankotsu was once human,
he doesn't produce any.
The Shikon Jewel shards want me
to destroy you.
The black light of a tainted shard.
Inuyasha!
Bankotsu is using the powers
of the Shikon Jewel shards in his halberd!
Perfect!
Now that I know,
I can use my Backlash Wave.
He's thought of something.
I won't fall for the same trick!
Do you think I would keep
using the same attack?!
Huh?!
He summoned a thunder storm.
Damn, what's he scheming?!
Arghh!
Take this!
Dragon Thunder!
Can't predict where they'll fall, though!
Tons of lightning bolts!
He won't be able to
use the Backlash Wave!
Watch out, Shintaro!
Kagome, don't leave the barrier....!
Aghh!
Kagome!
Sango!
Shippo!
Kirara!
Kagome....!
Kagome!
Kago....!
You dare....hurt....Kagome....!
I told you....
I can't predict where
my Dragon Thunder will fall.
Why don't you just lie there!
I'll cut you and your sword into pieces!
Arghh!
Why, you....!
This match is....
just between you and me!
Bastard!
You didn't have to involve
Kagome and the others!
Quit being so naïve!
Die!
Quit using the same techinque!
How many dirty tricks must
you pull before you're satisfied?!
Are you stupid?
There's no dirty or fair
in a match to the death!
I'll take you down even if it kills me!
You're mine!
Arghh!
W-What...?!
Saint Hakushin's altar ornament....
As I expected....
Saint Hakushin's...?
The demonic aura around the
Tetsusaiga has been purified...
What's the meaning of this?!
That vajra....
was at the core of the sacred barrier
around this island.
It seems Saint Hakushin....
Is an ally of Bankotsu.
That's impossible!
I guess he wants me to
finish you off quickly.
Although it bothers me that he
doesn't have faith in my ability.
Too bad this has to end, you all!
Kagome....
Woman.... Why you....
Coward!
Ahh!
His arm turned to bone.
A sacred arrow? So she's
Kikyo's reincarnation?
What...?!
Bankotsu is....
disappearing!
Why you.... Bankotsu!
Come back here!
Bankotsu!
Damn! A barrier!
He's gone!
Inuyasha!
Are you all right?
Yeah....but....
Not only Bankotsu.
But the vajra is also gone.
It helped Bankotsu escape?
Probably.
Saint Hakushin....
Where has Saint Hakushin gone?
Damn, I feel awful.
What the hell happened, anyway?
Where am I?
Bankotsu....
Kohaku and Kanna?
Where is this?
It feels awful here.
Not a very nice place for
men of evil thoughts.
But you're okay?
No wonder you're a ninja.
I'm not a ninja.
That's right. The light from the
vajra enveloped me...
Who is that....?
I get it.
He's the Saint Hakushin
Inuyasha kept talking about.
This is Saint Hakushin's mummy.
This is the mummy who created the
barriers around Mt. Hakurei and Hijiri Island.
Father....
died protecting the temple?
Saint Hakushin disappeared from
the island because of
a demon known as Naraku.
Father died fighting Naraku.
I see. He died honorably.
Our father's bones.
Father....
We will give him a proper funeral.
He's not here!
Where is he?!
You're late!
Hey, Koga!
Great! We finally caught up
to you.
I chased it until it
ran in here.
Meat! Meat! Meat!
It's huge!
Kinda reminds me of home.
But it feels bad in here.
Because of the barrier.
A barrier protects the mountain
so demons like us
can't get near it
and permeates even this cave.
Man, that's cautious.
We leave after we eat.
Huh?
The Band of Seven are hiding
inside the barrier.
I'll find a way to get through this
barrier no matter what!
Shintaro! Sisters!
Take care!
I'll pray for your good journey.
If for some reason,
you ever feel lonely,
please don't hesitate to call on me....
Oww!
That's enough, Monk!
Take care, all of you!
Wow!
Look at this valley, Jaken!
Even though we're far away
from Mt. Hakurei,
I still feel awful.
The purifying aura that keeps out
anything demonic reaches all the way here.
What are you up to, Naraku?
Lord Sesshomaru!
So cool!
Hurry!
Rin, don't leave me behind!
Don't go too fast.
I'll fall!
Please don't scream like that!
I can't help it.
- How annoying!
- I can't take this....
Lady Kikyo, must you go?
Forgive me.
I wanted to stay longer.
First, Dr. Suikotsu....
now, even you.
I hoped you would stay
until Dr. Suikotsu returned.
After all that happened,
you still wait?
Dr. Suikotsu suffered in pain sometimes,
but he was kind.
The virtuous side of Suikotsu
protected these children.
Yet...
If you meet Dr. Suikotsu,
please tell him that we
are waiting for him.
Yuta....
All right. I promise.
Because of Mt. Hakurei's barrier,
he disappeared.
Yuta, Chiyo... the Suikotsu
you knew is no longer...
The barrier has become
stronger since.
I've reached my limit, too.
The power of the barrier
is becoming stronger.
The barrier is making Shippo
so dizzy.
Hey Miroku, you sure Naraku is
hiding in Mt. Hakurei?
I'm sure that Saint Hakushin is
the one creating this barrier.
And the Saint protected
Bankotsu, one of Naraku's men.
I'd have thought that a mass of
evil air like Naraku
wouldn't be able
to enter a sacred place.
But once inside,
there's no better place to hide.
There are those after him....
The Wolf-Demon Koga,
Sesshomaru and you, Inuyasha.
As well as Lady Kikyo.... All are unable
to go to Mt. Hakurei.
Let's go.
Hey, you....
Sango and I will check
out Mt. Hakurei.
Inuyasha and Kagome,
you wait here.
But just the two of you?
Watch over Kirara.
I can't take her.
Sango....
Don't worry, Kagome.
From this point on, even I won't be
able fondle Sango's body....
You're doing it now!
I'm not worried about that.
We don't even know what's
inside the barrier.
But Inuyasha can't go in.
It has to be the two of us.
But....
Sango, Miroku.... Just check around.
Don't take any risks.
Exactly our intent.
We're off.
Will they be all right?
We just have to
have faith in them.
The Band of Seven?!
They disappeared?!
They've taken refuge
inside Mt. Hakurei!
Damn it! Ginkotsu! Renkotsu!
Come on out!
This is bad! Koga is trapped
in the steel threads!
If he gets dragged inside,
he'll be purified!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Koga's Solitary Battle!"
Where are their Shikon Jewel shards?!