Goshinki, a demon
created out of Naraku's body...
His fangs were used
to forge the evil sword Tokijin...
by Kaijinbo
who appeared before Inuyasha!
His eyes were strange...
and his movements,
as though he were being manipulated.
Playtime is over.
You should've killed me in one sweep.
Before this happened...
I'll slice you in half
along with your sword!
A draw?
Draw?! No way!
I'll admit that sword is a handful,
but that Kaijinbo isn't in control of it!
If this Tetsusaiga weren't
so damned heavy...
he wouldn't be a problem!
Damn that Totosai!
This thing is so heavy!
Hah! You can't even lift up
that sword properly!
Damn!
Prepare yourself!
You're about to die!
W-what?!
Totosai...
Your sword isn't much.
This is!
The sword held up...
but Kaijinbo himself was unable
to withstand the power of the sword.
The very sword he forged
overpowered him.
The fool!
Totosai... you!
Still got complaints?
How am I supposed to hold
such a heavy sword?!
One thrust is all I can handle!
Want to know how to handle
the heavy Tetsusaiga?
There's a way to handle it?
It's simple.
You're not gonna tell me
to build up my strength, are ya?!
Correct.
I knew it.
He shouldn't have said so.
What's going on?
The evil aura around the sword
hasn't dissipated.
The aura is too strong,
I can't draw out the sword.
Whoever commissioned Kaijinbo
to make such a sword?
We'll have to construct a barrier
around the sword...
or we won't be able
to contain the aura.
Miroku, can't you put
a sacred spell on it?
The aura is too strong.
I don't know if my spells
will be able to seal it completely.
Well, we're lucky to have you here.
Why don't you build
a tower to contain it?
In order to create a tower
to surround it...
we'll need to hire men
and that takes money.
Money. You always make money
with your fake fortune-telling.
Fake? How rude!
Isn't it a monk's job to help people?
It is, but...
I need money to have fun
with ladies and...
so I don't know whether we'll
make enough.
Shape up, Miroku!
What're you blabbering about?!
You're just wasting time!
I'll use the Tetsusaiga to blast it to bits!
What?!
Can't this be broken?!
Such evil aura.
Almost like it's alive.
Say... I wonder who ordered
such a sword to be made?
We'd better leave this place
before that person appears.
You're saying to run away?!
Anyone who is able
to draw out a sword of such evil...
will have enormous power.
You're no match right now.
I'll wait here!
Inuyasha!
It'll be dangerous to wait around here.
Yes! It's wiser to get away for now.
No!
I'm not moving from this spot!
Listen, Kagome...
knowing Inuyasha's personality,
he'll never budge.
Let us just watch him for a while.
Yes...
We'll wait one day until
Inuyasha calms down a bit.
Tomorrow morning,
if he still insists on staying put...
use your command on him
to make him sit...
then I'll knock him unconscious
with my staff.
Then we'll all carry him away.
Isn't that a bit too drastic?
Perhaps... but it can't be helped.
Hmm... yes... I understand.
Then, tomorrow morning.
Did I say something bad?
He's late, Lord Sesshomaru.
That Kaijinbo,
where'd he go with that sword?
Lord Sesshomaru!
Rin, stay put.
A woman...
This smell...
Just like that strange one
who approached you...
with the arm with
the Sacred Jewel fragment...
The one wearing the baboon hide.
Because of him,
we went through hell that time!
You almost got devoured by an arm...
and I was beaten to a pulp
by that depraved monk!
Just recalling that time makes me sick!
It's a scent I remember.
The same scent as the one
who tried to trap me, the beast Naraku.
Hmm... so you're Sesshomaru,
Inuyasha's older brother?
Pretty slim.
I'm Kagura the Wind Sorceress.
Just another incarnation of Naraku.
Incarnation?
Yes...
And the fangs you gave to Kaijinbo
to make the sword...
were those of
a demon named Goshinki.
Like me, he was also
created out of Naraku.
So what?
Did you come just to tell me that?
Don't you smell it?
The sword which reeks with the
aura from Goshinki...
Tokijin is so close.
That sword belongs to you.
What's with that woman?
So arrogant.
Rin, you may move.
O-okay.
Tokijin...
You're so strange.
Shut up!
Stop mumbling the same thing
over and over!
I will not shut up until you promise!
You must never throw away
the Tetsusaiga again!
What do you think, Kagome?
I think we should tell Inuyasha the truth.
The truth?
That the Tetsusaiga also serves to
keep Inuyasha's demon side sealed?
Yes. He doesn't know it,
so he carelessly casts the sword away.
That time, Inuyasha transformed
trying to kill Goshinki.
I wonder if we should tell him?
Nope, nope...
You must not tell him!
Old Myoga!
You know Master Inuyasha.
If he learns about the secret,
rather than the sword...
he'll rely on his transformed claws
and fangs to fight.
Hmm... will it become a habit then?
Of course! After all, Master Inuyasha
is such a simpleton at heart.
I totally agree.
Geez, but you're a busy fellow.
Changing into a human one minute,
then a monster in the next.
Don't call me monster!
I don't know what's going on myself!
Don't you know? You are stupid!
Totosai!
What're you going to tell him?!
Oh no!
Myoga told me that when
you're on the verge of death...
you transform.
Well... demon's blood
does make up half of you.
But if you ask me,
that's not true strength.
Inuyasha, as I explained, the weight of
Tetsusaiga increased due to your fang.
Originally, the Tetsusaiga was forged
from just your father's fangs.
In other words,
you relied on your father for protection.
However, this Tetsusaiga is different.
You must master your own fang
and protect your own self.
When you can freely wield
this new Tetsusaiga...
is when you will truly have
found your strength.
Yes!
Master Totosai is absolutely correct!
- Yes, yes!
- Inuyasha, hang in there!
Inuyasha, you're strong!
When you put your mind to it,
you can do anything!
W-well... yeah.
Dang, why do I feel like I've been had?
W-what...
Sesshomaru!
There he is!
Why're you here?
That's my line.
I only came after this sword.
I guess the demon
you killed was so bitter...
it wanted revenge against you
even after it became a sword.
W-what?!
He knows that Tokijin was made
from the demon's fangs.
Which means...
I am the one who commissioned
Kaijinbo to make the sword.
Sesshomaru, do not touch the Tokijin.
Even you will be possessed
by the Tokijin's evil aura.
Just who do you think I am?
The evil aura...
is dissipating!
The evil aura was overtaken
by Sesshomaru!
I don't like him!
Humph... the sword chooses its master.
Draw your sword, Inuyasha.
I want to verify something.
You want to verify
something about me?
Stop, Inuyasha!
Get back, Kagome!
Do you think you can win?
Hah! He's not one to wait if I tell him to.
Exactly. So come at me, Inuyasha.
If you don't, I will attack.
Damn!
Don't regret it later, Sesshomaru!
Damn, it's so heavy!
It's all he can do to resist the blow!
He's losing to the power of the sword!
This is bad!
There's no way that Inuyasha
can win like that.
Well... he doesn't know how
to use Tetsusaiga.
And this sword, the Tokijin, which is
dangerous in anyone's hands...
was commissioned by Sesshomaru.
D-damn!
As I thought,
I only smell the blood of a half-demon.
However, that time...
Inuyasha's blood definitely changed.
Just what did that mean?
I'll see with my own eyes.
I must finish this in one blow
or I'll be killed.
Did you alter
the way you fight, Inuyasha?
You usually come at me blindly.
Damn. Just shaddup!
Hmm... It seems the Tetsusaiga
has gotten a bit heavier.
Not just a bit, damn you!
You are better off without a sword
that is too heavy for you!
The Tetsusaiga has been!
Inuyasha!
No! It's like David and Goliath!
D-damn!
Master Inuyasha, hurry
and get a hold of the Tetsusaiga!
Old Myoga...
I don't need it!
Huh? No sword?
No, Inuyasha!
He plans to fight Sesshomaru
with only his bare hands!
Master Inuyasha, don't be rash!
With such a heavy sword
I'd lose even a match I can win!
Master Inuyasha!
Shaddup! Just stay back!
Ouch!
He's been thrown
by the power of the sword!
Why you!
I see now. Enough of this.
Die!
No! Run, Inuyasha!
This smell...
Inuyasha!
He can't be...
transforming again!
Everyone, take Inuyasha and get away.
Totosai...
Hurry!
Miss Kagome!
Sit!
But why didn't you go after him
when you had cornered him?
Lord Sesshomaru?
To think that he made me, Sesshomaru,
tremble with fear for a second.
Inuyasha was, at that moment...
He's strong.
He might be able to kill Naraku.
My heart is in Naraku's hands.
However, no way will I remain
a servant forever to him!
I am the wind!
One day, I shall be free!
Juromaru...
Naraku's fourth demonic incarnation!
He's expressionless
and you can't tell where he's looking...
but he moves with super speed
and even Inuyasha is no match for him!
Juromaru has an older brother
named Kageromaru...
and they've come at us
like a tag team!
But our side has Miroku
and Sango, too!
And even Koga comes to our aid!
No way can we lose!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Juromaru and Kageromaru"
Don't miss it!