So you've brought her.
K-Kagome...
I did it!
I win.
Banzai!
- Banzai!
- Wrong one...
You're really good, Kagome.
Miroku, I'm disappointed in you.
These karuta cards are so fascinating.
They're not karuta.
We call it trumps. (playing cards)
Torampu?
Trumps.
Cut out the racket!
Can't you play quietly?
Say Inuyasha, come and join us.
Not interested!
Why's he so angry?
He's in a bad mood.
Inuyasha!
Sulking won't make
Tetsusaiga any stronger.
Shaddup! I'm not!
Naraku's barrier...
Until he's able to break the barrier,
we can't even touch Naraku.
Wind Scar!
The Wind Scar had no effect.
I told you...
I continue to grow stronger.
It's a problem, all right.
Hah! No need to worry.
I'll take care of it!
What'll you do?
Have you any ideas?
Knew it! You haven't got a clue!
Shouldn't have gotten
my hopes up.
Hey you guys!
Leave it to me.
Huh?
Inuyasha!
Old Myoga...
I know how to handle
Naraku's barrier.
You know something?
I hurried over just to tell you.
Tell me!
And I'll let you suck all the blood
you want outta Kagome.
Why me?!
This is no time for jokes, Inuyasha.
You must go immediately to
the nest of the Demon Bats.
Demon Bats?
Near a village on the
western shores
is the nest of the
Demon Bat Tribe.
The nest is protected by
an impenetrable barrier
and no one is able
to destroy them.
The guardianship of the
barrier is passed down
from generation to generation.
You must kill this
guardian demon.
To put it plainly,
kill the demon guardian who
has the power to put up this barrier
and let Tetsusaiga absorb
its blood.
By killing a strong opponent,
Tetsusaiga will synergize
his power?
And make Tetsusaiga stronger?
Exactly.
Now then.
Kagome, your blood...
Awright then, let's go!
Demon-hunting, huh?
If that's all it takes
to make Tetsusaiga stronger,
I'll kill a hundred,
even a thousand of 'em!
You lied to us!
You said if you gave your
daughter to them,
Our village wouldn't
be attacked!
Well?!
More villagers have
been killed!
That's not what you promised!
Why'd they attack us?!
She's probably one of them...
one of those Demon Bats!
Yeah! Show no mercy!
Let her have it!
H-Huh?
W-Who're you?!
You mentioned Demon Bats
just now.
Tell me where their nest is.
Are you all right?
How dare you attack
a woman like that!?
As if we would know
where the nest is!
Ask that woman!
She's a rotten bitch who
calls herself human,
but bore the child
of a Demon Bat!
The child of a demon?
Why do you want to know
where the nest is?
Well...
I'm gonna destroy them.
Huh?
Wait a minute, Inuyasha.
You said you gave your child
to the Demon Bats.
What does that mean?
The Demon Bats have always
lived in this region.
They prey on humans and animals
and suck out their blood...
they're frightening demons.
But Tsukuyomaru...
My daughter's father, Tsukuyomaru,
was different.
He did not kill humans.
And after Shiori was born,
I don't know if he convinced
the other Demon Bats,
but they stopped attacking
Our village.
Yes, Our village was at peace.
Was?
Tsukuyomaru died.
And there was no one
to stop them.
Aghh! The Demon Bats!
Soon after, Tsukuyomaru's father,
Taigokumaru, who is Shiori's grandfather,
came to see me.
If I handed Shiori over to him,
he promised to leave our village alone.
Taigokumaru and Tsukuyomaru
were guardians of the barrier,
a duty passed down from
generation to generation.
And Shiori, as Tsukuyomaru's daughter,
was needed to carry on the work.
Why did it have to be Shiori?
If this Taigokumaru had
the guardian power...
Power wanes.
And once one passes on
his duty, he loses the power.
In other words, Shiori is
the only one remaining
who has the power to
protect the barrier?
Hah! Hah! Demon child!
Half-demon! Half-demon!
I'm home, Mommy.
Shiori! How'd you get
those scratches on your face?
It's nothing. I just fell.
What's the matter?
I just fell, I said.
I'm so sorry!
I agonized over this,
but in the end,
I gave up my Shiori
to Taigokumaru.
So you've brought her.
As I promised.
In return, never attack
Our village again!
Yes, I give you my word.
Now Shiori, go.
I changed my mind.
I'm afraid of Grandfather.
Please go, Shiori!
For the sake of the village!
Mommy!
Forgive me.
You'll be happier
over there.
Pardon my asking, but
Shiori is half-demon, right?
Would a half-demon child
have such powers?
From the looks of it,
you are also a half-demon.
Then you understand that just
because you're half a demon doesn't mean
you're accepted by the demon world,
nor does it mean you're
embraced by humans.
Well, Inuyasha?
I wonder.
Shiori had ample power to
fulfill her duties.
That's why...
I thought it was for her good
to go to them.
And if that would save
the village, I thought...
But the Demon Bats went
against their word.
- Take me there.
- Huh?
Take me to that old man,
whatever his name is.
Then we'll go, too.
No! I'll be fine alone.
But!
I'm the one who has
business with 'im.
Penny for your thoughts?
I was thinking back...
Old Myoga!
Why'd you follow me?!
And why not?
I won't be in the way.
I told you not to come!
Go back!
Don't say that.
This way.
Let us go, Inuyasha!
Do as you please!
Eat.
Huh?
I cannot have you
starving to death.
That cave over yonder.
Where it glows.
Huh? Mommy!
Shiori!
Myoga...
You sure about this?
The way to make Tetsusaiga stronger?
Yes... You must kill that girl.
Shiori! Shiori!
Mommy!
I wondered what
the ruckus was.
It seems we have visitors.
Is he the one?
Taigokumaru.
You tricked me!
Hmm? What are you talking about?
You promised to leave the
village alone in return for Shiori!
Yet...
You really believed it?
As if a demon would really
keep a promise to a human!
Then return Shiori to me!
Mommy...
I will not.
Shiori will be the guardian of
the barrier for the rest of her life.
She inherited the duty from her
late father, Tsukuyomaru,
and she is doing a fine job.
It's hard to believe that she
has a human for a mother.
Hey lady, I think the only way to get
your daughter back is through force.
Force? Can you?
That cocky, old bat... He's standing
in front of Shiori.
If I attack now,
I can get him
without hurting Shiori.
Wind... Scar!
What?!
He repelled my Wind Scar!
Oh dear! The barrier of the Demon Bat
is to be feared!
Rumor was right about
it being impenetrable!
Just who are you, kid?!
It doesn't matter who I am!
Give Shiori back!
I see... So the mortals sent you.
Well, you can die here!
I won't miss this time.
Why you!
Stop!
Please stop, Grandfather!
Please don't hurt Mommy.
I'll work hard.
So please...
Please don't hurt Mommy!
Did you hear that?
This child has far more
sense than you!
Why you! Cut it out!
Let me ask.
Do you think Shiori will be
happy back in the village?
Huh?
I know it all.
The villagers ostracized her
because Shiori is a half-demon.
And because they valued
their lives more,
they didn't hesitate for a second and
offered Shiori to me.
How can I return my dear granddaughter
to such selfish villagers.
It didn't work?
I'll resign myself to this.
But...
What Taigokumaru said
was true.
This village didn't accept
me or Shiori.
Maybe she's better off there.
Hah! You're so naïve.
Huh?
Demons never accept half-demons.
Even if they're blood kin.
I'm a fine demon.
And I accept you, Inuyasha!
Me, too!
Isn't it only 'cuz
I protect you!
Anyway, as long as Inuyasha cannot
break the barrier,
nothing can be done.
And didn't we come here
because of that?
Hah! I know that!
Kill a half-demon who guards
a strong barrier...
and let Tetsusaiga absorb
his blood.
Then Tetsusaiga would grow
in power
and be able to break
through Naraku's barrier.
But...
No way can Inuyasha kill
the half-demon.
She's just a little girl.
Mommy...
I want to see you.
If only Father were alive...
Why did he have to die?
I guess she misses her mother.
If this keeps up, there's no telling when
she'll ask to go back to the village.
Then... I will make them disappear...
Your village and your mother!
Huh?
Half-demon?
Mother... What is a half-demon?
Inuyasha...
Huh?!
It's you, Kagome.
Thinking about Shiori?
Not only that.
You're so kind, Inuyasha.
Stupid! I'm not!
It must've been hard for you...
I probably couldn't imagine
the hardship...
But you know, Inuyasha?
I...
No, not only me...
But even Miroku, Sango,
Shippo and Myoga...
I know.
Good boy!
Oww! Don't treat me like a dog!
Huh?!
What's the matter?
Huh? That's!
A whole colony of Demon Bats!
I'll work hard as the
guardian of the barrier,
so please spare Mommy and
the villagers.
Little Shiori-
So young, yet so diligent!
But unless Inuyasha kills this
innocent child,
Tetsusaiga can't increase its power!
How can Inuyasha do such a thing?
Wait!
There's just one way!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Red Tetsusaiga Breaks the Barrier!"
Inuyasha's concern transforms Tetsusaiga!