I'm Kagome Higurashi, a ninth grader.
My family are caretakers of
a very old, historic shrine...
and I've led a very normal life.
But on my fifteenth birthday,
I was dragged into the civil war period...
by a demon who suddenly appeared
from the old shrine well.
Here, countless demons
wishing to increase their power...
search for the Sacred Jewel.
This is where I met a half-demon
named Inuyasha.
Inuyasha wants the Sacred Jewel
to become a full-fledged demon...
Ever since, we've traveled together
from place to place...
in search of Sacred Jewel Shards which
are scattered throughout the country.
We've fought many demons in our search
for the Sacred Jewel Shards,
but we've also made friends
along the way.
Shippo is a very cute fox demon child.
He always tries so hard and helps us
with his fox magic.
Miroku is a monk.
His Wind Tunnel, inflicted on his palm
by Naraku's curse,
has the power to suck anything
into it.
He's a dependable person, but...
Sango is the last survivor of a
tribe of demon slayers.
Her mission is to destroy Naraku
to avenge her tribe...
and so, she has been traveling with us.
The worst one is that Naraku!
Without sullying his hands, he resorts to
dirty tricks and sets sneaky traps...
A despicable beast!
He's been steadily collecting the
Shikon Jewel Shards,
growing more and more powerful.
But we'll pool our strength together,
and someday, we'll get rid of him!
We'll seek out Naraku's castle
and destroy him!
Our journey continues!
I'm so sorry to trouble you.
But I felt this sudden pain.
Don't mention it. It's all part
of a monk's duty.
Not again.
Again.
Yup, again.
How do you feel now?
Thank you very much.
I feel much better.
But you shouldn't overexert yourself.
No, I'm fine now.
Really?
Well, I'm glad then.
By the way...
Yes?
Will you bear my child?
Not again.
Again.
Yup, again.
I'll be off.
Take care.
Miroku...
Why do you always come on
to pretty girls?
It's just that I cannot ignore
a girl in distress.
Hah!
Anyway, we must hurry.
You're the one who kept us waiting!
Thank you!
Oh! Say, how about taking a short break?
That sounds nice.
- Huh?
- What?
What's the matter, Miroku?
My travel funds... my money... is gone.
What?!
I'm sure I had it this morning.
It must've been that woman
at the roadside!
She was a pickpocket!
What?
No wonder she didn't go bonkers when
you stroked her butt!
What have I done?!
C'mon! Let's go!
Say! Where's Miroku?
What happened to him?
He was lagging behind a while ago.
Maybe he's depressed
after getting robbed.
I'll go check.
Hmm...
What is it?
No. Nothing.
Ho... I see.
We're all worried sick and
we don't know what to do.
Well, there's no need to worry
any longer.
What are you doing, Monk?
Huh? Well... nothing... yet.
The men who went into the mountain
haven't returned?
We're sure they've been captured
by demons.
Please help us!
Saving people for free again?
Come on, Inuyasha!
Please!
Please help us!
Please... save my husband!
You have a husband, too?
Yes.
I guess it's very lonely without
your husband.
Oh please, Monk, lend us
your power.
All right. We shall go and
free your men.
Thank you so much!
Got that, Inuyasha?
Well, I'm the one that has to
deliver the finishing blow.
Exactly.
Now then, let us go.
Please be very careful.
According to rumors,
the demon is a beautiful woman.
I shall go alone.
But why did Miroku go off by himself?
He probably wants to be alone
with the beautiful demon.
He never learns, does he?
Sango, are you following him?
Of course!
Leave that womanizing monk and
he'll be the one who gets bewitched.
Come on, Kirara!
Say, Inuyasha.
Huh?
I've been thinking...
I'm willing to bet that Sango has
feelings for Miroku.
Huh? What're you saying?
Haven't you noticed?!
Huh?
I sorta had an inkling.
You're so dense!
Well...
You've seen how Sango gets upset
when Miroku strokes her buns.
Listen... Women are creatures that
cherish mood.
What's "mood"?
Huh?
Err... well...
Anyway, Sango likes Miroku!
I wonder about that.
Hey! What're you sighing for?
Nothing.
Do you get it? We're going to
destroy a demon!
I know.
According to the villagers,
long ago, defeated soldiers escaped
deep into this mountain.
And there was a princess among them.
But all the men who protected her died.
And eventually, the princess also died.
Oh?
And her bitterness turned her
into a demon?
That's about it.
Hmm...
I guess that's how women are.
Huh?
Well... women certainly are persistent,
prone to jealousy and bursts of anger,
and hatred... I've known so many like that.
You're so experienced.
However, even I don't know what kind
of demon is created...
from the bitterness of a princess who
dies a lonely death.
l just have to see with my own eyes.
Still, why decide to go alone?
Well... I have my reasons.
Can you see it, Sango?
Huh?
It's the entrance to the other side.
Furthermore, this barrier...
...seems easy to enter,
but difficult to exit.
Here.
Put it on. It may prove helpful.
Okay.
Let us go!
Yes!
Miroku! Easy to enter?
You must've been kidding!
Such strong resistance!
Miroku!
Sango!
Where are you, Sango?
We've been separated.
A mansion?
Who is there?
Why are you here so deep
in this mountain?
A demon... this girl?
Well, whatever the reason,
come to the house.
Miroku!
Where are you?!
Demons?!
People...
Old men... all of them!
Umm... Old man...
Ehh?
Say, old man!
I... ain't an old man!
Y-You are old.
I ain't old!
I ain't old either.
Ain't one either.
I ain't an old man!
Ain't old!
Ain't an old man!
You're all not... old?
Miroku's the problem.
I wonder how he feels about Sango?
Any woman will do for him.
But I think Sango is a special case.
Well, he does try to feel up Sango's
butt often enough.
C'mon! I don't mean it like that!
I'm tired of all this talk.
Huh? You're the men who disappeared
from the village?
What happened?
It was like a dream...
I was lost and in trouble when the
most beautiful princess appeared...
She brought me to a magnificent villa
and I had such a grand time.
Grand time?
It was grand...
Yeah... It sure was grand.
Then when we snapped out of it,
we were like this.
The demon sucked the life spirit,
the youth, out of the men.
You survived the war?
Yes...
And my vassals have all died.
I am alone... and very lonely.
How tragic.
Monk...
Huh?
I am unable to
leave this place.
Will you spend at least the night
with me?
Is that your wish?
Monk... Please look
into my eyes.
Anyway, when the princess gazed
at you with those eyes...
I was mesmerized and nothing
mattered anymore.
Kirara, you stay close to
these people.
Cripes! That womanizing monk
will fall right into her trap!
Princess!
Oh Monk!
Miroku!
Stay alive until I get there!
Why that...!
Wake up, you lecherous monk!
A woman's voice?!
Princess!
Damn! Where are you?!
You will not interfere!
It cannot see me?
All right!
Wait, Sango!
Miroku! Weren't you bewitched?
Don't speak! If you remain quiet,
it won't know where you are.
I see! It's the power of the beads
that Miroku gave me.
But why isn't he destroying the demon?
The true form of the demon is
a female coyote.
Become part of my power!
Miroku!
Stay away!
I wanted to take care of this
quietly, but...
Princess! You'll have to endure
a bit of pain.
Princess?
Please bear it!
A princess inside the demon?
Princess!
Damn monk!
I shall show no mercy now!
Princess!
Give back the princess!
Sango!
Okay!
Hiraikotsu!
Why you!
Where are you?!
Where?!
There you are!
My power...
The demon power l gathered...
Miroku... What's the meaning of this?
I was very rough.
Monk...
You were alone for so long.
It must've been lonely.
Yes, because I was so weak-hearted,
I fell victim to a demon.
You'll be all right now.
I'll take you to the village.
Thank you very much.
She disappeared.
That is her soul.
She died all alone.
Rather than bitterness...
it was loneliness that kept her
from finding peace in death.
The demon coyote stole the
princess' body and soul,
then impersonated her to lure men...
and sucked out their youth
to gain strength.
I've placed the princess' ashes
in this grave.
If you offer prayers, I'm sure
she will watch over the village.
Thank you so much!
You brought our men back
home to us!
It was like a beautiful dream...
I'll say.
Miroku?
Yes?
Did something happen
in that mountain?
Sango has seemed awfully depressed
since coming back.
Well... I don't know what it could be.
I feel like such a fool.
Sango...
What's the matter?
Miroku, you really didn't need me there.
No such thing! You're the one
who destroyed the demon.
Only because you helped me.
No, I relied on your help.
Because I believed in your strength.
You're imagining things!
Sango wouldn't fall in love
with that lecher!
Why not? Look at that mood!
So what is "mood" anyway?
Sango, you came because you were
worried for my safety, right?
Well... that's... of course, I was worried!
When it comes to women,
you don't discriminate.
I was sure you'd get into trouble.
Forgive me.
l just couldn't ignore a woman
who might be grieving.
I'm not jealous or anything!
That's what you call "mood."
Mood!
More than any woman...
Your concern for me
makes me happiest.
Hey! What're you saying?!
Oh no! What'll I do?!
Go for it, Sango!
Sango?
That hand...
Why not touch my shoulders...
or somewhere more...
Don't you know anything else!
Well... She seemed to be silently
begging me to touch her.
Miroku...
Rather than women themselves,
you need to brush up on knowing
women's feelings.
See? Didn't I tell you
that you're all wrong?
See?
Boy, such a fool!
Better fix it.
What?! Going back home again?
Do you like "tests" that much, Kagome?
Well, it can't be helped.
I have things I need to do.
What is this creepy-looking fruit?
A fruit with a human face from Togenkyo?!
Are you kidding?!
Using humans to make
anti-aging potions?!
And you call yourself a sage?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Fateful Night in Togenkyo, Part l"
Damn! The moon is disappearing!