Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings a
group of strangers together.
500 years across time, their
destinies are controlled by
the few remaining shards
of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
A detestable demon appears!
I love pork cutlets,
but I refuse to become
a demon's bride!
That's what I thought...
But things didn't turn
out quite the way I expected.
For the first time in ages,
I went home to the present.
While I was taking part in
the Cultural Festival,
we ended up having to put
down several demons.
What a time it was!
A demon!
Inuya-I mean, Pekopon!
Do something!
You don't need to
say it!
Wind Scar!
Hah! How's that?!
Finally, it was time to
return to the Feudal Era.
We have to do our best to
find the remaining shards
of the Shikon Jewel.
Father....Mother....
Tonight I will have
to leave you....
Don't worry. We're all
going to protect you.
How could I give my daughter
to marry a demon?!
Here he comes!
Where is she?
My lovely bride!
It's here!
How lovely....!
My dear girl.... Will you
bear my children?
Yes, Master!
Then come, my bride!
What? A demon who
steals young girls?!
Yes.
You see, our shrine was demolished
by a band of demons
as they came flying through,
and the demon which had been sealed
inside was set free.
That demon, whenever he sees
a beautiful, young girl,
he asks if she will bear
his child and then abducts her.
How awful!
It's atrocious!
Wanting them to have his babies!
How dare he!
As if you're one to talk!
Those villages that refused him
were thoroughly destroyed.
What a despicable being!
We'd love to help you out,
but we have the remaining
jewel shards yet to find....
But we can't just leave
them like this!
Those demons appeared because
of Mt. Hakurei, didn't they?
So, is there no one
who will help them?
Well, I guess it's up to me.
I'll go.
Inuyasha!
I can take care of the little snits
and be back in no time.
I'm sure if Inuyasha goes,
there'll be no problems at all.
Thank you so much!
We can't leave our beautiful maidens
in the cave forever!
What did you just say?
We've gotten all the lovely girls
from the surrounding areas
and put them into a cave
where the demon can't find them.
I think I'll go with you!
I'd worry if Inuyasha
goes all by himself.
Sango, you're going, too?
I'm also worried
about the young girls,
but not for the reason
Kisuke mentioned....
Kaede! We'll
be back in no time!
They all ended up going?
The demon only goes after
young, single girls.
Hmm....? Young? Single?
- We have to stay on our toes.
- Don't worry. I will.
What is Sango all
worked up about?
You're as clueless as ever.
There it is!
It's that cave!
- Kisuke!!
- Oh!
Everybody! Kisuke has returned
with help!
- Kisuke!
- How wonderful!
- Thank goodness he's back!
- We're saved!
What's with them?
Everybody! You can relax now!
I've brought these experts
at killing demons!
- Thank goodness!
- I'm so glad!
You can trust these
folks completely!
Yup! Except their character....
Hey?!
I was speaking of Miroku....
I'll get right to it.
On the way over here
I thought of a strategy
to keep the demon from
choosing you all as brides.
Is there a way?
There is. Just one....
The demon only chooses
single girls.
Yes, that's right!
In that case....
Miss? Will you have my baby?
Then the demon won't want you!
I see....
Monk....!!
Huh?
That joke isn't funny!
A demonic aura!
Oh, no! He may have
found this place!
Inuyasha!
So this guy was the cause of
the presence I've been feeling....
He stinks of a wild beast!
Miroku!!
Master Miroku? Please hurry!
- Yes.
- And then me!
Now, this is to ensure
a safe delivery....
You girls can't believe
everything you hear!!
Don't let the girls come outside!
That demon wields a huge spear
and is very fierce.
I'm dying to get a look at him!
Wait for us!
Let's get far from the girls' cave
and go out to meet him!
If he's a beast, won't he be
able to smell the girls out?
In that case, he'd be drawn by
the smell of Kagome.
Hey! But since the demon only
goes after young, pretty girls,
I'll let you off this time.
Young and pretty? Where?!
Sit!!
Idiots never learn.
Have you given up and brought
me a bride?
That must be him!
Huh?
Y-You? You're the demon who's
looking for wives?
Right! Young lady,
would you like to bear my child?
I think I've heard that
before somewhere....
Hey, hey!
Jeez! What a letdown!
Who are you?!
I thought he was a
much scarier demon
and I'd be able to have some fun
for the first time in ages!
A pig demon....
I'm not a pig!
I'm a wild boar!!
Well, clearly they don't need me.
Inuyasha, you handle it.
Hey, you guys! Do what
you like with this guy.
Sango, would you, please?
You two!!
Yes?
Look at them!
Fearing my power and running off
with their tails between their legs!
How pathetic!
You wish! It's because you look
really weak!
How you underestimate the
the power of Chokyukai!
Chokyukai? I've heard that name
somewhere before....or have I?
What? You know him?!
I like pork cutlets but
I don't have any pig friends.
Not a pig! A boar!
Now listen and be amazed!!
This fellow here is a descendant
of Sagojo, the great water demon
from the ancient epic tale from the
continent, "The Journey to the West."
This one is a descendant of
the Heavenly Saint, Son Goku!
And I am Chokyukai,
descended from Chohakkai,
the General of the
Army of Heaven!
Huh?!
Too impressed even to speak?!
Well, I've taken a lesson
from my ancestor, Chohakkai,
and decided to marry
a human girl.
What's the swine talking about?
What?! You've never heard
of "The Journey to the West"?
So, you're really descended from
Chohakkai, in the "Journey to the West"?
You know that?
Not me.
I have no clue what
he's talking about.
But I should've known Kagome
would know. She's so smart!
Young Miss? You seem to have
heard of my ancestor?
"The Journey to the West" is
a famous Chinese epic tale
of the monk, Sanzo, who makes
friends with three demons...
a monkey, a water sprite
and a pig....
and together they go to India to
retrieve the holy sutras.
So you do know him!
I told you! I like pork cutlets on rice
but I don't know any pigs!
You know all about my ancestor!
What a fine girl you are!
You should be happy!
I think I'll make you my wife!
No way!
When a girl says, "no," she
frequently means, "yes!"
I'll make you mine!
I like pork roasts,
but no thanks!
What is that you keep saying?
Well, this is getting tiresome....
Huh?!
Watch out!
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Inuyasha is
acting strangely....
Inuyasha!
What's wrong, Inuyasha?
I....
Master....!
Ugh! Don't tell me
he's your type!
That's not what the problem is!
There's something funny about
that golden diadem.
Yow! It's tight!
Huh?
What happened to me?
You nearly volunteered
to become Chokyukai's wife.
Ack!
When placed upon
a girl's head,
this diadem has the power
to make her fall in love?
If I place it on
a girl's head,
I can make her love me!
Hey!
Forget it, idiot!
Master....!
Huh?
So, it doesn't make the wearer
fall in love with the one that placed it?
Anyone wearing it falls
in love with Chokyukai!
Wait, Miroku!
Okay, enough fun for one day....
Hey!
Oh, no!
Now, my dear, shall we go?
Yes, Master.
Over my dead body!
I won't let you interfere!
Kagome!
Huh?! Kagome....?!
Oh, Master....
Why, you...!
You still want to interfere?!
Son Goku! Sagojo!
Yes!
Go!!!
Grrrrrr!
Woof!
Hey, the mongrel's not too bad....!
I've had enough of you!
I'll knock you all back to the continent!
Time for you to run off with
your tail between your legs!
Shut up, Pig Demon!
I told you! I'm a boar!
I'll beat you to a pulp!
Fine!
Master! Good luck!
Kagome!
Now, die!
Inuyasha!
Well, now that I have my bride,
I'm done here.
Shall we go?
Yes, Master!
Wait!
Dammit!
Kagome!
Welcome home, Master!
I've brought all of you
a new companion!
You'll sit at the head of the table.
You're worthy of that.
Yes, Master.
Inuyasha.... Are you all right?
Damn.... About now, Kagome is....
Kagome is....
Master!
Damn! I was careless!
Well, this is no time to
get all depressed about it.
Yes. That one is a demon
from the continent.
It's possible our methods of
eradication won't work on him.
I have here a sutra with prayers
from the continent on it.
We could try using this....
But how are we going
to find his lair?
Easy. Just follow his scent!
But with Kagome in
the enemy's hands,
we can't be too aggressive.
That's true.
I have a strategy.
Shippo, come listen.
That's an idea! I hadn't
thought of that!
We'll need everyone
working together.
Yep, I've gotta keep it
together!
My, my! What a fine
night this is!
Someone dance for me!
Excuse me!
A female voice like
the tinkling of bells!
What do you need,
traveling woman?
I've lost my way and
am in a difficulty.
If I could ask to spend
the night here....?
One night or a thousand nights!
Come, show me your face.
I am too shy....
Jeez, this is hopeless.
My, my, my!
You're just my type!
Would you bear my child?!
Well....
It looks like he hasn't noticed....
Either that or he has really
strange tastes....
Kagome!
Well, we shouldn't be
standing outside talking.
Let us go in.
Hurry it up, Inuyasha!
What's wrong? Are you
trembling with joy?!
Fine! Then I'll
tremble with you!
This... is... about...
All I can take!
What's this? You were with
that dog bunch!
Snap out of it, Kagome!
Inuyasha!
You forgot something!
You all tricked me!
Good job, Shippo!
I won't let you have my bride!
Now, Inuyasha! Give that
sutra to Kagome!
This is a prayer from the continent!
Wrap it around your
arrow, and shoot it!
Gotcha!
That's not a bad pike
for a pig to wield.
You ain't seen nothing yet!
So you wanna challenge me?
Huh?
What am I feeling....?
Oh, no! Not that!!
You shouldn't toy with
a woman's affections!
Don't do it!
Wow!
Damn! I let that
swine get away.
But he won't be causing
anymore trouble.
I'm glad we were able
to rescue everyone.
Yes, aren't we, Miro...?
Ladies, would you
bear my children?
That monk! He's talking
just like that demon!
Suspicious.... Do you think
he's one of them?
- Come on! Say something!
- Forget it.
Hey! Girls!
Is everyone all right?
Everyone! It's Kisuke!
Well, clearly he's not popular
enough to cause us worry....
Right?
- It was so frightening!
- Thank you, Kisuke!
That pig demon
was really disgusting!
That monk, too....
Little baby foxes look up to
Shippo as their master!
What's with you guys?
You are our leader,
Boss Shippo!
Master, train us
to become strong!
You have secret techniques, don't you?
You mean the fox demon technique
of the Smashing Top?
Something more amazing!
Amazing?
Could they mean
that trick Inuyasha uses?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Shippo's New Technique,
The Heart Scar!"
This is my tragic
love story.