That's right!
We're here to save Kagome
who was abducted by
the Panther-Demon Tribe!
Koga and Sesshomaru
also appeared
and fought the Panther-Demon Tribe...
Then come to our castle
to get her.
We'll be waiting, Inuyasha!
Why you...!
Sesshomaru!
Miroku!
Sango!
So you're alive, Shippo!
Old Myoga!
Where is everyone?
Probably in the cats' castle.
Hurry up and move outta the way,
or you'll get it!
Go through us if you can.
You!
What!
What is this?!
Damn it!
Over this way!
Move!
No way!
Then take this!
Royakan!
Is that thunder?
You thwarted my lightning.
I'm impressed.
The bastard!
He doesn't move fast.
But his thunderbolts are dangerous.
Now take my fire!
Damn!
Sis!
I'm surprised.
I thought you'd be weaker
than before.
What do you mean?
That arm.
After all, who was it
that cut it off?
The party will start
very soon.
Come at your leisure.
What's wrong?
Don't hold back.
Come at me.
The thunderbolts are swift,
but he's the one
firing them.
Awright!
On guard!
Too slow!
The slow one...
...is you!
Had enough?
Everyone... retreat!
Serves you right!
What about the one
who's down?
He's breathing.
I don't think he fainted...
more like he's asleep.
Then leave 'im.
Let's go.
I know Kagome is there!
Damn! Which one is real?!
What are you doing, Inuyasha?
Shaddup!
You are such a burden!
Now... Look, look, look!
To see who's real!
She's the real one?
Yes.
Hmm... not bad.
My name means "to perceive right."
Do not take me lightly!
As long as I know which
is which...
We'll continue this at the castle.
Damn her
and her stupid tricks!
The time is upon us, Master!
It will be very soon.
The moon is almost
directly overhead.
Soon, the dogs we despise so much
will be slaughtered
and the Panther-Demon Tribe will
rule victorious over this land.
A barrier...
Soon, our master will
be resurrected.
Sesshomaru, prepare to die!
Our... master!
Give me blood... flesh...
and a soul!
What's this?!
The cats!
Where is this anyway?!
Kagome!
Koga!
Damn! What is this?!
As if you can break
the supreme master's barrier!
You can stay there and watch the
sacrificial lambs being devoured.
They're feeding us
to him!
Miroku!
Give me blood!
Kagome!
What's that?!
The color of Tetsusaiga is!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That dog! He broke our
master's barrier!
What is he?!
Lord Sesshomaru!
I searched for you, my lord!
That Inuyasha... When did he
learn to use Tetsusaiga like that?
I am shocked!
Inuyasha!
Kagome, are you all right?
Uh-huh!
I knew you'd come.
No need to worry anymore, Kagome.
Huh?
Koga! Why you...!
Give me blood!
Inuyasha!
Rest assured, Kagome.
Freeing you is easily done.
No, Koga!
He took on the Supreme Master!
Inuyasha!
The Sacred Jewel shards
are in his throat.
Gotcha!
I'll get 'em back.
Okay.
Everyone, stay together and run!
This way! Hurry!
You guys, do not let the prisoners escape!
It's useless!
There's no escape!
What're you doing, fools?
Aren't we important
sacrificial lambs?
You're not supposed to
kill us, right?
Now move!
Way to go, Sis!
That's our gal!
All right!
Don't just stand there.
Protect Kagome!
Are you conscious, Miroku?
Miroku!
Sango!
How gratifying!
C'mon, Let's go!
Hurry! Now's our chance!
Yeah!
Take this!
Master!
Give me blood... a soul...
Please wait just a bit
longer.
I will present you...
with the head of our
despised enemy's son!
I don't care who he is...
But you can't use human blood
and flesh to resurrect him!
Well, you're going to
be the first!
Come at me!
And you'll become fodder
for Tetsusaiga!
Ohh!
You are the one, Lord Sesshomaru!
There is nothing like
victory in war!
What victory?
We let them go.
I cannot use this sword.
Tenseiga is a sword
of healing.
I cannot kill my enemies
with it.
The other sword that
Father left... Tetsusaiga.
Wind Scar!
And to think... I cannot wield
that sword Tetsusaiga.
Gotcha!
Pinned down like this, you can't
use that sword, can you?
W-What?!
What're you doing?!
Stay down, Inuyasha.
They are my prey.
No way!
You stay out of this!
Enough!
Why you...!
Don't get in my way!
Ohh... Why can't they join
forces at a time like this?!
Why you...!
I do not need any help.
Shaddup!
They're so reckless!
Are they really siblings?
What're they thinking anyway?
If they're in disarray,
we must stay united.
We'll combine all our powers
at once.
Let's!
Okay!
Awright!
Give me life!
Supreme Master!
We shall offer you
their lives in but a moment!
I want it now!
Karan!
Master!
He... he devoured his
own kin to revive himself!
You there... The two sons
of the Great Dog-Demon.
Your turn is next!
Shunran!
Karan!
Shuran!
He can't have!
Dogs!
You will now feel
my wrath!
You're still mumbling
in your sleep!
I'll wake you up!
Move!
Wind Scar!
I did it!
It didn't work.
You got the strength
to fight my old man.
I'll give you that!
But I...
Don't get cocky, Inuyasha!
Don't compare him to
Ryukotsusei whom you defeated!
He has the power of
the Sacred Jewel shards now!
It's a huge cat-demon!
He's resurrected!
But in order to revive...
he needed live sacrificial
offerings.
Maybe the dog was
offered.
No way!
Die!
Lord Sesshomaru!
You can become a
part of me, too.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Lord... Sesshomaru...
Why that...!
Tenseiga?
You want me to draw you?
Father, why did you leave
me the Tensaiga?
I still do not know.
However...
That's!
What's that sword?
It won't work, kid!
Its blade is too dull.
Die!
Why?!
I'm losing...
I'm losing my power!
B-Bastard, what did you do?!
The rest is up to you
and Tetsusaiga.
Hold it!
Give me...
Give me my soul!
Wind Scar!
Give me... life!
I'm taking these back.
Sis!
Y-You three!
What happened to us?
I thought the master
had killed us.
But why?
It's because of Lord Sesshomaru's power!
Your master took your lives.
And Lord Sesshomaru used
the Tenseiga to restore them.
Sesshomaru?!
Why that...!
Hey, you should be grateful!
Right, Lord Sesshomaru?
Huh? Lord Sesshomaru?
Oh, don't leave me!
So whaddya want?
Shall we continue our fight?
No, we'll return to the west.
Sis!
It's over.
There's no reason to
seek revenge anymore.
Tell that to Sesshomaru.
We're not that close.
You should know that.
Well, when you feel
like talking to him.
Yeah.
We've been saved!
The cat-demons won't
be back.
So you're safe now.
Thank you so much!
Thanks to you, we can live
here in peace now.
We'll be off now.
Oh...
I wasn't able to help
Lord Sesshomaru again!
It's too late.
Just forget it.
With these guys around,
no wonder the mortals
are scared.
What a burden to be lumped in
with them!
I'll say!
Hey mutt! You expect those mortals
to thank you?
What?!
By the way, we still have
a score to settle.
Hey! Anytime!
Don't get wise!
Inuyasha! Sit!
What're you doing anyway?!
Damn!
In the mountains...
In the forest...
In the wind...
In my dreams...
Lord Sesshomaru,
where are you?
With faithful Jaken
at your heels...
Rin.
Huh?
Oh! Lord Sesshomaru!
Let us go.
C'mon.
Okay!
I will wait all alone.
For Lord Sesshomaru's return.
What?! Sango has a proposal
from a lord?
Yes! She has me at her side,
yet Sango is so flirtatious!
What'll you do, Sango?
He's handsome, upright,
and really loves you.
So unlike Miroku.
It's not our place
to express our opinions.
Won't you make up your mind?!
Well, I'll decide for you then!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Only You, Sango"
Oh, you there, miss.
Will you bear my child?
I doubt it.