Wind Scar!
I used the Tetsusaiga to
break through Naraku's barrier
and I almost had him!
But he abandoned his castle
and he disappeared leaving
no trace at all... not even his scent.
Naraku had completely
disappeared!
The demon Naraku had
left behind in his castle
told us that Naraku had gone to
a place "where no one could touch him."
Is there really such a place?
He was probably so confident
that he wouldn't be found
that he allowed the demon
to say such a thing.
I'll devour you,
Sacred Jewel shards and all!
You're just huge, that's all!
Watch!
Take this!
Why you...!
Koga!
Ayame!
As if I'd die so easily!
But we can't stay idle!
This time, I'll find Naraku
and destroy him forgood!
Where are you?!
Where, Naraku?!
What's this?
Uh-huh, I sensed it too.
The demonic aura's been getting
stronger and stronger.
Ademon?!
Hey! Wait, Inuyasha!
Appear, apparition!
So there you are!
You will die,
weasel-demon!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
An old woman?
Don't be wandering about
like this.
Go on home and
sleep.
Dog ears!
Anotherdemon?!
Begone!
What're you doing?!
Is this how you repay
a debt?!
Stop it.
Don't even try to
stop me!
Monk, hold him still!
Hold him still!
Demon dispersal!
Demons are increasing?
Thatexplains the demonic
aura in the area.
Demonic aura?
We journey around the countryside
slaying demons.
So we're in the same business...
Anyway, due to this sudden
increase in demons,
I had to come out of retirement.
Just an old woman's whim!
Better you stay retired.
Shall I teach you a
lesson again, dog?!
Now, now... Madam Exorcist.
Don't you know the reason
forthe increase in demons?
Probably the curse.
Curse?
Of the Demon's Head Castle.
Demon's Head Castle?
It probably has a proper name.
Buteveryone calls it
Demon's Head Castle.
It's said that the head of a demon
vanquished by an ancestor
was buried to ward off evil spirits,
and the castle was built overit.
Who'd believe stories
that you tell?!
But for some strange reason,
lately, the demon has been revived,
tormenting people.
And no amount of exorcism
has worked.
So...
Now then, follow me.
Where to?
To Demon's Head Castle.
Where else?
Didn't you say you travel
around slaying demons?
What'll we do?
We have no time
forthis!
But since we know
the story...
Finding Naraku is
top priority!
Isn't that so?!
Uh-huh...
I understand the reward
is great.
Reward?
Now, now... let us go.
We split the earnings evenly.
Hey!
Why you...!
M-My lord!
Please forgive me!
I did not see anything!
Nothing at all!
My lord!
In any case, our lord has been
acting strange in recent days.
He locks himself up in his room
and refuses to leave.
Say, Inuyasha...
Isn't the castle sorta creepy?
Yeah, that field was nothing
compared to this.
So this must be the core
of the demonic aura.
From the severed demon's head?
It has surrounded the
entire castle.
What's the matter?
Why the glum look?
And what're you mumbling about?
They all sense the demonic aura
and are uneasy.
Demonic aura?
What's that?
Well... don't you feel or
sense anything weird?
Like what?
"Like what", you say?!
It's all in your imagination.
Or are you all feeling scared?
Still young, yet so hopeless!
I think this old woman
is a fake!
Hmm... Even I sense
the demonic aura.
That's!
This is the seventh one.
The lord slays every vassal ormaid
that tries to approach his room.
Do you think the lord's erratic
behavioris caused by the demon curse?
Most probably...
The demon appears afterdark.
Until then, stay in here.
One... two... three.
One... two... three!
Now listen up.
You must be prepared.
You're so full of energy, old woman.
I'll say. She's amazing
amidst this demonic aura.
Even forthose as well-trained as us,
the demonic aura in this castle
is unsettling.
Let's finish up this job
and get out of here quickly.
You're right.
You are the ones who've come
to exterminate the demon?
Please be careful.
And please save my father
without fail!
Father?
You are the princess
of this castle?
Many priests and priestesses
have failed at exorcising the demon,
and died.
Rest assured, my princess.
I shall stand firm here
and conduct the exorcism
no matter how many days it takes.
Didn't you say we should finish this
up quickly and leave?!
The demon!
Ademon has appeared!
Do not worry.
Leave it to me!
Ademon's head!
I'll go! Kirara!
I'll destroy it in one blow!
Sango seems so intense today!
You're right.
Hiraikotsu!
It went right through!?
What the...!
Move, Sango!
Wind Scar!
Did you see that?!
That's how you do it.
Inuyasha, look!
W-What's going on?!
What's happening?
I hit it square with my
Wind Scar...
and it didn't even flinch!
That demon's head... could it be?
Damn it!
Once more!
Take this!
How's that?!
What...!?
Wait, Inuyasha!
Why?
If my Wind Scar didn't work,
how do you expect to destroy it?!
No weapon will work on that.
Miroku?
Spiritual Power!
It disappeared...
Princess, the demon's head...
Oh my!
Just as I thought.
That was an illusion.
Illusion?
Does that mean the demon head will
appear again tomorrow?
Yes. That is just make-believe.
An illusion to divert attention
from the real demon.
Hmm...
That means the real demon is hiding
somewhere in this castle.
Probably.
The demonic aura hasn't subsided at all.
Hmm... demonic aura?
I don't sense anything at all.
I see...
Some exorcist you are.
Didn't you say that the lord
is deranged?
Yes.
Ratherthan a demon's curse,
you sure the lord isn't possessed
by the demon?
If you are noticed,
you will be killed.
When that time comes,
I'lljust fight back.
Don't be hasty.
He is the lord of the castle,
after all.
Well, Miroku?
Isn't it a demon?
No... he's definitely human.
And...
What?
I can't believe that the demonic
aura covering this castle
is coming from the lord.
Well, don't you feel a
little better?
Sorry, but...
What? Not any better?
Did it work on you, Kirara?
Well?
Strange...
This is a very special
purification salt.
Most demons succumb
to this.
Hah! What a fake exorcist!
As if it'd work!
What did you say?!
Then I'll test it on you!
Hold it!
Overhere, overhere!
Wait I say!
Demon disperse!
No way!
Sit!
What?!
Stop it, you two!
Huh?
My father could be the demon?!
Yes, but...
According to the monk,
yourfatheris just possessed
and the demon himself
could be elsewhere.
Oh dear!
MasterMonk.
Huh?
The princess would like
to see you.
Me?
Hey, you don't intend to
go alone?!
Don't worry, Sango.
It's true the princess
is very pretty.
But my heart...
belongs to you.
Hey! Who'd worry about that?!
You don't know when the
demon will appear.
It's too dangerous to
go alone!
If that's what you mean,
don't worry.
Miroku is quite strong
by himself.
Why the glare?
Stupid!
You still have much to learn about life.
What?! You fake exorcist!
I'm not sure about her
ability as an exorcist,
but she's pretty sharp
as a woman.
Huh? Not you, too!
Now then...
Monk...
Yes?
Take this purification salt.
As a precaution.
Take one packet.
All right.
Thank you.
It's a very long stairway.
You probably have heard...
The burial site of the
demon head is down below.
Demon head burial site?
Yes...
Beneath this castle is buried,
the head of a vanquished demon.
I would like you to see it.
I heard that to ward off evil,
the demon's head was buried.
Yes.
Until now, there was never
a problem.
But...
The burial site was uncovered
and the demon escaped.
And inside this hole...
Huh?!
T- This is...!
This is...!
These are the skeletons of
the priests and priestesses
who tried to exterminate
the demon and failed.
How terrible!
The demon of this castle craved
humans like them
and absorbed theirpowers.
That's why it wants me here, too.
Yes.
To absorb your spiritual powers.
Damn, that Miroku is late.
Uh-huh... he's late.
I wonder what he's doing?
You're talking about that lecher!
By now, he's with the
princess and...
No, noteven Miroku would do
anything in this demonic aura.
Stupid! He's so lecherous, a
demonic aura wouldn't stop him!
Why, probably he's feeling
quite comfortable.
Inuyasha, sit!
Why?!
You have no sense
of delicacy!!
Notenough training.
But Sango, maybe we should
go and look.
Not necessary.
I don't want to interrupt him.
She's forcing herself to say that.
It's here!
M-My lord!
Please stop!
My lord!
Move!
The lord is... turning into a demon!
T-The lord... the lord!
Stop.
So he's the demon after all...
Y-You are...
It's too late to realize that.
The airin here is
filled with demonic aura
and your body
should be going numb.
Damn you!
I added my own spiritual power
to the exorcist's purification salt.
It seems to have some effect.
But this is bad...
This demon is quite powerful.
And my body won't move
due to the demonic aura.
Monk, there's no help
forthcoming.
Besides, that half-demon is
probably fighting
the lord back at the castle.
I used my magic to manipulate
that puppet lord.
W- What?!
Inuyasha!
Hope you're prepared, Demon!
I'll finish you in one blow!
What'll we do, Kagome?
Miroku hasn't come back since
he went underground
with the princess.
And Sango is still so jealous.
You and I are the only ones
able to set up a preview
forthe next episode!
Hey, Kagome!
Huh? What is it, Shippo?
This is not the time
to be sleeping!
Well... the princess is sleeping
so comfortably, too.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Secret of the Possessed Princess"
What's going on anyway?!