And there!
What's all this?!
I can't go home that often.
And girls have lots of
shopping to do.
Here, this is for you.
Potato chips!
And for you, Shippo.
Wow! Thank you, Kagome!
This tastes great!
Ohh?
Kagome, it's spinning by itself!
Here, Miroku.
Thank you.
Where's Sango?
Not back yet.
I thought you'd all be
together by now.
It's been a while since she
returned home.
Besides repairing her Hiraikotsu,
she probably has lots of
things to do.
Maybe she won't come back.
'Specially 'cuz of the lecher
who likes to stroke buns.
I am NOT guilty of that!
I wonder 'bout that...
Since it's Sango, I guess there's
no need to worry...
Not as good as Father's,
but pretty good for me.
Father... Everyone... I'm home at last.
Forgive me for ignoring you
for so long.
Sango, do you think you can continue
as a Demon Slayer?
Yes, Father. I think I'm suited
to this work.
I see...
I trained you until now,
not just so you could take over.
I want you to live strong.
Father, what did you mean
by that?
Stop!
Please let Serina go!
Kirara!
Just who are you?!
Sis!
What's wrong?
We haven't had food or water
for three days.
Isn't this good, Serina?
Uh-huh!
There's more.
Another serving?
- Yes!
- Please!
I'm the elder, Serina.
And I'm Suzuna.
After leaving the village,
we followed rumors in search of
the Demon Slayers' hideout.
You attacked me knowing that
I am a Demon Slayer?
We just wanted to test
your skills.
You're pretty good, sister!
Please accept us as apprentices!
Apprentices?
You need a massage, sister!
Teacher, please accept us!
No.
Oh c'mon, Teacher!
I said, no!
Please, Teacher!
I'm not your teacher.
And no is no!
I'm in a hurry!
We cannot return to our village until
you take us in as your pupils...
and train us in the art of
demon extermination!
Please!
There seems to be
a reason for this.
We live in a village of farmers in a
clearing in the mountains.
In order to expand the farms,
we began clearing
part of the mountain of our local deity.
Then all kinds of demons began
attacking us.
Not just one or two!
Many of our villagers have died.
It's fine if you're able to
move to another village.
But the elderly and those
with children cannot leave...
and each day is spent
in dread.
Hmm... The forest of the deity had
provided a barrier for you.
We heard of a village of
Demon Slayers.
As you can see, there are
no Demon Slayers left.
Or I can go with you?
Our village has no money for payment.
We didn't come here thinking
we would hire a Demon Slayer.
And our village is so far away.
Thwarting them once or twice
doesn't faze those demons.
So please train us!
We'll do our best for everyone's sake!
Suzuna!
I'll do my best!
You can't learn
the Demon Slayers' art overnight.
But I can teach you how to
deter minor demons.
Thank you!
They'll wait for me even if
I delay my departure one or two days.
Here are the weapons to
slay demons.
Yes!
Let's try it here.
Don't just look, help fan!
W-What is this?!
A powder mixture of herbs and medicines
which demons hate.
We can exterminate demons with this?!
You can protect the village, yes!
This smoke is really something, but...
Can we really beat them off with this?!
Sister...
I mean, Teacher... Isn't there something
more exciting?
Learning tricks haphazardly
can be dangerous.
It's late today. Tomorrow, I'll show
you how to make this powder.
Sango didn't come back.
Umm... I'd like to ask you
a question.
Yes?
Will stroking a woman's bottom
destroy mutual trust between two people?
Trust is also respecting the
distance between each other.
Is that how it is?
If Sango doesn't return,
it's all your fault!
She WILL return without fail!
He sounds confident,
but he sure doesn't look it.
Serina, just leave it to me!
So easy! Can't beat a ninja's skills.
You're so dependable!
Look!
It's just like Pa said...
The materials are the secret
to the Demon Slayer's weapons!
Materials?
The fangs of demons, bones, hides...
No wonder Slayers can
counter demon attacks.
Then if we have these, we can...
Become just as strong!
Oww! Serina!
What're you up to?
You're no ordinary village girls.
Those moves...
Yup! We come from a village
of ninja agents.
One day, the clan lord ordered us to slay
a demon... something we weren't used to.
We were able to use ninja skills
to destroy the demon.
But other demons came
seeking revenge!
Our people who knew only
ninja tactics...
were nearly all devoured
by these demons.
Serina, it's safe now.
Pa!
Father!
Hang on, Father!
Serina... Suzuna...
At least you two... be strong...
Father!
Pa!
Those were our father's dying words.
Be strong and restore our village
to what it once was...
That's what he probably wanted
to tell us.
Wait!
Serina!
I knew it!
This is bad...
Some weapons haven't been exorcised
of demon spirits yet.
Weapons which still have
demon spirits...
also summon demons back.
Kirara!
Hurry, Kirara!
Those two are in danger!
Please wait, Suzuna!
Cripes! You're always like this, Sis.
I'll take more of the load.
I'm sorry.
No wonder Pa was looking forward
to me as his heir.
Forgive me.
I'll train hard and become a strong ninja
like Father wanted me to be.
Let's hurry.
What's that?!
Both of you, get on Kirara!
Go back to the village!
We're not returning these!
Forget those things!
Hundreds of demons are coming
in search of...
the demonic aura which
those weapons are exuding!
It's true! Hurry!
It's too late!
I have no choice but to destroy
those monsters, then try to escape!
Serina! The time has come to show
Pa our mettle!
Yes! We are children of ninja!
As long as we have these weapons
of extermination!
Serina... Suzuna...
At least you two... be strong...
I've trained you until now,
not just so you can take over.
I want you to live strong.
Father...
Wait!
You're wrong!
Your father didn't mean for
you to do this...
What would you know!
There isn't a father in the world
who doesn't...
wish for his daughter's happiness!
Your father didn't want you
to take over as ninja!
He wanted you to be strong
and to become happy.
That's...
Now get on Kirara
and follow close to me!
Serina... Suzuna...
At least you two... be strong.
He wanted you to be strong
and to become happy.
Suzuna!
What're you doing, Serina?!
Sango is right!
Sango!
Hiraikotsu!
Let's go!
Don't interfere!
Huh?!
Suzuna!
Serina...
Don't come near!
Sango!
Miroku!
Wind Scar!
It's unlike you to be
bothered by the likes of them!
Inuyasha!
I'll take over now.
Wind Tunnel!
Sango!
We came for you!
Everyone...
Let's go, Serina.
Be strong and live,
both of you.
Miroku was so worried,
we decided to come.
And just in the nick of time, too.
I'm glad we made it.
Miroku, you were that
worried about me?
Call it a premonition...
I kept seeing your face, Sango.
It wouldn't go away. So...
Oh, thank you, Miroku.
Don't mention it.
Get a grip, Miroku!
I sure don't wanna be
a grown-up like that.
Uh-huh!
Kagome!
Naraku brought that evil priestess
who fought long ago with Kikyo.
Oh no... I can't figure it out!
I can't follow the lessons!
She's using the Sacred Jewel Shard to
cast a spell on you!
Everyone tells me I should
break up with Inuyasha...
Hey, listen to me!
Did you know? They call you
the rough, two-timing, jealous boyfriend!
What?! Why?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The 50 Year-Old Curse of the Dark Priestess"