I meant for you to hide here.
If I don't forget, I'll come
back and dig you out.
Are you sure?
You must not forget.
Grandpa, is Kagome's
story true?
'Course it's true!
A ghost appeared from
inside the well...
and kidnapped Kagome!
As the legend of our
shrine goes...
There is something in the
"bone-devouring well"
that takes the corpses of
evil spirits
and makes them disappear
somewhere.
And if this "somewhere"is in
the time dimension...
Well, we must do something.
There!
Huh? Sealed?
Yes...
With written oracles to
ward off evil spirits
and seal off the entry
to the netherworld.
The well will never
be opened again.
No mistaking the smell
of that girl...
Her clothing...
Damn! She really did
go home...
In here!
Hmmm... Home sweet home!
It's like it never happened...
that I was in another age
and another time.
You must combine your powers
with Inuyasha
and gather the fragments of
the Sacred Jewel and restore it.
Oh dear... The Sacred Jewel
is in pieces.
That Yura with the inverted hair...
I wonder what she was?
She must've been after
the Jewel, too.
I'll bet Inuyasha would
be so angry
if he learned that the fragment
was stolen from me.
Who cares about you!?
I prefer to go it alone!
Yes...
Inuyasha can manage
without me.
All right, I'll forget him.
Besides, I can never return
to that world again.
Kagome, Yuka is on the phone.
And it's also dinnertime!
Okay!
Gramps...
Will the seals on the well
ever come off?
Never.
Each seal contains powerful words
of magic that can't be broken.
No matter what kind of evil
spirit, it will be impossible.
It's a hot pot for dinner!
- So you can rest assured, Kagome.
- Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot!
She's not listening.
It's such a glorious age!
Let's dig in!
Huh... Inuyasha?
You!
Who said you can go home?!
You... Where'd you come from?
The well! Where else?
The well? But it's...
Do not lie!
Those oracles have been used
of this shrine since ancient times...
and cannot fail!
Oracle? You mean, this
flimsy piece of paper?
Didn't work!
Gramps!
Now come with me!
Wa... wait! I don't want to go!
Just a minute!
What?!
Mom...
Your ears... Are they real?
Lemme try, too!
Mom, this is no time for that...
Although I did the same thing.
Inuyasha...
A strand of hair!
Hair?
Can't you see it?
Huh?! It's moving!
Kagome... There's blood...
What happened?
This!
Only I can see it.
But being able to "see"
isn't enough.
Yura's manipulating strand!
No!
More strands... are coming out!
That old crone was right.
You have the vision at least.
You brought something awful
with you!!
Kagome!
Sis!
Don't enter!
Here... I must stop it right here!
Inuyasha! In front of you!
- Open up, Kagome!
- Kagome!
It gathers together again,
even when it's cut.
There's no end to this!
Huh?! That's?
That's it!
The main strand that's
controlling everything.
Inuyasha!
It's this one!
Cut this strand!
This? Where?
Inuyasha can't see it.
Then...
There's only one way!
I see it!
It retreated.
Strange...
If Yura was after the Sacred Jewel...
she already accomplished
her goal.
Could she actually be
after me and Inuyasha?
Inuyasha, let's return!
Wow... That was a quick
change of mind.
I don't really want to go.
Huh?
But if I stay here, Gramps,
Mom and even Sota...
will be in terrible danger.
Huh?
This was woven with the fur
of the Fire Rat.
It's much stronger than
an ordinary armor.
Th... thank you.
Well, 'cuz...
You look like you have
really weird skin.
You're the weird one!
Oh well, whatever.
Let's go!
Uh-huh!
They should be returning soon.
This time, I'll give them
a big reception...
Do you understand, Inuysha?
Kagome is my sister Kikyo's
reincarnation.
However, she isn't aware yet
of the scope of her powers.
She needs your help
right now.
Watch out! There's hair all
over the well, too!
Are you saying that this Yura with
the combed Hair is after us
Yes. Look, she took the Sacred
Jewel fragment...
yet she still comes after us!
Hold it! Did you say she
took it?!
I can see several glowing
strands of hair there...
There's the main strand that's
been bewitching the others.
That means if we follow
the main strand, we'll find Yura!
That way!
Okay!
There's no time to
stand around and quarrel!
You need Kagome and
Kagome needs you!
And you must get through this
difficulty together!
A bonfire...
Their heads are gone!
They're fallen warriors.
They must've gotten tangled
in the hair strands.
Such bad luck.
Stop looking so depressed!
And don't start whining about
wanting to go home.
I... thought I'd borrow this!
We must destroy Yura quickly
or many innocent people will die.
The arrows you shoot
probably won't hit their targets.
How rude! If I practice, maybe!
Practice?
Did you practice?
From now on! Just watch me!
I'm going to improve!
Huh?!
This girl...
She's hopeless, but
I gotta admit, she's gutsy.
The main lines are gathering.
She's close!
They're coming!
From the left!
The right, too!
Too many! Use your instincts
to evade them!
Whhaa...?! What a useless woman!
I thought you came to fight?!
There!
Before you!
The rear, too?!
Inuyasha...
A giant sphere of hair...
Yura's hiding place?
Hmm... such a fine prey.
You're Inuyasha, aren't you?
So you're Yura?
How do you know me?
I heard the gossip in the wind.
That a half-demon named
Inuyasha is serving...
the reincarnation of a
shrine maiden...
and helping her to protect
for the Sacred Jewel.
What?!
Me? Serving that
brainless girl?
You've gotta be kidding me!
I see... Well, both of you
are brainless.
Turning the Sacred Jewel
into this.
That's the Jewel fragment
she stole from me!
In any case, I'll deal with
you two...
and go look for the
other fragments.
Hmm... Deal with me?
You're the one who'll rue
the day...
you appeared before my eyes!
The same tactic over and
over again!
Damn it!
Such pretty hair...
But you haven't taken
care of it, have you?
So many split ends.
Inuyasha!!
Now, I'll shred you
to pieces!
Release Inuyasha!
Because I won't miss
this time!
The woman who disappeared
from the well?
Now! Hurry it up!
Release Inuyasha, you say?
You two must be
quite chummy!
Fool! Forget me
and get away!
It's not that pretty, but I think
I'll take her hair, too.
What'll I do?
"Not that pretty"?
I condition my hair everyday!
Stop being so rude!
Where are you aiming, stupid?!
No! All my victims!
The heads of those
fallen warriors we saw...
Your head will soon
occupy a place there.
All this fine silver-colored hair...
I can't wait to control it.
Before that, however...
You there! Woman!
You scare me, so die!
How do you like
my demon fire!
You'll feel the heat all the way
to your bones!
He... help!
Serves you right!
You're being punished
for messing with my nest!
Aghh...
That woman...
she'll be left with no bones.
Why you!
Are you sad? Poor thing...
Well, you'll be joining her
in no time, too.
Take this!
Blades of Blood!
Blades of blood?
The strands are loosening!
My hand...
Now you can't control
your strands!
You...
You should treat ladies
more gently.
People will laugh at
you, you know?
Playtime's over!
Darn! I almost had your head!
I wouldn't allow that!
You're just a half-demon
with half the power.
Damn!
Poor little thing...
You wanted this in order to become
a full-fledged demon, huh?
The Sacred... Jewel...
Don't move.
I have to sever your head
very carefully...
so that blood won't
stain those silver locks.
Quit your joking!
Hah! That'll teach you!
You're so arrogant.
Thrusting your hand into
the breasts...
of a woman you've only
just met.
You... you...!
You didn't feel anything?!
You stole my Jewel fragment,
didn't you?
Now that wasn't nice at all.
Where is it?!
Where is Yura's weak spot?
That woman...
You shouldn't have looked away!
You are becoming a pain!
You didn't bat an eyelid when you
were struck or hurt.
Now, you seem awfully upset.
Something worrying you
over there?
Inuyasha!
There's something inside that
...that red skull!
Red Skull?!
You're not getting away!
My web of hair!
Damn!
If it hurts you, let go.
I did it!
What are you?
Why don't you bleed?
Now that she mentions it...
Even when engulfed in flames...
Is it because of this robe?
It's an armor made from
the fur of the Fire Rat.
It's much stronger than
ordinary metal.
Inuyasha...
You seem like an
ordinary mortal...
How's this then?
Blades of Blood!
l... Inuyasha...
Don't you faint on me!
I can't be looking after you!
Watch out, Inuyasha!
Why that!
I am immortal, you know!
That's it! The strand coming
out of this red skull...
It's connected to Yura's hand!
That woman... I'll kill her!
So that's Yura's true form...
This red comb?
That's the Adornment Comb of
the Dead.
It was used to comb the hair
of the dead...
that's how it probably
got bewitched.
In this day and age, an
enchanted comb or two...
is nothing to be surprised at.
Inuyasha... you're badly hurt.
Because you let me wear your
Fire Rat armor.
It's nothing.
But the Sacred Jewel!
I found it.
I wonder how long it'll take to
accumulate them all?
Let's go, Kagome.
Huh?
What?
It's the first time you
said my name.
So what?
Maybe you've decided to be
a bit nicer to me?
Hey! Don't get cheeky!
Who'd be chums with a
girl like you?!
What?! And who was it
that just saved you?
Look... if it hurts, just
speak up and say so!
Shut up!
Inuyasha...
Join your powers and fight!
And hurry up and remember that
you buried me!
I was saved by the Fire Rat robe
thanks to Inuyasha...
That reminds me of a story of Princess
Kaguya from the Tale of Taketori.
She didn't want to get married so she
gave away the Fire Rat robe instead.
So that robe was from
the demon world.
And now the phantom sword
Tetsusaiga?!
Battle begins between two brothers
for the possession of the sword.
Next time, Inuyasha "Aristocratic
Assassin, Sesshomaru" See you soon!