Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings
a group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled by
the few remaining shards of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
In a creepy village where there are no men
and only demon women,
Sango is bewitched by a demon
and attacks Miroku.
This isn't right! Why do those two,
of all people, fight each other?
We continue our journey hoping to
gather the Sacred Jewel shards
before Naraku gets to them.
We hear about a village of demon women
and come upon a village
devoid of men.
But we found nothing suspicious
and intended to leave right away,
but Miroku's bad habit
surfaced once more
and we ended up staying
the night.
However...
What's going on?
I'm going to follow them.
Wait, I'm going to get
Inuyasha and Miroku.
They're probably close by.
Nevermind. There's no time
to look for them.
But....!
Sango!
Huh?!
Where am I?!
We shall make you one of us.
Now, swallow this.
Swallow without chewing.
Shortly thereafter, the egg
will hatch inside your stomach.
And you shall become one of us.
Damn it! As if I'd swallow such a thing!
What kind of demon are you?!
Give me your flesh.
Wakana!
Wakana....!
How I've searched for you!
W-What is it?!
Kagome, stay back.
Damn you!
What did you do with Sango?
Just try and hide her from us....
Wait, Inuyasha!
Each one is exhaling some
kind of demonic aura.
Hah! So we did end up in the village
of the demon women!
Give you my flesh?
I heard rumors about the demon women
skinning their victims....
But you're the one who's
manipulating them!
Exactly!
In order to return to my former self,
I needed male flesh.
"Former self"?
You're going to die anyway,
so I shall tell you.
I was once the demon that
ruled the marsh.
But one day, I was exorcised
by a monk
and sealed within a scroll.
And, not satisfied with that,
those humans tore away my flesh
and painted a Kwannon
on the scroll
completely restricting
by movements!
But my soul did not die!
I've waited patiently for
the moment of resurrection!
You shall become a part of me!
Spiritual power!
Fool! You cannot run away!
I'm so glad you're alive.
As am I, Shinosuke.
Good, Wakana.
We'll leave the bothersome monk
for later...
I shall take that
young man's flesh instead.
Inuyasha, be sure to
take it easy on them.
These people are being
controlled by someone.
I know that! I don't make it
a habit to hit women.
But this way...
...it will be endless, dammit!
Now let's see...
That girl is missing.
Maybe she returned to
that shrine.
Probably all the girls in the village
are being controlled by
whatever it is.
How do I get them
back to normal?
That's...!
Wakana, where are you taking me?
Umm.... Inside the Kwannon shrine.
Wakana?
The fiancée that Shinosuke
was searching for?
Huh?!
Shinosuke, don't go!
Shinosuke!
Huh?!
Run!
Monk!
What is it, Monk?
Run!
Run...
Huh?!
Run!
Why that...!
My spell is broken!
What's wrong, Wakana?
What is that thing?!
Shinosuke, take Wakana
and escape!
- Why?
- Hurry!
Yes!
How troublesome!
I'll use my Wind Tunnel!
Damn! I can't use
it on her...
Punishment!
I almost had her.
Sutra seals?
I guess it's worth trying.
Forgive me!
But you will awaken from this!
Wha...?!
So they were bewitched by that!
Master Monk.... What am I doing here?
You don't have to try
to remember.
Huh?!
Forgive me.
Monk!
Rest assured.
She will be fine now.
Okay....
What is that?!
A hanging scroll....?
What's happening?!
A salamander demon!
How wonderful!
A half-demon's skin for the taking.
Huh?! What're you saying?!
The flesh of a half-demon is worth
the flesh of five humans.... No, ten!
I shall devour you and
completely resurrect myself!
Hah! I don't know what the hell
you're talking about!
But don't mess with me!
Kagome!
It has finally shown
its true form.
Miroku....
Inuyasha, I can take those girls.
Huh?
You can do something?
Leave it to me!
Awright, it's all yours!
Forgive me!
They spit up salamanders!
So they were manipulating
the girls!
Hah! That's because they are
weak-hearted women!
What did you say?!
I'm sick and tired of
hearing your lectures!
Damn his brute strength!
These women are all
unfortunate souls
who lost loved ones
in war.
They probably looked to
the Kwannon hanging scroll
for guidance and comfort.
But the salamander was sealed
in the hanging scroll.
Hanging scroll?
That one that came
flying just now?
Yes.
And why'd you show up now?!
I don't know all that's happened
while I was sealed up, however....
Inuyasha!
I know that the demonic aura that appeared
in the world has given me power!
Demonic aura that appeared
in the world....?
So Naraku's influence has
reached even here?
Get ready, bastard,
'cuz now I'm serious!
This is too much for me!
Sango, can you help?!
Huh?
What're you saying, Miroku!
Sango's not here!
What?!
Haven't you noticed?!
What's Sango doing?!
She disappeared!
You keep fooling around
with the women!
So Sango got upset and went to
deal with the women alone!
Sango....
Huh?
Kirara?
What's wrong?
She's all wet.
Here I come, demon!
Half-demon!
I'll devour you!
Wind Scar!
He did it!
Now everyone will....
Huh?!
Why?
We destroyed the demon.
How come they're still bewitched?
We'll have to exorcise the demon
from each one of their bellies.
Huh?!
Kagome, please take over this.
Inuyasha, you know what
you have to do, right?
I'll leave it to you!
Huh?!
I just remembered some
urgent business.
Let's go, Kirara!
Sango...
Be safe, Sango!
He dove into the water.
Yes....
Hey, quit dawdling
and come help over here!
Hiraikotsu?
Huh?!
Sango!
Sango, you were forced to swallow
one of those demons?
I will save you right now!
Sango!
She won't be as easy to deal with
as the womenfolk.
I have to get close to her.
Now!
What is it, Inuyasha?
Huh?
The smell of blood....
Blood?
Don't worry, Kirara.
Leave it to me to save Sango.
Sango....
I shall purge that demon
in your belly.
Damn! You're a fearsome
opponent!
I'm glad we're on the same side.
Sango....
I thought I was going to die.
Miroku!
Is Sango all right?
Yes.... Well.... I guess.
Miroku, you're badly hurt.
Yes, well....
What's this egg?
A demon egg.
If it had hatched, I'd have
been worse off.
Then Sango, too, was....
Bewitched?
How'd she let such a stupid
thing happen to her?
She was upset.
Because Miroku keeps flirting
with the girls.
Huh?
It's my fault?
Of course!
You brought it all
on yourself!
Oh....
I see, so you're returning
to your homeland?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
We are truly indebted to you.
Oh no...
We didn't do much.
I'd like to thank the monk as well.
Don't worry about that.
Huh?
He's kinda busy right now.
I'm sorry, Miroku.
It's all my fault....
Don't worry about it, Sango.
Besides, Kagome scolded me
that my bad habit with women
was the cause of this.
Forgive me.
Y-You don't have to apologize.
I was careless.
You didn't have anything
to do with it, Miroku.
Sango, I just want you to hear
my feelings.
You are a very special woman to me.
Huh?
"Special"? What a jerk!
He's flirting with her like
he does every other woman he sees!
I've never had such strong feelings
for a woman as I do for you.
But....
But that's why I feel I cannot
love you as a woman.
Huh?!
You are my comrade and we fight
alongside each other.
That's how I feel.
So he's saying they're just friends?
What a mean thing to say!
That's unforgivable!
l-I know that without your telling me!
I never hoped or thought that
you would love me.
Sango....
We're finished with this conversation, right?
I'm going.
I'm just beginning....
If this battle with Naraku should end,
and the curse of my Wind Tunnel
is broken....
and, if I'm still alive....
At that time, will you come
live with me....
and bear my child?
He proposed!
He what?
Sango....
Yes....
You will?
Ten.... even twenty of our babies?
Yes!
Does that mean you'll stop
flirting with other women?
Huh?
You....will....not, right?
You will, won't you?!
So are things settled between them?
I'll bet they fight again real soon.
The curse of the Sea God?!
Sango and Miroku are turned
into glass statues!
That woman is suspicious!
A beautiful woman lays a trap
in order to get Tetsusaiga!
So you were behind this, after all!
I do not need a woman's help to
defeat someone like you.
Lord Sesshomaru, just who
is that girl?
She was so pretty.
She is not human.
Next time,
an Inuyasha Special!
"The Woman who Loved Sesshomaru"
I will fulfill your wish!