Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gatherall the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The land of herancestors
was destroyed
and heryounger brother, Kohaku,
has fallen into Naraku's hands.
But Sango has a cute, dependable friend,
Kirara, who's always by her side.
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Ourfriend Kirara is a feline
demon with two tails!
When she battles, she grows
in size and even flies through the air.
But usually, she has the appearance
of a lovable, little kitty.
She's very good-natured and endures
the willful ways of the others.
But once in a while, you should
teach everyone a lesson, Kirara!
Kirara!
Has anyone seen Kirara?
- No.
- Neither have I.
Something wrong with Kirara?
I woke up to find her gone.
Maybe she went for a walk.
Kirara isn't one to go
off without telling me.
Then she ran away?
Maybe she's in heat.
She's at that rebellious stage.
What?!
What're you saying?!
Don't make Sango worry!
Kirara seemed herusual self.
Just 'cuz she's gone awhile
ain't no reason to panic!
Inuyasha!
We can't be worrying about
every little thing!
Just leave her alone and
she'll be back in awhile.
I hope you're right.
Don't worry!
Kirara's not a kid.
Now it'd be different
with anotherkid I know.
You're right.
H-Hey! Just who do
you mean, Inuyasha!
Who else?! There's only you!
Ouch!
Kagome, Sango...
this fish is done.
That Inuyasha!
Who said she'd be right back?
She hasn't come back!
Shaddup! How was I to know!
What?! Have you forgotten
what you said earlier?
Say that again, you...!
Oww! Let go!
I'm going to look for Kirara.
Hey, wait!
No use searching senselessly!
This is where Inuyasha steps in.
What's this?
Kirara's plate.
She uses this to eat cat food.
And what'm I supposed to do
with that?
I thought maybe you should sniff it.
I already know Kirara's scent!
Do yourbest, Inuyasha!
Well? Anything?
Nope. The scent ends here.
After only three steps?
In any case, let's split up and search.
Useless! The end of her scent means
that she flew away.
Besides, I don't catch any scent
of Kirara around here.
Still, we can't just ignore it.
I know that!
Well then...
Sango, don't you have any ideas?
Huh?
Like you had a fight or Kirara
knows someone around here.
There must be something.
You say that, but...
Anything will do.
Like she lost her appetite...
or was moody lately.
Or maybe there's a large patch
of catnip growing nearhere?
Maybe... it's my fault.
What?
I always go to battle and drag her along
without thinking twice about her.
When we need to go a distance,
we take herforgranted
and ride her.
I make hergo on errands
and don't reward her.
Even her favorite fish...
she only gets a rare treat of it.
Sango, don't blame yourself
so much.
Kirara's not the type
to run away over that.
I got it!
Got what?
The reason Kirara disappeared.
When Inuyasha teased me earlier,
I realized it.
It's obvious when
you think about it.
What is it? Tell us, Shippo.
Kirara...
Kirara had enough of
all of you...
and disappeared!
Hey! Come out and say it
instead of dragging it out like that.
What do you mean?
I haven't...
Are you sure?
Put yourhand on yourheart
and think hard.
Can you truly say that you have
never been mean to Kirara?!
Yeah, I can!
I can't think of anything I did.
Then it can't be helped.
I'll outline yourvery acts
of thoughtlessness...
one by one!
First Inuyasha!
In orderto masterthe
Backlash Wave,
you practiced the Wind Scar
on Kirara!
Wind Scarpractice?
Wind... Scar!
Damn!
Kirara! You all right?!
Oh no!
Bald spots!
It'll all grow back.
It's okay, it's okay.
Okay, time to eat! Let's go eat!
I saw you, Inuyasha!
Is that true?
Thinking back,
she did have some bald spots.
If you thought no one was watching,
you're mistaken!
Kirara ran away...
Because of you, Inuyasha!
Is that right?
Kirara's bald spots were
caused by you, Inuyasha?
And Kirara...
Hold on a minute!
That's putting all the blame
on me!
Silly! Kirara's probably forgotten
all about it by now!
Then you're saying there's
another cause?
Maybe it's that.
Huh?
Miroku, don't say you've forgotten.
H-Huh?
Oh... young village girls.
It's time foryou to appear
on the scene, Kirara.
Kirara, go!
Oh! Such a cute kitty!
Hername is Kirara.
She's my kitten.
So cute!
As are you all.
- Oh dear!
- Monk!
Not only that!
Such a manly monk you are!
Please spend the night
in this village.
Come to my place!
- No mine!
- Mine!
Kirara, you're needed here!
Kirara!
Evil spirit begone!
I saw you, Miroku!
H-How terrible!
Miroku, you're awful!
Err... that was...
How could you!
Kirara is ourfriend!
You can't take advantage of her.
Rememberthat!
Oh?
And you nevertook advantage
of her, Kagome?
Huh?
- Huh?
What'll I do?
What's the matter?
Oh, what'll I do?
What'll I do?
Not anothertest!
Test? No, I don't have a test.
What'll I do?!
I know!
Feels great!
Please, Kirara!
Please!
If you hearmy plea,
I'll give you flounder and
tuna-flavored cat treats.
Please!
I saw you, Kagome!
Why did you go back home
that time?
T-That time?
Sorry, but please wait there.
I'll be right back.
Kirara, wait. Okay?
HAPPY BIRTHDAY GRANDPA!
Let's start.
Let us.
Happy birthday, Grandpa!
Oh, Kagome!
You came back, after all!
Inuyasha isn't with you?
Here you are. My present.
This is...
I'm not sure...
But unlike that water imp hand,
this is genuine.
You can stay awhile today?
Well...
It's a special occasion!
Now let's have dinner.
Agreed!
A special occasion...
On top of which,
I completely forgot the treats!
Even you, Kagome?
Oh... that's...
I hope you've learned
yourlesson
and won't be mean
to an innocent demon ever again.
Especially Inuyasha...
Huh?
If you evergive me
a noogie again...
you won't get Kagome's snacks
for one week!
That's not for you to decide!
Sango!
Sango, don't misunderstand.
We just...
I'm sorry... I...
We didn't mean anything bad.
I know that.
I'm in no position
to criticize.
You shouldn't!
I'm no different.
I'd turn overin my sleep
and smother her...
When I'm in a bad mood,
I'd make her fly across
the night sky.
That's nothing much.
I'd make her transform just
so she could light the camp fire.
Grab her paws several times
a day...
Pinch her nose while
she was asleep...
Dress her up just for kicks...
K-Kagome...
What WE did was tame!
That's evil!
Such a foolish human.
To even think you could leave
my territory.
S-Spare me!
No such thing!
This forest has so little food.
Damn it! I came here thinking
it was Kirara...
but it's only a baboon wannabe
and a mortal.
Hey mister... get outta here.
A-Anotherdemon!
Hey...
Bastard, you dare let my prey go!
Inuyasha!
Ademon!
Where's Kirara?
Not here.
But I smell Kirara!
Who are you all?!
T-That's!
The scarf I gave Kirara!
Not only that. Look!
Bones are scattered all over there.
It can't be!
Why you...!
Did you eat Kirara?!
Fools! As if I'd rememberwho
I've eaten.
Did you eat her?!
Don't worry. I'll let you
join herright away...
in my belly!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
This is my forest!
Everything here is my ally!
Watch out!
He's too fast!
He uses the counteraction of the
tree branches to move at high speed.
And he attacks from a high altitude
which is always fail-safe.
He wasn't just boasting.
If only Kirara were here now.
Kirara?
Yes. From now on,
you must take care of her.
Ohh!
Kirara...
You're just a petty demon
that jumps around a lot.
Well, leave it to me!
I won't forgive you!
I will avenge Kirara!
Don't think that you can defeat me
simply by taking down
the tree branches!
Sango...
We should have cherished Kirara
more dearly.
Kirara was...
Huh? You!
Kirara!
You're okay!
I'm so glad!
Kirara... Kirara!
Making us worry so much!
But why?
Inuyasha!
It's been a while, Inuyasha!
Old Myoga!
Why are you here?
Totosai bade me bring a
whetstone for
Inuyasha's Tetsusaiga.
Awhetstone?
How did you carry such
a heavy stone?
It was an easy task.
I asked Kirara to
help bring it here.
I came all this way and
rode Kirara back to Totosai's hut.
It was a tough commute.
Kirara! It's been a long time!
I know it's sudden,
but I need yourhelp.
What're you doing
at this hour?
Shippo! Tell Inuyasha and
the others
that I'm borrowing Kirara.
We'll be back in one day.
Okay.
B-But what about that scarf?
Oh that...
What're you doing, Kirara?
We don't have any time to waste.
And that's it.
Shippo...
Well... I... probably...
was half-asleep.
Half-asleep, huh?
Hope you're ready forthis, Shippo!
Help me, Kagome!
Inuyasha!
- Not too hard.
- What?!
Heard that?
No, Miroku!
Sango!
I'm so glad, Sango.
Look at the sky!
Nice day!
Kikyo! Is something wrong?
Let's hurry and get out of here.
It's too late.
I've lost my shinidama.
Leave me and justgo.
If you go alone,
you may get out alive.
Don't give up so easily!
In orderto escape,
we have to join forces.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kikyo and Kagome: Alone in the Cave"
Oh, the warmth of someone who lives.
Is this the source of
Kagome's strength?