The moon is about to disappear.
Huh?!
A shooting star!
I wish that I can stay by
Master Sesshomaru forever and ever.
Rin...
Don't fall behind.
O-Okay.
This strange feeling...
Evil spirit... Why are you so restless?
Tomorrow is a new moon.
Even the moon has days when
it can hide in darkness.
But with Naraku holding on
to my heart,
there's nowhere for me to run.
What?!
The demon spirits that Naraku
kept around him...
They've gone through the barrier!
Hey! Koga!
Koga!
Let's rest a bit.
My body won't hold up!
Even the wolves are out
of breath. Koga!
Damn you guys!
If I had to wait for you,
we wouldn't reach Naraku's castle
even in a hundred years!
Then Koga...
You weren't just running around
here and there?
I can smell it.
This foul odor.
It's close... Naraku's castle.
This time... I'll attack his castle
and kill him!
I'll avenge my comrades who
were tricked and slaughtered.
Without fail!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Isn't it in this direction?
Shaddup! Don't talk to me!
I can't concentrate!
Isn't it useless to sniff the ground
to find Naraku's castle?
Damn!
Inuyasha's nose isn't
working now.
Tonight is the first night.
Oh! The night of the new moon!
Night of the new moon?
That's right.
Tonight, Inuyasha loses his powers
and becomes a mortal.
Inuyasha, let's not do anything
rash tonight.
Even if we find Naraku's castle,
without your powers,
you can't fight.
Don't be ridiculous!
We've come this far!
But! We can't act hastily.
Huh?
That's!
A cyclone?!
It's approaching!
Hey! Kagome!
You're here, too?
K-Koga!
That's what you get for
sniffing the ground.
Hey, mutt! So you followed
the smell, too?
Why you wild wolf!
I'll kill you!
Sit!
Koga, did you come to find
Naraku's castle?
Yeah... I don't know what it is,
but I'm getting strong whiffs
of Naraku's foul smell.
It's never happened before.
That means!
The barrier around Naraku's castle
is weakened.
In any case, if I follow this smell,
I'll find his castle.
Don't worry, Kagome.
I'll kill that Naraku...
I'm not the one
you want...
No, Inuyasha!
Don't stop me!
I'm gonna settle it
today, once and for all!
Stop it!
Huh? What's up, mutt?
What's this? Somehow, you don't
stink like you usually do.
Didja take a soak in the river?
W-What?!
Hey! Don't get close to my Kagome!
Get away!
If you're jealous,
try separating us!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Koga!
Caught up with you at last!
Oh yeah, I have no time for this.
See ya, Kagome!
Hey! Running away?!
Naraku's head is mine!
Huh?! Hey, wait up, Koga!
Oh, hello, Kagome!
Hello!
We're in a rush, so good-bye!
Damn him!
Shall we go after him?
No, better not to do
anything tonight.
What?! Are you crazy?
He's gonna beat us to it!
Calm down, Inuyasha!
Besides Koga,
do you want Naraku to see
you in your human form?
If he learns about the day that
a half-demon loses his powers,
your life will be in danger!
And if Naraku is the enemy,
you have to be even more careful!
Damn! What a time... when Naraku's
smell is all over the place!
Damn, this castle is stifling!
All the vassals who were brought
here to this castle...
have been exposed to Naraku's
toxic barrier and died.
What is it, Kanna?
Sneaking up from behind like that!
This fellow... He's Koga, the leader
of the Wolf-Demon Tribe.
Is he near this castle?
Is it a coincidence or...
Kanna, does Naraku know
about this?
No... He's not here.
That's right. Naraku disappears
once in a while.
Kagura...
I'll go and kill him.
No need to wait for
Naraku's orders.
You'd better stop, Kagura.
I hate Naraku's way
of stooping to trickery.
I'll kill anyone who has
Sacred Jewel shards.
Who needs a plan of action?
It's all in Naraku's hand...
life and death.
We are all Naraku's tools.
Who cares?
He's not here now.
This is a weird fog.
I can't see a thing!
Damn!
The smell is strongest right here.
It has to be around here.
Koga! Up above!
Skeletons with swords?
Yo! Been awhile, Koga.
Why, you!
W-What's that?!
Those skeletons!
They're the guards of the castle.
There're countless numbers
of them.
Wind Sorceress Kagura!
I haven't forgotten your despicable face,
not for one day!
After all, you're the one who
killed my comrades!
Prepare to die!
It's payback time
for all you did!
You should talk!
I barely missed taking
your Sacred Jewel shards.
I'll get them this time, for sure.
It'll be easy shutting
down Koga's speed.
I'll let him dance for me.
Dance of Corpses!
Huh?! Still resorting to tricks!
Dance of Blades!
Ridiculous!
Take that!
Did it!
Fool! I'll cripple you!
Dance of the Dragon!
- W-What?!
- A whirlpool of bones!
Damn!
Now choose your fate, Koga.
Let the skeletons in the whirlpool
cut you into bits...
Or jump out
and be slain by me.
It doesn't matter to me.
Hey! Even Koga doesn't have
a chance in that!
- W-What'll we do?
- But we're not strong enough...
Why, that bitch!
She's enjoying it!
If we can take away that
powerful fan of hers...
maybe we can win.
Yeah, you're right!
So get up close and
steal it away!
- Who?
- You!
Stupid! She'll notice me before
I get close
and I'll be cut into bits!
But to fight Kagura and that wind...
Wait a minute!
Wind! There IS a way!
Hey, Ginta!
Don't be hasty!
Koga's actions are proof that
Naraku's barrier
has become weaker.
I think we should at least verify
the castle's whereabouts.
But we can't take Inuyasha
in his state.
So Miroku and I can go.
And if Inuyasha won't listen,
we'll have Kagome
make him "sit,"
then we can knock him out
to keep him quiet.
Not that again?
Like I said...
Koga likes to be complimented.
So l just thought
if I flattered him,
he wouldn't become curious about
your sense of smell.
Still, your eyes were all sparkly!
You tend to get too chummy
with that wild animal.
I do not!
You do!
Inuyasha!
What?
Kagome!
That voice!
They're Koga's men.
Inuyasha, hide!
What's the matter?
The Wolf Demon Tribe are here again.
This is a bad time.
Kagome!
Something terrible's happened!
Huh?
Koga and Kagura are fighting?!
A-And... it doesn't look too good.
Inuyasha, you must not show yourself.
Damn! Don't worry!
I don't intend to go help Koga.
Still... if Kagura's appeared,
that means Naraku's castle
is nearby.
But Naraku had put up a barrier
to prevent us from getting close.
This bothers me.
I guess we have to go
and check.
Sango!
Inuyasha, you stay with Kagome.
You want to keep your mortal
state a secret, don't you?
Damn! No way!
What're you doing?!
Stupid!
Now listen here. If you reveal what
you see, I'll kill you!
O-Okay!
A-All right.
Inuyasha...
Well, he shut them up.
So shall we go?
I can smell blood in the air.
Go... twist and turn harder!
What's the matter, Koga?
Too scared to come out?
Or...
Are you already dead?
Damn! That bitch!
It's useless... No matter how many
bones I destroy, there're countless more.
And my strength won't hold up
against these blades.
What'll I do?!
Hmm... Maybe I'll let him out.
If he's in too many pieces,
I'll have a hard time finding the shards.
No need to worry about that!
Huh? Above?
Why, you!
Pretty persistent.
Is what I'd like to say...
Prepare to die!
Damn! I can't move!
Fool! You can jump or run...
but you can't escape my wind!
Fujin!
My Sacred Jewel shards!
Now then...
I'm taking the two shards
from your legs.
Now you're just an ordinary demon.
So... it's time for the finishing blow.
Damn!
Kagura!
Your life's been spared, Koga.
She got away!
Miroku... Koga is...
Koga!
Your!
The Sacred Jewel shards were
removed from your legs!
Koga! You're badly wounded.
I'll tend to you right away.
Leave him alone, Kagome!
He's gonna die anyway!
Why, you!
Inuyasha?
You're hopeless, Koga! Getting cut up
by the likes of Kagura!?
What about you?
Looking so weak!
I suspected Inuyasha was
just a half-demon...
He was one, after all.
I heard that half-demons fear
for their lives...
And when they're in the mortal state,
they never appear before an enemy.
You're pretty gutsy... coming around
me looking like that.
Now that you know my secret...
Wanna fight?!
Shaddup! I'll finish you off right here!
Koga!
This is an ointment I brought
from my country.
It works well on sword cuts.
Thanks, Kagome.
Why, that... Kagome!
Serves him right!
Still... Not only Koga, but even Inuyasha
approached the castle.
That means Naraku's barrier
is weakened.
That's right!
Naraku is... not here!
What a relief.
Yeah... why should I hand them
over to Naraku?
Now is the time to escape...
Now when Naraku's barrier
is weak.
But... Naraku has...
That's!
Don't ever forget, Kagura.
Your heart is in my hands!
Damn!
I can easily turn you back
into mere flesh.
Kagura... Do not forget.
You are merely a part of my flesh.
I created you out of me.
Do not forget that.
Damn! No! No!
I cannot escape from his grasp.
Huh? A shooting star!
There is someone!
Yes!
That one!
He has the power to sever the bond
between me and Naraku!
Kagura... So you escaped.
It sparkled! A star just sparkled!
Did you see, Lord Sesshomaru?
Lately, Lord Sesshomaru does things
that even I, his vassal, cannot fathom.
I'm so lonely.
This child... She is ignorant of
my concerns...
And sleeps away.
Lord Sesshomaru?
It's his scent.
Huh?
This is...
The smell of that fellow who
was so rude to you... That Naraku!
Is he nearby?
W-What is this?!
Ohhh!
Yo!
"Yo"?! Why, you!
Sesshomaru...
Did you follow Naraku's scent, too?
Lord Sesshomaru!
This woman is the one
Naraku created from his body...
Wind Sorceress Kagura, I recall?
I'm glad you remembered me.
Take your hand off your sword.
I didn't come here to fight.
Sesshomaru, I want to make
a deal with you.
A deal?
You know what these are.
I'll give these Sacred Jewel
shards to you.
In return, kill Naraku.
What?!
Free me from his grip.
My name is Kagura.
I am the wind.
I live freely.
So you'll betray me, Kagura?
Silence, Naraku!
So you're also a half-demon
who loses his powers at times.
Foolish woman...
Did you think you could
escape my clutches?
I am Kagura. I will live freely
like the wind.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Howling Wind of Betrayal"
I saw you, Inuyasha...
as a mortal!