I had caught a terrible cold
and returned to the present-day world
to get better.
All my friends came to
visit me.
But then, I learned about the
test the following day.
Hojo, please help me study!
But my feverjust wouldn't
go down.
Just when I thought
I wouldn't make it...
Here. Medicine. Drink.
Thanks to the potion that Inuyasha
made for me,
I was able to get through
the test somehow.
The weather's great
and I feel great!
I'm overmy cold... and I made
it through the test.
It's all thanks to you, Inuyasha.
Yeah, whatever...
Thank you, Inuyasha.
Hah! What're you saying?!
If you're that much better,
let's justgo on back.
Say Inuyasha...
W-What?
Shall we go shopping?
Huh?
Hah! Why must I come along
with you forthis?
We'll be going on a long journey,
so we have to stock up
on supplies.
Last time, didn't you tell me
NOTto go out?
That was then, this is now.
Just what's going on?
When we're walking like this,
it's as though we're on a date.
Just what're you doing?
Hey Kagome!
These are all edible, right?
Okay Inuyasha,
what do you want most?
Ninja food.
Wow!
Instant noodles are...
overthere.
H-Hey!
W-Wow!
Which would you like?
Well, it's hard to choose...
Maybe we bought too much?
That's an understatement!
Stupid! Don't stop so suddenly!
- That's...
- What?
Hey, why're we hiding?
It's Sota. I wonderwhat he's doing?
A present, maybe?
Found something you like?
W-When you've decided, let me know.
What's he doing?
I dunno...
And what happened?
His foot slipped into the pail
and he fell into the water.
Yourpoor father.
It's his fault forbeing so clumsy.
He didn't get hurt?
No, just a huge lump on his head.
Sota...
What's the matter, Sota?
No appetite?
Uh-uh... it's nothing.
At times like this, here.
What is it?
A scale from a mermaid...
passed down through
generations of Higurashi.
Tape this scale onto yournavel
and sleep with it
and amazingly...
Buyo, you can have it.
No! Hey wait! Wait!
I'm all done.
It's from a mermaid!
No kidding!
I wonder if something happened?
Maybe he's not feeling well?
He's all right.
- What?
It's a sickness...
Iove sickness.
- Love sickness?
Well now, I'll have to make red-bean
rice to mark this milestone.
I know! I'll use that as a reason for
yournext absence!
Don't bother!
- Your teacherwill be fooled.
- He will not!
Such a wonderful sickness to have.
Say, Inuyasha...
Huh? What is it?
Can I talk to you?
Talk?
An important talk, man to man.
If you don't have anything to say,
I'm going.
No wait!
What is it?
Hurry up and speak!
What is love?
Is love eternal?
W-What's this,
all of a sudden?
Tell me...
Who said, "I love you" first?
You or Sis?
Tell me!
W-Why?
Well, you're boyfriend and
girlfriend, right?
What?!
Aren't you?
If you weren't her boyfriend,
Sis wouldn't skip school to
visit your time and all.
And you wouldn't come here
to take care of her.
W-Well...
So tell me, who said it first?
How did you declare yourlove?
D-Dummy!
As if I'd say that to Kagome!
Then did Kagome tell you?
What did she say?
Or maybe, neither of you
have said anything?
W-W-W-What?!
You haven't, huh?
Y-Y-You!
Say Inuyasha...
What should I do?
Like I know!
Hername is Hitomi.
I didn't ask!
Hitomi is in my class.
And she sits next to me
in the classroom.
Like I should talk...
But she's very cute with
big, round eyes.
And she's fair and used
to live abroad.
And doesn't like parsley.
And she doesn't carry
a backpack...
I didn't understand
all of that...
But in otherwords,
you love this girl?
But...
But I don't know how
Hitomi feels about me.
That's why...
I want to declare my
love to her.
W- Why must he tell
me all this?
Please Inuyasha.
W-What?
Can I practice with you?
Huh?!
Let me practice declaring
my love with you.
Huh?!
Please!
J-Just once.
Thank you, Inuyasha!
What's the matter?
Hurry it up!
I have to prepare myself.
If you're notgonna say it,
I'm going inside.
Wait!
I... I...
I... I... love you!
W-What're you doing?!
You don't have to laugh.
Well, it's so stupid!
Why didn't you come
to me from the start?
I'm much wiser about a girl's
feelings than Inuyasha!
'Course, you're a girl!
Leave it to me!
I'll show you how!
'Cuz you're my dear little brother!
U-Umm...
Perfect. It'll be all good.
Here.
Sis...
Now listen.
During lunch break, allude to
yourfeelings ever so slightly.
Then after class, call Hitomi out
and when you're all alone,
make yourdeclaration.
I have to stay in this get-up
and go to class until then?
And what's so bad about that?
This is an important moment
in yourlife!
But!
Come on.
Do yourbest.
Sota Higurashi! Banzai!
Inuyasha, you say it, too!
Banzai!
Declaration?!
Yes, a declaration!
Kagome, did Hojo tell you
he loves you?
And that's why you look
so happy?
But you'll be two-timing him.
No! Not Hojo!
Then who?
You're saying that other guy
hasn't declared his love foryou yet?
You'd betterget that straight.
It can cause problems later.
She's right.
That's not it!
I'm not talking about me.
It's Sota!
Sota?
You mean, yourkid brother?
Yes. He's going to declare his
love in school today.
I wonder how he'll do.
She seems so excited.
About someone else!
I'll say! So different from
the usual Kagome.
Sota is late.
Jilted?
No way!
But it is possible.
Yourplan probably
didn't work.
I'm home.
Sota!
S-Sota...
T- This hopeless look...
No mistake...
He's been jilted!
Sota... cheerup!
Quit acting so depressed!
There're lotsa otherwomen.
What?!
What?
It's not that.
Huh?
I wasn't jilted.
Then what happened?
I couldn't tell her.
Couldn't tell her?
Just like you said...
I called Hitomi out after school.
What's the matter, Sota?
Err... Well...
If you don't have anything to say,
I'm going home.
Uh... Just a minute, Hitomi!
I...
I lo...
Sota?
Huh?
I don't like men who can't
speak up clearly.
It's the end forme!
So that's what happened?
Stupid!
You haven'teven told heryet.
So quit crying like a baby!
It's the same as being jilted!
I'm a weakling and I'm not worthy.
And I can't speak up!
What're you saying?
Then YOU have to change!
Don't worry.
I'll make you strong.
Inuyasha...
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Now then, try it.
But...
Try it!
l-Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Good! Not bad at all!
R-Really?
Okay, once more!
'Kay.
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer...
Hey, Inuyasha!
What?
What're you trying to do
with him?
This is all a matter of spirit.
As long as Sota gets into
the spirit of doing it,
that's all that's necessary.
Oh, I see.
Yes!
What's the matter?
Err... Just talking.
Y'know Sota...
I maybe imagining it,
but that training you just did
seems to be building up your strength.
Yeah...
I think you've gotten
a bit stronger.
R-Really?
Of course!
You're definitely a
different Sota from awhile ago.
You see, Sota?
So do yourbest!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
- Banzai! Banzai!
- Why even Grandpa and Mom?
Nevermind. Just do your best, Sota.
l-I feel like I've been tricked.
Banzai! Banzai!
Banzai!
Man! This is harderthan
exterminating demons!
I hope it works.
Still... what an indecisive kid.
I know.
I'm so disappointed
in my youngerbrother.
Mulling overthe problem like
that isn'tgonna solve anything.
I'll say. If he loves her,
he should just say so!
Yeah! Right!
Sota...
So you came back
with your tail between yourlegs?
It's impossible.
Afterthinking about it,
I realized that just a little
training isn'tgoing to make me strong.
I can't change my character
thateasily!
Oops... He figured it out.
Damn it all!
Will you cut this out?!
Stop dawdling like this!
Go and settle it now!
You say that, but...
Quit making excuses!
C'mere!
Hey! Stop!
Hey Inuyasha!
Now listen up, Sota.
Until you tell her,
don't come back!
But!
If you come back without
telling her,
you won't be allowed inside!
This is my house!
Spirit! It's all in the spirit!
Make up your mind!
That's all it takes!
But...
Damn, what a weakling!
Sota! Didn't you say
you love her?!
Aren't you a man?
Pluck up your courage
and go forit!
I'm going.
Awright!
Do yourbest.
Let's go, Inuyasha.
Huh?
I have to watch over him.
As his big sister.
You sure about that?
Let's go!
Hey Kagome!
What's the matter?
You seem sorta different today, Sota.
Hitomi...
I have something important
to tell you.
Sota...
Aren't you a man?
Pluck up yourcourage
and go forit!
Inuyasha...
Hitomi, I'm not strong.
And I'm an indecisive person
who can't speak up.
But... But...
I really like you!
Sota!
Will you be my girlfriend?
Okay.
Hitomi...
Sota!
T-They're only in
the third grade!
P-Pretty good, kid!
One... two... three...
Nothing forgotten, right?
'Kay, let's go.
Yes.
See ya, Sota.
Okay, take care.
'Bye.
Say Inuyasha...
Yeah?
Thank you.
Yeah...
Let's go, Kagome!
Uh-huh!
What? What're you looking for, Shippo?
Kuroro, who lived in Koume's village.
A strange faith healerhad her
banned from the village
saying she brought bad luck.
Kuroro resembles Kirara and
she's very smart.
Cats are natural enemies of rats.
Maybe this is connected to the village
being overrun by a huge pack of rats!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Suspicious Faith Healer
and the Black Kirara"
I'll take care of things here!