Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The Band of Seven have disappeared
through the sacred barrier.
Furthermore, Koga of the Wolf-Demon Tribe
and Sesshomaru, Inuyasha's older brother,
gather at the base of Mt. Hakurei
to destroy Naraku and his followers.
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
You're mine!
That's Saint Hakushin's...!
Hold it!
D- Damn... a barrier...!
Miroku, you sure Naraku is
hiding in Mt. Hakurei?
Sango and I will go
check out Mt. Hakurei.
Inuyasha and Kagome,
wait here.
Just look around.
Don't take any risks.
Exactly our intent.
Will they be all right?
We just have to have
faith in them.
There!
Damn! No luck here either.
That Koga never listens to anyone!
Nope. Once he makes up his mind,
that's it.
There he is!
Koga! Wait!
You're too slow!
What took so long?
You've gotta be kidding!
We're not slow.
You're too fast.
Koga, let's call it quits already.
We've been searching around
the mountain for days,
but there's no way to get
past the barrier.
Besides, this mountain
gives me the creeps.
It's not easy running around
back and forth.
So why don't we....
give up already?
Shut your trap!
The Band of Seven are here.
I'm sure of it!
Even if it's only outta pride,
I'm gonna break this barrier.
It seems they can't see us,
after all.
How convenient this
barrier is.
Although I don't find it pleasant,
I'll have to take advantage of it.
All right, Ginkotsu.
First, the legs.
Blow his legs off.
But Koga....
Shaddup! The Band of Seven
are hiding in there!
I'm gonna find them and
kill them all myself!
Are you able to, I wonder?
I intended to have your legs
blown away.
Why you...!
Inuyasha....
What?
It's useless getting
all worked up.
Calm down, will you?
I'm not worked up.
Then stop it....your fidgeting.
Will they be all right?
Huh?
Those two.
Will they really be all right
by themselves?
Hah! They're more dependable
than you, that's for sure.
Stupid! I'm not talking about that!
Then what?
Well....
This and that.
This and that?
I wonder how far this goes?
There's no demonic aura, and nothing
out of the ordinary here.
If it weren't for what happened
on Hijiri Island,
we wouldn't have thought to
check this place.
But Sango, we must not
let our guard down.
I know.
Do not let your guard down.
I can't believe this!
I had one lecherous thought,
and I'm feeling sick.
Is the barrier of Mt. Hakurei
so strong?
Is something wrong?
Err.... No, nothing.
You're so strange, Miroku.
They appeared outta nowhere!
So you've been hiding
behind the barrier.
Yup. We've been here
before your very eyes.
Hah!
So our searching the mountain
wasn't in vain.
I never thought you'd appear
on your own, though.
That may be true.
But Koga, you have
the Sacred Jewel shards.
Damn, he got my legs with
the first shot.
I'd better end this quickly.
K-Koga!
Stay away!
Koga...
You sure you can destroy
that metal monster?
They're just like that Kyokotsu.
They were resurrected with
the jewel shards.
If I take them away...
You bastards....
I'll turn you into bones again!
Ginkotsu, pull back.
Running away?!
Not running.
What?
We'll destroy you from
a safe distance.
They're gone!
This is ridiculous!
How can he defeat an enemy
he can't even see?!
Koga, we're sitting ducks!
Let's get outta here!
As if I'd run away!
I knew what I was getting into.
But what do I do?!
I have to lure them
outta the barrier!
W-Whaa...!
I will not give in to this!
What ARE you doing?!
Err.... Nothing.
Damn! There's nothing I can
do at this point!
Steel threads?!
This is bad!
If he gets caught in that,
Koga will be dragged into the barrier....
and he'll be purified!
Take that!
I wonder how long you'll last?
I know!
The time has come.
Ginkotsu, finish him.
Is he dead?
Or....
Either way, I need
the Sacred Jewel shards.
Ginkotsu, go forward.
He was blown to bits.
No way.
Why you...!
You fell for it.
You aren't going back
into the barrier now!
Why're you celebrating, idiot?
What?!
We don't need to escape.
You're the one who
can't escape.
H-He's right!
Besides... just what can
a wounded wolf do?
He knows about
my legs.
Finish him, Ginkotsu.
Let's see you try!
Fool!
We'll see who the fool is!
It's somewhere
in his body.
Where?!
Here?!
The bastard! He aimed
for the shard in my neck.
Ren... kotsu....
He....!
H-He talks?!
You dare.... You dare....!
Ginkotsu, you....
I stuffed the armor I ripped off
into the barrel of the cannon.
What?!
He's still alive....
Why you...!
Ginkotsu, you're not going
to use that?
W-What?!
Hah! Where're you aiming?!
I'm over here!
Why you...!
I've had enough!
Ginkotsu!
Now you're the only one left.
I won't let....Renkotsu be killed.
What?!
Huh?
Inuyasha?
What's the matter?
Let's go.
But....
Never mind.
C'mon!
Where're we going, Inuyasha?
Hey, Inuyasha!
This time.... This time....
my hands will reach her!
I....will....do....it!
Oh....come on....!
Just what are you doing?!
Suikotsu, I really mean it.
When we're in a battle, don't you
turn into a good person on me.
Shut up.
That's why we're moving away
from the barrier.
That damned doctor.
Appearing whenever
he has the chance.
It's hard to push him
back inside.
Oh yeah?
Then let's follow
our plan.
I know.
They're coming.
Lord Sesshomaru!
A sword?
One of Naraku's followers?
How perceptive of you....
Ginkotsu....
T-This is....
I refuse to die in a place
like this!
Say, we should wait
for Miroku and Sango.
I can't wait around
like a fool.
This is the disgusting smell
of an explosion.
Not only that,
I smell the blood...
of a wolf!
Huh?
Inuyasha....Kagome....
Koga is....Koga is....
Koga!
Koga's legs were wounded.
He couldn't get away.
He must have been caught in
the blast fighting Ginkotsu...
Is he dead?
Don't be stupid!
Inuyasha....
Koga is a Demon!
He wouldn't die in a place like this!
Hey Koga!
Quit lying around!
Get up!
Koga!
D-Damn it, I let one get away.
So he's alive.
Koga, I'm so glad.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
What a relief!
I'm so glad!
Koga!
Hey you skinny wolf!
If you wanna stay alive,
take that hand off of...!
Inuyasha.
Band of Seven....
No, damned Naraku!
I'll get you without fail!
Suikotsu and Jakotsu are sent by
Naraku to kill Sesshomaru.
If you look away, your head will fly.
For a dead person,
you talk too much!
Don't run away!
And Kikyo meets Bankotsu.
The fate of a dead mortal....
Has this man's heart been
totally taken over by darkness?
Next on Inuyasha:
"Lured by the Black Light"
Does sadness lie beyond
the blackened light?