Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Thanks to Myoga, we narrowly
escape death.
And we're following a new lead
towards a Sacred Jewel shard.
What?
Why is Kikyo here?
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
To live is to die,
To die is to live.
My name is Kikyo.
A priestess unable
to reach the sacred place.
No... priestess is but
a label.
I am actually a corpse
with a cursed existence.
No matter how much I desire
to help others...
I live off the souls
of dead persons.
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
Good is bad.
Bad is good... Or is it?
In the heart of man
lie good and evil...
The two coexist.
Men can become good.
And they can become evil.
Yet...
That physician who calls
himself Suikotsu...
Is one of the dead like myself,
but he looks after
orphaned children
and gives medical attention
to the villagers.
It seems as though he hangs on to life
through the Shikon Jewel shard.
But I can detect no cloudiness
in its glow.
Only the heart of goodness.
A pure spirit.
Is there truly such a person?
I shall watch the situation
a bit longer.
Inuyasha...
Huh?
I'll take over the guard.
You should rest, too.
Just go back to sleep.
I've had enough sleep.
Besides, the Band of Seven won't
attack anytime soon.
I hope you're right.
According to Koga,
he defeated the one named
Kyokotsu, of the Band of Seven.
And Sesshomaru defeated
Mukotsu.
And you beat Ginkotsu,
didn't you, Inuyusha?
Arghh!
Wind Scar!
So, three of the Band of Seven
have been beaten.
That's a huge blow to them.
Yeah.
That's why, before the Band of Seven
regroup and attack again,
I want to make the first move.
First move?
What else? Hunt them down
and get rid of them all.
I see.
That's just like you.
There are lots of ways
to find them.
They reek of dead bodies
and graveyard soil.
And those wretches possess
Sacred Jewel shards.
I will not forgive them!
I'll find them without fail!
I can save her!
I promise to save her!
Doctor! It's too late
for that child!
Kill her and escape from here!
That's ridiculous!
There's still hope!
The samurai are heading
this way!
If you don't make a run for it,
you'll be killed!
Flee if you want!
I'm going to save this child!
What're you doing, fool?
You're!
Why don't you stop acting
like a saint already?
The real you could care
less about saving people.
Deep inside, you want to hurt
people, to kill them.
That's not true!
I...
Yo! We've come for you.
Geez! Will you stop being
such a pain?!
Aghh!
Idiot!
You can't get away.
Aghh!
Huh!
l-It was a dream.
What a horrible dream...
You're awake already, Suikotsu?
Huh?
Oh... Good morning, Kikyo.
Good morning.
Looks like it'll be a
fine day today.
I cannot understand...
I've kept a close watch
on this man.
Yet I can feel no presence
of evil about him.
All I see is the face of
a good doctor.
So why has such a man
grounded his spirit in this world?
Over that way.
I feel a faint presence
of a Sacred Jewel shard.
Awright!
We've found the Band of Seven.
Inuyasha!
What is this Band of Seven?
So, there are more of them?
Yeah. So what of it?
I see...
I understand...
Crow!
Inuyasha!
I just remembered
some business I must tend to.
I'll excuse myself now!
Hey! Hold it!
Take care!
What kind of business
does he have?!
Never mind, Inuyasha.
It's all due to Myoga that
we're alive today.
You're absolutely right.
I'll say.
Humph!
Thank you, Myoga.
Hmm?
Is Dr. Suikotsu away?
Yes, he went to pick
medicinal herbs.
Is that so?
I will tend to you
in his place.
Really?
Thank you.
Inuyasha,
there's something strange.
Huh?
Until now, the Sacred Jewel shards
possessed by the Band of Seven were cloudy.
But this one's very clear.
Then it doesn't belong to
the Band of Seven?
I'm not sure.
Dr. Suikotsu, I found some!
Yes... this is green gentian.
This one strengthens
the stomach.
We'll pick these,
then go home.
Uh-huh!
You're one of the Band of Seven,
aren't you?
Huh?
Dr. Suikotsu came to this village
shortly after the tombs of the
Band of Seven broke apart.
Tombs of the Band of Seven?
Yes...
On top of that, Dr. Suikotsu
had the same name
as one of the Band of Seven.
So there was a panic among the villagers
who believed he was a specter
who had escaped from the tomb.
Suikotsu is a specter
of the Band of Seven?
No way!
Even if the name is the same,
he is totally the opposite.
I saw the execution of the Band of Seven
with my very own eyes.
It was long ago, but
I remember it clearly.
It occurred fifteen years ago...
Seven mercenaries who escaped
from the east
committed countless atrocities.
They fell into a trap set
by the lord of the region
and were executed.
Suikotsu, one
of the Band of Seven,
was a mean one with
a diabolical expression.
But our Suikotsu is
totally different.
He's a living saint.
There!
Oh...
It feels good.
The pain's all gone.
There are lots of effective
medicinal herbs around here.
Thank you very much!
Please say hello to
Dr. Suikotsu.
Is something wrong?
The presence of a shard...
Huh?
It's approaching.
Two of them...
No, three.
Who are you?
Quit acting dumb, Band of Seven!
Wait!
It's some mistake!
I am a physician!
I am not the Band of Seven!
Don't try to deny it!
Your body emanates the smell
of death and graveyard soil...
just like the rest
of the Band of Seven!
Death?
Me?
I'll make you show your true colors!
Run away!
Wait, Inuyasha!
Don't hurt the children!
Shaddup! I know that!
Dr. Suikotsu!
Why, you...!
What're you doing?!
Are you all right, Dr. Suikotsu?!
Dr. Suikotsu!
Don't worry about me.
Hurry and run away.
No! We won't go anywhere!
We can't run and leave you behind!
The way it looks,
you're the bad guy attacking
a good man.
W-Why?
He's too different from the Band of Seven
we've encountered so far.
Hah! It's all a put on!
The same trick Renkotsu used!
I won't be fooled a second time!
Show your true self!
Huh?!
T-The village!
Dr. Suikotsu!
No! Everyone will be-!
Hey wait!
We're not done here!
Arghh!
Hurry, everyone!
You'd better run, too!
I will be all right!
So they're the Band of Seven!
Kikyo!
What on earth!
So this is where you've been!
Huh?
Hey, Suikotsu.
Geez! You caused so much trouble!
W-Wha...!
Come on, Suikotsu.
We came all the way to get you.
Be grateful!
W-Who are you?
Just what are you anyway?!
I can't believe that he's lying.
Just what is going on?!
This is terrible!
Full of holes!
I've never seen battles
conducted like this.
It's probably the work
of the Band of Seven.
I sense a Sacred Jewel
shard nearby.
Oh yeah...
This place reeks with their smell.
Huh?!
Kikyo!
Inuyasha.
So you were in this region, too.
Lady Kikyo...
Huh? Why?
Kikyo... What're you doing here?
We can talk later!
Oh... Okay.
You guys... You're still alive?
Inuyasha!
Hah! Perfect timing!
I'll take care of you all
right now!
You managed to stay alive...
for nothing.
Such bad luck.
Humph!
I'll pay you back, big time!
If only they didn't possess
Sacred Jewel shards,
I'd suck them into
my Wind Tunnel.
Stay back, everyone!
You're not fully recovered!
You can't handle them.
Leave 'em to me!
All right, Jakotsu.
Take care of Suikotsu.
Huh? Me?!
You're the one for the job.
They intend to kill me!
I'll handle Inuyasha and his friends.
Aww, Renkotsu!
You always keep me away
from Inuyasha.
Huh?
Maybe you've taken a liking
to Inuyasha, too?
If you keep talking such nonsense,
I'll pull out that tongue of yours!
Quit babbling!
I'll take you all on!
Don't make me laugh.
You're such a fool!
These flames aren't even hot!
You're the fool!
Aah!
A net of fire!
Arghh!
Bringing along all
these humans.
Inuyasha, that's your weakness!
Why you...!
Take that!
Hah...
C'mon, Suikotsu.
Don't be a pain.
I don't know who you are,
but you've come after me.
So why don't you just kill only me?
Why attack the whole village?!
How long are you gonna
keep this up, Suikotsu?
Snap out of it!
Otherwise, I'll really kill you!
Get back!
Fire, Ginkotsu!
Damn!
Jakotsu, shame on you.
Fire, Ginkotsu!
Kikyo!
Inuyasha!
If you don't pay attention,
your friends will die.
Inuyasha...
The souls are leaving me...
Kikyo!
Hang in there!
Dr. Suikotsu!
Kids, stay away!
Stay back!
Don't come!
Dr. Suikotsu!
Please stop!
What the hell's going on?!
Isn't he part of the Band of Seven?
Dr. Suikotsu!
l-I... I'm all right.
Are you hurt?
No...
We're okay.
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
What're you doing, you fool!
Good is Bad.
Bad is good.
What're you doing, you fool!
Good is Bad.
Bad is good.
Quit acting like a saint!
Good is Bad.
Bad is good.
Your heart craves killing...
killing people.
To live is to die.
To die is to live.
Your heart craves killing...
killing people.
To live is to die.
To die is to live.
The Sacred Jewel shard
has turned black!
To live is to die.
To die is to live.
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
Good is evil.
Evil is good.
Dr. Suikotsu!
Huh?!
What are you doing, Dr. Suikotsu!
He's finally awakened.
Yeah...
Stop! Please stop!
Why that...!
Inuyasha, hurry and save him!
I know!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
Just what are...!
Me?
I'm Suikotsu of the Band of Seven.
What's going on?
He's a totally different person
from a minute ago.
That Suikotsu has two hearts
within him?
Whatever!
As I thought, you're just one of the
Band of Seven, after all!
Hah!
This is how you conduct
close-quarters combat!
Suikotsu's true self is awakened
and he begins his assault.
Ginkotsu bares his claws
against Kikyo.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Hidden in the Mist: Onward to Mt. Hakurei!"
Kikyo reveals the power
of the sacred mountain!