Naraku...
Fifty years ago,
in order to steal the Sacred Jewel...
Naraku tricked Inuyasha
and Kikyo to battle each other.
Die, Inuyasha!
Now he is gathering
the Sacred Jewel fragments...
and his evil power is growing steadily.
Miroku has been cursed by Naraku...
with a Wind Tunnel in his right hand.
Wind Tunnel!
One day, the Wind Tunnel
will devour Miroku himself.
He must destroy Naraku
before that happens.
Sango's father
and fellow monster slayers...
were killed before her very eyes.
Naraku had resorted to the dirty trick...
- of using her brother Kohaku.
- Kohaku!
He never dirties his hands...
a despicable coward!
Someday, we'll get him!
So you're saying that this Kagura
was born from Naraku?
I'm saying it's a possibility.
But...
Naraku is a man.
How can a man give birth
to a woman?
Naraku became one from
a host of various monsters.
What if one of them
became separated from him?
I see...
She didn't know enough about us...
to be Naraku in disguise.
In any case,
regardless of how a woman looks...
if she's basically made from Naraku,
I'm not interested.
It's not like you're going
to go out with her.
Miroku, get ahold of yourself!
Fool! I can easily create wind!
Take that!
The Wind Scar!
A woman with the same
scent as Naraku.
For sure, she had a spider-shaped
burn scar on her back...
the same as Naraku.
But it's strange.
For a woman,
this Kagura was somewhat strong.
If he can create someone like that...
Uh-huh...
Why didn't he do it earlier?
That's just it. It's not that
he didn't choose not to do it...
He couldn't do it, until now.
Does that mean Naraku
has gotten new powers?
Kagura, because you took
Tetsusaiga's blows...
I was able to see the power
of his sword.
Go now. Once more.
Already your older sister, Kanna,
has been dispatched.
Damn! Where'd that bitch go?
She resisted the Young Lord
of the Keeper of the Oil.
When you find that Koharu,
beat her soundly!
Yes, my lord!
Oh... what'll I do?
Oh, who's that?
- We found her!
- There's Koharu!
W-who are you?!
That's my line.
You look like
ordinary humans.
She's not Koharu!
How pretty... Bring her back.
Yes, sir!
Come with us!
If you resist, you'll get it!
Oh no... she's in danger!
Wait!
So you're their leader?!
Young Lord!
F-forgive us!
Young Lord... hang on!
Huh?! The Young Lord's face
is changed!
What's with them?!
Err... Um...
You're the one they were after?
Y-yes.
Sango?
What's the matter?
Master Miroku!
It is you, Master Miroku!
How I've longed to see you!
Huh?
Have we met before?
I'm Koharu!
Koharu?
Oh... that girl!
It's been three years, Master Miroku!
Oh... you've changed so much!
My goodness... how nice to see you!
Is she Miroku's friend?
Seems closer than just a friend.
I agree.
I...lost my parents and siblings
in the war.
The Keeper of the Oil took me in,
but worked me night and day.
It was hard work...and I was hungry.
I cried every single day.
Then...
Here, go on and eat.
Only Miroku who was in the village
to perform an exorcism was kind to me.
You're Koharu, right?
How old are you?
Eleven!
I see.
Listen, Koharu.
Will you bear my child?
W-why're you pulling away from me?
Miroku! How could you say
such a thing to a child!
You animal!
I was so happy!
Take responsibility!
Yes...
But I didn't lay a hand on Koharu.
I hope not!
She was still a child.
Back then, Master Miroku
left the village right away.
I believed that he would
come back for me.
I trusted him.
Recently though, the Young Lord
of the Keeper of the Oil...
started looking at me strangely.
Last night,
he tried to force himself on me.
And you escaped?
Yes! I beat him up
with the firewood and...
when he stopped moving...
l-I see...
Master Miroku, please take me!
Koharu!
I have nowhere to go!
Besides, I'm an adult now.
I can bear your child.
She's younger than I am.
Girls of the Feudal Era
are amazing.
Hope you understand, Miroku...
we can't take that girl.
Yes...
Still, we can't just abandon her.
Yes... Until I find someplace safe
for her to stay, I cannot leave.
I'll say... after all, you even asked
her to bear your child.
No... I ask that of every girl I meet.
You never asked me.
I'm sorry, Sango! Will you...
Don't say another word!
Master Miroku is your first love?
Yes!
I've never forgotten him for a moment!
I knew we'd meet again...
That thought helped me
get through even the toughest times.
First love, huh?
I'm so fortunate. I can die in peace!
Oh, such a poor child.
Headman, do you think
she can stay in this village?
Of course! Leave it to me, Lord Monk.
I promise not to be a burden!
So please!
No!
It's very dangerous to stay with us.
Just forget it and stay here.
It's better this way.
Yes, yes!
Koharu...
I just spoke to the headman.
Master Miroku...
Koharu, come with me.
Master Miroku, we just met again.
And to be parted so soon...
Please understand, Koharu.
When it comes time to battle...
I'm not sure
whether I'll be able to protect you.
The demon I seek is that formidable.
It's hard for me to say goodbye, too.
Is he trying to convince her?
Seems more like he's seducing her.
Cripes, he's so touchy-feely!
He's only making her more attached.
What?
I may be imagining it, Sango...
but you've been awfully prickly.
You're imagining it!
S-sango...
Master Miroku, please stay with me
for one night, at least.
You heard Koharu.
Please stay the night.
No... the longer we stay,
the harder it will be on Koharu.
What's wrong with staying
one more night with her?
Koharu is new to this village.
I can't...
If reason gives way to passion
and Koharu gets with child...
Koharu will be burdened
for the rest of her life with my memory.
Reason gives way to passion?
What does that mean, Miroku?
Well...
You don't have to explain!
Shippo is still a child!
Crying...
I just can't stand tears.
Inuyasha...
Listen! We'll be leaving
the village after dawn.
But remember, no tears tomorrow!
Got that?
Yes!
Hmm... ?
Master Miroku, how is the bath water?
Just right.
I'll do my very best and prepare the
finest meal for you!
Hmm... I'm looking forward to it.
The stewed vegetables are delicious!
Isn't it?
How cute of Koharu.
She outdid herself
to please Miroku with her cooking.
Inuyasha?
We're surrounded.
Huh?
The meal Koharu painstakingly
prepared will go cold.
Hmm... but it's strange.
I don't smell any demons.
In any case, let's go and check.
Kill them!
Don't let them leave the village!
Beat them to death!
What's with these guys?
Are they from the village?
Are they being mind-controlled?
Kill them!
Why you!
Inuyasha, they're mortals!
I already know that!
What's going on anyway?!
So many of them. I'd better go, too.
It's terrible!
What's the matter, Koharu?
A demon appeared
and the headman and the others!
What's this?!
Headman!
A demon did this?
Koharu! What kind of demon was it?
Well... I just got a glimpse of it...
But why? Inuyasha didn't catch
any scent of demon.
Is that it?
Disappeared!
Hiraikotsu!
Sango!
Shippo!
Sango, are you all right?
Kagome...
This girl is the demon?
Koharu, what's the matter?
I want your soul.
Inuyasha, hold back!
The villagers are being controlled!
Do not hurt them!
I know that!!
Still... it'll never end like this!
You guys are so dense.
Why don't you just kill them all?
So that they'll never get up again.
Kagura!
Not you again!
Ha! I guess if you could kill them,
you'd already have done it.
So you were the one
controlling the villagers!
Yes, it was me.
Humans without souls
are as good as dead.
Without souls?
Why around now, even that Kagome
is having her soul sucked out.
What?!
Does that mean
there's another demon?!
Now then,
unsheathe that Tetsusaiga, Inuyasha.
This time it won't end like the last time.
Kagome...
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Got cold feet?
Miroku, go back to Kagome
and the others.
Inuyasha, what about you?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm gonna get rid of this wench!
Dance of the Wind Swords!
Go, Miroku!
All right!
It's too late!
Thanks, Kirara!
Koharu!
Koharu, brace up!
Master Miroku, I was so scared!
Don't be afraid.
You're okay now.
Hey! What're you doing to Kagome?!
With his evil power increased,
Naraku has created Kagura...
then Kanna,
both of them are his offsprings.
In his palm glows
a Sacred Jewel fragment...
that Kikyo has taken away from me!
Why is it in Naraku's possession?
Inuyasha unsheathes the Tetsusaiga
in the wind created by Kagura!
With Miroku's Wind Tunnel
and my sacred arrow...
we shall finally destroy Naraku!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Wind Scar Fails"
Look forward to it!