Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku with my Tetsusaiga!
The events which occur
at Mt. Hakurei
cause the sacred mountain's
barrier to collapse
and returns Inuyasha's demonic powers.
The time for the final showdown
between Inuyasha and Jakotsu has come!
It's up to us and Miroku, Sango,
Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
I'll take those dog ears
as a souvenir!
Hah! If I pull my sword back,
you'll end up
in bits and pieces.
So long, Inuyasha!
Of all the men I've killed,
I liked you the best.
Damn fool!
I'm not what I was
a while ago!
Wind Scar!
It's over.
You're still alive....?
Well? What're you waiting for?
Go on and finish me.
I don't mind dying
at your hands.
Are you sure about this?
If you don't kill me now,
I may just appear before
you again.
I'm pretty stubborn, you know.
Then I'll just beat you again
and kill you!
This is Naraku's scent!
It's coming from the direction
of the demons!
Naraku's in the core
of this mountain!
That Inuyasha....
What a naïve guy....
Still....
I guess this is it.
This is the Snake Sword
of Jakotsu!
How dare you!
Don't screw up.
Is that right?
You're Inuyasha, huh?
You're cute in
your human form, too.
What the heck....
I had a lot of fun.
Forgive me, Jakotsu.
Be it only one more,
I need your Shikon Jewel shard.
I will use whatever means
necessary to remain alive.
It's close...
Whatever it was that escaped
Mt. Hakurei.
A barrier?
And it's a pure barrier.
The same kind that
encircled Mt. Hakurei.
Then...
Is this the person who
put up the barrier?
Huh?!
Demonic energy is
seeping out of the broken barrier.
This is Naraku's demonic aura.
You seem to have been
most virtuous in your lifetime.
First a monk,
now a priestess?
Do you also pursue Naraku?
Did Naraku hide himself
deep inside the barrier
you created?
What is that look
you give me?
Are you trying to
look into my heart?
I do not even have to try.
Your heart is plain to see.
It is okay to be bitter.
Those fools revered you
and called you holy,
and made you promise
to become a living saint...
Then they buried you alive
in solitary darkness.
Hate them!
Hate all humans
and this world.
Do you scorn me?
I, a saint who saved people and
forgave their sins,
became lost and died suffering.
Then Naraku, a demon,
saved my soul.
Was it saved?
Then what is this sadness?
This sadness which
permeates out of the barrier?
I was not a saint.
While I was on the brink
of death, I realized it.
And in that place, his soul
became bound.
And into the darkness
of his soul,
Naraku appeared.
However,
But hating people...
protecting the evil Naraku...
Was that really your desire?
Your soul will not
find salvation
by keeping such
a tainted barrier around you.
Is there anyone in this world
who has not wandered,
who has never sinned?
I had to be such a one.
And I resolved to be one.
I was like you
when I lived.
I tried to live without doubt,
without mistakes.
So I was right.
You are also dead?
That is why I can understand
some of your pain.
To doubt is to be human.
And that is why humans
try so hard to be divine.
I could not become
a living Buddha.
My attachment to material
life sent my soul to hell.
Do not be ashamed that
you yearned for life.
So please, dissolve
this barrier.
And if I do, what?
I wish that you will let
me touch your soul.
You want to lay me
to rest?
You, a dead priestess?
What're these vibrations?
They're almost like...
heartbeats.
With each pulse, Naraku's
scent becomes stronger.
You must be there, Naraku!
I've finally reached you!
Does this mean Naraku
is making his move?
Jakotsu's Sacred Jewel shard...
Shall I use it?
Whether I run or stay to fight...
I'm coming out of this alive!
There's something
strange about Mt. Hakurei.
The barrier is becoming unstable.
Could... Could something have
happened to Inuyasha and the others?
What's the matter, Kagome?
Koga....
You all right?
Just tell me if there's
anything I can do.
Koga's finally making
his move!
I've gotta see this!
Inuyasha is inside the barrier!
And Kagome's all alone!
Not quite fair....
But if he's gonna woo her,
this is the perfect time!
Do your best, Koga!
Koga....
Kagome!
Please take care of
Shippo and Kirara!
I'm going to check
out the barrier.
K-Kagome!
Hey wait!
K-Koga....!
Please be safe, Inuyasha...
Miroku, Sango!
You're in my way!
Move it!
Bankotsu...
Hey, so you're alive, Renkotsu.
Yeah....
Damn Bankotsu...
Let's see... he has the shards
from Kyokotsu, Mukotsu and Suikotsu.
Four in all.
The shards I took from Kagome
are imbedded in his halberd, Banryu.
I have three shards... from
Ginkotsu and Jakotsu...
That's right!
If I can keep Bankotsu from
using his halberd,
we'll be as good as even.
If I'm going to do it,
it has to be now!
Two and....
That's right,
there was one more.
W-Why you....!
Damn, you smart guys
are dumb!
You kept mulling and mulling
things over,
and it's too late now.
Y-You intend to kill me?
Well, what should I do?
You killed Jakotsu
for the Sacred Jewel shard!
You should talk!
In the end, all that counts
is power!
And the more shards you have,
the stronger you are!
What's so funny?!
You have shards imbedded
throughout your body....
And you used us to get them!
Wanna try it?
What?
Here.
What's the matter?
Take them.
Don't worry, I won't
use Banryu.
I'll show you the difference
between you and me.
Well, what're you waiting for?
Hurry it up.
If you won't attack,
then I'll come at you first.
Die!
What's the matter, Renkotsu?
Hurry and fight.
What's the matter?
Hurry it up.
Or, I'll come at you again.
Damn it!
Hah!
l-I got him!
Absolutely not!
W-What's the difference?
What is it?
What am I doing differently
from you?!
The difference is....
I don't betray my friends.
How sad.
Now, I'm the only one left.
I know....
I've got things to finish.
This will be the Band of
Seven's final battle!
Now then, I've dissolved
the barrier.
Dead priestess, you said
you want to lay me to rest....
and dissolve the barrier
around Mt. Hakurei.
However....
I was buried alive and
my soul is filled with anger
and hatred.
It cannot be saved.
I never believed that
I could save your soul.
I just want to know....
What it is that makes
you so sad.
Sad, you say?
Even though I hold
you like this....
I cannot feel your hatred
and bitterness.
Hate them!
It's all right to hate.
Hate all humans
and this world.
I....
Yours were not tears of bitterness
toward humanity and the world.
Yes....
I....
I wanted to die an admirable death
as a saint.
But I could not.
I did not want to admit....
my own weakness.
So I cried in despair....
over my weakness of heart.
How painful it must have been.
Yes, it was painful.
You have done more than
enough good in this world.
Please....
Please be free now.
Is it all right?
Yes, it's all right now.
There is no one in this world
who never feels lost...
who has never sinned
in his life.
Those who try to be forever divine...
Those who try to be forever kind...
Those who are tainted by evil...
Everyone wishes to be saved.
Isn't that right, Kansuke?
He has found peace.
The sacred ground...?
The barrier...?
has dissolved!
That's....!
Demons are swarming out
of Mt. Hakurei!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Oh Lord Sesshomaru!
The mountain!
They're coming at me!
Koga!
If anything happens to you,
who knows what that mutt
will do!
Awright, come on!
Come on out, Naraku!
Inuyasha, you won't be
meeting Naraku.
'Cuz you met me first
instead.
Bankotsu....!
In pursuit of Naraku, our group
joins up at Mt. Harukei!
But before that, Inuyasha must battle
Bankotsu who stands in the way.
Are you going to interfere?!
Damned right! All my brothers
have been killed.
I'm gonna avenge their deaths.
You'll just be playing
into Naraku's hands!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Final Battle:
The Last and Strongest of the Band of Seven"
Never mind orders!
My fight with you comes first!