Could there possibly be a demon
who can duplicate the Sacred Jewel?
What?!
Inuyasha shattered
the Jewel!
Fool! The Sacred Jewel
wouldn't break so easily!
But I sensed the same presence
as a Sacred Jewel.
It's an imitation Sacred Jewel.
There is a demon trying to
duplicate the Sacred Jewel.
The Jewel may be inferior
to the real Sacred Jewel,
but it still empowers
demons with more strength.
This aura is probably toxic to humans.
It's an evil spirit.
It will defile the human soul!
It's probably the power of
the Sacred Jewel.
It's daybreak.
So you've regained consciousness?
W-What happened to me?
You were buried in the soil.
Huh?
It was difficult digging you out.
Especially since we were injured, too.
What happened to Kagome?
And Inuyasha?
Kagome seems to have been
kidnapped by that Bull Demon.
What?!
Inuyasha went on ahead in
pursuit of Kagome.
Now then, we must go, too.
Uh-huh, let's hurry!
Damn!
The bull's scent was so strong...
Where'd it disappear to?!
I don't smell Kagome either.
All that's left is...
Who are you?!
If we kill you, Orochidayu
will give us more Sacred Jewels!
So die, half-demon!
Die!
Don't take us lightly, kid!
We have Sacred Jewels!
Then...
I'll destroy you along
with your Sacred Jewels!
This is?
We battled that Bull Demon and...
Everyone?
Where's everyone?
Looks so yummy... so yummy!
That's!
The Frog Demon of Tsukumo!
And that boy!
Huh?
Who's there?!
Izumo!
Kagome...
Are you alone?
Yes. I'm so glad you're okay, Izumo!
The demons have ordered me...
to use my knowledge to create
not a fake Sacred Jewel,
but a real Sacred Jewel.
How?
It seems they've also been studying
up on the Sacred Jewel.
That's right!
The Sacred Jewel shards!
Good, they're safe.
But...
You're probably thinking
there's no escape from here.
Their workplace and mansion
are just beyond here.
Get some rest.
Wait!
The villagers have been captured
by the Frog Demon.
We have to rescue them before
he eats their souls.
Even if we don't have weapons?
You're right.
We must find something.
The Frog Demon's weakness
is fire!
Shippo!
They keep coming
one after another!
Go on! Or you won't
get your reward!
Those who distinguish
themselves in battle
will be rewarded
with a real Sacred Jewel!
I was told to use this place.
Are you going to obey
those demons?
If that is the only way
to stay alive... it can't be helped.
I'm sure Inuyasha will come
to rescue us.
Aren't you interested in
the Sacred Jewel?
Interested?
You must have a wish that
you want granted
with the power of the Sacred Jewel.
Hmm... Well...
I want to retrieve the shards
that Naraku has.
But I have to do that myself.
We should check inside the mansion.
Will you help?
Sure. I hope we can build a fire.
A fire!
Damn! There's no end to this!
Found him!
Let 'em come!
They've gone.
But we can't stay here
like this!
I'm worried about Kagome.
So am I. But we must rest a little
or we'll collapse.
Found 'em!
Miroku!
Let's go, Sango!
Okay!
Why isn't there anything
we can use?!
This is terrible for
a demon's mansion!
Huh?
Izumo?
The Sacred Jewel was borne out of
the immense spiritual powers
of a priestess named Midoriko.
Huh?
Yes, I've heard that.
It was created during a battle
between Midoriko and demons.
Midoriko tried to destroy the demons
and the demons tried to
destroy Midoriko.
The souls of the two sides were captured
and became one.
Yes...
The pure soul of the priestess, Midoriko,
and the evil souls of the demons
are intermingled in the Sacred Jewel.
The imitation Sacred Jewels had
human and demon souls sealed within.
However...
That is not enough.
Aramitama, Nigimitama,
Kushimitama, Sakimitama.
In other words, courage, friendship,
knowledge and love are necessary
in order for the Sacred Jewel
to attain true power.
Izumo?
What's the matter, Kagome?
They're gone.
It'll be dark shortly.
The birds did not fear
the dark.
I am the one who
fears the dark.
And those birds
fear me.
Umm... Izumo?
Izumo was my father's name.
He had scholarship and excelled
in poetry and writing...
He loved flowers and birds.
Izumo was my father.
He can't be...
The name my mother gave me...
is Gyu-oh.
Huh?
That was my appearance
during the day.
This is my appearance at night!
A half-demon?
Exactly... Kagome.
Get away!
Go away!
As you see...
By day, I appear as a man
like my father.
But at night,
I am a bull demon
like my mother was.
In order to free myself from
this half-demon fate...
I will create a real Sacred Jewel!
So it was all your doing?
Have you been deceiving us?!
I traveled to many countries
to learn about the Sacred Jewel.
That is how I found out
about you.
With your souls, I can create
a Sacred Jewel!
Our... what?
Priestess!
Your spirit and those Sacred
Jewel shards
will form the basis of
the new Sacred Jewel!
However, that is not enough!
Hence, I must collect more spirits!
The spirit of courage will come
from that half-demon!
The spirit of knowledge will come
from that priest!
Hiraikotsu!
The spirit of love will come
from that slayer!
Miroku! Sango!
Run into that valley!
And the spirit of friendship will
come from that little fox demon!
The four spirits will become
the divine good...
and I SHALL create a Sacred Jewel!
I won't let you!
Don't treat us like ingredients
for your Sacred Jewel!
Yes... Priestess!
Fight!
Resist!
And make your spirit even
stronger!
Only vultures will come near
this abominable body!
Birds take flight at the sight
of me...
and flowers wilt from my breath!
I'm sick of it!
With the power of the Sacred Jewel,
I will grasp all things beautiful!
Then your wish is...
I will become human with
the Sacred Jewel,
and abandon this soul!
Move!
You're in my way!
Kagome!
Where are you?!
You cannot get away, Kagome.
Kagome!
Kagome! You're okay!
No, everyone!
Stay away!
Kagome, we're here to rescue you!
Miroku!
Shippo, run!
Shippo!
Kirara!
Go!
Die!
Kagome!
So this is their hideout!
Inuyasha! More of them!
Who's next?
What're you doing?!
Go and weaken him more!
B-But... Orochidayu is...
Orochidayu is dead!
Now obey me!
Shut up, half-demon!
Half-demon?
You're just a half-demon,
yet you dare order us around!
Since Orochidayu is gone,
I will be!
Gama... take his soul!
Huh?!
Hurry it up!
Damn bull! So you're behind all this!
And you, a half-demon, too!
Well, whatever...
just come at me!
Get him!
And you'll get a Sacred Jewel!
Wind Scar!
Please, let everyone go!
No!
I need their souls.
And yours as well.
And which soul do you have now?
Izumo? Or Gyu-oh?
My soul is now within chaos.
That's why with the Sacred Jewel,
I will obtain a human soul!
If you're going to kill us
in the process,
you can't become human!
Why?
The Sacred Jewel will be tarnished
by your greed!
Silence!
With the Sacred Jewel, I can become
an undefiled human being!
Izumo! Please!
Please stop this!
Even if you appear as Gyu-oh,
your soul can still remain Izumo.
Silence!
Izumo!
I will abandon this appearance!
Inuyasha!
Enough already!
Your courage is absolutely
necessary to me!
And in order to get you,
I will do anything!
Why you...!
I WILL create a real
Sacred Jewel!
You are one stubborn bastard!
Everyone, hang on!
Inuyasha!
Don't you detest your
half-demon appearance?!
Don't deny it!
Half-demon! Half-demon!
Will you stop harping on that?!
I'm me!
As long as I'm strong,
I don't care what I look like!
What?!
You!
Wind Scar!
The Sacred Jewel!
I need the Jewel!
Why you...!
Before day breaks,
I need the Sacred Jewel!
Wake up, Miroku!
Inuyasha!
The sun!
Not yet!
Don't shine yet!
Hear me, oh Sun!
I am going to change my destiny!
Rejected by humans...
Even demons wouldn't accept me!
All because I was born
a half-demon!
So what of it?!
Quit complaining!
And make something
of yourself!
Damn!
The sun!
Not yet!
Give this Gyu-oh just a few
more moments!
Please, oh Sun!
What's going on?
The imitation Sacred Jewel...
How I regret it!
He's!
Izumo was the half-demon.
He was Gyu-oh at night.
And a human during the day.
The miasma in the imitation
Sacred Jewel was too toxic for humans.
Kagome!
Am I going to be able to die
as a human?
Izumo...
Thank you...
Thank you!
Hey! What's the matter, Kagome?
Nothing. Be right there.
Ouch!
The miasma has gone inside my body...
the toxic poisons!
Jaken has been stung by
Naraku's toxic insects!
We have to find the
antidote flower!
Or Jaken's life is in!
Hear me, Rin.
I have been blessed to accompany
Lord Sesshomaru on his travels.
I have no regrets in my life.
No, Jaken! Don't die!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Jaken Falls Ill"
Oh dear... is this really
the end?