Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
While Inuyasha fights,
the Band of Seven attack the temple
and Miroku, Sango and Kagome
stop breathing!
I... I tried to do my best!
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairy Tale
Inuyasha!
Pure is impure
lmpure is pure
The Seven-Man Mound is where
the bodies of seven mercenaries
known as the Band of Seven
were buried.
Recently, it split into two.
That's not all.
The bones of the seven mercenaries
buried here all disappeared!
We're so worried that it's
some kind of curse.
I understand.
I shall purify the site.
Thank you so much,
Priestess!
- What a relief!
- That's for sure.
It'll put their minds
at ease.
There's no sign of evil
here anymore.
In fact, the air is clean
and clear.
Is it because of Mt. Hakurei?
The spiritual mountain that purges the
sins of all criminals.
I heard of a place where even villains like
me can find salvation.
Please take this...
... this lock of my hair to that place.
Forgive me... but I will not be able
to fulfill your wish.
To live is to die.
To die is to live...
Kagome!
l-Inuyasha!
You're alive!
I...
You protected everyone from
the heat of the flames with your fox fire.
But everyone stopped breathing!
That's!
Kagome...
This can't be happening!
Open your eyes, Kagome!
Say something! Kagome!
Do not shake her like that, Inuyasha!
Myoga?
Both you and Shippo will end
up burning to death, too!
We must escape to
a safer place!
Damn!
If only I had been more suspicious
of Renkotsu...
If only I had beaten
Ginkotsu much sooner!
Don't cry, Shippo!
You did well.
But...
If they all die, everything I did
was for naught!
It's my fault!
If only I hadn't brought
them to this temple!
You fool!
If you're saying that...
I'm the one!
It's all my fault!
It's all because of me!
Hey! Enough of your crying!
Crying will solve nothing!
We must take these three
to an open area.
Don't force yourself, Shippo.
I'll do it.
Inuyasha...
Kagome...
Stay alive!
Wait, Koga!
Are you sure we'll find
Kagome here?
Yeah, I'm positive!
But that mutt!
I doubt it, but what if he couldn't
protect Kagome?
I see...
That girl died.
Huh? Why these tears?
I don't feel sad...
Hey, Shippo.
Let me ask you again.
Are you positive that the three
of them swallowed the antidote?
Uh... yeah. I'm sure of it.
It was a special antidote
that Jinenji gave me.
Yet... it had no effect.
Hmm...
Huh?
Shippo, where did Inuyasha go?
Don't tell me...
That he's gone to
take revenge?!
C'mon out, Band of Seven!
I'm right here!
If you wanna fight,
c'mon out!
Jakotsu! Renkotsu!
And you others!
I'm gonna kill every
one of you!
Quit hiding and come out
to fight!
Damn!
So Renkotsu...
Inuyasha is still alive?
Yeah... rest assured.
I'm so glad!
I had my mind on Inuyasha...
So when I was fighting that Koga,
I couldn't really get into it.
So you let him get away?
It's unlike you.
Can't be helped.
The guy ran super fast.
Well, nevermind.
All right. This is just right.
Just wait, Ginkotsu.
You will be reborn.
Yes...
I shall make you much,
much stronger.
I wonder what Inuyasha's
doing right now?
Damn!
I messed up!
If I had seen through
Renkotsu's true self...
Damn! Damn! Damn!
What are you cursing
yourself over, Inuyasha?
Get lost!
I'm in no mood
to talk to you.
Well... Only now you realize
how weak you are?
Shut up!
After all, you're only a half-demon.
You can barely take
care of yourself...
and yet you wield the Tetsusaiga
which was forged to protect others.
It was impossible from the start.
Then maybe I should kill you
and take your Tenseiga?
Then I can resurrect Kagome
and the other two.
Humph! As if you can master
my Tenseiga!
Won't know unless I try!
He's gone...
Is what I've done...
making me see illusions
of that bastard?!
Ready or not!
Huh?
He's not here.
Oh, there's Lord Sesshomaru!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Where have you been?
Found him...
Huh?
I found him.
Found who?
That brat...
Brat?
Brat? Oh, you mean the boy
who was with Naraku?
Oh, Kohaku?
Oh...
Oh! Just a minute, Lord Sesshomaru!
Is Sesshomaru going to
kill Kohaku, after all?
Inuyasha...
Shippo, don't cry anymore.
Men never show their tears,
no matter what.
O-Okay...
Kagome...
Forgive me! Forgive me!
Just because I'm so hopeless...
You... you had to go through this...
Inuyasha...
I can't... breathe...
Kagome...
I'm dizzy...
You're...
That's to be expected.
I sucked out a lot of blood
with the poison.
Huh?
Even for me, this poison
is pretty potent.
Myoga... you?
Oh... you'll bear my child?
I shoulda let this one die.
Miroku!
Oh, was it just a dream?
How disappointing...
He was dreaming about
a woman.
Sango, are you okay?
Uh-huh...
Everyone... is... alive...
I'm so glad.
I was able to revive you because
the poison had not completely
gone through your system.
I made it in the knick of time.
But we've gotta hand it
to you, Myoga!
I guess you can be
useful sometimes.
Insolence! I'm always useful!
I'm sorry, Inuyasha...
for making you worry.
Stupid!
Why apologize!
Inuyasha?
What's with you, Inuyasha?
You told me not
to cry...
Shaddup!
Huh?
Don't be silly, Shippo.
I have served Inuyasha for
many, many years.
But I have never once
seen him shed tears.
I'm not lying... look!
Where?
Why should I cry?!
Everyone's alive!
Inuyasha... thank you.
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
Good is bad.
Bad is good.
To live is to die.
To die is to live.
Perhaps it is the power of
Mt. Hakurei to purge...
But in the surrounding areas,
there is absolutely no miasma.
Almost too pure...
It must be painful
for you, too.
Is it impossible to try to
get any closer to Mt. Hakurei?
I sense the presence of
a Sacred Jewel shard!
Hmm?
This will do.
All right.
Come again in three days
and I shall apply more ointment.
Thank you so much.
That man...
He has a Sacred Jewel shard
in his neck.
Take care.
You take care, too, Chiyo.
Oh my! Such a beautiful Priestess!
Who is that man?
Oh, that is Doctor Suikotsu.
A doctor?
Chiyo... do we have a visitor?
You are known as Suikotsu?
Yes. And you are?
My name is Kikyo.
Dr. Suikotsu!
Whether it be a demon or human...
if one with a wicked heart implants
a Sacred Jewel shard in the body,
the shard will become
totally defiled.
However... this man's shard
is not tarnished at all.
Not only that, this man...
is one who is already dead.
I'm sorry, Inuyasha, that I let
the Sacred Jewel shard get stolen.
Don't worry about it, Kagome.
We can always get it
back later.
But hey, drink this!
Miroku... Sango!
Both of you too!
What is... it?
Just drink it!
It's my special potion.
I sucked out a large amount of
blood from you three
along with the poison.
Now if you drink that,
it'll increase your blood
and make you healthy.
Even then... this is pretty
hard to swallow.
Just grin and bear it.
With all of us in a weakened state,
and needing care,
Inuyasha can't make his move.
He's right.
We have to get better quickly.
Myoga!
I brought more ingredients!
Oh! Good job!
Huh?!
If I regurgitate the blood of
this poison snake with herbs,
my special, secret potion
will be ready.
Here I go!
Churn, churn...
Here!
'Kay!
Now then, everyone!
I'm...
...starting to
feel more sick.
It would've been tolerable
if we didn't know how it was made.
Kagome!
Koga!
I'm glad! You're all right!
Why you...!
Hey mutt, you're alive, too?
I'll kill ya!
Hey!
Damn bastard!
Koga, why are you here?
Well, I was pursuing Naraku
when a strange fellow
wielding a snake-like sword appeared.
Could that have been...
Jakotsu?!
And he said that Kagome
was dead.
You came because
you were worried?
Holding her hands like that!
I'll really kill you!
Shut your big trap!
Whaa...!
Kagome's hands are much
colder than usual!
And her cheeks which are
usually so rosy...
are pale like a fish's belly!
I'll bet you put Kagome's life
in terrible danger!
Well, I'd never let anything
like that happen! Ever!
Why you... - !
Hah!
Inuyasha!
I can't take it either!
- Teach 'im a lesson!
- Yes, yes!
I'll never...
Huh?
I'll... I'll never put Kagome
in such a situation again.
So you can get lost!
Inuyasha...
Huh?
Humph!
These children lost their parents
to famine and disease.
And so... I've been taking
care of them.
They're sleeping so soundly.
Huh?
What is it?
Err... nothing.
Something terrible's happened!
Dr. Suikotsu!
Please help him!
What happened?
He fell and cut his leg
with a sickle!
It hurts! Hurts so bad!
Huh?!
Dr. Suikotsu?
Is there anything I can do
to help?
Oh... Kikyo...
I'd appreciate that.
What's the matter?
You're so pale.
It's nothing.
What a relief!
The wound is not as
deep as I thought.
It hurts!
Dr. Suikotsu...
You're perspiring profusely.
Shall I take over?
Thank you...
Please do.
Dr. Suikotsu...
Huh?
They just left.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't be.
Dr. Suikotsu doesn't
like the sight of blood.
Hmm...
And I call myself a physician.
The moment I see blood,
my whole body starts to shake.
You've been a doctor in this village
throughout your life?
No...
I was born in the eastern region.
I traveled to many villages
ministering to patients.
And finally ended up here.
This is a wonderful village.
It's poor, but because it's deep
in the cold north,
the war hasn't reached us
and it's peaceful.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Dr. Suikotsu?
My hands...
Huh?
The blood...
I must wash my hands...
I must wash...
There's no blood on you.
Dr. Suikotsu gets like
that sometimes.
When it's bad,
he'll keep washing for
an hour.
It won't come off.
It won't come off!
It still won't come off!
Another dead person appears
with a Sacred Jewel shard in possession!
You belong to the Band of Seven!
I am a physician, Suikotsu.
You're mistaking me
for someone else.
Quit lying and show your
true self!
Chiyo, Yuta... run away!
Huh? He let the children go!
Isn't he with the Band of Seven?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Secret of the Pure Light"
The man with two hearts
awakens at this moment!