Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Naraku's enormous miasma disappeared
in the direction of the ox-tiger.
Just beyond that, a mysterious specter-
neither human nor demon... appears.
A new battle is about to start!
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Ox-tiger... it's this direction.
The enormous, evil miasma flew away in
the direction of the ox-tiger (northeast).
There seems to be no mistake that
the miasma is Naraku's.
Damn that Naraku!
Where'd he disappear to?!
He probably went into hiding
because you broke through his barrier.
But we're talking about Naraku.
It can't be only that.
Maybe!
What is it, Inuyasha?!
Maybe Naraku is...
luring us in the direction of the
miasma and has laid a trap!
A trap?
He's laid all kinds of traps
until now.
If we keep going and
get close to Naraku,
you think he'll do something?
But what awaits us?
The demons are running away...
As I thought, this scent is...
Elder, our dens in the valley
have all been destroyed.
Our burrows have been burned, too.
It's devouring everything
in sight.
Half of the demons in the mountain
have become its prey.
Our fangs and claws are useless.
To fight them, we need
the Sacred Jewel shard!
Hmm...
Grandpa! It's coming!
So it ate everything in sight on the
other side of the mountain...
and has come down to
the borders?
Our comrades have been devoured!
Only Koga can stand up to it!
Damn!
If only Ayame dragged him
by the neck and brought him home!
The ogre!
Run!
We'll be eaten!
Grandpa! Let's split up!
Why are these demons
attacking us?!
The ogre has eaten all
their prey, and they're hungry.
Damn! Before the ogre eats us,
we become fodder for demons?!
Why you...!
Everyone, hurry and cross the river!
How could the ogre descend
the mountain so quickly?
A giant miasma flew over?
The area's abuzz with talk about it.
But it disappeared.
Disappeared?
Where?
No one knows.
The river upstream connects to
the mountains in the north.
We've come close to Ayame
and the Elder.
Ayame said the ogre had come
and everyone was nervous.
So she came to take me back.
But I chased her away.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Blood!
Great Elder!
Grandpa!
S-Sorry...
I'm just a bit tired.
Grandpa! Hang on!
They're closing in on us!
I'll be a decoy and
attract the demons.
Make your escape
during that time.
But then, you'll!
Protect the Great Elder and find Koga.
And defeat the specter!
Don't worry!
I won't get killed
by small-fry demons!
Elder!
No, Elder!
Please come back!
Elder!
It's impossible!
You're wounded, too!
Let's go, Ayame.
We can't dally.
You must honor the Elder's wishes.
Why you...!
Koga!
Sorry. Do you belong to
the Wolf-Demon tribe?
Old man, can you speak?
You saved me, but I think
it's over for me.
Old man, aren't you the elder
of the Northern Mountains?
Ayame came to get Koga
just recently...
Koga?
Is Koga here?
I'm Koga.
I'm glad I got to meet you, Koga.
We abandoned our territories
and descended from the Northern Mountains.
The demons are the same.
Ran away? From what?
The specter.
Specter?
It came from way beyond
our northern border.
It's not a demon. It's not human either.
But its body reeked of
dead people and graveyard dirt.
And it...
started to eat the demons
in close proximity to it.
What'll we do, Koga?
I'm going.
To find the specter?
Aren't we searching for Naraku?
This isn't our business.
That's why we're going to
confirm the facts.
Our brethren were slaughtered.
How can we ignore it?!
Besides, the mutt is heading this way.
Inuyasha?
I'm sure of this smell.
I don't want him getting
any glory.
Let's go!
Wait up... Koga!
Stinks of wolves!
Wolves?
This cocky smell...
Koga must've passed through!
Koga is also headed in
the direction of the ox-tiger?
I wonder if he found
some kind of clue.
You said Koga just now?!
That voice!
Huh?!
You're!
It's Ayame!
Ayame!
No doubt about that!
She's the Wolf-Demon girl who
detested you!
Here!
Thank you.
Didn't you go back
to the Northern Mountains?
I did, but...
But?
The ogre came after us,
so we ran.
Ogre?
An ogre who devours demons.
Huh?
An ogre who devours demons?
Master, we must reach the mountains
or we'll end up sleeping in the open!
Shouldn't we turn back towards the
village and find an inn?
Why such a coward?
Let us go!
I heard that lately, a giant ogre appears
in this area.
Nonsense!
I shall suppress any demon
with my spiritual powers.
A demon... eating another demon!
Master! Hurry, please use your powers!
Namu ami...
It's useless!
M-Master Priest!
A specter?
Probably it's neither demon
nor human.
It came from the northeast.
Northeast?
From the direction of
the ox-tiger.
In no time at all, it devoured
the demons, spirits and ogres
that lived in the mountain.
Then it descended to our borders.
Many of our friends were devoured.
The Wolf-Demon tribe aren't
such a weak tribe, right?
It's about the size of
a small mountain... that specter.
Is there such an ogre?
It's said since ancient times, that
dead men who carried grudges
and transformed without ever
letting go of their hatred are ogres.
Who is capable of resurrecting
such an extraordinary ogre...
who would devour demons?
Hah! It's gotta be him.
Naraku?
I must go and take the Great Elder
and the remaining Wolf-Demons to safety.
But...
I know.
If we ever see Koga,
we'll tell him that you were able
to escape. Don't worry.
Kagome!
Thank you!
Be careful!
Take care, Ayame!
Listen up! The specter smells
of dead people and graveyard dirt.
Master Kyokotsu.
They're very close.
The ones with the
Sacred Jewel shards.
I see.
It was worth heading over here
before my brothers.
Kohaku, right?
You can go now...
is what I'd like to say.
But I want the shard on
your back as well!
Do not try anything funny.
Heh... heh...
So I'm under surveillance, huh?
All right.
I value my life.
Especially since I've been
resurrected.
Don't touch my wolves!
Is it you...
the one who has the
Sacred Jewel shard?
I'm taking it...
and your life.
L-Look...
...at that huge body!
Huh! So you're the specter?
Just as the Elder Wolf said.
You smell!
You're neither human nor demon!
You smell of dead bodies
and graveyard dirt!
So I still smell?
It's been some time since
I emerged from my grave.
He didn't blink an eye!
Is he really a specter?!
I'll have to eat more and
put on muscles.
You over there, the muscular one...
You can become part
of Kyokotsu's flesh!
Damn you, ugly bastard!
You also reek with the smell
of my comrades!
I see...
Your leg, huh?
You have a shard of the Sacred Jewel
in your leg.
Kyokotsu, you say?
Just what are you?!
I don't smell Naraku
on this one.
So I'm certain that he wasn't
borne out of Naraku's flesh.
Just what am I, you say?
I'm human, what else?
No way!
Impossible!
So you're an average Joe
who emerged alive from the grave?!
Thanks to this
Sacred Jewel shard.
I feel much better than
when I was alive.
A Sacred Jewel shard!
A real one!
Hey! How did you get
a hold of that!?
Why ask?
You're only gonna end up
as my meal anyway!
Think you can capture me
with such clumsy moves?!
Here's what pesky guys like
you get.
Where're you aiming?
Aim straight!
Missed again!
Koga!
A dead man...
shouldn't act so smart!
As if the same tactics
would work!
I'll send you back to
your grave!
Look Kagome!
That light!
It's the glow of the Sacred Jewel!
But... such a strong light is...
Could Naraku and Koga
be fighting?
But I don't get any scent
of Naraku.
That's!
The glow of the Sacred Jewel.
Sacred Jewel...
Could it be...
Koga!
Hah! Where're you hitting?
You clumsy bastard!
H-He did it!
Amazing!
Serves 'im right.
And you think you beat me?
Why you...!
Koga!
Koga! Before you!
K-Koga!
Too bad. I'll devour you,
Sacred Jewel shard and all!
Shut up!
You...!
Doesn't hurt at all.
It's over!
W-Wh...!
My Sacred Jewel shard!
Koga!
Koga! Where are you?!
Are you alive?
What?!
Naraku's saimyosho!
So the one manipulating Kyokotsu...
was Naraku!
Mere bones.
I guess he revived after the
Sacred Jewel shard was imbedded.
Thank you, Koga.
You avenged my comrades
and friends.
Those who died can
now rest in peace.
Naraku's miasma disappeared
towards the ox-tiger direction.
Yes, that's what Kagome said.
I see.
See ya.
Take care.
That's just what Kagome said.
Same as Kagome, huh?
So Kyokotsu died?
Yes, Jakotsu.
Damn him... stupid fool.
Oh well...
He was the weakest of us all.
So what's he like, Kohaku?
My opponent... Inuyasha.
Is he really handsome?
Please ascertain that for yourself.
I can't wait to see you... Inuyasha!
Mercenaries who've been
executed for their inhumane acts!
We encounter a man who manipulates
a bending sword,
near the graves of
the Band of Seven.
Well?!
This is my Jakotsu snake sword!
Even when repelled,
it bounces right back... just like a snake!
Damn! I can't tell where
the blades will appear!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Band of Seven, Resurrected!"
Inuyasha, your cute dog ears...
give 'em to me!