Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
You...
Why did you kill my minions?
He...has Sacred Jewel fragments
on his right arm and both legs.
Inuyasha, watch out! He!
So you're the leader of
the man-eating wolves!
What of it?
You killed my dear wolves!
I won't forgive you!
Shaddup!
You reek of human blood!
How many have you killed?
I just let them feed.
Any complaints, you dog?
You call me dog?!
I hate the smell of dogs.
It makes me sick to my stomach!
Well then, I'll slit that belly in two...
and let some air through!
What?!
- W-what!
- He's fast!
Inuyasha, watch out!
He's using the power
of the Sacred Jewel!
His right arm and both legs!
That woman...!
Damn! Why didn't you say so earlier?!
That explains why
you're acting so cocky!
It's just the power of
the Sacred Jewel!
Hah! Stop whining like a sick dog!
You have Sacred Jewel fragments
and that's the limit of your power?
What a laugh!
Shut up, mutt!
Back off, you stray wolf!
Both of them are so uncouth.
He's... one of the
Wolf-Demon Tribe!
You know him?
I'm the young leader of the Yorozoku.
Remember the name - Koga!
I've heard about them
from other slayers.
They're demons who control wolves.
They disguise themselves
as humans...
but their true nature is the wolf,
and they're a wild bunch.
They're coming from this side, too!
Kirara!
They're running with their tails
between their legs!
Now it's up to Inuyasha!
Look at you!
You have your hands full
just being on the defensive!
The perfect chance...
to test my Tetsusaiga on him.
The flow of demon energy
collides to create...
a fissure in the wind!
This is it...
The smell of the Wind Scar!
The true power of the Tetsusaiga...
Be known!
Watch out!
What?!
Hey, retreat!
This is dangerous!
W-what the...!
He ran away!
He makes up his mind quick.
Inuyasha... were you testing
the Wind Scar?
Yeah...
But he just ran.
He's only talk.
I wonder...
What?
That Koga wouldn't know the
power of the Tetsusaiga.
If he knew instinctively that
he was in danger...
It's not just brute strength
that we're up against.
I think this is it.
Man... All we do lately
is make graves!
I've gotten pretty good at digging.
I'm turning into a Good Samaritan!
We followed Kagome's sense
of the Sacred Jewel fragment...
and we came to this village.
Only to find the entire village annihilated.
The battle for the
Sacred Jewel fragments...
has brought nothing but tragedy...
killing countless innocent villagers.
So?
So... while I feel that taking
possession of the fragments...
before Naraku can is a good thing...
I cannot approve of your
seeking the Sacred Jewel...
to use its power
to become a complete demon.
That's all.
Hah! Not that again!
You're persistent, aren't you?
No matter what anyone says,
I'm gonna become a full-fledged demon!
You're wasting your time
trying to stop me.
The power of the Sacred Jewel
can be used for good or evil.
However, Inuyasha...
in all our travels together...
we've never heard of anyone
finding happiness using that power.
I have to conclude the power of the
Sacred Jewel is hungry for blood.
Do you know about the
Wolf-Demon Tribe, too?
They live in packs
up in the mountains.
They think they're
supreme Wolf-Demons...
and bully other demons.
Cute little demons like us
all left the mountains...
because they claimed the
territory as their own...
and control it ruthlessly.
You've never heard the
name Koga?
Hmm... There are many tribes
of Wolf-Demons.
He claimed that he was
the new leader.
He must be some upstart kid
who took control of a tribe.
Sango, I brought more firewood.
Thanks, that's plenty.
Kagome... Have you seen Kirara?
Kirara?
Kirara was walking around outside
with Inuyasha.
With Inuyasha?
That's right... She's been following
Inuyasha around quite often lately.
I cannot approve of your
seeking the Sacred Jewel...
to use its power
to become a complete demon.
Damn! C'mon, concentrate!
All right...
I can see...
the whirlpool of demonic energy.
When the vortex of demonic energies
collide, the Wind Scar is formed.
If I cut through the Wind Scar
with the Tetsusaiga...
I can defeat my enemy
with its true power.
How about that, Kirara?
Perfect form, huh?
With you around,
my training's been great!
Let's go back and eat.
Kirara!
What're you doing?
C'mon, it's chow time!
I knew it! That sword of his
uses a weird magic.
Damn it!
My hair is still standing on end!
But I know what to do now.
Inuyasha! Watch out!
He has fragments of the Sacred Jewel.
On his right arm and both legs!
A woman who can see
the Sacred Jewel.
I'll make her work
for me.
All right! I got the wolf scent.
I'll follow the scent
and get them without fail!
I hate the smell of dogs.
Makes me sick to my stomach!
That cocky bastard!
Calling me a "mutt"!
I don't blame him for getting
upset at being called a "mutt."
But he sure looks like one.
What?!
Say that again, Shippo!
He can hear me
from that distance!
Now that really is canine power.
Shippo!
C'mere, so I can give you
a hundred wallops!
This area feels very weird.
Do you sense it, too?
Kirara's also been very restless.
I feel a foreboding energy
approaching...
Different from wolves.
Another demon is here then?
You're too slow, Miroku!
Where've you been?!
Inuyasha!
Do your nose and ears
sense anything?
Nose? Ears?!
You're treating me
like a dog, too!
Damn! You piss me off...
every one of you!
That's not what I'm saying!
I'm just asking if you sense a
different presence!
Everyone, look up!
Inuyasha!
Sango!
Miroku!
Damn, what're they up to?
W-what is that?!
See ya, mutt!
Inuyasha!
She's mine!
Kagome!
No, what...?!
With Sacred Jewel fragments
in my legs...
this cliff is nothing!
No! You're not reaching it!
We're gonna fall!
Shaddup! Stop screaming!
I will scream!
Damn! Let me go!
W-what?!
That show-off!
T-they!
That'll teach him!
No one can keep up with my legs.
Of course not! You have
Sacred Jewel fragments!
When you cheat,
you don't get bragging rights!
What?!
Just what is the meaning of this?!
Kidnapping me!
W-what?!
A bird?
But isn't it awfully big for a bird?
If that's not a bird, then!
W-what're they?!
Those stupid birds are gathering
to come after me.
Good timing... Now look hard.
Do you see any among them
with Sacred Jewel fragments?
Sacred Jewel fragments?
No... None of them.
Do those demons also
have fragments?
So... None of 'em have it, huh?
Then I've got no use for 'em.
So long!
Now scram!
It's Koga!
Koga's back!
Hey, Koga!
Yo... I'm back.
Where is this?
This is the Wolf-Demon Tribe's den!
Damn!
We were really washed downriver.
Koga's goal was to kidnap Kagome.
Kagome?
So that's why the wolves separated me
and then retreated immediately.
Looks like it.
Sango!
What of Kagome?
I almost caught up with them...
but I had interference.
Interference?
What is this?
A bird?
Not just ten or twenty of them.
They covered the sky.
So this is the other demon energy
we sensed.
It seems that these high mountains
are all their territory.
Even you found them a challenge...
Now we have the Wolf-Demon Tribe
and these birds on our hands.
Those are Shippo's warning signs!
That reminds me...
I thought he was missing...
so he's been kidnapped with Kagome!
They're pointing toward the mountains.
We can't waste any more time!
Hey, Koga! Who's that woman?
This place is full of
man-eating wolves and skeletons!
Hey, Koga! Tasty-Iooking prey!
Lemme eat some of her!
They'll eat me!
This woman is not food!
I'll kill anyone who
takes a bite outta her!
Scary...
Oh, I get it... I'm able to see where
the Sacred Jewel fragments are...
so he needs me.
At least they won't kill me right now.
Huh?
Oh this...
Seems he stuck fast to my tail
when I captured the girl.
Here... You can eat him.
Kagome!
Hey wait!
You want my help, don't you?
If you lay a hand on Shippo,
I refuse to help you!
Oh? That makes it easy.
Hey, move!
Whoa... You guys put on weight again!
All of you are eating too much!
Here!
- Shippo!
- Kagome!
This Koga...
Maybe he's not that bad.
Move, move!
We've got injured! Make way!
What happened?! Hang in there!
Get water, quick!
Them again?
They were suddenly attacked
during guard duty.
Only these two managed to escape.
The others fell off the cliff.
Such terrible wounds...
You saw them earlier.
They call themselves
Birds of Paradise...
but they're our natural enemies.
This is their doing.
They swoop down silently...
and capture our comrades
with sharp talons.
Then what do they do?
They eat them.
Wolf bones are scattered
around their nests.
Even you're no match for them?
That's just it...
The trouble is,
one among the Birds of Paradise...
possesses a Sacred Jewel fragment.
He's faster than we are...
he even killed 20
of our wolves in one swoop.
They were never this strong before.
So it must be the power
of the Sacred Jewel.
That's why you want me to find
which one has the fragment.
We'll attack their nest
and steal the fragment.
We won't make senseless sacrifices.
We'll attack that one bird
with the fragment en masse.
Got it? You know what to do?
All right, I'll do it.
If I can get out of this camp,
maybe I'll see Inuyasha.
For now, it's safer to just
do as they say.
Kagome! Just bear it
for a while longer.
My mushrooms are sure to
lead Inuyasha and the others here.
What's this? Can you eat it?
Yuck!
Stop picking weird stuff!
My mushrooms...!
That was the last mushroom!
Damn! Where'd Shippo go anyway?
He's no use at the crucial moment!
The smell of wolves is
all over the place.
Even Inuyasha's sense of smell
is useless.
All this wolf scent
has overpowered Kagome's smell.
What's wrong, Inuyasha?
It's not wolf... but I'm starting to
smell some ugly birds.
I have to rescue Kagome...
so don't bother me at
a time like this!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
It's a showdown for...
the Wolf-Demon Tribe
and the Birds of Paradise!
Demon birds fly down swiftly and attack.
The Wolf-Demons and their wolves...
fight ferociously on the cliffs.
Inuyasha still has't come...
and Koga says things
that don't make sense!
This is no time...
This is no time for declaring affection!
Next on Inuyasha: "The Man
Who Fell in Love with Kagome!"
Don't miss it!