It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
forourdreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
At last, the path is opened.
In pursuit of Naraku,
we enterthe borderthat separates
this world from the afterlife.
In the graveyard where
Inuyasha's fatheralso sleeps,
the guard of the Sacred Jewel shard
lies in wait!
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
I'll swallow you up in one gulp!
W-Wha...?!
Damn you!
Naraku!
He takes every advantage
of them, then....
Well, weren't you planning
to defeat Princess Abi, too?
You should be grateful.
Thanks to me, you all are....
now able to go to the border
between this world and the next.
The time has come!
He cut off Tekkei's head....!
A river of blood....
This connects to the border between
this world and the next.
Naraku!
What are you looking at?
This river of blood
will not last.
Hah! I don't need to
be told that!
Let's go, Inuyasha!
Right!
Let us go, too!
It's no good, Master Inuyasha!
Huh?!
Even if you are able to get to
the border on this current,
how do you intend
to come back?
Well....
even Naraku has
the same problem.
This isn't the time to be
worrying about how to get back.
That's exactly what I say!
Huh?
What's the matter, Shippo?
I can see things that
look like human faces!
Huh?
These are....
probably the feelings of resentment
of the people
whose blood Princess Abi's mother,
Tekkei, drank.
How many people were killed....
just so he could get his
hands on the Sacred Jewel shard?
We have to bring this to
an end quickly.
Right!
Yayakoshi yo...
Yoyoko...
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru,
what could that be?
it's a giant bird.
Ho! Huh?!
It is headless!
That scent of a massive amount
of blood has disappeared.
Huh?
It seems you were too late,
Sesshomaru.
The entry way has closed.
Huh?!
K-Kagura!
Just what are you up to anyway?
You've been showing up a lot
around Lord Sesshomaru lately.
Lord Sesshomaru isn't
the least bit interested in you!
Or....maybe he is.
What do you mean
by "entry way"?
Hmm... How unusual...
he's taken the bait.
To the path that leads to
the border
between this world
and the next.
Naraku and Inuyasha
have already gone through.
From yourmanner of speaking,
it seems that you
know something else.
I doknow something else....
About anotherpath.
Although Sesshomaru,
even you may not be able
to cross that path alive.
What's happening?
Something seems wrong.
Huh?!
A light!
The exit?
Kagome, hang on tight!
Huh?!
This is!
Inuyasha!
Man, we could have been
blown away, too!
Inuyasha! Isn't this....?!
Yeah....
Go that way!
Father...
This is....
the borderbetween this world
and the next?
Ademon graveyard....
Is that Inuyasha's father?
Huh?!
It's so huge....
Inuyasha...
This isn't the time
forleisurely sightseeing.
Naraku got here before us!
Uh-huh.
Damn that Naraku...
He probably intends to lay low
until Kagome finds
the Sacred Jewel shard.
I can sense the Sacred Jewel shard!
Inuyasha!
Huh? Inuyasha?
Huh?!
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha! Snap out of it!
Huh?!
What happened?
Huh?
Are you all right....?
You suddenly lost
consciousness.
What was that just now?
Why am I thinking about
that time now?
Kagome!
You're all right?
Yes! Don't worry about us!
These are shining spears!
Huh?! We'll be skewered!
Is this Naraku's doing?!
Huh?! These are adamantite!
Adamantite?
Like diamonds?
Huh? Daiyamon?
Never heard of such a thing!
It's the hardest jewel
in this world.
These spears are made
of adamantite.
But Inuyasha....
I don't sense
Naraku's ghostly aura at all.
Then who the hell is
behind this?!
I don't like this.
The spears are shooting out
of my old man's grave!
Dammit! What's going on?!
The light spears have stopped.
Huh?!
Inuyasha.... The Sacred Jewel
shard is in yourfather.
Wha...?!
You there!
You are not dead men, are you?
Huh?!
You are grave robbers
afterthe Sacred Jewel shard!
Huh?!
Just what the hell are you?!
Making a nest in the belly
of someone's father!
"Father," you say?
Are you saying you're the son
of the Great Dog Demon?
Master Inuyasha....
This skull...
Could it be Hosenki?
Aren't you Hosenki?
It's me, Myoga!
Hosenki?
The one who made the black
pearl for Inuyasha long ago.
Myoga, you say?
Then this young one
must be Inuyasha?
Yes!
Master Inuyasha is not your enemy.
Without a doubt, I made the black
pearl at your father's request.
However, Inuyasha,
you passed through the black pearl
once to come to this world.
Having fulfilled its purpose,
the black pearl has lost its power
and returned to its place
in yourrighteye.
Was it you....
who made me see those visions?!
Visions?
Those were probably thoughts
still left in the black pearl.
In the black pearl?
Didn't the visions you had
tell you to leave this place?
It goes without saying,
entering the land of the dead
again is not allowed....
no matter who you are!
Ahh....Umm....
I can see it!
Hosenki has the Sacred Jewel shard!
Why did you bring the
Sacred Jewel shard here?
Huh? So you have it, after all!
Hand it overpeacefully!
If you do, we'll go back.
I cannot.
That is because it was
this Sacred Jewel shard's will
to come to the land of the dead.
The shard's will?
I am the demon who controls jewels.
And I have the powerto
heartheir will.
When I existed in
the land of humans
and my life was nearing
the end,
a Sacred Jewel shard came
into my possession.
And the shard spoke to me
and said that
the Sacred Jewel must never
be allowed to become whole again.
Most of the Sacred Jewel shards
are in the possession of evil men
and are tainted.
And if it were to become
mixed with those,
my shard would also
become tainted.
And that is precisely why
I must keep it here in
this demon grave
beyond the reach of
the hands of evil.
It was the Sacred Jewel shard's
desire to come with me here!
Huh....
Master Inuyasha, it would be
wise to back off here.
Leave the shard to Hosenki....
Huh?! Are you half-asleep
or something?!
Naraku has already come
to this world ahead of us!
He's hiding somewhere,
waiting forhis chance
to get the Sacred Jewel shard!
Hmm....
No matter who comes,
I shall not let him have it!
Huh?! Hosenki, you....!
What's this?
The sky!
This is no ordinary happening.
I shall not go easy
on you either!
W-Wait Hosenki!
Let me explain....!
Kagome, you stay put!
Inuyasha!
Hey you! Betterlearn to tell
the difference
between friend and foe!
Tetsusaiga isn't working!
It's useless, Master Inuyasha!
Hosenki's arms are hardened
adamantite!
Old Myoga.... When did you come here?
It only took a moment.
Dammit!
He's too reckless!
He has nothing to
land on.
H-Hosenki!
Are you seriously trying to
harm Inuyasha?!
The Sacred Jewel shard is!
Be careful, Inuyasha!
Hosenki's Sacred Jewel shard
has turned black!
What?!
What's going on?!
The Sacred Jewel shard turns
good orevil
depending on the heart
of its possessor.
From his story just now,
I don't think Hosenki brought the
shard here out of personal greed.
I sense the presence of
tainted Sacred Jewel shards....
The size of this presence....
It's Naraku's!
So Naraku is influencing this?!
Kagome, where is he?
Where is Naraku?!
I can't tell.
The presence is all over the place!
I can't tell in which direction.
Didja hearthat, Hosenki?!
If you hang onto it,
your soul will be taken
by the tainted shard!
Give it up now!
Don't make me laugh!
I am not so weak as to
lose my soul
to a minorirritant such as this!
I will notgive it up
to anyone....!
Damn! I guess I have no choice
but to take it by force.
Hey Hosenki!
Before your soul is devoured,
I'll take the Sacred Jewel shard
outta you myself!
Take it if you can!
His whole body is
turning black.
It must be the evil from
the shard spreading.
I'm coming!
Master Inuyasha,
go easy on him!
Hosenki is an old
friend of your father.
He is not a bad demon!
If I could beat him easily,
I'd do just that!
Wind Scar!
Did it work?
Huh?
Not again!
I... I will not run away!
Inuyasha?
Huh?!
Inuyasha!
Why you...!
Wind Scar!
The Wind Scarisn't working!
I have to get close to
the shard!
Hiraikotsu!
I must stop Hosenki's attack!
I know!
If I can purify that shard...
My arrow will probably work...
Go!
I got it!
Hmm... That was pointless...
Huh?!
It didn't purify the shard!
Even Kagome's arrow
had no effect!
The arrow didn't reach
the shard.
That body is like armor!
Not only that!
Hosenki was a great demon
who lived for a long time.
Kagome's arrow doesn't
have enough spiritual power.
So....the spiritual power
needs to be stronger?
If it's Kikyo's arrow....
W-Why?
Kikyo's arrow rejected her?!
Give this to Kagome.
But whethershe can use it
fully ornot...
will depend on Kagome.
What does it mean?
Is it impossible forKagome?
Huh?!
The spot that was hit
by Kagome's arrow...
he's covering it.
Kagome, aim for that spot
once more!
B-But....!
Hurry up and shoot!
A-All right!
Just because Kagome's arrow
didn't reach the shard,
doesn't mean it had
no effect at all.
I'lljust cut it here!
Wind Scar!
It broke open!
Awright!
Now I can get the shard!
You....fools!
Huh?
Inuyasha!
You and I....
All of us were just made
to dance by the black jewel.
Inuyasha....
Inuyasha!
I finally possess the last of
the Sacred Jewel shards.
Hosenki's shard is stolen
by Naraku!
He's come sneaking out,
and that's what I've been
waiting for!
Sesshomaru is guided by Kagura
to the site of the showdown!
Did you rush overto
save your youngerbrother?
What a kind brotheryou are.
A half-demon like you....
corrupting my father's grave!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Final Battle at the Graveside:
Sesshomaru Versus Inuyasha!"
The only one who can kill
Naraku is Sesshomaru!