Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The battle is about to begin
on sacred grounds.
Having increased the power of his giant
halberd Banryu with the Shikon Jewel shards,
Bankotsu, the leader of the Band of Seven
stands ready, awaiting our arrival.
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Father, it hit Hijiri Island.
Yes. You stay here.
What about you?
I must check to see that
Saint Hakushin Temple is safe.
This is the staff entrusted to our ancestors
by the wise one.
Take me, too!
Shintaro, you must go home.
But....
Understand this.
If anything should happen to me,
as the son of the village headman,
you are the only one
who can protect Hijiri Island.
Don't worry. I'll be home
by morning.
Father....
Huh?
Well, Inuyasha?
This isn't it.
It didn't smell
like this marsh.
It was the scent of water
and flowers that
I sensed from Naraku's
demon puppet.
And it was pure like
Mt. Hakurei.
Well then, let's try checking
other lakes.
I wonder if Sango and
Kirara are okay?
Mt. Hakurei!
Huh?!
Kirara, it's painful for you to
cross the barrier, too?
I'm sorry.... forcing you like this.
Everyone!
Sango!
How did it go?
Not good.
The barrier around Mt. Hakurei
is even stronger than before.
It's impossible to enter
through it then?
I'm sure of it. Naraku has
been close by.
Let's check every waterway
around the mountain.
Please, take me out!
No, you have a duty to take the
place of your father as headman.
We can't place you in
any danger.
But Father has been gone
for two weeks!
Something must have happened
on Hijiri Island.
But the only ones allowed
on Hijiri Island
are the village headmen....
Which means only you.
Just give me a boat.
I'll go alone.
Your father didn't do anything
to raise the wrath of the Saint, did he?
We can't have the village
cursed, too.
My father has lived his whole life
fulfilling his duties as headman!
He wouldn't do anything
like that!
We'll be punished if
we go there.
Hiriji Island is a sacred place.
Hey!
Did I just hear something
about a sacred place?
Will you talk to us?
Close to the center of this lake
is an island which is
forbidden to common folk.
The duty of village headman has been
passed down through my family.
And only our men have been
allowed on the island
to tend to Saint Hakushin.
Saint Hakushin?
He was a great, wise priest who
lived over a hundred years ago.
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
Good is evil.
Evil is good.
To live is to die. To die is to live.
He became a living Buddha
and is enshrined in a
temple on the island.
To live is to die. To die is to live.
A living Buddha?
It's called sokushin-butsu.
A priest of great virtue meditates
and fasts until his body mummifies
and attains Nirvana.
In other words,
a dried-up priest?
Watch what you say!
You said your father
hasn't returned home.
Yes, it's been over
two weeks.
A strange light fell on
the island.
Huh?
Father was concerned
about the temple.
Strange light?
Probably Naraku.
Shintaro, it's impossible
for you alone.
Sister....
But Father told me to take care
of things if anything happened to him.
The villagers said something
about a curse?
The villagers are wrong!
Father protected the village
all his life.
There has to be a reason for
his failure to return!
Yes.... We're worried about
our father, too.
And the villagers fear a curse.
We're at a loss.
Let's go, Inuyasha.
Yeah.... There's got to be something
about that sacred place.
You'll go? Really?
Of course.
It's only natural for you
to worry about your pa.
Thank you!
I'll guide you across
the lake.
The island is always covered
with mist and can be dangerous.
Please take care of
our younger brother.
Shintaro is the only male
left in our family.
That must worry you.
If you'll agree, I can help you
and your sisters bear some males.
Can we really entrust our
brother to you?
No complaints, right?
Inuyasha! Don't threaten them!
I'm sorry. We just want to borrow
your boat for a while.
We'll return it!
Don't worry.
It must be the sacred aura
from Hijiri Island.
It's so strong, even
Kirara can't transform.
To live is to die.
To die is to live.
Saint Hakushin
beneath the earth
Mt. Hakurei will return to Hijiri.
What is that?
It's a children's song that's been sung
around this region for a long time.
From the time he was alive,
Saint Hakushin had amazing spiritual powers
and saved many people
of this region.
There! You can see Mt. Hakurei.
At the base is a place
of purification.
Place of Purification?
It's a temple built
by the wise one.
If you pray there, any and all sins
are absolved.
Mt. Hakurei again?
Listen.... I wonder who put up
the barrier around Mt. Hakurei.
You're right. Someone had to
put up the barrier.
But it's the total opposite of the
kind of barrier Naraku would use.
It seems as if a holy person
put up the barrier, but why?
Hijiri Island.
Be careful. There are
craggy rocks everywhere.
If the boat hits against
one of these rocks....
Huh?!
Arghh!
Say that sooner!
Geez! This was a borrowed boat!
Shaddup! Keep complaining
and I'll leave you!
I can't swim.
Shippo, I can't see in front of me!
Huh? This is....
Are you all right, Miroku?
You saved me!
This is....
The same barrier as Mt. Hakurei....
Although not as strong.
I'm sure of it.
These flowers....
smell the same as
Naraku's demon puppet.
There never used to be
flowers like these.
Are you all right, Shippo?
Yeah....
The scent is overpowering
Kirara, too.
This is all too convenient...
Why did that Naraku...
create a damn puppet just
to help the Band of Seven escape?
And then leaving this strong
scent of the flowers...
It's like I was lured to these
sacred grounds by it.
What's that?
The Wise One's temple!
It's destroyed! But why...?!
Aghh!
Father's clothing....
Huh?!
F-Father!
His father came to the
island two weeks ago.
It's too soon to turn
into bones.
Could it have been
Naraku's demons?
I'm sure of it now.
But why?
This island has the temple and....
Huh?
I sense a Shikon Jewel shard!
Damn! About time!
Making me wait so long in here!
What?!
This place makes even a human
like me feel sick.
It must be even more
trying for a half-demon, Inuyasha!
Bankotsu!
Damn, it was a trap!
Did you do this,
Bankotsu?!
Don't look at me.
I was only told to wait here.
Be careful, Inuyasha!
Bankotsu's halberd has
Sacred Jewel shards in it!
It got scarred during
our little match the other day.
So I used them to mend it.
Let's do it!
This time,
I'll cut you to pieces!
That's my line!
Inuyasha is on the defensive!
Because of the Sacred Jewel shards
in Bankotsu's halberd.
Dammit!
I'm sick of this!
Wind Scar!
W-What....?!
He couldn't invoke the Wind Scar?!
No wonder he told me to
fight you here.
Damn!
Why can't he use the Wind Scar?
Tetsusaiga's demonic power is
being purified by Hijiri Island.
Huh?
Furthermore, no matter how
evil Bankotsu's spirit may be,
he was still a mere human.
Compared to Inuyasha in whom
courses demon blood,
the effect of Hijiri Island on Bankotsu
is minimal.
Inuyasha, you're much weaker
than when we last fought.
Now hurry up and die!
I want to get off this uncomfortable
island as soon as I can!
There has to be someone
putting up this purifying barrier.
Just as I thought...
It's over there.
Huh?!
Shintaro!
Saint Hakushin!
Please help Inuyasha!
This is....
Father's....
Shintaro!
Saint Hakushin isn't here.
Not here?
He was enshrined in there!
What's going on?!
Does this mean Naraku
attacked this island to...
Miroku, Saint Hakukshin's
mummy is gone!
Naraku may've stolen it!
Gone? Then it wasn't
Saint Hakushin who....?
Then who is putting up this
sacred barrier on Hijiri Island?
Yahh!
Arghh!
Inuyasha!
Damn!
Miroku....
I thought Saint Hakushin was
putting up this barrier.
What're you saying?!
The Saint was someone
who saved people!
Why would he put up
a barrier?!
The strange light you and
your father saw
was a demon named Naraku.
Naraku?
Your father fought Naraku and tried
to protect the Saint.
Saint Hakushin!
So then....that skeleton was
my father.
Naraku was planning to use
Saint Hakushin's spiritual power.
Your father tried to stop him.
That is the duty of
the village headman.
Father didn't die because
he was cursed.
Isn't that right?
Yes!
Then where is
Saint Hakushin's mummy?
Who put up this barrier?
Damn!
One more time!
This is the end for you!
Inuyasha, hang on a bit longer!
If I can find the core
of the barrier....
Shippo, lend me your powers!
Huh?
Shippo's demonic powers which
I transferred to the sutra charms
should produce a reaction!
They've been purified!
It's over there!
That's an altar ornament
Saint Hakushin always used!
This is it?
I'll use this staff that Saint Hakushin
once owned. We'll try together!
Miroku....
Let's try.
Give me strength, Father!
The flowers have disappeared!
The Wind Scar is back!
The barrier is broken!
This is what created
the barrier.
But this vajra was
locked up in the temple.
Does this mean that Saint Hakushin is
lending his powers to Naraku?!
Don't think this'll save you.
With the barrier gone,
I'm feeling much stronger, too.
That disgusting barrier is finally gone.
So let's settle this
once and for all, Inuyasha!
Take this! Dragon Thunder!
Multiple lightning bolts!?
Damn you!
Involving Kagome and the others!
There's nothing unfair
in war!
I'll kill you if it kills me, too!
Inuyasha fights Bankotsu!
During their battle, Saint Hakushin's
power saves Bankotsu!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Sacred Vajra
and the Mystery of the Living Buddha"
Could Saint Hakushin be
helping Bankotsu?!