Time's up!
I studied when I was
in the other dimension.
And despite Inuyasha's complaints,
I came back here.
How'd it go?
Terrible.
Hey! Hey!
Wasn't today's test easy?
D-Don't say that!
Say... Kagome...
How's your guy?
- Guy?
- Yeah, right!
The delinquent!
He's not a delinquent.
The two-timing one!
H-He's not actually two-timing...
Then how would you
describe him?
Err... pla... tonic?
Platonic?
He's a platonic two-timer?
Don't say that!
But Kagome...
I've been meaning to tell you.
What?
He's no good for you.
I agree!
What's with you guys?
He's no good. Bad!
Is he really?
What do you mean?
He's spoiled and rough, right?
Well... Yeah...
And jealous, right?
Say, does he know about Hojo?
Well... I don't think so.
Then who is he jealous about?
Maybe Koga.
Koga?!
There's nothing between me
and Koga! Nothing.
Then why's he so jealous?
Well... Because Koga said he's
in love with me.
Kagome, are you two-timing, too?!
No!
I don't feel anything for Koga...
I don't like or dislike him.
I didn't have a clue...
That you're so popular outside of school.
I'm not. It's all one-sided
on Koga's part.
One-sided, maybe.
But he declared his love.
I wish someone would tell
me he loves me!
I'm in... love with you!
It's so wonderful, Kagome!
Well, I guess it's nice.
Actually, I've been asked
to bear a child, too.
By whom?
Koga? Or the delinquent one?
Neither.
- A third guy?!
- Huh? Who?
It HAS to be an older man
who'd ask such a thing!
Well, naturally. But I think
he already has someone he likes.
- It's illicit then?!
- Don't get involved, Kagome!
It's nothing.
He goes around saying that
to every young woman he meets.
What do you mean?!
Please bear my child.
C'mon! It means nothing!
But, Kagome... How do you meet
these guys, anyway?
Yeah! Even this current guy seems
like a delinquent.
And this Koga guy seems
pretty pushy, too.
Hojo doesn't have a chance!
I guess you like the strong type,
huh Kagome?
It's not that! It just happens...
l just know you're going to
have problems with men!
She'll be unhappy
in marriage!
Don't say such things!
And how's it going lately
with your delinquent honey?
Huh? What'd you mean?
Things going smoothly
with him?
Well... There's been...
No particular problem.
So it's going well.
She must like him, after all.
Let's change the subject.
We shouldn't have worried.
I'll say.
Just go about your business.
But it's working out and
that's good.
Yo!
I wonder...
82 on my arithmetic test!
You studied hard, didn't you?
Sis! 82!
I heard! Good job!
What're you doing?!
Next time, go for a perfect score!
Y-You're choking me!
Okay, settle down.
Time for dinner.
All right!
Okay!
Thank you for the food.
Mmmm... Yummy!
You DO eat when you're
on the other side, don't you?
Veggies and mountain roots.
But nothing like this.
Then eat your fill.
When are you going back?
My test is over.
I'll get a good night's sleep
and go to class tomorrow again.
Maybe after that.
How'd you do on your test?
Don't even ask.
Can't be helped.
You've got a lot to handle.
This is heaven!
Simply heaven...
Divine!
I wonder how everyone's doing.
Oh, well...
Divine!
It's lonely without Kagome.
Think so?
I don't notice anything.
Liar! I know.
You go into a daze
once in a while.
You're really missing Kagome.
Oww! Hey! What're you doing?!
When did Kagome say
she's returning?
Let's see...
One... two... three...
Tomorrow.
She's coming back tomorrow?
We'd better go back to the village
and be there to greet her!
But we've been here and there...
with no success.
Without Kagome, we can't get any
leads on the Sacred Jewel.
And there was no sign
of Naraku either.
If only I had a scent of him,
I'd get on his track immediately.
Want to come out?
Then I'll let you.
Who was that?
My younger brother?
He's different from you all.
Let's go.
Hey, Boss!
Which village will be hit next?
Someplace with lots of
women and sake!
Sounds great!
Huh? What's that?
Boss, come over here!
What's up?
What is that?
It's alive!
Creepy thing!
Kill it!
Huh?! A hand!
What is he?!
H-He... hasn't got a face!
Who am I?!
Are you sure, Inuyasha?
Who can mistake this scent?!
This way!
It reeks of Naraku!
Naraku and the smell of human blood!
They've been slaughtered.
They're bandits...
H-His!
What's the matter?
His face has been carved out!
This one, too!
What?
This one, too.
Every one of them...
all without faces.
How frightening!
This isn't normal.
It's Naraku's doing.
But why their faces?!
Are you the source of evil,
specter?
What?! He's faceless!
Master Muso...
Stay back.
Yes.
Specter... where are you from?
Where? I don't know.
Why have you done such a
cruel thing?
Give me... your face.
My face?
You killed people because
you want a face?
You evil specter!
A face...
Master Muso!
Evil specters like you...
Must be destroyed!
Give!
He did it!
My face! I have a face!
Hey, like my face?
Impudent! I'll slay you!
Now that I have a fine face,
I want a fine sword.
Your sword looks pretty nice.
Why!
Yes, it's a fine sword, all right.
You! Just who are you?!
Hah!
Dang! Why?!
It's not enough!
I want more...
Something more.
Maybe I'll go to that village next.
That village?
What's this?
Hold it right there!
Huh? Who are you?!
Been looking for you, bastard!
I'm off.
Bye-bye!
Be careful, now!
Do your best!
And there!
It never ceases to amaze me.
Why can only Sis go through?
Hmm... It's Kagome's fate.
That's the only explanation.
Oh yes...
I'd better go shopping,
so I can stock up on food
for her when she returns.
I'll go, too.
And so shall I.
Where's Naraku?!
Naraku?
Don't act stupid!
You're another one
of his offshoots!
You reek with his smell!
You know about me?
Say, tell me who I am.
Shaddup!
Inuyasha, I think he's the one
behind all the killings, not Naraku.
One thing's certain...
He has the same smell as Naraku.
Are you the one who killed the bandits
and stole their faces?
Yeah, I was the one.
But they were all so ugly,
I couldn't use them.
But now this one...
nice, huh?
Did you steal that face, too?
Yup. I wanted a handsome face.
And money, women...
I wanted it all.
And I stole them all.
But it's not enough.
There's something missing.
Tell me... what is it I crave?
Why, you!
He's not joking.
He doesn't even know
who he is...
He's definitely unlike the
others Naraku has borne.
Humph! So they've come
face to face.
He's the most abominable creation
of my flesh.
Inuyasha... for you, too.
Now, then...
You attacked the village and
set it afire, too?!
Yeah.
I felt if I slaughtered some people,
I'd remember something...
But it didn't work.
Although it was fun.
Just what are you?!
I told you, I can't recall.
I know! How about Muso?
My name's Muso.
It's not bad, is it?
It's the name of the
bonze who gave me this face.
"Gave"? Didn't you kill him?!
Why that look?
I don't like it.
And I don't like YOU!
You know...
I really don't like your face.
Tell me, have we met before?
It's no use talking to you!
Inuyasha!
Someone who smells exactly like
Naraku is killing people senselessly!
You deserve to die!
Just try it!
Die!
He did it!
Not yet!
What's his body made of?!
Like it's clay or something.
Naraku's Poison Insects!
His arm!
He's absorbing the Poison Insects
into his body!
My Wind Tunnel is useless!
This is amazing!
So what's in that village?
What're you talking about?
That village is calling me.
If I slaughter the villagers,
maybe THIS time,
I'll remember something.
Why, you!
What?!
Hmm... Pretty good!
Hiraikotsu!
There!
He's formidable!
We must use caution.
Yes! He's made from Naraku,
after all.
Piece a cake!
Inuyasha!
How's that?!
You!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Sorry I'm late!
Don't come, Kagome!
That woman!
What did l just feel?
He's an offshoot of Naraku.
Stay back!
Uh-huh...
Who is she?
Don't just stand there in a daze!
Die!
He did it!
It's working!
What is it?
What is this?!
Woman?
Huh? Yeah... That woman!
What're you babbling about?
I'll finish you off!
The woman! Move!
Woman!
Why, you!
Why, that!
I!
Run!
Kagome!
You're the one!
W-Who is he?
What does he want?!
I've wanted this... woman!
Taking us for fools!
He was made
from Naraku's flesh...
Yet he claims
he never heard of Naraku!
Kagura tells Inuyasha and the others
of Muso's whereabouts.
It is the cave where fifty years ago,
Kikyo tended to the bandit Onigumo.
It may be a trap!
But we should find out something
if we go!
And during that time,
Naraku sets out to destroy Kikyo!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Onigumo's Memory Restored!"
I'm gonna get revenge for what
happened fifty years ago!