A whole colony of Demon Bats!
They're the Demon Bats!
They're heading for the village!
Huh?!
Hey you guys!
What're you gawking at!
Let's go!
Help!
The village...
Don't grieve over them, Shiori.
They're the ones who
harassed you and your mother.
Don't worry.
If you protect me with
the barrier,
I will spare your mother's life.
No need to hold back.
Annihilate the entire village!
Hold it!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
You old bastard!
You won't get away with this!
Hah!
You're an eyesore, kid!
Why you!
Inuyasha!
Attaway, Miroku!
Let 'em have it!
Keep it up!
Inuyasha!
You're late!
Where were you dawdling!
How many of 'em are
there anyway?
There's no end to this!
I'll get the small fry!
Hiraikotsu!
The barrier!
It turned back the Hiraikotsu!
This isn't good.
As long as Shiori is around,
I cannot use my Wind Tunnel.
What's the matter?
Can't make a move?
Damn!
Isn't there some way to separate
Shiori from Taigokumaru?
If there is, please do it!
Huh?
Please! Do something about them!
We'll all be killed!
The villagers!
Hah! I don't need to be asked
to kill Taigokumaru!
But that's only after
I get Shiori back.
That's crazy!
Besides, Shiori is on
their side!
You want me to kill
her, too?
l-It can't be helped.
Shiori is a demon's child,
after all.
How cruel!
Shiori was given up by her mother
to the Demon Bats
to save your village!
So selfish!
Miroku, doesn't Inuyasha
despise people like them?
Well, he's been through
the same experience.
Did you hear, Shiori?
What do you want?
Huh?
Even if you return to a
village like this,
no good may come of it.
Do you still want to return?
He came earlier to the nest today
with Mommy.
If you still want to return home,
I will help you!
Help?
You brat!
You think you can defeat
me, Taigokumaru?!
Hah! Brat, you're also a half-demon!
You reek with the smell
of a half-demon!
Shaddup!
So what of it?
You're thinking of your
own situation
and feeling sorry for Shiori.
Hah! Not likely!
I hate old rotten bats
like you, is all!
Half-demon?
He's the same as me.
Shiori! Make up your mind!
Do you want to stay
or return home?
I want to go home.
To Mommy.
But...
Huh?
Mommy...
Shiori!
Huh?! Mommy!
You understand, don't you, Shiori?
Unless you continue to protect
me by guarding the barrier,
your mother will die.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do!
Brat! Don't confuse Shiori!
Shiori!
Just protect yourself!
You brat!
Is that the power of the barrier?
Good work, Shiori!
That's what you must do.
If just a part of Taigokumaru's body
goes outside the barrier,
I thought I'd have a chance.
But doesn't Shiori have the power to
adjust the size of the barrier?
Watch out, everyone! Get away!
The village...
H-Help!
I have no use for
this village any longer.
Get rid of all of them.
Taigokumaru!
Stop this now!
Missus...
This village was peaceful
when your son, Tsukuyomaru, was alive.
Because Tsukuyomaru
protected us!
He wished a happy life for
Shiori and me,
so he prevented attacks
on our village.
Please!
Please honor Tsukuyomaru's wish!
Honor his wish?!
How absurd!
Tsukuyomaru was my son,
but he was a fool!
Falling in love with
a mortal only hastened his death!
What do you mean?
Just as you said,
Tsukuyomaru swore he
would protect this village.
And if he could not,
he threatened to abandon his
duties as guardian of the barrier
and leave the tribe!
Even his heart had been
stolen by a mortal woman!
That's why...
That's why?
Why what?
You didn't?!
Kill your own flesh
and blood?
Exactly.
I sent Tsukuyomaru
to the netherworld.
Huh?!
As long as I had Shiori,
he was of no use.
Missus!
Hang on!
Taigokumaru, you're unforgivable!
I'll kill you!
Just try it.
However, as you can see,
Shiori doesn't have the power
to control the barrier.
And if somehow, your sword breaks
through the barrier,
Shiori will die with me.
Why you!
Are you confident
of success, Inuyasha?
Can he kill just Taigokumaru
without hurting Shiori?
Shiori cannot control
the barrier.
Even if Inuyasha can break through
the barrier...
killing Taigokumaru
will also kill Shiori!
What's the matter, brat?
How will you kill me?
Shaddup, old bat!
I'm no teasing up anymore!
Oh? You eased up on me earlier?
Then let me see...
your true power!
Take this!
Backlash Wave!
Right now, there's a crack in the barrier
from the old bat's ghostly aura.
The spiral of my Backlash Wave
should go through it and reach that bastard!
The ghostly aura from that brat's sword
is twisting into my ghostly aura
and coming towards me!
Now go through and
blast that bat's head off!
Huh? The barrier's bending!
How's that?
Huh? It's back to normal.
Taigokumaru isn't hurt!
Damn! I was a second too late!
Good work, Shiori!
That's how you do it.
Get out.
Huh?
I avenge my father!
Why you, Shiori!
You, a half-demon,
dare do this to me!
I never suspected she
had such power...
Even I, Taigokumaru, could
not control the barrier!
- She's falling!
- Shiori!
Shiori!
Hah! Even if my granddaughter
is a half-demon,
I would never let
mortals have her!
Watch out! Shiori's mother!
Die!
Mommy!
Say your prayers, old bat!
Damn!
He did it!
Backlash Wave!
It's over.
Hey!
There!
Shiori!
Mommy!
Shiori, I'm so sorry.
I made you go through
so much.
Mommy!
Now then...
Nothing more to do here.
Let's go, all!
What are you saying?!
Old Myoga, you're still here?
Have you forgotten the purpose
of your coming here?!
You needed to kill the demon who
protected the barrier,
and allow Tetsusaiga to
absorb the blood
to make it even stronger!
Huh? You came here to
kill Shiori?!
Err... Well, at first.
Don't worry. I'm not such
a jerk that I'd kill a child!
Especially, when she's such
a young innocent girl.
And she's also a half-demon.
I'll find someone else who puts up
an even stronger barrier
and kill him instead.
Inuyasha! You were never
like this before!
Hah!
What does that mean?
Well, I...
He means you've matured.
Well, we'll be off.
See ya!
Wait!
Shiori?
Here...
Huh?
Break that sphere?
Yes, I want you to break it.
This blood crystal is
the precious heirloom
passed down to each guardian
of the Demon Bat barrier.
It's from this crystal that
we obtain the power
to put up a powerful barrier.
And... it stores within itself,
the power of
each generation of guardians,
like my grandfather's and
my father's.
So if you break this crystal,
I think you'll be able to
strengthen your sword.
We couldn't have asked
for anything better!
Inuyasha, go ahead and break it!
Yeah!
The faster we break that sphere,
the better.
Huh?
The sphere is releasing vapors.
Let it go!
Huh?!
Mommy, your hands!
The sphere put up a barrier!
I guess it won't let me
break it so easily.
Now that makes it...
...even more interesting!
Huh?!
Are you all right, Inuyasha?
Damn it!
Shiori, as if I'd let you go!
That's Grandfather's voice!
Just releasing the sphere won't
break your bond with the Demon Bats!
Even you, with a human mother...
a half-demon!
Taigokumaru!
Grandfather!
I'll kill you here and now!
You old bat!
Inuyasha!
Shiori! Come to hell
with the rest of us!
W-What?!
It got repelled!
Shiori!
Why you... Shiori!
The old bat's power is weakening!
Now's my chance!
Let Shiori free!
Huh?
The sphere is shattering!
Finally, it's over.
W-What?
My blade is turning red!
Tetsusaiga absorbed the sphere's power!
Which means the sword has
increased its power!
Shiori!
Thank you.
You're the one who
saved me, right?
You weakened the old bat's power.
Uh-uh. I didn't do that.
Someone's gentle arms embraced
my mommy and me,
and protected us.
That was Tsukuyomaru.
Your father's hands.
Yes.
Your father probably wished
for your freedom, too.
Huh?
Nothing.
Heh! Hey, let's go!
I'm hungry!
Me, too!
Shall we go?
Inuyasha also wanted
to rescue Shiori.
He probably forgot all about
making Tetsusaiga stronger.
That's why the spirit of Shiori's father
lent Inuyasha a hand.
What is Inuyasha thinking about?
How unusual for Inuyasha
to contemplate about something.
Hey!
But those two will probably
go through hard times still.
Hah! Don't worry about them.
Can't be a half-demon if
you're afraid of hard times.
Well, we do have a fine example
right here among us.
Hopefully, Shiori doesn't turn
out as warped.
You guys're!
Now that's more like
the Inuyasha I know!
Whaddya mean?!
Inuyasha deep in thought
just isn't Inuyasha!
He's right. Don't do something
you're not used to.
What?!
I'll drop ya both!
What're you saying?!
We're just concerned about you!
Yes, we are, Inuyasha!
Don't take me for a fool!
You're all going to fall!
Inuyasha didn't say a word
when he left Shiori.
Not even a "Do your best"
or "Hang in there."
Even though there were many things
he could say.
Inuyasha chose silence to
encourage her.
I'm sure she got his meaning.
What's the matter, Kagome?
Good boy!
Hey, don't treat me like a dog!
Hey Shippo! You...
...get on my nerves!
Enough, already.
Cripes! I never should a
come along!
Demon-cat siblings,
each named for one of the four seasons...
the Panther-Demon Tribe appears
from the West.
Their aim-Sacred Jewel shards
and Inuyasha's life!
Who cares about them!
It all started fifty years ago,
when Lord Sesshomaru meddled
in the great war.
Isn't that around the time Inuyasha
was sealed to the tree?
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Plot of the Panther Devas"
This is gonna be fun!
I'll let 'em have it!