It tastes great.
Kagome, are you all right now?
Thank you for worrying
about me, Shippo.
It seems my soul went flying out
and back into my body...
but I seem to be perfectly fine.
The only thing that's changed is that...
after his run-in with Kikyo...
Inuyasha spends more
time staring into the distance.
I don't know anymore...
I gather up all the fragments
and become a full-fledged demon...
then what?
If I become a demon,
will I become stronger inside?
Can I forget Kikyo?
Will my heart not be
swayed by anyone else?
Kagome, there's something
funny about Inuyasha.
I think you're right.
Take that, you!
Ow... What was that for?
Quit moping!
Have you given up on gathering
the Sacred Jewel fragments?
Zip it, will you!
Even I sometimes
have things to think about.
That's really funny.
What's that?!
Wait, you little pip-squeak!
I'm not that dumb!
Why you!
Such sorrow from the
Sacred Jewel.
Kikyo claims that
Inuyasha betrayed her...
Inuyasha claims that
she betrayed him.
Their stories don't match.
Will gathering the fragments
lead to the solution of this puzzle?
To the right...
I hear there's a young woman
working at the rest house up ahead.
They say she's lovely,
with fair skin and large eyes.
I'm feeling a bit hungry.
Shall we stop in?
Sure.
To the left...
It's true she has fair skin
and large eyes, but...
Here you go.
Should've gone right.
I hear the daughter of the lord
hereabouts has been possessed...
and has taken to her bed.
My, that is a terrible thing.
Are you sure this one's
a monk of high virtue?
Yes. So he claims.
Monk, if you can't drive
away the demon...
I'll not offer you a bowl of
gruel, understand?
My, to live in such opulence
in so turbulent a time.
Your subjects must
surely resent it.
Impudence!
Princess, a monk has
come to see you.
Pardon me...
Let me see your face...
My! Her face is so swollen!
It was always so!
Are you really a monk?
That statue of Buddha...
I received it from some
impoverished nobleman.
It's a blessed statue.
All right...
Leave the princess here,
and take everyone outside your gate.
What?
And... listen carefully...
No matter what you hear,
you are not to look in.
Uh-hmm...
I will now begin the exorcism.
Now...
Leave peacefully and
I will show you mercy.
I don't suppose
you'll give in so easily.
Huh! So you're a demon weasel!
Huh? That light...
A fragment of the Sacred Jewel?
What is it?
That sounds like some beast...
What's going on in there?
Shall we take a look, my lord?
No, wait...
He said not to look
until he gave the word.
I don't want to catch
any flak from the exorcism.
But, my lord...
it sounds like someone's
searching the mansion.
Just hold on awhile...
So you say this tiny weasel
turned into a demon...
and had a hold on you?
Yes.
And what of the monk?
He gave me no name,
and left as cool as you please.
Oh, my lord! It's a disaster!
Oh!
Everything worth anything
has been taken.
And three horses, too.
I've been had...
Now, where can
I sell these off?
Oh, well...
After all the trouble
transporting everything...
they fetched such a small price.
I guess this Jewel fragment
was the only item worth anything.
A hot spring bath! How wonderful!
My, but it feels glorious.
A girl... Huh?
That's a fragment of the
Sacred Jewel...and it's huge.
Don't you dare peek!
Oops...
Don't worry.
There's nothing there
that interests me.
My! Humph! How rude!
Huh? Shippo, what are you doing?
I'm going in too.
Wait a minute!
Inuyasha, you come too!
Wha?
I've always wondered...
Why don't you and Kagome
ever bathe together?
It's more fun bathing together!
Listen...
When my ma and pa were alive,
we always bathed together.
You're a kid, so you probably
don't understand...
Be honest. How far have
you gone with Kagome?
When I ask things like that,
grown-ups get tongue-tied.
I wonder why?
You wonder why?!
I almost said something I shouldn't!
Yikes! I won't ask again!
So, I'm not a beauty like Kikyo...
What's wrong?
I'm fine. Get out of here!
- Shoo! Shoo!
- Monkeys...
She's with a guy...
Too bad. I hate violence.
No, please... Miroku...
I said I'd compensate you, didn't I?
Yes...
How long do you intend
to stay mad?
You saw me naked, so we're even.
I didn't.
He did, didn't he?
I can't really say...
I have to attack the guy, right?
Yeah.
Meanwhile, I'll take the girl.
But, Miroku...
why go so much trouble?
If you use your right hand,
it'll be over in seconds.
Fool. You know better than that.
If I use this hand, everyone will die.
That's true...
Well, if anything should happen,
please save me.
Don't worry.
Change!
Huh?
I've come for you...
Inuyasha!
Eeek! Who are you?
You have nothing to fear.
I am a Buddhist monk...
no one suspicious.
When I reached for the
Sacred Jewel fragment...
you were attached to it, you see.
You've got that backwards, mister.
Kagome! What's going on?
That guy!
Get out of my way!
Out of my way I say!
H-he's going to kill me!
Tsk...
What a vicious friend!
What's the matter with you?
Inuyasha!
Let me go!
Certainly.
All I need is this...
Inuyasha, are you all right?
Damn...
Who was that guy, anyway?
He said he was a Buddhist monk, but...
What was it he did
with his right hand?
I felt like I was being pulled
by a strong wind.
What did he do from
way up there?
Oh, no!
Huh?
He stole my bike!
The nerve!
Forget the bike!
You were being kidnapped!
I look away for one second, and...
Inuyasha...
I'm sorry.
It wasn't you I was worried about.
It was your Sacred Jewel fragment...
Well...
It seems he stole
my Jewel fragment, too.
What?!
Damn that guy!
He can't have gone very far.
I'll find him wherever he is.
Inuyasha, what's taking
you so long?
Leave me alone.
The smells are all mixed up,
so I can't tell.
People are gathering around.
They're really suspicious of us.
Where'd that bugger go?
A demon here in our village?
See?!
That guy and kid aside,
look at that girl.
Is she a demon?
Who, me?
Good for you!
He's probably not here.
No doubt about it. He's here.
Why would a robber
hang around... Oh!
Yippee-aii-ayy!
Phew..."We have nothing
but beauties," he said?
I'd have been better off
drinking with the tanuki.
You!
You bike thief!
Oh, it's you!
You're just what I need.
You're a sight for sore eyes!
I'll take care of you.
Hold it.
Such violence...
What do you mean?
Just who was it that used
a tanuki to attack us?
I guess you're not ready to
hand over the Jewel fragment.
This isn't something
a demon should have.
Don't get funny!
Ah! Hey!
Hold it!
I will not fight a senseless battle.
Is that right? Then you'll die!
He stopped the Tetsusaiga!
This guy's no ordinary mortal.
Do you insist on being punished?
Who the hell are you?
My name is Miroku.
I use my spiritual powers
to save people.
- What's going on?
- A demon?
- He's slaying demons?
- Can he do it alone?
Hey! A monk is slaying demons!
You use your powers
to save people?
Why, you're nothing
but a robber.
Give us back that
Sacred Jewel fragment.
We went to a lot of trouble
to gather all those fragments.
I understand...
However, it would be best for
you to let me keep this...
Inuyasha...
So, you know who I am?
Not at all.
Your beautiful companion
called you by that name.
My, he doesn't seem to
be such a bad person.
Wake up, Kagome!
He stole your Jewel!
You won't be flapping your lip
when I get done with you.
You're very strong.
Damn!
He parries my every stroke.
Hand that Sacred Jewel fragment over...
if you want to live.
Oh! Trying to run again?
People! Get as far away
as possible... for your safety.
Give up! You lose.
His right hand!
Sorry, but I hate losing.
Spiritual power!
Wha!
It's like that time on the cliff...
What is this wind?
A Wind Tunnel
in his right hand!
How long can you hold out?
Get away!
You'll get sucked to your death!
It's like a black hole!
This isn't about spiritual power!
Kagome! We'd better run, too.
I've got to stop him.
That Miroku...
People!
Get as far away as possible...
He's trying not to suck in humans.
D-damn!
Surrender.
If you get sucked in,
you'll never get out.
Forget it!
I'll chop that right arm off!
It's no use.
It'll suck you in, sword and all.
Kagome!
Ow...
These prayer beads...
They seal off his right hand.
He controls himself.
He's not an evil person.
Kagome... Did you willingly rush in?
Well, this Miroku...
He could have killed us
long ago using his right hand.
I'm sure he'll be reasonable
if we talk to him.
Kill him after all!
You good-for-nothing monk!
Settle down. We'll talk.
I'm gathering the
fragments of the Sacred Jewel...
in order to find a certain demon,
and eliminate him.
That's demon's name is Naraku.
Naraku?
This Wind Tunnel in my right hand was
created by a curse placed by Naraku.
What sort of demon is Naraku?
He is malicious, and devours people.
That's all I know.
What do you mean?
Well...
It was my grandfather
who battled Naraku in his youth.
That was about 50 years ago.
Their battles lasted several years.
Whenever they met,
Naraku appeared as a different person.
As a different person?
In their final battle,
he took the form of a beautiful woman.
My grandfather had great spiritual
power, but unfortunately...
Bet he was a lecher.
That's a good guess.
Naraku pierced my grandfather's
right hand with the seals...
and escaped himself.
That Wind Tunnel that
I have cursed you with...
shall be passed on to your
progeny, so long as I live.
Each generation shall be cursed,
until no one remains.
This Wind Tunnel gets bigger
by the year, and stronger.
If I don't kill Naraku,
I'll probably get sucked in myself.
Does that mean you'll die?
Yes. And that's all right...
if that's my fate.
But I can't let Naraku go unchecked.
The Sacred Jewel that
vanished 50 years ago...
has appeared today in fragments.
Naraku is sure to
gather the fragments...
in order to strengthen his powers.
It is said that Naraku nearly
got the Jewel 50 years ago.
After killing the priestess
protecting it.
You say he killed the priestess?
Yes.
He's the one who took my form and
wounded Kikyo.
There's no doubt about it.
Miroku! You say Naraku takes
different forms?
What does he look like now?
If I knew that, I'd have found him
long ago, and slain him.
He laid a trap for Kikyo and me,
and made us hate each other.
The one who killed Kikyo is still alive
and is after the Sacred Jewel.
I will find Kikyo's killer
and avenge her death!
If we keep looking for these fragments,
we're sure to run into Naraku, right?
How'd you get that?
Let's gather the fragments together.
Huh?
Well, I'm sure Inuyasha's
not about to give this up.
Of course, not!
That's why.
I'm not very good at
dealing with people...
But, if you don't kill Naraku soon,
you'll die, won't you?
Kagome...
Are you concerned about me?
Of course...
Then, I have a request.
Will you do me the favor of
bearing my child?
Huh?!
What's this all about?
If I should fail to destroy
Naraku, and die...
I need a child to carry on
my family's mission.
Quit it, will you?
You lecherous priest!
I'm a monk.
If you lay a hand on Kagome again...
Inuyasha...
Well, pardon me. I thought you
were just a companion...
You're in love with Kagome?
Huh?
Please forgive me.
Damn it! She's just a Jewel detector!
Jewel detector?!
How dare you!
Well, I guess you do
have someone you love.
Huh?
What shall I do? Miroku is nicer...
Why, are you going to betray me?
You must be nicer to the womenfolk.
Shut up!
I'm only a Jewel detector...
Weren't they having a
serious discussion?
I don't understand
grown-ups.
- You could learn from Miroku.
- Gentle.
- Yes. Be more gentle.
- Yes, be gentle...
Hey, don't touch me there!
Did you touch her again?!
Naraku...
We now know that
that demon was the one...
who caused Inuyasha
and Kikyo to hate each other.
Traveling together...
we discover the scent of
ink on an old battlefield.
Demons escape from a painting
of hell and attack Inuyasha.
Why is the painting alive?
A fragment of the Sacred Jewel gleams
in the bosom of the mysterious artist.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Cursed Ink of the Hell-Painter"