Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel....
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
We face another attack from
the legendary Seven Spectres.
What's their connection
with Kohaku,
Sango's lost brother who is
being controlled by Naraku?
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Hmm....so Kyokotsu died?
Yes, Master Jakotsu.
Stupid fool!
Oh, well....
Can't be helped.
He was the weakest one
among us.
Tell me, Kohaku.
Huh?
Is this Inuyasha handsome?
Please ascertain that
for yourself.
Hmm.... I can't wait
to see you, Inuyasha!
I wonder what color your blood is?
Inuyasha....
Look....
Another battle?
I don't think so. I didn't sense
anything like that around here.
I wonder if they're going
to subdue something?
So pretentious!
We had such a scare!
Hear ye!
That was a lesson from Buddha!
You have seen the fear
in your heart!
Hmm.... However....
Huh?
There's a mountain shrine over there.
Talk about heaven in hell!
This is heaven sent!
Fool!
You always try to depend
on others....
Your weak heart is why
you see illusions!
Yes, sir!
Now then, let us seek shelter.
What? You intend to depend
on others, after all.
I heard that the border patrol
was totally annihilated.
It was terrible, I hear.
No way man could've done it.
Are the rumors true?
That phantoms of the Band of Seven
mound have been resurrected?
Phantoms of the Band of Seven?
Err....may I inquire?
You're gonna ask?
We can't just pass through.
The Seven-Man Mound was a
mound to quiet the Band of Seven.
Band of Seven?
Over a decade ago....
They came here from
the eastern province.
They were seven mercenaries.
They served no lord.
But worked from war to war.
And they were so strong....
They could do the work
of a hundred men.
But their killing style
was too atrocious.
Those who were slain
by the seven mercenaries
were cut up, burned....
They were a group of evil men
who loved to kill.
Oh my...
And the warlords who
feared their strength....
sold them out and ordered
them hunted down.
I heard they put up
a hard fight.
I would think so.
The seven mercenaries
escaped into the mountains....
But there were totally outnumbered.
And just a bit further north,
they were finally captured.
Each one was beheaded
and buried.
Still, the villagers feared
their curse
and decided to quiet
the seven souls.
And erected a mound
at the base of the sacred mountain.
That is the Seven-Man Mound.
I see....
We heard that those spirits
have been resurrected.
Err....
Yes....
It's said that the mound
broke apart into two.
And there wasn't any lightning, either.
So it's believed that
the seven souls escaped.
Right?
Yeah, yeah!
Hmm....dead souls.
What do you think?
It's possible that with
Naraku's evil gone from here....
all the rabble have become free.
Specters or demons.... I dunno.
But we're just walking
in that direction.
If we come across them,
we just kill 'em!
What's the matter?
I sense a Sacred Jewel shard.
Kirara!
Huh?
Kirara is acting strange.
Huh?!
Sango!
Sango....
Kirara!
You sensed Kohaku's presence?
He must be somewhere
in this mountain.
Huh?
Saimyosho....
Kohaku!
I wanted to erase it...
but it wouldn't go away.
That face...
But...
Kohaku!
Who are you?
You're still under Naraku's spell....
Why? Why is your face....?!
Just remember a little at a time.
We'll be together from now on.
Umm....
Kohaku!
Stop!
Die!
Kohaku! Wake up!
Kohaku!
Kirara?!
That's....!
Kohaku....!
Don't be hasty.
You're being watched.
You were late, so I came instead.
That woman....you know her?
You there!
Make way in the road!
Huh?
Hey! Stop your horses!
Did you say something?
W-Who are you?
You look strange.
If you're going on ahead,
be careful.
I hear a frightening
specter appears.
Fool!
We're on our way to
exterminate it!
I guess you have no idea
what it's like.
And you know?
Huh?
I'm that....specter!
What?!
Gun battalion! To the front!
What's that?
Hmm....
A specter over a decade old
wouldn't be familiar with these.
Fire!
Huh?!
What were those sounds just now?
Maybe....gunfire?
Guns?
Hmm....
So this is the matchlock guns
I heard about.
Evil spirit!
Second battalion! To the front!
Not again?
I get it, you know!
Enough!
The smell of blood!
Yeah....and lots of it.
Impossible!
He just swung his sword....
from that distance!
This brings back memories
of the past....
Damn! Do not fear him!
Surround him!
He's using hypnotic magic!
I don't use such a thing.
Neither then nor now!
This smell...
It's weak, but...
Yes!
The smell of graveyard soil!
Huh?
What happened?!
Don't come!
Huh?!
Hmm....
This is unusual. I'll take it
back to Brother Renkotsu.
These are the warriors from
the crossroads earlier...
They were slain by that one person?
Huh?
Could you be....Inuyasha?
How'd you know my name?!
So cute!
W-Wh...!
I love those ears!
Give 'em to me.
Who is he?
Just who are you?!
You don't smell like
a living person.
Just of dead bodies
and graveyard soil!
Huh?!
Hmm....
Inuyasha, could he be....?
Yeah....
The villagers were talking
about you.
That some disgusting specter
appeared from his grave.
A group of seven evil men
who loved to kill.
Mercenaries who were later
hunted down and beheaded.
You must be one of the seven!
Answer!
Inuyasha is cute.
But you're pretty sexy yourself.
Can I suck him up?
Sure.
Huh?
Wait!
He has a Sacred Jewel shard.
Huh?!
Maybe he revived through the
power of the shard.
Who gave you the
Sacred Jewel shard?!
I love that angry face, too.
Shaddup!
Why you...!
I'm gonna make you talk
about everything you know!
Hmm....
Interesting sword you have.
Which is stronger?
My sword or yours?
Inuyasha!
Get back! It's a trick sword!
Heh-heh....
I thought it was strange...
the way the soldiers were slain.
They were all downed in one blow...
Without any time to repel him.
I figured it would be
something tricky...
But not only that...
His sword is...
Inuyasha!
It's a bending sword!
How's that!
This is the Snake Sword
of Master Jakotsu
of the Band of Seven!
Enough of this!
Even if he repels it,
it comes right back!
That sword....it's like a snake!
Run some more!
Damn!
Go!
Isn't this fun?
Damn! I can't tell where
the sword will appear next!
Good.... That face turns me on!
Show more fear!
Hiraikotsu!
Inuyasha!
Sango!
Are you all right?
Inuyasha!
Yeah!
Woman....!
You...!
Don't interfere, woman!
Stay out of my fun
with Inuyasha!
You make me sick!
So cold!
Shaddup!
Who gave you the
Sacred Jewel shard!?
Confess now!
- Are you all right?!
- Sango!
You're bleeding!
It's just a graze.
But the Sacred Jewel shard was
probably from Naraku.
Huh?
Earlier, when you sensed the Sacred Jewel....
it was Kohaku.
Huh?
Near Kohaku, I saw the saimyosho.
So he's still under
Naraku's spell?
Sango....
Why, you...!
Yeah....he's at it.
Jakotsu hasn't changed one bit.
Oh, the poison has paralyzed me.
What could he want with me?
There's a poison barrier
all around.
No one will come to help.
I'm so blessed....
To have such a
cute girl.
I'm not perfect, but
please accept me.
Are you kidding?!
I must do something!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Stealthy Poison Master: Mukotsu!"
Sesshomaru?
What're you doing here?!