Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Those pursuing Naraku
converge on Mt. Hakurei.
But Bankotsu, the last
and strongest of the Band of Seven,
blocks Inuyasha's path.
It's up to us and Miroku, Sango,
Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Naraku!
Lord Sesshomaru! What's that?
As I expected....
Koga!
Kagome!
You guys are too slow!
You two....!
Koga!
We finally caught up!
You just up and left!
I'm glad you're okay.
Kirara?
Shippo?
I feel better.
For some reason, the sacred
barrier has been dissolved.
And I can smell it
from that mountain....
Naraku's scent.
And it's much worse
than before.
Here they come!
Hey! Stay away!
Maybe they're hungry!
L-Lord Sesshomaru!
Leave it to our Lord Sesshomaru!
Well, it's time for my
Staff of Two Heads!
Come at me all you want.
I'm rooting for you, Jaken!
Thank you!
Let's go!
Go? Where?!
To Naraku! Where else?
Let's go, Kagome!
Kirara!
Come help me!
Hey! Wait!
Wait up!
I wonder if they're all okay?
I'm sure they are.
Bankotsu....
You plan to block my way?!
Damn right!
You killed all my
Band of Seven brothers.
I'm gonna avenge their deaths.
I don't remember killing
all of them.
But if I can only get to Naraku
over your dead body,
let's get on with it!
Wind Scar!
Fool!
That won't work on me!
A blast of heat?!
So we're even, huh?
When we last fought
at Hijiri Island,
he countered my Wind Scar.
He's gotten stronger since then.
Damn you Bankotsu....
You're using the Sacred Jewel
shards of the others....
Naturally, every one of them.
They're my keepsakes
of my little brothers.
Kyokotsu.
Mukotsu.
Suikotsu.
Ginkotsu.
Jakotsu.
Renkotsu.
And add mine to that....
and it totals seven.
I have more than enough
power to fight you!
Wind Scar!
I don't have time to
waste on you!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Strange....
Were you always this weak?
Or....
Have I become too strong
for you?
You have seven
Sacred Jewel shards and
that's all the power
you can muster?
Damn, you have a big mouth.
But you can say that only
after you've killed me.
Hah!
I'll carve each and every one
of those shards outta you....
Prepare to die!
A specter like you should
go back to sleep in your grave!
What about you, Inuyasha?!
A demon who was sealed
to a tree!
Damn you....!
Oops, you're not a demon,
but a half-demon.
Naraku told me all about you and
that dead woman named Kikyo.
Why you...!
A half-demon who was
sealed up for fifty years
has no business criticizing
those of us who were resurrected!
What?!
Naraku talked to you
quite a lot, huh?
Well, I've met him twice
already.
What's that supposed to mean?
The first time we met was
before the Band of Seven was formed.
Looking back, it was a
strange coincidence.
So you're old pals, huh?
Hah! I don't befriend demons!
Back then,
all I wanted to do
was find strong opponents
and beat them one by one.
I didn't care if they were demons,
as long as they were strong.
I heard about a frightening demon
and entered that lifeless forest.
I came to fight the ruler
of this forest.
It could have been him.
Did you kill him?
Are you a demon slayer?
Or some kind of monk?
I don't care about slaying
or whatever.
If you're strong,
I'll fight you.
Oh? You want to test
your strength?
Anyone who had demon power
from the moment he was born
wouldn't understand this!
From the moment I was born?
What's so funny?
I desire demon power, too.
You're a demon, aren't you?
I search the land for the power
which I was unable to acquire.
The Shikon Jewel?
I don't know if it will
manifest itself in this world again.
Hey, Big Brother!
What?! You destroyed
it already?!
At least leave me one
to kill, will ya?
Are you hungry?
Jakotsu, let's go to war.
Huh? Why?!
I thought you never wanted
to obey the orders of samurai again.
We won't.
We'll become mercenaries
and slaughter every one we fight...
I won't let them complain...
'cuz I'll stand at the helm
of a band of skilled warriors.
Will it be only you and me?
Huh? I guess we'd better
recruit more comrades.
Wait up, Big Brother.
You serious?
How many men should we have?
Huh?
Oh well, if you're serious,
I'll go along.
But let's get some
good-looking guys.
Stupid, they gotta be strong!
Oh, you're right.
Can't carve up
handsome men.
I AM stupid.
And then we met again.
He told me much more
than he did the first time.
Naraku didn't resurrect
you for memories!
Are you stupid?!
What?!
He's not that kind of guy.
One glance at him
and that's obvious.
You're the stupid one!
He's taking advantage of you
and making you do his dirty work!
It doesn't matter!
As long as I live,
there are things to do!
Like settling this fight
with you!
Why you...!
I've been given
a second chance at life.
Even this Banryu...
Wind Scar!
Awaken, Bankotsu.
Awaken...
I grant you a second chance
at life.
Who are you?
To think the man I met so
long ago was Bankotsu
of the Band of Seven...
You're that demon I saw...
My name is Naraku.
Naraku?
What's this?
We were beheaded...
Correct. This is inside your grave.
I imbedded a Sacred Jewel shard
inside your body.
It is that power you feel now.
I see. This Sacred Jewel shard
has many uses, doesn't it?
Serve me.
Then your life will be
everlasting.
Go forth with your comrades...
and kill my enemies.
Who cares about his orders?!
You survived?
That's how I like it!
I'll keep you company
until you die!
It's collapsing.
The barrier around the
sacred mountain
has been totally dissolved.
This place is overflowing
with an evil aura.
Is it Naraku's aura?!
Yes.
And it's much stronger
than before.
No! This is
a demonic aura!
And it's getting stronger!
This is....
the cloister from before?
Miroku....
Yes, there's something.
Huh?!
Naraku!
Wait!
You're...!
If you keep looking down,
your head'll roll.
Kagura!
Humph!
Miroku, Naraku has....
disappeared.
He appeared, then
made his escape....
Kagura!
Naraku is still incomplete.
Is that it?
Huh? What do you mean?
Naraku took refuge
inside Mt. Hakurei
because his barrier was broken
by Inuyasha's red Tetsusaiga.
My... barrier...
That's why Naraku hid
himself in here....
to restore his powers!
Sorry, Monk.
He doesn't tell me anything.
He doesn't trust me.
Ask Kanna about Naraku.
Although she probably
won't talk.
You WILL tell us everything.
Well then, see for yourself.
I'll help you....descend!
Hah!
Damn, there's no end to this!
If only Bankotsu were a demon,
my Backlash Wave would
take care of him...
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Out of breath?
But he's human.
Even if he's an evil specter,
he doesn't have a demonic aura!
Take this!
Without the opponent's energy
to entrap and send back at them,
I can't use
my Backlash Wave!
Damn Naraku!
He thought ahead and used
a specter to fight his battles.
I don't know what
you're thinking of,
but you're going to die, Inuyasha.
Hah!
I intended to kill you
in one swoop....
But I'll fight you for
a while longer.
What's going on, Koga?!
All the foliage around
Mt. Hakurei is dead!
It was destroyed
by Naraku's aura.
I sense Sacred Jewel shards.
And I can feel them
in two places
below the mountain
and towards the center.
Two places?
The one deep in the center
is stronger.
That's Naraku, right?
Probably.
Show me the way, Kagome!
But what'll you do there, Koga?!
Kirara, hurry!
Hey!
Don't leave us!
Damn you!
Stay outta our way!
Die! Die!