Did you draw these, Shippo?
You're very good.
Oh, what a cute cat!
That's you, Kagome.
See the resemblance?
And this is Inuyasha.
And this one's Koga.
It's the love triangle
of a two-legged dog, a wolf...
and a cat who cried out,
"I'm going home!"
W-wait a minute, Shippo!
Have you shown this
embarrassing play to anyone else?
I showed Old Kaede.
She complimented me
that it was well done.
Old Kaede... knows the reason
why I fought with Inuyasha?
Not only Old Kaede.
I wanted everyone
to praise me...
so I showed them all
in the village.
What about it?
How embarrassing!
I guess I can't go back
to the village for a while.
It's not a lie! Kagome is my woman!
I love Kagome!
The Wolf-Demon Tribe...
I met Koga when we encountered
the Birds of Paradise...
who tried to take the
Sacred Jewel fragments.
Koga...
Kagome...
Do you love this guy?
Huh? Love?
I love Inuyasha?
You must love him.
All right, that side was all clear.
That guy!
The enemy!
Where?!
Where're the Birds of Paradise!
What're you saying, Hakkaku!
The Birds of Paradise are all dead!
You looked like such a fool just now!
Shut up! That was a dirty trick!
Only because you slacked off
and fell asleep!
Damn...
They're from the northern caverns.
There's someone in possession
of a huge Sacred Jewel fragment.
And he's the lord of some castle!
This isn't a joke.
Let's combine forces,
the northern and western caverns...
and take the Sacred Jewel
from the castle.
We'll divvy up the fragments equally.
Well, Koga? Wanna join us?
Sorry, but I'm not interested.
Hey! Why?
I have something else
I have to take care of first.
I see... well, we won't force you.
Didja see? I think he's injured.
Are you sure about this, Koga?
Turning them down?
If we don't join them...
the northern clan will get
all the Sacred Jewel fragments!
Let them go... it doesn't matter.
Well, I can't!
I'm gonna go with them!
Me, too!
I'm not interested now.
If you want to go, I won't stop you.
We're gonna join up
with the northern pack now.
Whoever wants
Sacred Jewel fragments, join us!
Yeah!
Damn!
Take this!
First, I'll bite off that right arm!
I never expected it...
that the demon bird would
steal my Sacred Jewel fragment...
from my right arm.
I'll get the fragment back in time.
But before that comes that dog!
With that huge sword,
he killed the demon bird in one swoop.
That guy...
I won't be satisfied until I kill him
with my own hands!
This wound isn't healing
as fast as I hoped.
This way, I'm sure of it.
I get a sense of
Sacred Jewel fragments.
We really need Kagome, after all.
She's the only one who can sense
the Sacred Jewel.
Yes, so Inuyasha,
don't fight with her anymore.
Do not fight!
Hah!
A demon bear that
terrorized the village.
That's what the villagers said.
At first, it was just
a mischievous bear ruining the fields.
Suddenly, it grew huge
and attacked the village.
Inuyasha? You seem displeased.
Of course!
Sure, it's important to search out
the Sacred Jewel fragments...
that Kagome senses.
But rather than a bear,
I'm searching for a wolf!
Koga...
We know that
that skinny wolf-demon Koga...
still has two
Sacred Jewel fragments in his legs.
If this mountain smelled
more like wolf than bear...
I'd feel more like fighting.
So you want to say...
that butchering Koga
comes first with you?
Koga, his love rival?
What're you doing?!
Shippo, you don't bug Inuyasha...
and you won't feel his fist.
Bears!
Don't worry.
They're ordinary mercenaries.
Ordinary?!
You're pretty cocky, kid!
From the looks of you,
you have no money.
Well then,
you can leave the women.
Hey you...
I'll give you a good piece of advice.
If you don't want to get hurt,
better run away.
What?! How dare you!
Kagome!
Yes! I can feel
the Sacred Jewel coming closer.
Get back!
W-what's that!
It's in his forehead!
The Sacred Jewel fragment!
Damn! What a huge bugger!
But your head is still just a bear, right?
Take this!
Naraku's poison insects!
Inuyasha! Look!
They're taking
the Sacred Jewel fragment!
Is it a trap?
Probably.
Fine with me!
This time, Naraku won't get away!
Dear, dear... you've set your sights
quite high this time.
Well, it's easier for me.
The Sacred Jewel fragment...
It makes demons even stronger...
an enticing opiate.
You plan to lure them here with this?
What's this?
You can't beat them
without this thing?
You're either careful...
or cowardly...
but you love traps, don't you...
my dear master?
Here it is... the castle full
of Sacred Jewel fragments.
When the men of the castle appear,
never mind!
Just kill them all!
Yeah!
What's this castle?
They don't even have guards posted.
There's someone!
Go! Get 'im.
What? Only small fry.
Get him.
Someone more virile.
Hey! Keep quiet!
What's up!
What's the matter?
- He went with the northern pack!
- Yeah...
Hey, what's wrong? What happened?
I got just one!
It's a Sacred Jewel fragment!
Hurry to the castle!
If you don't, everyone will be killed!
A Jewel fragment!
I'm using it!
Let's rest inside.
But you...
How did you make it back here
with those injuries?
He's dead!
Naraku!
W-what's this?
Wolves...
Could they be wolf-demons?
But why would they be here
in this castle?
On top of that...
What's that? They're still alive!
I don't sense any life in these men.
They're zombies!
You see? Even if they're put down,
they revive immediately!
They're supposed to be dead!
How come
they keep coming back alive!
You can't cut them
nor can you beat them.
And if you lop off their heads,
they'll reattach right away.
That is my Death Corpse Dance.
Oh? Here already?
I wanted to play a bit longer.
W-what?!
W-what's this?!
What now?
They're all collapsing!
Why that!
Inuyasha!
That's Koga
of the Wolf-Demon Tribe!
Koga?
Inuyasha!
How could you be so cruel!?
Let me tell you one thing!
When I got here,
your comrades had all been killed!
Shut up!
You're covered head to toe in blood!
You can't lie to me!
Damn! It was a trap!
Koga, you're wrong!
We came here looking for
someone named Naraku!
Then!
Kagome?
When we got here,
all the wolf-demons were lying here...
but then they all came alive and...
Kagome!
Don't try to protect such a guy! You cur!
Dead when you got here? That's bull!
Koga...
We were trapped! It's Naraku's trick!
We followed Naraku's poison insects
to this castle.
The wolf-demons probably followed
some clues here, too...
then were killed.
And Koga arrives to
save his comrades.
Only to find Inuyasha
covered in their blood.
The wrath of having his comrades killed
won't be quelled.
They will fight to the death.
What?
The blood has gone to Koga's head!
As it is,
they really will fight to the death!
I have to stop them...
But...but how?!
I must stop them...
but...but how?!
His arm's gotten stronger!
Koga! You found another
Jewel fragment for your arm!?
You stole my fragment
the last time we met.
This one's even better!
That glow!
It's not the light from the Sacred Jewel!
It's black and the glow is warped!
What is that fragment?!
Stop, Koga!
Please! Listen to me!
This is a trap!
The one who killed
your friends is not Inuyasha!
Shut up!
I only believe what I see
with my own eyes!
Koga!
Stop, Kagome!
This hard-headed punk
can't understand complicated things.
Fools like him can only be tamed
with brute strength!
The Wolf-Demon Tribe lives in packs
and cherish their comrades.
Seeing so many killed at one time...
Koga's wrath won't be easily controlled!
I thought he'd listen to you
at least, Kagome.
I can't blame Inuyasha...
since Koga is attacking him.
There's no choice
but to stop him with a duel.
Naraku is trying to make me fight Koga.
And he's watching us from somewhere.
Inside the mansion?
I can smell Naraku!
Hey, pay attention!
Where are you looking?!
What'll we do? Shall we help him?
Inuyasha was looking for Naraku,
the one who laid the trap.
Then is he... inside the mansion?
Charging into the enemy's trap
is not a smart strategy, but...
But we have no choice do we?
Who are you?
What're you doing here?!
My name?
I am Kagura.
She's Sango...
and you're Miroku, right?
Naraku's agent!
Tell us! Where is Naraku?!
He's not here.
But he left something for you.
He says this should keep you busy...
A demon puppet!
Now then...
I'll go see what's going on outside.
Koga and Inuyasha, huh?
Not my types at all...
so I don't care which one dies.
Koga and Inuyasha
have begun their duel to the death!
Naraku's goal
is the Sacred Jewel fragment.
To get the fragments
in Koga's legs...
rather than dirty his hands...
Naraku is trying to use Inuyasha!
The Tetsusaiga has been repelled!
Inuyasha's right arm is broken?
Inuyasha faces
one crisis after another...
but he will not lose
to some female demon!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Deadly Trap of Kagura,
the Wind Sorceress!"
Don't miss it!