Half-demon Inuyasha...
born half demon and
half human.
Unable to come to terms with
this circumstance...
he tries to possess the
Sacred Jewel...
in order to become a
full-fledged demon.
Despising such a younger brother...
the cold-hearted Sesshomaru
concocts an evil plan.
In a cart appears Inuyasha's
human mother...
who is supposed to be dead.
Seeing his mother bound in chains...
Inuyasha's feelings of anger
reach the boiling point.
Impossible!
My mother died a long time ago!
As if I'd fall for such a trick!
Trick, huh?
Do you not understand?
Bringing dead spirits from
the netherworld...
is a simple task for someone
as great as Lord Sesshomaru.
He was even so kind as to
give her flesh!
Her own son won't believe
that it's her.
How mortifying it must
be for your mother!
I am returned from the dead...
Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
You hopeless imbecile!
Mother!
Inuyasha!
Miss Kagome!
- Miss Kagome!
Hey! Look!
Over here!
What're you doing in the
middle of the night?
Did I wake you?
I'm sorry.
I was just lowering the bicycle seat
to Kagome's height.
She took her own bike
to the other dimension.
I thought she'd have a hard time
using this one when she returns.
Sis won't be back for
two or three days.
She took so much clothes
with her.
I know.
But I just want to do what
I can for her.
Sis is so lucky! You're so concerned
about her.
Oh, but I'm just as concerned
about you, Sota.
Concerned that you won't
wet the bedding again.
How can you say that?!
I'm already in the third grade!
I won't do that!
I want you to help Sister
out too, okay?
I know.
A falling star!
Oh! Please let me win
the lottery!
There's no face in the
reflection! Inuyasha!
Inu... -
My voice... I can't speak.
Please notice it, Inuyasha!
She doesn't have a face!
She's...not your mother!
Inuyasha... I must return
to the netherworld.
Oh... Must you go?
Inuyasha... Look at the
surface of the water.
That's back when I was a kid...
So you remember!
When you were a child...
I often embraced you
like that.
Good boy... Let me hold
you tight.
I won't let go.
Become one with me.
Mother...
Inuyasha!
Wh-Why can't I move?!
This is...all an illusion!
Kagome!
Snap out of it!
It's me, Myoga the Flea!
Who would have thought that
the one looking for the tomb...
would be Sesshomaru,
Master Inuyasha's elder brother!!
Such a formidable foe!
Poor thing, you're chained up
and unable to move.
I'll undo the spell
in a moment.
Hmm?
Looks delicious!
Thank you!
I think I can move now.
My son... My dear son...
Hey you! Un-Mother!
What's the use of sucking the
breath out of him?!
Master Jaken!
What you do to him later is
no concern to us!
But first, you must get the
information out of him!
The location of the tomb...
of Inuyasha and Lord
Sesshomaru's father!
That Jaken fellow is
Sesshomaru's henchman?
The Human Head Staff...
You must watch out
for that.
'Kay!
Inuyasha!
Please remember...
Where is your father's tomb?
I don't know...
Think harder!
Open up your heart
to me.
What's that?!
The black pearl in the right...
The black pearl in the right?
That's not enough to go on!
Find out more!
Master Jaken, if I delve
any deeper...
this boy's spirit will
be broken.
So what? Just do it!
There, there... Inuyasha.
I can't breathe, Mother!
The face!
Hey! Not yet?
Hurry, or I will face the wrath
of Lord Sesshomaru!
Huh?!
Why you... puny troublemaker!
Wait!
Let Inuyasha go!
No!
Inuyasha!
Huh?!
He's being sucked in!
What'll I do?
Kagome!
You must awaken
Master Inuyasha's spirit!
Spirit?!
The demon is the Un-Mother.
She was created by the
forlorn spirits of mothers...
who lost children to famine
or war.
If you reawaken the spirit that's under
the spell of the Un-Mother...
his body will be released!
Awaken the spirit?!
But how?
Oh joy... You and Mother will soon
be one...
I won't make it in time!
That child... is Inuyasha?
Yes!
That is the work of the
Un-Mother's magic!
If I erase that image, then...
Inuyasha! Wake up!
Inuyasha... Are you all right?
Damn!
Damn it to hell!
How dare they... use my mother
like that?!
It's all the work of Sesshomaru
and Jaken.
What?!
Inuyasha...
I know where the tomb is.
What?!
Sesshomaru!
Why you!
I never imagined it would be there!
Very clever...
That father would pick
such a place.
The black pearl in the right...
Father didn't want anyone to
disturb his resting place...
so he hid his tomb there.
You...
What kind of nonsense
are you talking about?!
So you were entrusted with the
tomb unknowingly.
Well then, would you like to visit
father's grave with me?
Master Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
No wonder it was useless
looking underground.
Visible, but invisible.
The true protector of the grave
cannot be seen.
And... it is the black pearl imbedded
in your right eye.
And just for that...
You tricked me with
my dead mother's image!
It was just a joke.
Why you!
Unforgivable!
Die!
Huh?!
The Un-Mother?
She protected Inuyasha?
The Un-Mother is a demon
filled with motherly love.
It's in her nature to try to
protect children.
My son...
Hey you!
Don't interfere!
Or else we'll both be killed.
But...!!
Jaken!
Lord Sesshomaru!
I have my Human Head Staff back!
How I have waited for
this moment!
The old man laughs!
The tomb will now open!
They've disappeared!
Master Inuyasha, hurry and enter
before the entrance closes up.
Lord Sesshomaru intends to
take sole possession...
of your father's treasure!
I'm not interested in that!
Don't say such a thing!
Shut up!
Who said I wasn't going?!
That Sesshomaru...
I'll kill 'im!
Kagome, it's dangerous,
so you stay here...
Huh?
Will you hurry up!
Hey!
Hey, Sesshomaru's inside!
That's why we have to
go teach him!
Neither blood nor tears flow
through him! He's unforgivable!
Father...
Those bones are
your father's?
Can't you tell?
Well, even if you say that...
How was I to know?!
It's so huge!
His father...
was a phantom of
incomparable stature.
And here he is in his truest form,
undisguised.
The treasured sword imbedded
in his bones...
That is what Lord Sesshomaru
is after.
I am finally here.
To possess the sacred sword
imbedded in my father's bones.
The lethal fang sword... known to kill
a hundred beasts in a single stroke!
Known as Tetsusaiga!
Tetsusaiga was forged from one
of his father's fangs.
Being in possession of
this sword...
empowers you with as much
strength as your father!
Can't pull it out?
He was ever so cautious.
There's a spell on it.
Sesshomaru!
Hmm?
I haven't finished
with you yet!
Damn!
Where'd he go?!
This is our father's resting place.
Be respectful!
You hypocrite!
You're the one trying to
to rob his grave!
Now get out of here!
Master Inuyasha!
Look behind you!
Behind me? Why?
That's the sword...
made from your father's fang...
That's Tetsusaiga!
Huh?!
It's just an old, rusty sword!
Tes-something-or-other?!
Hah! You can't even cut a
turnip with this!
Master Inuyasha!
Please draw the sword out.
Lord Sesshomaru, you were unable
to pull Tetsusaiga out.
Isn't that so?
And you say that Inuyasha can?
But of course!
Master Inuyasha was meant to
inherit the Tetsusaiga!
The fact that the tomb was entrusted
to Inuyasha is proof of that!
Now hurry, Master Inuyasha!
Draw the sword out!
What inheritance?!
What treasured sword!
I could care less about
this rusty sword!
But Sesshomaru!
You've insulted me once too often!
Now you'll die inside
our father's grave!
Where are you aiming?
Oww!
Such a childish attack!
Master Inuyasha!
You cannot fight unarmed!
Get the sword!
Shut up!
Inuyasha!
Just go and draw the sword out!
Kagome!
Sesshomaru couldn't do it!
Now, if you pull it out
with ease...
Sesshomaru's pride
will be in shreds!
How embarrassing for him!
I see...
All right!
That'll be really fun to watch.
Hey, I can't wait to see your face!
No!
Master Inuyasha is immune
to the spell...
which cast off Lord Sesshomaru!
I knew it! Tetsusaiga is destined to
belong to Master Inuyasha!
Draw it out, Inuyasha!
Huh?!
Oh dear!
Hey...
I couldn't pull it out!
Wh-why?!
Let's cut the comedy.
My poison claws will
sublimate you!
Wanna turn me into
slime, huh?!
You won't get away!
Why you...!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Let me assist!
Hey you!
Coward!
What?!
Take that!
You puny troublemaker!
Why little wench!
Even humans like me
can fight!
I won't lose this time!
What?! Is that all you can manage?!
Darn it!
I'm not done yet!
This is it!
Disappear!
Inuyasha!
Huh?!
Sorry... I pulled it out.
Sorry...
What'll I do?
The Un-Mother... a tragic demon
who is the reincarnation...
of spirits who lost their children
during the Warring States Era.
Sesshomaru used this demon
for trickery...
and I find that unforgivable!
I have no idea how I came to
be the one to draw the sword...
But I'll use it to make him pay!
What?! Sesshomaru turns into
a giant dog-demon?!
Next on Inuyasha: "Showdown:
Sesshomaru vs. Tetsusaiga!"
Don't miss it!