Oh boy...
At least we're still alive.
We're better off wielding
hoes than swords.
I thought we'd all be dead,
but we can go back home.
It's all thanks to that
priestess.
We must be grateful.
Hey, he's conscious!
Brace up, Yohei!
The priestess's medicine worked!
Priestess!
Yohei is revived!
Evil still seeks this man's life...
What's the matter, Priestess?
Nothing. He'll be all right.
He can probably get up tomorrow.
Does a priestess named Kikyo
serve this temple?
Are you the one who tends
to soldiers injured in war...
regardless of which side
they fought...
and who uses strange powers...
to bring back even those near death
back to life?
No strange powers...
Only knowledge of healing.
You can tell us at the castle.
Come with us.
Lord Kagewaki, master of
the Hitomi Clan...
has been in delicate health
since birth.
He recently became the head
of the clan...
after his father passed away.
His condition has
steadily weakened...
and yet, he won't let physicians
near him, not even his own vassals.
No one may pass!
The order is...
I have brought a priestess
who will cure Lord Kagewaki.
However, the lord forbid
entry to anyone!
The lord refuses to see anyone!
What is this castle?
This shroud of evil?
Hey!
So this man is the lord?
I sense no life in him.
As if he is dead from
neck down.
Kikyo...
Forgive me, my lord!
But she refuses to stay away!
She claimed to cure your illness
and forced herself!
Calm down.
Leave!
Yes sire!
You there... what is your name?
Kikyo.
Kikyo is alive.
The woman I myself set up
fifty years ago...
the woman who died,
taking the Sacred Jewel with her...
is still alive.
This woman... What's going on... ?!
W-what?
This is awful!
These, too.
All withered.
What's going on?
There's no dry spell.
Suddenly this past month...
Huh? Rain?
l-it's red... like blood.
What's that?!
Hmm... So it rained
pieces of demon carcasses?
Yes... it was so creepy!
Our fields are ruined.
Not only our fields...
the elderly, the young
and the weak...
so many of them
have succumbed!
I expect that much...
There must be a source for
a very strong miasma near by.
I understand.
So we're gonna help again?
Do we really have time
for this?
We have to find Naraku!
Even if you apologize,
I won't forgive you!
About Naraku...
That arrow that Kagome shot...
should have caused a
very deep wound.
As strong as he may be, Naraku would
be out of commission for a while.
Besides...
I've already received a gratuity.
We must help.
When'd you?!
Don't take it then!
And don't you get gratuities
after you do something?!
After the fact,
they usually give less.
You amaze me!
You dirty priest!
I am a monk.
Sango, what's the matter?
I'm pretty sure the miasma source is
over at the base of that mountain.
I was wondering if there is
a demon other than Naraku...
who could create a miasma
so strong.
Other than Naraku?
Well Kikyo?
What do you make of
the Lord's illness?
Well... I think it may be
beyond my skills.
I see... I knew it was no
ordinary illness.
So even you will
abandon him.
I am merely a priestess.
Please permit me to leave.
Forgive me, but the Lord has
forbidden you to leave.
We will have you stay here for awhile.
Kikyo is supposed to
have died...
I can wait to kill her...
until after I discover
her true self.
Tonight, my wishes
will be fulfilled.
I've found an interesting woman.
Because of the miasma, not even
a blade of grass grows here.
We'll soon be there...
What's going on in
this mountain anyway?
Huh?
What's the cave?
The miasma comes from...
Sango!
Are you all right?
You're still not fully recovered.
You must take it easy.
Sango and Kagome,
you wait here.
It's only a demon-slaying...
no sense in all of us
going in there.
Miroku, let's go.
Shippo, the miasma doesn't seem
to bother you.
Watch over them.
Leave it to me!
Be careful. This miasma
is pretty strong.
I can feel...
a strong whirling miasma.
Shall I go?
Let me out.
And bring me a bow
and arrow.
Sango, are you all right?
The miasma is getting stronger.
Yes... Kagome, how can
you put up with it?
Uh-huh... for now.
What's this? Something's
pulling me in!
What's going on inside the cave?
I wonder if Inuyasha and
Master Miroku are okay?
The miasma is getting stronger.
Hey, what're you doing, Miroku?!
So hopeless!
I have undergone training,
so I have some endurance.
An average human
would not stand a chance.
There's something...
Let's go.
What is that?!
Demon remains?
Demons fighting each other?
Hundreds of demons have been
fighting and killing each other here.
Those who lost and their debris
showered the village.
These are the remains.
Awful. But why are they doing this?
The last demon standing...
Merged its body with the other's!
Why can't I get out?!
The last demon standing was
supposed to leave here alive?!
It can't be that this is... ?!
Is there another demon here?
You mean me?
Wait, Inuyasha!
Lemme go!
If my hunch is correct...
No! This is bad!
I'll fight you!
They're taking too long!
Let's follow them.
Not you, Sango!
If you go in there in
your condition, you'll die!
Sango, let's get away from here.
It's bad for your health.
Kikyo...
Is Inuyasha inside?
Kikyo?
That priestess is Kikyo,
isn't she?!
Kagome!
Are you following her?
Yes! Shippo, you stay
with Sango!
Kagome, that woman...
That's Kikyo.
I don't know why she's here, but...
something evil is
going on inside!
Kirara!
Take Kirara with you!
Be careful, Kagome!
Thank you! Later!
The souls of the dead inside my body
are trying to get out.
Are they drawn by the
miasma in this cave?
I can feel something
other than the miasma...
Is it from the man in
the castle... ?
Damn you!
Next, the finishing blow!
The wound is closing up!
Hold back your sword, Inuyasha!
Do not fight!
Shaddup! If I don't fight,
I'll get killed!
Listen!
This is just like the Fuko spell!
The same method to create Kodoku!
Fuko spell?
Kodoku?
What the hell is that?!
With the Fuko spell...
poisonous worms and lizards
are placed in one pot...
have them kill each
other off.
The last one remaining alive then
becomes a creature called Kodoku.
You can say that, but...
I will kill you!
I will be the only one to live
and get out of here!
I have no choice, do I?!
This is turning out bad.
Unless the spell cast in here
is broken...
Inuyasha will...
Huh?! What's that?
Inu...yasha...
Kikyo!
The souls of the dead
are leaving me...
I see...
This miasma is from Kodoku...
Why?!
Kikyo is here?
Soon it will come out...
With my spell, I sealed
countless demons in there.
One by one, they killed each other...
until only one remains victorious...
and that one will become...
my new body.
Kikyo!
Damn!
Kirara!
Oh no!
What... ?!
I sense the Sacred Jewel.
Not this fragment...
There's another.
Someone else with
a Sacred Jewel fragment.
It couldn't be...!
The miasma is absorbing
Kikyo's souls of the dead...
and getting thicker.
Miroku!
Are you all right?
Hang in there!
Kagome!
No, Kirara!
Miroku... what is this?
This cave is under
a Fuko spell.
Unless we stop Inuyasha...
he will become fused
with the demon!
Fused?
I sense the presence
of the Sacred Jewel!
Is this a trap then?
The strength of this miasma...
There's no mistaking it...
Naraku's behind this.
This woman is not human.
I will devour her!
Do not touch Kikyo!
Stay cool, Inuyasha!
Get real, will ya!
I will protect Kikyo!
Kagome...!
Kagome!
What're you doing?!
I'm going to pull Kikyo up!
Otherwise, Inuyasha will continue
fighting for Kikyo's sake.
Inuyasha would never stand by
and watch Kikyo's slaughter.
I'm a bit jealous, though...
Are you conscious?
Can you stand?
So foolish...
By your coming here,
Inuyasha will lose you forever.
What're you saying?!
Inuyasha is trying so hard
to save you! Yet you!
Kikyo...
No, Inuyasha!
Don't kill it!
Inuyasha!
Kikyo...!
What?!
The spell is broken!
The miasma is disintegrating!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Are you okay?
Yes... but Kikyo was!
Look!
Naraku!
Since you destroyed
his body, Kagome...
Naraku needed to create
a new body for himself...
That's why he used the Fuko spell!
So the mountain miasma lured you...
and you entered the cave
upon which I had cast my spell.
Inuyasha...
you could have fused into
this body, too.
Is this the woman who
broke the spell?
Thanks to her, I'm able to
possess a new body.
Don't be stupid!
The spell was broken...
so that Kikyo could
save Inuyasha!
It looks like this woman
is Kikyo...
the one who followed you
in death fifty years ago.
You bastard!
Do not touch Kikyo...
with your filthy hands!
Inuyasha!
Damn...damn it all!
I don't understand...
If it's true that Kikyo wanted
to save Inuyasha...
instead of breaking the spell...
why didn't she aim the arrow
at the demon Kodoku?
Instead, Kikyo broke the spell...
and enabled me to
possess a new body...
Naraku now possesses
a new body.
His renewed power seizes upon
the dark side of our hearts.
Inuyasha's feelings for Kikyo...
Miroku's weakness,
his Wind Tunnel...
Sango, still troubled by
Kohaku's phantom.
Kikyo, are you going to save us?
Those are the Sacred Jewel fragments
that we've gathered!
What're you going to
do with them?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kikyo, Captured by Naraku!"
Don't miss it!