Hold it, Kagome!
You're on clean-up duty, too!
I have to meet someone!
Sorry, please overlook it this time!
Someone? As in, boy?
Oh dear...
I already told you,
there's no one like that!
I'll make it up to you!
It's good for your health.
Step on it.
Hojo?!
He seems nice...
But a bit individualistic.
Hmm...
Do you like movies, Higurashi?
Wanna go... Just you and me?
W-what?!
- Hey!
- Kagome!
You mean, as in a date?
What'll you do, Kagome?!
Will you go?
Why don't you, Kagome?
You've never been on a
date, have you?
Huh?!
Have you really, truly,
never been on a date?!
Don't be silly!
Of course, I've!
...never been on a date...
I guess I'll go.
Really?
Okay then, this Saturday.
It's a date!
Huh?!
Darn! I'm off to the
other world...
What was I thinking,
making a promise like that?!
Umm... Do you think I can
come back on Saturday?
I don't see why not.
Really?
I dunno what day
Saturday is, though.
Oh... let's go.
It feels so good!
Look, fish!
Hey, Kagome!
We're not here to have fun!
Okay, okay!
Let's see... I don't detect any signs
of Sacred Jewel fragments here.
Shippo... You're a demon!
Don't go getting seasick!
I feel terrible!
Jeepers... No one's taking
this seriously!
- Huh?
- What?
Spider webs?
Such long strands...
Master Inuyasha,
is something wrong?
Nothing.
- Huh?
- Someone!
Don't come near!
Nice catch!
What was that?
Umm... Thank you for...
Let go, you demon!
Of all the nerve!
Err... What was that just now?
A demon called the
Spider Head.
It started living in this mountain
just after the spring.
Several villages have
already been attacked.
It traps humans in its web,
then devours them.
It's a frightening demon!
I see...
Inuyasha, let's save them.
Any sign of Sacred Jewel
fragments?
I didn't sense anything from
that Spider Head just now.
Then let's go...
I want to cross the mountain
before nightfall.
But there is a demon!
How can we just pass?!
Hey! I'm not hunting down demons
just for goodwill towards man!
I know, but...
Usually, he'd at least
check it out.
I'm going home. No way will
I be beholden to a demon!
He saved you!
What an ingrate!
Shut up!
I hate demons!
Let's at least see her home.
Huh! It's that temple, right?
Nazuna? Who are these people?
Master!
Huh?! Were you attacked by
the Spider Head?
I went to put flowers on
the graves...
and I've gone and brought these
wicked demons to the temple, too...
I'm sorry.
Are you still on that?!
Demons, huh?
Calm down! We're leaving
right away!
Oh no... You can spend the night
at this temple.
Master!
Now, go and prepare supper.
Yes.
Forgive her rudeness.
Nazuna's parents were killed
by the Spider Head.
I've been taking care of
her since...
but she has a terrible fear
of demons.
Umm... Are there a lot of
Spider Heads in the area?
As more and more men die in war...
the number of Spider Heads
seems to increase.
In leaps and bounds...
Leaps and bounds?!
Say, let's take up his offer
to spend the night here.
Why do I have to let some
stupid demon control my life?
I have sealed this temple with
sacred sutras...
so the Spider Heads cannot enter.
You can rest easy.
You see!
I guess I have no choice.
That Nazuna has a sharp mouth,
but she sure can cook.
Huh?! I thought you disliked
her a while ago.
Well, a woman who can cook
can't be all that bad.
Night has fallen.
Say, Inuyasha...
Is something the matter?
No...
What?!
Inuyasha... Could you be...
Afraid of spiders?!
Boo!
I'm not a...
Am I wrong?
Absolutely!
Where are you going?
Shut up! I'm gonna sleep alone!
Damn... I'm losing my
sense of smell.
We're surrounded!
Aghh! Spider Heads!
This side, too!
There may be many of them,
but they're not formidable opponents.
It's just a post-meal exercise
for you, Master Inuyasha!
Dang that priest!
Whatever happened to
his sacred sutra seals?!
Master!
Master, the Spider Heads!
Inuyasha!
Kagome! Shippo!
Make your escape!
But!
Shut up!
I can ward them off alone!
What's with him today?
Why isn't Tetsusaiga transforming?
Damn!
Foxfire!
Inuyasha!
Get away!
N-Nazuna... The seals have
been broken!
My sutras can no longer
ward off the Spider Heads!
Master...
Master!
I think we're safe now.
Damn!
Inuyasha... What's wrong?
Shut up!
Something's wrong with
you today!
You guys had better worry about
yourselves first.
W-what's happening to your hair?
If you think I can protect you
as usual, you're wrong!
What's this?
Inuyasha... right?
Quit staring at me!
Your dog ears are gone!
You look just like a human...
And my fangs and
claws are gone, too!
What's going on, Inuyasha?
Half-demons like Master Inuyasha...
Iose their demon power for
a period of time.
Myoga!
Because this is
a life-threatening period...
half-demons never reveal this
weakness to anyone.
For Master Inuyasha,
it turns out that...
it is this night of the new month
when the moon is dark.
When the moon is dark...
The start of the new month
when the moon isn't visible?
And today is that day.
Master Inuyasha... Why didn't you
at least inform me?!
If you knew, you'd have
run off somewhere by now.
Well...
Have you so little faith in me?
I have little faith in this
period of time!
What about me?
If I had known about
your weakness...
I would never have insisted that
we journey into this den of demons!
Have you so little faith
in me, too?!
I don't trust anyone!
That's how I've lived
until now!
You have no right
to complain!
I'm sorry. But...
I just thought you could
open up to me a little...
H-hey! Don't cry!
It's because you're so
proud and stubborn...
that we're in this terrible
mess right now!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
What?!
I can't believe that
you're so stupid!
If Inuyasha is a powerless,
mere mortal...
I'm the only demon that can
protect everyone!
I must be strong!
Here they come!
You!
Nazuna!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Please... Please save the priest!
What? The priest?
That... that demon is strong, isn't he?
I thought you said you hated
demons?
Go rely on that priest's
sacred sutras.
What happened to you?
You look like...
I've just turned human
for a while!
What's the matter?
I forgot my backpack!
Forget it!
The Sacred Jewel fragments
are in there...
What?!
S-sorry!
Here!
You and Nazuna can
wait here!
Even if Tetsusaiga won't transform...
you can hit Spider Heads
on their heads!
Inuyasha...
All right, we're going back
to the temple, Shippo!
Huh?!
Me, too?
I have to be strong...
Be strong!
Priest!
So you are the mastermind
behind this!
I heard rumors that a half-demon
was roaming around...
with fragments of the
Sacred Jewel...
Darn... he took some of it!
And of all the luck...
you fell into my trap just
when your powers are gone!
I may not have any demon power...
but my human strength
can beat your brains out!
St. Elmo's fire!
Darn!
Pretending to be human is
quite a burden...
Die!
Inuyasha!
Now then, I'll take the
Sacred Jewel fragments!
No!
Then you, too...
Master...
Why?
He tricked you.
Kagome... Inuyasha is!
Inuyasha!
Tetsusaiga's powers are at work.
If Myoga appears at a time like this,
it must mean we have a chance.
Huh? What do you mean?
You've taken in
quite a bit of my toxin.
Soon, you'll start to corrode
from the inside!
No... Master...
Kagome... Run...
No!
Idiot! Listen to me!
I REFUSE to run away
by myself!
Hurry, outside!
Not outside!
There's a small room in
the back of the main hall!
As if you can get away!
Kagome!
Thrust the Tetsusaiga into the door!
- Huh?!
- Hurry!
W-what?! Damn!
Tetsusaiga's power will ward
them off for a while.
His hands are cold...
Inuyasha, hang on!
Inuyasha!
Just because I insisted
that we stay here...
It's not your fault.
But I!
I'll suck out the poison!
Hello... I've put on a
few pounds here...
Now it's up to Master Inuyasha.
He's perspiring so much...
Sorry, did I wake you?
No...
Kagome...
Yes?
Why?
Why were you crying?
You mean, a while ago?
I... I thought you were
going to die.
Crying... for me?
Let me use your lap.
Huh?
Okay.
Do you feel a little better?
You... smell nice.
Huh?
What?
You said you don't like
my smell.
That... was a lie.
What's he saying?!
Oh dear... Why is my
heart pounding so hard?
Hey, Inuyasha...
He's asleep.
What?!
What's that?!
Probably the priest's doing.
How's Master Inuyasha?
He's not recovered yet!
Watch out!
Shippo!
I'm taking possession
of the remaining fragments!
Hey, you dared to steal
the Master Priest's body!
There never was a priest.
All of this was to lure the
half-demon...
who possessed the
Sacred Jewel fragments.
You... killed my father and
the rest of the villagers?!
You served me well...
thinking that it was all
part of a vendetta.
How dare you!
You need not fear the
Spider Heads anymore.
Once dead, you'll become
one of us!
Damn him... Dad...
I was such a fool...
You're pretty determined
for a human.
You?
Inuyasha!
The dawn is breaking!
You're just a human right now!
What a fool you are!
Why you... Back to normal?!
Well, before you transform,
I'll get rid of you!
Will you stop touching me with
your slimy, ugly arms?!
The moonless night is over!
The demon sword also
transformed.
You got that right!
The fragments of the
Sacred Jewel?
It calcified inside the demon's body.
Jeepers... Is that all we have?!
It's quite a lot.
This far is fine.
The village is close by.
Really?
Then take care.
Inuyasha...
Thank you.
I'll remember that there are
good demons, too.
Forget that!
All demons are bad.
I won't forget, Inuyasha!
I won't forget you!
Hah!
Inuyasha...seems to be okay.
You...smell nice.
I...didn't hear wrong, did I?
Was he really serious?
I want to ask him...
Huh?! What're you staring at?
Got some complaint?
Forget it. He's still the same.
Ughh... Inuyasha...
Let's stop and rest.
Sure! Get over that seasickness
and I'll stop.
Inuyasha... Turn this way...
Huh?!
In a battle for the Sacred Jewel
fifty years ago...
Inuyasha was bound to a tree
by a shrine maiden's arrow.
Old Kaede's sister, Kikyo,
was fatally injured in that fight.
We returned from our journey to
find Kikyo's gravesite violated!
Who was it that robbed the grave?!
And what was the aim?
A calamity is about to befall!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Kikyo's Stolen Ashes"!
Don't miss it!