It all started with the Sacred Tree.
Fighting and searching
for our dreams...
and a strong bond
is formed between us.
A new hope!
A bright future begins now!
Kohaku who controls the huge pack
of demon rats comes to a decision.
Inuyasha rushes to help
the siblings
who face a crisis after
a heart-wrenching reunion...
And who appears but Kikyo!
The final shard guides us!
On the other side of the well,
a new day awaits in
the age of warring states!
A Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
You let your subordinates
eat the meat of their prey,
and devour the bones yourself.
You are Zushinezumi....huh?
I had a hankering for
bones like yours.
You're quite skilled, Kohaku.
Bring that little shrine that
he has on his back.
All right.
Don't make a mistake
and open it here.
Or you'll die.
They keep coming, don't they?
The rats will scatter everywhere
and attack wherever humans live.
Everywhere is overrun by rats.
Sango....
You said that Zushinezumi increase
in proportion to the numbers
which are cut, right?
Yes.
They don't die even if
you cut them,
so they keep increasing.
Since they've spread so far,
we can't trace the source.
By source, you mean
the miniature shrine?
Yes.
I heard that if you destroy
the shrine,
the rats will disappear.
It's like they're headed
for one place.
Somewhere, there is a mayose.
Mayose?
A spell that lures demons together,
then destroys them.
But only one with immense
spiritual power can cast such a spell.
The only one capable of this...
is Kikyo.
At the end of this flow of rats
is Kikyo!
Let's go, Inuyasha!
K-Kagome!
I'll try to go to the source,
where the rats are coming from.
Sango!
It bothers me....
That the number of rats
hasn't decreased at all.
Which means that the shrine
is still letting rats out.
So we must go to the source
or it will not end.
Let's split into two groups.
I'll go with Sango.
Inuyasha! Look!
The rats are climbing something!
l-It looks like a tree.
A tree?
It reaches up all the way
to heaven!
The rats are disappearing
into the sky....
Is this the mayose?
Why?
Kikyo has come out of hiding.
Do not close the doors.
That bastard!
He was enjoying this!
If I close these doors,
the rats will stop.
Even now...
It may save some lives.
I'm being watched...
If I close the doors,
Naraku will know that my
memory has returned.
Kohaku!
Huh?!
Were you behind this?!
Sister...
Kohaku....
On my way here,
I saw countless villages
devoured by rats.
How I wish you were not
a part of this!
I cannot....disobey my orders!
Kohaku!
Sango!
You mustn't, Sango!
Killing them will only
result in more rats!
Miroku, please take care
of the rest!
Sango!
No matter what,
I must destroy that shrine!
They won't even
turn to look at me.
They're intently heading
towards their destination.
Which means the power
of the mayose is enormous.
Amazing....
What happens to the rats
who climb up to the sky?
They probably become purified.
Huh?
No sign of Kikyo.
So she laid the trap
and ran away?
Bothersome woman.
W-What is that?
What....?!
D-Demon slugs!
That Kikyo....
Just when I thought
I had lured her out.
Hakudoshi!
She left this silly tree
and went into hiding.
Are you the one
who released the rats?!
Need you ask?
The mayose tree
is starting to rot!
If we leave it like that,
it'll fall.
Would you slay us?
Me and the demon slugs?
Prepare to die!
Inuyasha!
You can't use the Wind Scar!
If you bring down the tree,
you'll be doing exactly
what Hakudoshi wants!
I know that, stupid!
He only realized it
after I told him.
In any case, I must
protect the tree.
My arrow should be able to
handle a demon like that.
Yes! That was great, Kagome!
Well, I have a large target.
Bastard, don't you move!
Do you know how many villages
were devoured by rats
just to bring Kikyo out of hiding?!
What? Is that what's upsetting you?
Why bother with things that
don't involve you?
Well then....
maybe I'll interfere with those villagers
there who are trying to run away.
Why you...!
Wind Scar!
He used it!
Did it work?
If you see Kikyo,
give her a message:
As long as she keeps running
from Naraku,
the same thing will happen
over and over again.
Damn it!
Huh?
K-Kagome....
- Huh?
- The rats are acting strange....
Until now, they were totally
intent to getting to the tree.
Maybe the spiritual power
of the tree is weakening.
What?!
We must hurry and get rid
of the demon slugs.
Inuyasha!
Take care of the demons
higher up the tree!
Gotcha!
What are the rats going to do?
Kohaku!
Please Kohaku!
Don't add to your crimes!
Sister...
The rats are returning!
The Zushinezumi are
headed this way.
Was the spell broken?
Wind Tunnel!
This is bad. I can't suck in
all of them.
There are just too many.
Kohaku!
Give me the shrine!
If that shrine is broken,
the rats will disappear!
Remember, Kohaku!
You....are a Demon Slayer!
The Saimyosho are watching me.
If I do anything that seems
like a betrayal to Naraku,
that infant...
I'll never be able to get near
Naraku's heart!
The rats!
The last one!
We've destroyed all
the slugs....
This is bad....
The rats aren't trying to
climb up the tree anymore.
The tree must have died.
Huh?! They're coming after us!
Damn you...!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Even if I kill them,
they multiply.
These rats are such a pain!
Shippo!
Snap out of it and transform!
We're getting outta here!
We're gonna run away?!
The mayose tree won't help
anymore.
I'm gonna go and
destroy that shrine!
Let's go!
Awright!
Transform!
Oh no!
The rats have fallen out of
formation and are scattering!
Can't you fly any faster?!
- You're heavy, stupid!
- Hurry it up!
Sango!
Miroku!
Destroy the shrine!
Hurry!
Can't you understand, Kohaku!
If nothing's done, you'll fall prey
to the rats, too!
But Naraku would probably
order me to do this.
To protect the shrine
even if it means death.
Kohaku, wake up!
Sister!
Wind Tunnel!
Miroku!
Kohaku!
Sango, get on Kirara!
The ground is too dangerous!
Kohaku!
Huh?!
Damned box!
If I break it....!
Huh?!
It won't break!
Is it being protected
by a demonic barrier?
Hurry and get away, Sango!
Kohaku....!
Huh?!
- Inuyasha!
- I'm going on ahead!
The smell of blood!
Dammit! I have a bad
feeling about this!
The smell of this blood...
Is it Sango's?!
The presence of
the Sacred Jewel shard...?
Kohaku?
Shippo, please hurry!
Sango!
Damn! If I use my Wind Tunnel,
it'll take Sango as well!
Miroku! Sango!
Inuyasha!
A sacred arrow?!
The demonic barrier is gone!
Hurry! Break the shrine!
The rats....
Kagome, the rats are
disappearing.
The shrine has been broken.
Kikyo....
Sango....
Sister...
She's badly hurt...
all because of me.
Sister...
Kohaku....
Kohaku, are you all right?
Sister....
Kohaku?
Kohaku!
Saimyosho!
Who is that woman, Kohaku?
Why did she protect you?
I don't know.
Hakudoshi...
So you were watching me.
Sister...
I don't want to put her
in harm's way anymore.
I must defeat Naraku
as soon as possible!
Kohaku!
Kohaku....
Sango....
I wonder if Sango is okay.
She was bitten badly
by the rats.
Physically, she's probably okay.
She's pretty strong for a human.
More than that, it's the shock
she received
learning that Kohaku had something
to do with the shrine.
Sango, are you in pain?
I cannot forgive what
Kohaku did.
Sango....
Because of those rats, many
villages were destroyed.
Not only that....
I don't want to...
Kohaku!
At the castle that was
assaulted by the birds,
he killed many people.
Huh?! They weren't killed
by the birds....
Even if Naraku ordered it,
what Kohaku did
is unforgivable.
I know that in my head.
But....
when Kohaku was attacked
by the rats,
I felt as though my heart
was being crushed.
When I saw that he
was okay,
I felt relief from
the bottom of my heart.
I just can't hate Kohaku,
no matter what.
Sango, that is fine.
You don't have to force yourself
to hate him.
But....
even after this....
Do you regret protecting Kohaku?
I don't know.
But if I hadn't protected him,
I think I would be regretting
it more.
And that's fine.
That is the way of
the human heart.
Uh-huh....
Thank you, Miroku.
Naraku...
You would stoop to all this
just to lure me out.
Asuka.... Kocho....
Take this and fly.
I will search for his whereabouts.
After a long absence,
I return to the present-day world
where I face endless questions
about Inuyasha.
Your boyfriend is at your house?
I want to see! I want to see him!
Your delinquent boyfriend!
But Inuyasha breaks the bike
that Mom gave to Sis!
Leave it to me!
I'll pay you back!
What?
You're going to use the Adamant Barrage
to create diamonds?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Lucky but Two-Timing Scoundrel!"
I'm make a ton of 'em with Tetsusaiga!