Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha defeats Bankotsu,
bringing to a close
the long battle with the Band of Seven.
Naraku uses the power of their
Sacred Jewel shards to rejuvenate himself
and finally shows his
new deadly form!
It's up to us and Miroku, Sango,
Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time
for a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Why you...!
Backlash Wave!
Thank you, Kirara.
I've got you, Kagome.
This is....
Inuyasha!
What happened to you?!
Kagome?
Thank goodness....!
Y-You fool!
Why'd you come in here?
But....
I told you to wait outside!
I was worried about you.
Hah! Don't bother worrying
about me.
Hey, skinny wolf!
I knew you...
What happened to
that skinny wolf?
Koga was swallowed up
into these walls of flesh.
That wolf was devoured?
That's why you have to
get out of here quickly.
Yeah....
Damn it!
This thing.....
Kagome, get away!
Huh?
That voice....
Naraku!
Did they say "Naraku"?
Impossible!
What an incredible evil aura!
I can't believe that this is coming
from Naraku!
Inuyasha!
You can't move,
can you, Inuyasha?
Naraku....
Why you...!
You've done well
to come here....
is what I'd like to say....
But it's already too late.
You are already entangled
in my intestines.
It's over for you.
Over?
You must be dreaming!
It's over....
when I rip out
your throat!
Got that right!
Today is the day
we destroy you!
Naraku, prepare to die!
Humph!
Sango, watch out!
Owwee!
This is acid!
No! We'll get dissolved!
Sango!
Arghh!
Shippo!
Kagome!
Kagome! Shippo!
Arghh!
Fools!
You still don't understand?
At this moment, the entire Mt. Hakurei
is part of my body.
To put it plainly, you are all
inside my body.
What?!
These fleshy walls are
part of Naraku?
Kagome, will we be devoured
like Koga?
Don't get so conceited!
There's no value in
eating you.
Especially a weak, little demon.
Does he mean me?
Or a half-demon like Inuyasha.
And even more so, mere humans.
You all would only weaken me.
Bankotsu!
Is he dead?!
The stupidity of humans
makes me sick.
Even villains like this Bankotsu....
He came here determined
to avenge his comrades
and he fought with you, Inuyasha.
The seven Sacred Jewel shards which
I gave to the Band of Seven....
When he possessed them all,
he should have forgotten about
revenge and run away.
Yet....
They prove themselves
to be such fools....
these mortals called humans.
Naraku! Why you...!
Sure, he may have been a villain....
My Band of Seven brothers
were all slain.
I'm going to avenge
their deaths.
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
I'm making it easy for you
to take my shards
by punching with this hand!
But he was hundreds of times
more decent than you!
Wind Scar!
And yet, Naraku, you....!
Why're you so riled up, Inuyasha?
You're the one who
beat Bankotsu.
Shaddup!
Huh?!
Arghh!
Inuyasha!
Now, I have them....
The Sacred Jewel shards.
The Sacred Jewel shards
are gravitating into one.
So you've finally
made your move, Naraku.
This demonic aura.... There's no mistake.
Yes? Did you say something,
Lord Sesshomaru?
Naraku... So you've appeared.
Huh?
Other than
around Lord Sesshomaru,
I've never felt such
a strong demonic aura.
If I'm not careful following him,
I may end up dead.
Lord Sesshomaru!
Good luck!
Let's go!
Yes, my lord.
It's begun.
Begun?
But it will end right away.
Don't we need to wait?
Kagura is no longer here.
Good bye....
The Sacred Jewel shards
are becoming one!
Huh?!
Whaa...!
What is that?!
Naraku's new body.
N-No way!
Such a pity.
Each one of you despises
me so much....
Now you've finally
found me,
and you can't even lay a
finger on me.
Yeah, like I'm trembling with fear!
You go to such pains to
hide yourself in sacred grounds....
so I was expecting some
big, scary monster!
You're wrong, Inuyasha.
Naraku is...
Inuyasha! Naraku's demonic aura
is much, much stronger than before!
Demonic aura?
Don't make me laugh!
Naraku's gotten more warped than before!
That's all it is!
Inuyasha!
Iron Reaver, Soul Stealer!
Humph! What a laugh!
That you dare attack me
with bare fists.
Hah! Is that so?
You want it so badly?
Then I'll cut you to shreds!
Come Tetsusaiga!
Now! Prepare to die!
Wind Scar!
Fool!
Whaa...!
He deflected the Wind Scar!
Kagome!
My Wind Scar won't subside!
Miroku, get behind my Hiraikotsu!
What's going on?!
Inuyasha, I've captured your Wind Scar
into the flow of my demonic aura.
Kagome, are you okay?
Stupid Inuyasha!
You let Naraku goad you into
unleashing the Wind Scar!
Shaddup!
It's coming again!
The Wind Scar will keep
circling in here....
Until you are all mincemeat!
Inuyasha, your Wind Scar will cause
the death of all your friends.
There is a demonic aura whirling
around inside Mt. Hakurei.
Huh? That's Kagura,
Naraku's incarnation.
She's holding something.
Huh?!
Whoa! Kikyo?
Stop, Kagura.
You will not be the one
to destroy Kikyo.
He can talk?
Fine.
Naraku, just what did you release?
Kikyo?
Kagome, are you okay?
Yes.
This wind...
We have to do something
about this wind!
Inuyasha and his companions
shall die here.
And I now have a new body.
There is only one thing left.
Naraku, are you running away?!
Those are...!
Go after him, Inuyasha!
Kagome...?
Go after Naraku!
Okay, but what about you?
I'm coming with you!
If this wind is coming from Naraku,
I may be able to disperse it.
Not only that....
I can see them!
There are two Shikon Jewel shards
at Naraku's feet.
Two of 'em?
You mean, the wolf's?!
I'm sure of it.
Koga is a demon, so Naraku may try
to absorb him into his body.
We have to save him!
That's IF he's still alive.
They must be insane....
Leaping right into
the Wind Scar.
Kagome, the demonic aura whirls
around with Naraku at its center.
'Kay!
Never mind what happens!
Aim your arrow straight for Naraku!
All right!
Get him!
Huh?!
I hit him!
Koga!
You're worried about a friend
at a time like this?
Your stupidity thoroughly disgusts me.
The Wind Scar is gone.
Kagome....
If your comrades are so precious....
What's happening?
It's breaking up!
Oh, no! Miasma!
Consider this my compassion....
You can all sleep together
in the same grave.
Kikyo...
I shall be seeing you soon.
Don't worry, Kagome!
I'll get that skinny wolf back
for you without fail!
Inuyasha goes to rescue Koga!
During that short interval,
Naraku appears before Kikyo.
Speak, Naraku!
Just what is your true intent?!
The bottom of this fissure is
filled with my miasma.
Your imitation body will not
be able to endure it.
Kikyo, this will be your grave.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Farewell Kikyo, My Beloved"
Inuyasha, you were the one
who could not save her.