Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all
the shards of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku with my Tetsusaiga!
Mt. Hakurei begins to disintegrate
and Inuyasha goes off
to save Koga.
During that time, a resurrected Naraku
appears before Kikyo,
but what is his true motive?
It's up to us and Miroku,
Sango, Shippo and Kirara!
Travel back in time for
a Feudal Fairy Tale!
Inuyasha!
Get him!
Koga!
If your comrade is so precious....
What's happening?
It's breaking up!
Kikyo...
I shall be seeing you soon.
Koga!
Dammit!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
We must get out of here quickly,
or the miasma will kill us!
Kagome, I understand just
how you feel....
but there's nothing else
we can do.
You must give up
on Koga.
I'm not gonna put
you in danger.
Koga!
Oh, Koga....
- Hey Shippo....
- Yes?
Take Kagome and
get outta here.
You can manage that,
can't you?
Huh?
Inuyasha, you aren't....?
Take good care of Kagome....
Great Demon Shippo.
Inuyasha....
But Inuyasha....
You wanna save that scrawny wolf,
don't you?
You'll only be in my way.
Now go!
Transform!
Kagome, get on!
Hurry, Kagome.
Kagome!
Don't worry.
I'll bring that scrawny wolf back.
'Kay.
Inuyusha, be careful!
You come back, you hear me?
Promise!
Yeah!
This evil presence...
Is this really from Naraku?
Still...
This presence...
Mt. Hakurei is disintegrating.
Huh?
Naraku!
Kikyo....
It's been awhile.
The miasma is horrible!
If he fell into that,
there's no way to
save him.
What are these things?
There he is!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
He's starting to dissolve!
Damn Naraku! He intended to
devour Koga along with the Sacred shards!
You're alive, scrawny wolf?
Mutt....
Naraku! What happened to Naraku?!
We'll talk later!
I'm getting us outta here!
It's no use. All the openings
are sealed.
Isn't there any way out?
It's too early to give up.
If there's no exit,
we create one!
Wind Tunnel!
Way to go, Miroku!
Let's go!
The mountain is crumbling.
Where's Inuyasha?
Don't you see him yet?
Maybe he didn't make it in time.
No, he's okay.
Something like this
wouldn't kill Inuyasha!
Be safe, Inuyasha...
You promised to come back.
The exit....
Where's the exit?!
You idiot! Don't you know
the way out?
That's not it! The exits
have been sealed!
You've gotta be kidding!
I ain't gonna die here with you!
Damn right!
For once, we agree!
No way will I die
in a place like this!
I see it! An exit!
Kikyo?!
What's this? A vision of Kikyo
at a time like this?!
Naraku, what is the meaning of that
appearance of yours?
Can't you tell?
This is my new body.
Don't make me laugh.
I'm not blind.
That body....
Dressed in such finery,
but that is just for show.
You escaped to Mt. Hakurei and
even put up a sacred barrier.
Just what were you up to?
You are very astute, Kikyo.
So you noticed...
Just before the mountain
disintegrated,
your incarnation, Kagura, left Mt. Hakurei
with something in her possession.
Now tell me! What is your true aim?
Inuyasha....
I sense it.
Huh?
I sense the presence
of Sacred Jewel shards.
Koga?
It's coming this way!
Inuyasha!
I'm so glad!
They're both safe!
Not again...?!
Kagome!
What about Kagome?
Watch out!
Inuyasha! Koga!
Damn, that was so careless of me.
I'm sorry, Kagome, that we
got separated.
You must've been scared.
Why you...! Don't act like you
got out alive by yourself!
Shut up, Mutt!
Hey Koga, you should thank him
at least.
Huh?
Inuyasha went to save you before
I even asked.
Hah! Don't misunderstand!
I just didn't want Naraku to get
your Sacred Jewel shards.
Oh yeah? Then I don't need
to thank you.
That's the least you can do.
Which is it?!
He wants you to thank him.
I'll ask one more time.
Naraku, what is your true aim?
Kikyo, did you come all this way
to ask me that?
I'm asking the question.
'Round and 'round goes
the spinning wheel of Fate.
Spinning and weaving a red thread.
Meeting Rasetsu, or should I say
Kansuke, was no coincidence.
It was all according
to my plan.
I just took advantage of his desire
to find a place to die....
It was simple.
By putting rumors into that dying man's
head about Mt. Hakurei....
and setting him on your path.
Now do you understand?
You did not come here
on your own.
I lured you here.
Humans often call this
"fate" or "destiny."
Once the threads of destiny
become tangled,
they cannot be undone.
To walk this path once more
only confirms my cursed destiny.
Only the weak utter
such nonsense.
The truly powerful....
create fate and destiny themselves.
That is nonsense, Naraku!
Oh yes....
You asked me about
my true aim.
You wish to know?
Then I shall tell you....
What it is that I must do here.
That is....
Your imitation body is formed from
bones and dirt,
so you do not bleed?
Naraku, why you...!
You underestimated me, Kikyo.
You came here feeling safe....
believing that I would not
be able to kill you.
Believing that as long as I
had the heart of a worthless human....
the heart of Onigumo, the bandit
who loved you with all his heart....
I would not be able
to touch you.
However, I feel nothing....even after
wounding you so.
Do you mean you've lost
that heart?
I see...
What Kagura had in
her possession...
was his human heart.
The bottom of this crevice
is filled with my miasma.
An imitation body like yours
will dissolve easily.
Kikyo....
This is your grave!
Why... am I remembering
those moments?
Inuyasha...
Huh?
Inuyasha?
What is this ominous
feeling I have?
Inuyasha!
Now do you understand, Kikyo?
This is the new body
I wished for.
You took extraordinary steps
to kill a mere woman, Naraku.
Sesshomaru, huh?
He shows Lord Sesshomaru
such disrespect!
He's grown too full of himself!
Stay back, Jaken.
I didn't expect you to
be following me, too.
Are you so interested
in me?
Silence!
You are the one who keeps
meddling, so we....!
Back away, Jaken!
Since you've emerged from
your barrier,
I assume you're capable of
producing a decent amount of power.
Would you like to try me?
Got him!
He's laughing?!
Sesshomaru, now I'll just reverse
the power of your sword towards you.
Lord Sesshomaru is
being pushed back!
It's useless.
I will not die.
Such impudence...
You wanted to test the power of
your new body against me?
Sesshomaru!
So you're still alive, Inuyasha?
What're you...!
It seems that Naraku was far
more interested in
killing that woman
than getting rid of you.
Kikyo's bow!
Kikyo!
Does this mean that Naraku killed Kikyo?
No way!
Naraku cannot kill me.
As long as he has Onigumo's heart-
the heart which cares for me.
Soul Collectors!
I did it again....
Once again... I let only you die....
This miasma is terrible.
There's no way she could
survive it.
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru!
Hold on, Sesshomaru!
Did you just stand by and watch....
Kikyo get killed?
Wait, I said!
I don't care to know what your
connection to that woman was.
But the one who killed
Kikyo was Naraku.
And...
the one who wasn't able
to save her....
was you, Inuyasha.
Rather than taking out your anger
on me,
I suggest you go after Naraku.
Exactly!
Kikyo....
I....
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha....
That's...
Did something happen
to Kikyo?
Naraku's....
Naraku's aim....
was to take Kikyo's life.
It can't be...
Kikyo is...?
Damn that Naraku...
Pushing this thing on me.
Kikyo is dead.
Huh? What was that?
Naraku killed her.
Damn! I'm sick of this!
I'm not into
babysitting a kid!
Kagura! Is it a lie that
Kikyo is still alive?!
Inuyasha won't come.
He's desperately looking
for Kikyo.
Is this baby an incarnation of Naraku?
What does he want with me?
You are the only one who can
see the Sacred Jewel shards.
Kagome, I want your eyes.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Darkness in Kagome's Heart"
Inuyasha will not come
to save you.