As we journeyed in search
of Naraku's whereabouts,
three young monkey sprites
appeared before us.
Clumsy, scatterbrained
and quick to jump to conclusions...
yet too cute to hate.
The three monkey sprites were
in search of
the sacred object which housed
theirMonkey God.
We finally found it in a pickling tub
being used as a weight.
And the Monkey God said
something very strange.
A huge evil aura had flown overhead
in the direction of the ox-tiger,
then suddenly disappeared.
No doubt about it!
It's Naraku!
Ox and tiger?
That's northeast?
Shall we go?
Yeah...
We know which way to go now!
We head northeast!
Damn! She's supposed to come, too!
What's going on?!
I'm sorry.
Stop it already.
Kagome didn't catch a cold
because she wanted to.
l-I know that!
I'm so sorry, everyone.
It's for the best. This trip is going
to be a long one.
We'll use this time
to get things ready.
Yes! I have to prep
all my gadgets.
So your cold is actually
a blessing, Kagome.
He's right.
So don't worry.
Damn! Hurry and get well!
Inuyasha, I understand
yourhaste.
But don't blame Kagome.
Yes, don't!
I agree!
I'm sorry.
Geez! I'm not blaming you!
Honestly...
Kagome will recover quicker
if Inuyasha isn't around.
But it's a problem that
Old Kaede is away.
You have a terrible fever.
Kagome, why don't you
go home to the modern age?
Home?
There are good doctors there, right?
And you seem to have
good medicine, too.
That's true.
I'm sorry, but I'm going
home for a bit.
Don't apologize!
Now come, Kagome...
on my back!
Can you manage, Kagome?
Thanks...
What're you doing?
Err... nothing.
Yes, she'll be staying
home again.
Huh? Oh no, it's just a cold.
It's for real this time...
Err... nothing!
Higurashi is absent again today.
This time, she has a cold.
- A cold?
- Only a cold?
Well? How's your appetite?
I don't have any.
Then I'll make you something
warm to drink.
You can take yourmedicine
afterthat.
All right.
It's been awhile since we saw her,
yet she has a cold.
I wonder if it was cold
back there?
She should take her time
and recover completely.
I know!
For a mere cold!
Until now, she stayed home
for all kinds of strange ailments.
I know!
Shall we go visit her?
Visit her?
She won't be hospitalized for a cold.
Kagome will be home.
I get it!
Good idea.
It'll be nice to
visit Kagome.
Are you going to Higurashi's house?
Oh, Hojo...
Kagome has a cold.
I see... a cold.
- Would you like to go visit her, too?
- I see... Cold, huh?
I wonder if he's going
to see her?
Adelicate situation.
Lady Kaede!
Do not panic, Rikichi.
Stay calm and attack.
Yes, but we haven't done
this in so long...
Be strong!
Inuyasha and the others aren't here.
We must deal with it ourselves.
It's coming!
Now! Attack!
Lady Kaede!
Get out of my way, punk!
Inuyasha!
What're you guys doing here?
Many demons have been
acting up lately.
Some even terrorize
areas where humans live.
It seems Naraku's disappearance
caused all this.
The demons lay low while
he's around.
Now they're doing as they please.
Want some more?!
See ya!
Hey, Inuyasha!
Did he come to save us?
Hmm... he's not that
commendable.
You're in the way.
Move!
Punk! Just who do
you think I am?
Who cares?!
I have business in this swamp.
This swamp is my territory!
Keep it up and
I'll swallow you head first!
Head, huh?
This head?!
Take... that!
Now then...
All right, next!
This valley belongs to me!
This waterfall...
Shaddup!
Why you...!
I'm not listening!
Lady Kaede...
The demons aren't
appearing.
I wonder if they
escaped somewhere?
What're you doing?
Well... since we're here...
You came to visit?
Thank you.
How's yourtemperature?
A slight fever.
How's yourthroat?
Are you all stuffy?
I've been coughing still.
Here, for you.
Thank you.
Even if it's just a cold,
take care.
She's right. You've been so
sickly lately, Kagome.
I know.
Does he come to
visit you, too?
He?
You know... the delinquent.
He wouldn't come.
Why not?!
He's not kind then?
It's not that...
What's with all this?
Hurry and get well!
He's far away.
Hmm... far, huh?
Kagome!
Someone named Hojo is here.
Hojo?!
Hojo?
Hi!
Hojo... What's the matter?
I heard you caught a cold.
So I came to pay
you a visit.
I gave it a lot of thought.
I wondered just what I could
do for you.
And...
This is the only thing I could
think of that's good foryour health.
Please eat it.
Thank you.
And also...
These are charms for
good health.
But ljust remembered that
yourfamily owns a shrine.
Thank you.
Our charms don't work
too well.
Hey!
And...
These are dumbbells.
I think you should
build up your strength.
Th-Thank you.
And...
You still have something else?
Why don't you ask him in?
Hey you guys...
What happened to Kagome?
We sent herback home.
Home?
We thought she'd get better
care in her own home.
So we sent herback.
S-She went home?!
Just when I...
What?
Where did you go
without me?
Shippo! Why you...!
What was that for?!
Shaddup!
Oh, looks delicious!
Gifts forus?
Er... no... he's probably preparing
forthe long journey.
I don't think so...
I'm sure I put it away in here.
Hey, Grandpa.
What're you doing?
Oh! Here it is!
The secret medicine passed down
through generations of Higurashi.
It works on any and all illnesses!
I finally found it!
Grandpa...
Kagome's cold will be cured
in a flash!
- Oh well...
- Just wait, Kagome!
- Oh, Buyo!
- I'll have in ten minutes!
Kagome!
Grandpa... sorry!
Oh... what have I done?
Yo!
Oh, Inuyasha!
How's Kagome?
She's been asleep.
But now she has some visitors.
Oh... I see.
All the boys went wild.
And Ayumi...
Stop already.
It became the talk of
my class, too.
Really?! Oh no!
I'll bet it's all over
the school.
I know!
Excuse me for a minute.
So you're here!
Here?
To Kagome's house.
Well, ljust came to see
how she was.
You're so kind.
Err... no...
He doesn't know, afterall.
That Kagome has a boyfriend.
But Kagome's boyfriend
is also kind.
Dummy!
Um... were you just
talking about me?
No! Kagome has...
Umm... Well...
There's someone who's
been bothering Kagome.
Yes, yes!
Someone who won't even
come to see her when she's sick!
School seems so much fun.
Sis!
Sota, what is it?
Inuyasha is here.
Inuyasha!
Yo!
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just came to see
how you were.
You came to visit me?
Silly!
Shippo and Sango were worried!
But I'm the only one
able to come here.
Thank you.
I feel better, but my fever
won't go down.
I'm feeling a little tired, too.
l-I didn't come here to
take you back, y'know?
You'd bettertake care.
Better if you rest here...
She's gone!
Higurashi...
What is it?
Um... Well...
Is there something troubling you?
Troubling me?
Well, not really.
And I'm not worried.
Well, I...
I wish you would confide
in me more.
I'll do whatever I can for you.
So...
Since we're going out, it's the least...
Umm... huh?
Don't you think this will be on it?
I think so.
What's going on?
Tomorrow's the comprehension test.
Test?!
And it's going to be used to
determine our course of study.
Forhigh school?!
Have you been studying
during your absence?
Not too much.
Kagome can't help it.
Besides, she's noteven sure if
she can make it to school tomorrow.
Say...
What'll we be tested on?
What?!
You plan on taking the test
when you're sick?
Of course!
Higurashi, are you all right?
Hojo! Please!
I knew it! There is something
troubling you!
Please help me study!
Is it okay for herto
stay up?
There's an emphasis on
math and science.
So you should memorize
yourformulas and equations...
Are you all right, Kagome?
Don't overdo it.
No. Please continue, Hojo.
See you, Kagome.
Uh-huh. Thank you for coming.
I'll be seeing you, Higurashi.
Yes. Thank you so much.
What is it?
No, nothing.
See you. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Now then!
Say...
Yes?
This test thing...
Is it that important?
Yes.
What's the sense in taking a test
if you don'tget overyour cold?
But once I'm better,
I'll have to go to school.
So I have to study.
Getting better is more important.
Both are important.
Just stay in bed!
No!
Kagome!
I WANTto go to school!
Go away! Don'tget in the way
of my studies!
What?!
Awright! I get it!
I'm such a fool...
Kagome, how do you feel?
I'll make some rice gruel,
so eat, okay?
Uh-huh.
They all look so good!
We can sell it and
make good money.
I don't think we should
touch it.
Kirara!
I haven't done a thing!
I didn't touch a thing!
Same here!
Inuyasha?
Oh... my head hurts.
Yo!
Hey, Inuyasha!
You didn't go back?
I need a cooking fire.
Cooking fire?
Will a gas range do?
What's that?
Fornourishment,
there's nothing like liver!
Boarliver, carp liver,
chicken liver...
And medicinal roots
and herbs.
Inuyasha, you're gonna
eat all that?
Not me.
T-Then...
All right!
Inuyasha...
Here. Medicine. Drink.
Medicine?
It smells!
If you drink it,
you'll get better.
It'll cure any cold
in an instant!
It's awful!
Bearit!
It may taste bad,
but it'll work without fail.
You made it?
Well, yeah...
If it'll work,
I'll put up with the taste.
You sure it'll work?
Trust me!
She's drinking it!
Sis is drinking liverpotion!
Liverpotion...
You're right.
I think it's working.
See?
Thank you.
Nothing doing.
But how did you know about
making such medicine?
Err... my motherused to...
Yourmother?
She made it foryou?
Well, the ingredients
are a little different.
She used dried ingredients.
I used fresh ones.
Fresh?
Fresh what?
Fresh...
Anyway, it'll work.
Uh-huh. Thank you.
I said it's nothing!
Sorry aboutearlier.
Forget it! Justgo to sleep.
Is that some kind of
magic spell?
Err... yeah...
My motherused to
do it long ago.
I see...
I'm off!
Yo!
Good morning.
How do you feel?
Much, much better.
Yourmedicine worked.
Didn't I tell you?
I can go to school.
I'll even pass the test!
Oh no! It's no good!
I'll be late even if I leave now!
I won't make it in time
forthe test!
You'll make it if you hurry?
Buteven if I hurry...
Hurry and change!
W-Wait, Inuyasha!
Just be quiet!
Will you make it?
Uh-huh.
'Morning.
Kagome!
How's your cold?
I slept through the night,
and I feel better.
What about the test?
I'll go forit.
Atta girl!
All stand!
Say, Inuyasha... I have to talk to you
man-to-man.
Talk?
What is love?
Is love eternal?
What're you talking about?
I... I love Hitomi!
Kagome, you do something!
Leave it to me!
I'll do anything for
my darling little brother!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Sota's Brave Confession of Love"
This is way harderthan
slaying demons!