Huh?! What's this?
It's a powerful miasma.
Be careful!
The evil is coming closer.
Where is it?!
Just hurry and show yourself!
At your feet!
What is that?!
The ground is melting!
Shippo!
Why, you!
Take this! Hiraikotsu!
Finishing blow!
Wait!
What?!
It can't fight anymore.
Why?! I was just about to have
a good fight!
It was just big,
and not much else.
What a letdown. His appearance
was so deceptive.
But all's well and nothing could
be better than that.
What's with them?
Thank you so much, traveling monk.
Our village has been tormented
by that demon.
By that demon?
We shall have a feast for you
to show our gratitude.
This was just part of
my training.
I must decline.
I see. But it's too bad.
The pretty girls of the village
eagerly await you.
But if that is the case...
Well, since you're being
so kind,
Buddha will punish me
if I don't accept.
Changing his mind because
of the young girls.
He really is a lecher priest.
These beans are so delicious!
It's so yummy! They're great!
It's been so long since
we've had such great food!
What's the matter, Sango?
You haven't touched your food.
Hmm... I can see in your palm
that you will be blessed with children.
Miss, will you be army children?
Y-Yes!
I'll have as many as you want.
Fifteen, sixteen...
It makes no difference.
Now then!
H-Hey... Sango!
Don't just sit there and watch!
Help me!
Why don't you father
two, even three children?
Just do as you please.
Sango is scary!
Now, now!
Old woman, you're always
so healthy.
I still can bear a child
or two!
Even in this age, they had
lively family communions.
That's nice to know.
What's a family communion?
Well...
Oh, moms, dads and grandparents
and siblings all dining together and
enjoying each other's company.
Oh...
What's nice about that?!
Such bad manners!
If you lie down right after eating,
you'll end up a cow!
Who cares?!
Myoga!
I was a bit concerned
about you, Inuyasha.
So I came... only to find you
battling a giant centipede.
I'm so glad you are okay.
When the fighting's on,
you're nowhere to be found.
But you always appear
at times like this.
What a schemer you are!
Oh, come now...
Where've you been, anyway?
Even an old one like me
has some secrets
he'd prefer to keep.
You give me the creeps!
Hot! Hot!
I'm so full.
Quietly, silently...
tippy-tippy-toe!
There it comes.
I've heard of child spirits
lingering on
in an old mansion like this,
but is that all this is?
W-What's!?
Wanna pee!
Stop!
Gotta pee!
Wait!
This is not the toilet!
My goodness...
What a way to be awakened.
You want to pee again?
You can go by yourself, can't you?
Sango...
Do you know what time it is?
She's come sneaking into my bed!
Such luck!
Come and join me...
Don't tell me you're still
angry about earlier?
The old woman was just joking!
What's all that ruckus?!
Sango!
You don't have to be so angry!
She's sleepwalking.
Cripes! Can't you be more quiet
when you fight?
Wait!
Sango is possessed!
Stop, Sango!
Stop it, Sango!
Sango!
Are you all right?
Huh?
Why am I here?
What happened, Miroku?
She slapped him before
she came to.
There's no doubt that someone
bewitched Sango.
I don't remember a thing.
But who would bewitch her?
I don't sense anything suspicious
around here.
A-Are you sure?
Myoga! When did you
hop onto Miroku?
Are you sure you don't sense
anything suspicious?
I'll bet you're hiding something!
Err... no...
I remember...
Long ago, my father told me
of demons who
realize their power for the first
time after death.
For the first time after death?
The most recent demon
we destroyed was...
Oh!
Then that weak, giant centipede
is the culprit?
Then we must make sure
it's permanently sealed again.
What's the matter, Myoga?
Nothing... It's nothing.
There!
It's just a carcass.
Nothing scary about it.
In any case, let's seal it
with a sutra charm.
Kagome, you don't have
any luck with men.
R-Really?
Unless you leave your
current fellow,
you won't find peace
or happiness.
What about you, Sango?
Hmmm... Let's see... Hmm...
You're no better with men!
You'd better forget about him.
He's too much of a womanizer.
Your palm-reading is
right on the mark.
T-Think so?
What? Are you done
with sealing the demon?
It's not over!
Stop slacking, Miroku!
Why you!
Unforgivable!
What?!
What're you doing?!
Is this payback for earlier?
So you've shown your true self!
You lecher monk!
I didn't think you were
such a man!
I misjudged you!
I always knew!
That's not it!
This time, the spirit of the
centipede has possessed Miroku!
No way!
Miroku shows no signs
of being possessed
by such a strong power!
Shippo, run from here!
I don't need to be told that!
Kirara!
You won't get away!
Halt!
What?! What's going on?!
If I can't catch up to that
little kid,
this body is useless!
What's with that accent, Miroku?!
That's why I said he's possessed!
Darn!
What was I doing?
Miroku!
Are you the real Miroku now?
What? What are you talking about?
He has definitely returned
to his old self, Inuyasha.
That's for sure.
Wait!
I feel something suspicious
approaching.
Huh?
What's that?!
Could it be the mate of
last night's centipede?
Is this the one who
possessed us?
Kagome!
Be careful!
It's demon fluid!
Stay here!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
What a pesky centipede!
Let's put a sutra charm on it.
Now, everything is settled.
Inuyasha?
Inuyasha?!
Hold it!
You won't get away!
Could Inuyasha be?!
The way he's running...
he looks like a flea.
Flea?!
Wait, I say!
This time, it's Inuyasha?!
What's happening?!
Wait, Myoga!
Inuyasha is calling you!
That is not Master Inuyasha.
What?
Stop, I said!
l-Inuyasha!
Don't think you can escape
from me.
My body is all yours.
l-Inuyasha! Snap out of it!
You and I will get married.
I still have my own dreams!
I want to fall in love...
and I want to declare my love!
Inuyasha! Sit!
What're you doing?!
Kagome!
Inuyasha! You're back to normal!
Huh?
What did I do?
You stupid dog!
Inuyasha!
What are you holding?
Please let me go!
Myoga!
Please let me go, Inuyasha!
Kagome, it's a flea!
An unfamiliar flea!
You're right.
It came out from Inuyasha's body.
This is my one wish
of a lifetime!
Please let me go!
Myoga!
It's the end of the line for you.
You cannot get away!
Who are you?
Oh dear... This is so embarrassing.
I'm called Shoga.
I'm betrothed to Myoga.
Our parents arranged it.
N-No, she's wrong!
You be quiet!
Old Shoga, huh?
Don't call her old!
Oh, no... When a flea reaches
my age,
she wants to settle down
and have a family.
But this one...
From long ago, he's been
such a womanizer!
Whenever there's a pretty woman...
He goes to check on her
without a word...
And he leaves without a trace.
So I came after him this time,
sworn to take him back even
if I must carry him on my back!
Scary!
Myoga, are you prepared?!
No! Please let me!
Please release me, Inuyasha!
No way!
Why?
You knew that this Old Shoga
was the one who bewitched us!
Inuyasha, do you intend to
steal my days of youth?!
What days of youth?!
I think I'd better tie
you to my back!
Good idea!
Now, now... Old Shoga.
Forgive him.
Yes. If you're going to
take Old Myoga's freedom,
you should stay here
and get married.
Marry?!
Then you can start a
life together!
Oh dear...
She's embarrassed!
She may be a flea, but she's
still a female.
We'll ask the headman to
be the go-between.
There's no need for
the headman!
No! No!
Myoga doesn't seem
pleased about it.
You have to resign yourself.
Become a fine flea
husband and wife.
No!
Myoga... Now we are
married at last!
He's so embarrassed!
You can at least say
you love me.
Myoga?!
What's wrong?
What happened?!
Shoga?
Old Shoga?
This isn't Myoga!
He switched places with
some roving flea!
That Myoga! He ran away!
Run! Run to the depths of Hell!
Why that old geezer!
Wait!
You won't get away!
Run! Run!
Wait up!
That flea! When it comes
to running away, he's the best!
Wait, Myoga!
No way!
Inuyasha... Can't you find
Naraku's castle yet?
Don't talk to me!
I can't concentrate!
This is the night of the
new moon.
Is your sense of smell
lost for this night?
Shaddup!
Huh?! This smell... It belongs
to Koga of the Wolf-Demon Tribe.
And...
Not only that!
Kagura is making a deal
with Sesshomaru!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Naraku's Barrier... Kagura's Decision"
Damn, of all times!