Oursworn enemy: Naraku.
Taking possession of
more and more Sacred Jewel shards,
he is becoming increasingly powerful.
It's not only his hatred
towards Inuyasha.
Each and every time, without ever
sullying his own hands,
he manipulates people and events.
In orderto undo the curse
he put on Miroku's Wind Tunnel and
to help Sango rescue herbrother,
Kohaku, from Naraku's despicable grasp,
we have to find Naraku and
destroy him as soon as possible!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
I smell him...
It's Naraku!
The smell of the wind has changed.
L-Lord Sesshomaru!
Rin has been abducted!
One of Naraku's incarnations
named Kagura appeared...
And out of the blue...
Let me reassure you, Lord Sesshomaru.
If you heed my request,
I shall return Rin in
good health.
Y-You are Naraku!
Naraku, huh?
What are you up to now?
It's nothing special.
Just... kill Inuyasha, that is all.
All this trouble,
just forthat?
Huh?!
W-What is this?!
Ademon puppet?
Did he think that I, Sesshomaru,
could be so manipulated
over a mere mortal girl?
Then Lord Sesshomaru,
will you forsake Rin?
And... Lord Sesshomaru,
where are you going?
Umm... Where are you headed?
Are you perhaps?
So you will come, Sesshomaru.
Is it really Naraku's smell?
No mistake about it!
That Naraku!
This time I'll find you
and kill you!
He never showed himself.
So why now?
Yes, that bothers me.
Oh yes... I...
was taken by
that Kagura lady.
Y-You're!
I was kidnapped.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Don't go outside!
I have to go!
Understand now? If you go out,
they'll tearyou apart.
Were you kidnapped, too?
Then let's run away together.
I'm guarding you.
I see...
Say what's yourname?
I'm Rin.
How old are you?
Why are you doing this?
Are you a demon, too?
What do you like to eat?
Do you like melons?
You sure talk a lot.
Huh?
Well...
Keeping quiet makes
me more scared.
I wonder if Lord Sesshomaru
will come to save me?
Lord Sesshomaru.
What are yourplans?
Huh? What's the matter?
It's Naraku's castle.
Huh?
Well now...
I don't see a castle.
The barrier opened up!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Oh, please wait!
So you purposely leaked your scent
and revealed yourlocation...
inviting me into this castle.
Well, would you have come
otherwise?
There he is!
Although, the child you seek
is not here.
Inside this miasma, she would
not be able to breathe at all.
That child is undermy protection
outside the castle walls.
You may rest assured fornow.
Naraku...
You should know that I am not here
to save Rin.
Huh?!
Oh indeed.
You do not seem to appreciate
being told what to do.
You did not come to kill Inuyasha
as ordered...
nordid you come to look
forthe girl.
You've come to kill me,
I know that.
You talk as if you think
you've lured me into a trap.
I'll ask you why later.
IF you remain alive.
Sesshomaru...
Even if you refuse, you SHALL
give me yourpower.
Geez! Wait up, will you?!
Wait, everyone!
What's the holdup?!
I sense Sacred Jewel shards!
From that mountain.
That mountain?
You sense the shards there?
What'll we do?
We'll go after the shards.
Inuyasha, go find Naraku's castle.
Awright! Take care of things
on your side!
Be careful!
What's going on?!
Naraku's scent is starting to fade!
Does it mean he's sealed off
the barrierto his castle?
I must hurry before
I lose the scent of it!
The barrier!
Damn barrier!
Take... my Wind Scar!
The Wind Scarisn't working!
He's not getting away this time!
Lord Sesshomaru, you did me
the honor of coming here.
I will gladly take you on.
What's this?!
Hmph! A collection of
rejected demons.
Naraku, is that yourtrue form?
True form?
No, this is only the beginning.
So... you want my life?
I don't get it.
What's the point of Naraku
killing Sesshomaru?
Could Naraku be planning to?!
It's close... The Sacred Jewel shard.
It bothers me...
that it's so close to
Naraku's castle.
Yes... and...
I think there's just
one shard.
That's right!
Sango's younger brother, Kohaku,
has just one shard...
Could it be... Kohaku?
It's sweet.
Want another?
Huh? Yeah...
Here.
If you like it,
I can go steal some more.
You don't remember anything, Kohaku?
No...
Even yourma and pa?
I've forgotten them.
So there's such a thing?
It's not that.
I just feel like I might remember
something frightening.
There are things you don't
want to remember.
Even me.
My ma, pa and
brothers were attacked by robbers
and all of them were...
I still have nightmares
about it.
It's scary, huh?
Am I talking too much?
I'm always told to
be quiet, but...
It's okay.
Been awhile since I talked
this much to someone.
What's wrong?
Be quiet!
That woman...
Herface... is the one face
I can't get out of my mind.
Wait, Kagura!
If he really remembers
everything he did,
this kid will truly be destroyed.
It's kindness to let him die
without remembering a thing.
Kohaku... Are you inside?
Kohaku!
Naraku... such a lowly demon.
The likes of you will
never lay a hand on me.
How long do you intend
to keep up this farce?
The more you hack away,
the more you will be
surrounded by parts of my body.
Then...
I knew it!
Naraku is trying to absorb Sesshomaru
into his own body.
What's going on?!
Sesshomaru's scent?
But right here, it suddenly ceases like
it's been erased.
Could this be Naraku's castle?
Miasma and toxic fumes...
this has gotta be it!
This is Naraku's barrier!
Go for it!
Tetsusaiga!
I can see it!
Naraku's castle!
Who is it? Someone is
breaking through my barrier!
Kagura, go!
An unexpected guest, Naraku?
Too bad forhim...
coming to visit you...
Only to see you... dead!
Just a little more...
Soon you will be absorbed
and become one with my flesh!
Huh?! Inuyasha!
Tetsusaiga's blade... is red!
Kagura!
So you're the one
who broke the barrier, Inuyasha?
As you can see!
Kagura, you're no match
forme any longer.
So if you understand, move away!
Otherwise, I'll kill you!
Damn! The Saimyosho...
I can't move.
They're watching me.
I guess I have to put on an
act of fighting.
What's going on?!
Kagura's wind has no power.
Are you... serious about fighting me?!
Is this all you've got?!
Damn! They've seen through me
that I'm not fighting seriously.
I guess I have to get real.
Just in time.
Let them handle it.
Damn, small fry!
Wind Scar!
Why you!
I think I overestimated
Sesshomaru.
Move! Why you!
Wind Scar!
Move! Move! Move!
You're in my way!
But... with that sword, Inuyasha
could probably defeat Naraku now.
Then I'll be free...
I miscalculated...
I didn'texpect Inuyasha
to break through and come here.
I found you, Naraku!
I will kill you for sure today!
Such a fool!
I've completely absorbed
Sesshomaru's demon power into my body.
You don't seriously think
you can beat me now?
Sesshomaru?!
I don't know whatgood
it'll be,
but I'll make you part
of my flesh, too!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Vanishing Point; Naraku Disappears"
Kohaku! Kill Rin!