Tetsusaiga's purpose is to suppress
the demon blood in Inuyasha.
Unless he masters Tetsusaiga...
Inuyasha will once again
transform into a demon.
Unable to bear it any longer,
Inuyasha...
seeks Old Totosai's counsel...
for a way to make Tetsusaiga
lighter to wield.
The answer lay in defeating
Ryukotsusei...
the demon who was put
under seal by Inuyasha's father.
There's only one way to stop
the reawakened Ryukotsusei.
He must use Backlash Wave.
Backlash Wave?
It is the ultimate technique
of Tetsusaiga.
But...
Inuyasha can barely wield Tetsusaiga,
not to mention the Wind Scar!
Let alone the ultimate technique...
Not dead yet, huh?
I'll put you at ease.
Inuyasha doesn't have Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha, wake up!
Inuyasha!
K-Kagome...
What is this evil aura?
It's entirely different from before.
So, his demon blood has awakened.
So be it. It'll make it more fun.
No! Inuyasha has transformed.
Inuyasha!
No, Inuyasha!
Change back!
What'll you do, Inuyasha?
If you stay transformed and battle
Ryukotsusei with those claws...
you will come out of this alive.
However, Tetsusaiga will...
Tetsusaiga will never become
lighter for you.
Little man, stop acting cocky!
A-Amazing!
He pushed back
Ryukotsusei's huge body!
Did Inuyasha win?
Hmm... let's retreat.
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious?
Inuyasha is fighting as a demon.
So you'll just abandon him?
That's cruel!
Wake up! If we stay here...
Inuyasha might even come after us,
after Ryukotsusei!
Old Myoga!
Each time Master Inuyasha
transforms...
he becomes less discriminating.
Kagome, you won't be an exception.
All right.
Old Myoga, please escape.
Huh?!
Let me down, Totosai.
I'm staying here.
Kagome, you!
Yes. I know what you're
going to say.
But...
But I can't abandon Inuyasha
when he's battling for his life!
Please Totosai, let me down!
A-All right, all right.
Oh well... it can't be helped.
Just a minute!
Inuyasha is acting strange...
Huh?!
Inuyasha!
Master Inuyasha!
He's transformed, yet he's trying
to pick up Tetsusaiga!
Could it be...as Kagome said?
Yes, Inuyasha is battling right now.
His heart against the demon blood
that courses through his veins.
He is fighting desperately!
Inuyasha, hang in there!
Why that... little punk!
Getting wise with me!
Playtime is over!
Inuyasha!
Oh?! What's that?
Huh?
Huh?!
The sheath of Tetsusaiga?!
What's going on?
I dunno...
Hmm... the barrier of the sheath.
That's right.
When we fought the
Thunder Brothers...
Yes! He used the sheath to deflect
the lightning attacks.
The sheath... Tetsusaiga's sheath
protected Inuyasha!
Yes, but...
there won't be
a second time.
The sheathe won't hold.
That thing is useless!
Take this!
Inuyasha!
Wind Tunnel!
Miroku!
W-what a strength!
You diverted it!
That was a close call.
It drained my strength
just to turn its path a tad.
Inuyasha is facing this
formidable foe all alone!
The little man's evil aura is dissipating.
Get on my sword with that
fat body, will you?!
Ryukotsusei! I'll defeat you
with Tetsusaiga!
With that dull sword, weak boy?
Don't make me laugh!
Shaddup!
I have to use Tetsusaiga or
there's no sense in fighting!
Fool! I'm not holding back anymore.
It's not my imagination!
Tetsusaiga is...
getting lighter!
Huh?!
Look!
Inuyasha and Tetsusaiga!
I know!
Now's my chance to
pierce through Ryukotsusei's heart!
Fool!
Huh?!
I did it!
He pierced through
Ryukotsusei's heart!
Did he do it?
It's light!
Tetsusaiga used to be so heavy...
but now it feels like
it's adhering to my hand.
How dare he put a blade
in me!
Little man! You will die!
He's not dead yet?!
What a demon!
His heart was pierced,
yet he acts fine!
Ryukotsusei was handful even
for Inuyasha's father.
Unless his body is chopped into bits,
he won't die.
That's!
It's my turn now!
Damn!
His body's so hard!
I told you that silly sword
is useless!
This smell...
the Wind Scar?
The Wind Scar is twisting around
my Tetsusaiga.
Little man, this is it!
Ryukotsusei, I'll show you that
I'm different now!
Wind Scar!
Wow... The Wind Scar!
Amazing!
Inuyasha!
Did he beat him?!
Not only did it get lighter...!
I can invoke the Wind Scar
at any time!
Hey, did you see this, Totosai?!
I did it!
Well, I'll give you points for that.
But it's too early to rest
on your laurels.
Huh?
W-what?!
Is that all you have, little man?
You disappoint me.
Did you think you could defeat me
with that?
W-what is he anyway?!
He was hit with the Wind Scar,
yet it didn't even affect him.
I told you so...
I told you...
my body is harder than armor.
Now then, it's my turn!
No good. Inuyasha, you'd better
get away.
He's serious.
What?!
What is this... tremendous evil aura?!
It's no time to be impressed!
Hurry and run!
No can do!
Ryukotsusei is so ready to fight!
Look, you can wield Tetsusaiga now.
Leave it at that.
Inuyasha!
Stop idle talk!
I've been waiting for
something like this!
Besides, if I defeat this thing,
I'll surpass my old man!
Little man! Go join your father!
It's huge!
We'll get caught in it!
Kirara, move away.
A ball of evil aura, incomparably
stronger than the ones before!
Inuyasha!
Fool!
In order to destroy Ryukotsusei's
steel-hard body...
Inuyasha must summon the
Backlash Wave.
But the way he is now,
Inuyasha can't...
I can't thwart it!
You can't run away now!
Well then...
I just have to cut it!
A ball of evil aura, uncomparably
stronger than the ones before!
You can't run away now!
Well then... I just have to
cut it!
What was that?!
It couldn't be...
Huh?!
He used the Backlash Wave.
It's that flow!
If I cut through that smoldering spot
with the Wind Scar...!
Right here!
What?! The little man's sword has
swallowed up my evil aura!
How can this happen?!
The whirlpool of Tetsusaiga's aura...
is pushing back Ryukotsusei's
evil aura.
This can't be... happening!!
My body... My steel body...
What... ? What was that?
It was totally different
from other Wind Scars...
Inuyasha!
Kagome...
Inuyasha! You did it! Awesome!
There's hide nor hair left of
that Ryukotsusei!
Amazing!
How'd you do it anyway?
Huh? That?
Master Inuyasha, how impressive!
I knew from the start
you had the power.
Old Myoga had you written off
the whole time.
Hmmm...
I see, Totosai, you...
Huh?
You're pretty thoughtful
sometimes!
What'd you do to Tetsusaiga?
It's much better than before!
Then you... used the sword
without realizing a thing?
Huh?
That was the ultimate technique of
Tetsusaiga... the Backlash Wave.
Backlash Wave?
Huh? That was the
Backlash Wave just now?
Precisely.
Backlash Wave...
twists the opponent's evil aura
around the Wind Scar...
and reverses the flow of the evil aura.
"Twists it around the Wind Scar...
and reverse the evil aura"?
The Wind Scar and the evil aura
are pushed back as whirlpools.
In other words, the opponent is
thrust with...
the Wind Scar and his own
evil aura simultaneously.
Anyway, that's the rationale.
But you had to be able to discern
where to cut through the evil aura.
And unless your will was stronger
than his enemy's evil aura...
it would've been impossible.
I'm impressed, Inuyasha!
Hmm... I just cut through the
spot that seemed funny.
He's gone beyond the reasoning.
Maybe, he's destined for
bigger things than I imagined.
Inuyasha, now you're able to
wield Tetsusaiga at will.
Not only that...
You'll be shocked!
Here you go!
The Wind Scar!
See? I can pull out the
Wind Scar anytime now!
There!
Hey!
How about it?
This here, too!
Hey! Stop! Inuyasha!
Stop hurling around a dangerous
sword like that!
Hah! There's no one who can
beat me now!
If you're jealous, stop me!
Inuyasha!
Oops!
Sit!
You are so excitable.
I'll say... Such a simpleton.
I must be strong for him.
Damn... Kagome said the word.
Hmm... He's still just a little punk.
Let's go...
A girl waits all alone for her brother who
has gone off to war, never to return.
Satsuki has a treasure
to make her wishes come true...
fragment of
the Sacred Jewel!
If it's the real thing,
we must take it from her.
Poor Shippo is in a dilemma.
I wonder if he has feelings
for Satsuki?
Just then, a demon lays a
cruel trap...
in order to get the Sacred Jewel
fragment.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Stone Flower
and Shippo's First Love"...
Don't miss it!