Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Kikyo appears at the base of
the sacred mountain, Mt. Hakurei.
And so does Ginkotsu,
even more powerful than before.
And Suikotsu of the Band of Seven,
the one with two hearts,
has also awakened!
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time.
To a Feudal Fairytale...
Inuyasha!
Dr. Suikotsu!
Stop!
What's going on?
Isn't he part of
the Band of Seven?
Dr. Suikotsu!
l-I... I'm all right.
Are you hurt?
No...
We're okay.
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
Dr. Suikotsu!
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
Huh?!
Good is bad.
Bad is good.
Huh?!
Good is bad.
Bad is good.
What are you doing, Dr. Suikotsu!
Good is bad.
Bad is good.
He's finally awake.
Good is bad.
Bad is good.
To live is to die...
Yeah...
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
Just what are...!
Me?
I'm Suikotsu of the Band of Seven.
Suikotsu, why you...!
That do-good physician...
held me back for
so long.
He!
What's the meaning of this?
He's an entirely different
person from a while ago.
That Suikotsu has...
two hearts inside him.
You're probably right.
I've heard of it before.
It's called split personality.
Another personality hidden in the
subconscious has emerged.
I don't understand any of that...
One thing I do know... you belong
to the Band of Seven, after all!
Suikotsu, here!
Kid...
You've been wanting
to fight me.
You'll get your wish now.
What's the matter?
Too scared to fight
without a sword?
Hah! Sounds like fun!
Plan to fight me
with those claws?
Let's see you try,
you deceitful bastard!
Watch what you say, kid!
Wha...!
Iron-reaver, Soul-stealer!
Not bad.
I'll turn you into mincemeat!
Die!
Your moves are too showy.
Close-quarters combat is
fought like this!
If you keep backing away,
you'll never be able to
mince me up!
Why, you...!
What's the matter, hey!
Don't get too cocky!
Wha...!
Inuyasha!
You bastard...!
Die!
It's over.
Stop!
Huh?
Dr. Suikotsu, what's wrong?
Please return to
your old self!
S-S-Stop!
Stop!
This guy...
What's happening to him?
That Suikotsu...
He hasn't completely awakened yet?
Well then...
Go, Ginkotsu!
Kikyo!
Pay attention!
Kikyo is!
Inuyasha can't reach her!
We have to save her!
But how!?
I'll go!
But Miroku...
If you can't use your
Wind Tunnel...
This is not the time
to say that!
Miroku...
Sango, you stay close to Kagome.
And open up the way with
your Hiraikotsu.
All right!
Hiraikotsu!
Not so fast!
I'm your opponent!
Outta the way!
Hah! You can go, after
you beat me!
Damn!
If only I had my Tetsusaiga!
Kikyo!
Lady Kikyo!
Thanks, Kirara!
He did it!
Miroku!
Kikyo... she's safe!
Hah! She wasn't the real target.
Geez! I'm not too keen
on this.
If we kill the kids,
there will be no one left
to distract Suikotsu.
Then he'll be able to suppress
that troublesome doctor.
Don't worry.
It'll be real quick.
Stop!
Huh?
Please... Don't do it!
Suikotsu... You!
Suikotsu still has
feelings of uncertainty.
If we kill the kids...
his heart may burst.
The barrier of Mt. Hakurei?
I'll get 'em all at once!
It seems we can't linger around here
any longer.
This is it for today!
Come, Suikotsu!
Retreat!
Err... why...
Let's go, Suikotsu!
You bastards!
You ain't getting' away!
Inuyasha!
We'll meet again!
Damn!
How irritating....!
Kikyo!
Please get up, Kikyo!
Kikyo...
Have the souls of the dead...
left her body?
Inuyasha...
Kikyo's Soul Collectors...
They disappeared?
What does this mean?
They can't get near her?
Take Kikyo...
Huh?
We have to take Kikyo
over there.
Otherwise, she probably
can't wake up.
Kagome...
So what'll we do?
Should I be the one
to carry her?
Only Inuyasha can.
Is it my imagination, or
are things a bit tense here?
It's not your imagination, Shippo.
Huh?
I don't want to see them
like this...
But it can't be helped.
Tell me, does Inuyasha still
have feelings for Kikyo?
Geez, you have to admire
Kagome's generosity.
Say...
Please don't say such
things right now.
Oh! Okay!
We're sorry!
I'm scared!
Huh?
Did I sound scary to you?
Kikyo...
Inuyasha...
Where am I?
On the outskirts of the village.
I see.
My Soul Collectors could not
get near the village.
No.
What happened to them?
You mean, the Band of Seven?
The men who possess those
defiled Sacred Jewel shards....
They retreated.
They took Suikotsu.
I see.
Kagome...
You must have seen it.
The Sacred Jewel shard around
Suikotsu's neck.
The clear glow turned cloudy.
And then... he left.
It's all...
because of this land.
Kikyo... what're you trying to say?
This land is evil.
It does not allow anyone with a
demonic aura to approach.
It is because Mt. Hakurei is purifying
the air in the surrounding areas.
Mt. Hakurei?
I've heard of it.
It is a sacred mountain which absolves
and cleanses criminals.
Yes.
That man known as Suikotsu was
able to live here
because deep inside, he had
a pure heart.
But his other personality...
the Suikotsu who belonged to
the Band of Seven surfaced,
so he wasn't able
to stay here?
The rest of the gang
stopped fighting and left
because of this mountain
known as Mt. Hakurei?
Pure is impure.
Impure is pure.
Good is bad.
Bad is good.
To live is to die.
To die is to live.
Yes...
Mt. Hakurei is too pure.
Mt. Hakurei...
What'll we do, Miroku?
Let us go.
I'm curious.
Kikyo, what about you?
Lady Kikyo!
I will stay here.
I want to stay close to
those children for a while.
Besides...
Besides?
Even if I wish to,
I cannot go.
Inuyasha...
You saw...
My Soul Collectors are being repelled
from this land.
It took all I had to stand
at the base of the mountain.
Kikyo...
Inuyasha, do you still...
Hey! Why's Kagome riding Kirara?
Well, because she doesn't
want to be carried by you.
What'd I do?!
Even if you didn't do a thing,
the mood between you and
Kikyo is too suspicious.
Women are very sensitive.
Kagome is hurt because she thinks
that you still have feelings for Kikyo.
Let her be for a while.
When Kagome has cooled down,
you can get on her good side again...
Hey! Kagome!
Hey!
He wasn't listening.
Answer me, you!
Why are you ignoring me?!
Hey, Kagome!
What?
If you have something to say,
let's hear it!
I have nothing.
You're upset!
I'm not.
Anyway, this is no time to argue.
You understand that?
Inuyasha...
W-What?
I mentioned it before...
That I'll stay beside you.
I know that there's a bond between
you and Kikyo.
So I can't tell you to
forget Kikyo.
And yet...
I'm going to stay by you.
It's what I decided.
Kagome...
So I'm not going to worry
about last night.
But...
Huh?
Why are you trying to pick
a fight with me?!
Why can't you just
leave me alone?!
I'm trying so hard
to endure this!
Y-You're angry, after all.
Sit!
Sit! Sit! Sit!
Sit! Sit!
Sit!
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
That's why I told him
to let her be.
Inuyasha looks so small.
Stop!
Hey! Renkotsu!
Where're we going?
Huh?
That's Kohaku!
He's come for us.
Now then, let's go meet
the Big Brother!
And the Band of Seven will
be at full force.
Is that it?
I finally found it.
The strongest of the specters, Bankotsu,
has rejoined the Band of Seven.
They're hell-bent on revenge
and begin an assault of the castle.
Those bastards in that castle
beheaded us.
I feel stronger than
before I died.
What? Don't tell me they're also
after Koga's Sacred Jewel shards!
Next on Inuyasha: "Enter Bankotsu,
the Leader of the Band of Seven"
Wash your necks and wait to die!