Here we come!
It's time for Inuyasha!
We're going to gather all the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
and I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
The Band of Seven are
all together.
Their leader, Bankotsu,
is their strongest.
His huge halberd and Inuyasha's
Tetsusaiga are about to clash.
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale...
Inuyasha!
You must be the Band of Seven!
So the wolf comes
before the dog.
I'll kill you!
Stay still!
Move it, you wimpy wolf!
Huh?
I found you....Band of Seven!
Hey Inuyasha!
Shaddup!
So you're Inuyasha.
I see you have brute strength.
You must be the last
of the Band of Seven!
Yeah, I'm Bankotsu the leader.
Ganging up on one wimpy wolf, huh?
Hey! No one's ganging up on me!
Shaddup!
Who's the one who almost
lost his Sacred Jewel shards?!
I'm not that stupid!
Inuyasha!
Koga!
Yo!
You're late!
So they've come.
They're all here.
You bastards....
You've had your way
for long enough.
I'll send you back to your graves.
Same here.
I'm going to avenge
Mukotsu and Kyokotsu's deaths.
It seems the one with the large
halberd is the leader.
Yes, although he looks
like the youngest.
What's the matter, Kagome?
Be careful, Inuyasha.
That man has three Sacred Jewel
shards in his neck.
What?
Yeah....
The shards Mukotsu and Kyokotsu had.
Hah! I wondered why
you were so feisty.
Is that what it was?
Naraku must have given him
the Sacred Jewel shards!
What?
Cripes! Leave it to Naraku to
revive a bunch of murderers like you.
Yeah, and he told us to use the power
of the Sacred Jewel shards
to kill every one of you.
Hah!
I'll tear you apart!
Fine! Just try it!
They're locked together!
Are they evenly matched?
Don't just stand there!
Kagome!
Kagome? Kagome!
Where're you looking?
Look out for yourself!
Are you okay, Kagome?
Y-Yes.
She's safe?
Hey, Koga!
I'll compliment you for
saving Kagome at least!
I don't need your thanks!
Thank you, Koga.
Go and hide somewhere.
They're after the Shikon Jewel shards
in my legs.
But....
That's Renkotsu...
The one who stole the shards
from me.
He still has them!
I get it.
That girl can see
the Sacred Jewel shards.
Damn!
Why you...!
If Bankotsu finds out that I kept
quiet about them,
there'll be hell to pay.
Ginkotsu!
Get that girl!
What?!
Kagome!
- Huh?!
- Run, Kagome!
I'll kill her in a flash!
As if I'd let you fire!
Koga!
What?!
Those cannonballs
won't touch me!
He's away from the cannon.
We must get the shards back.
Shards?
He took my Sacred Jewel shards.
Go, Miroku!
Leave it to me!
I can't let you go any further.
Suikotsu!
I'll fight you.
I can't stand doctors and monks!
You're a doctor yourself!
Not again!
Everyone's so selfish!
Are you the only one left for me?
Well, excuse me!
It's no fun fighting a woman.
So just die!
Not so fast!
Being a half-demon,
you're stronger than a human.
But why couldn't Naraku beat you?
What?!
Is that all you have?
If you know where Naraku is,
tell me now!
I don't like to be questioned!
If you want to know
Naraku's whereabouts....
Ask this.
Such a large mountain,
isn't it, Jaken?
Why did I have to come
to a place like this?
What's the matter, Jaken?
I feel awful!
From what?
Mt. Hakurei is a sacred mountain.
It's so pure, demons have a hard
time approaching it.
Rin, you don't feel anything
because you're human.
But I feel like I'm
being dragged.
Hey!
Let's go further and
explore, Jaken.
Wasn't she listening to
anything I said?!
H-Hey....
H-Hey....no!
I can't go further!
I'm going this way!
Huh?
There's no way a mass of evil
like Naraku would be here.
So why would Lord Sesshomaru....?
A sacred barrier?
I can't get near.
Naraku had a servant...
I came here following
the scent of that boy, Kohaku.
But the scent stopped.
Like it was cut off.
Lord Sesshomaru is late.
I want to get away from here.
I wonder where he went?
I hope he comes
to rescue us.
Huh?
Kohaku?
There's no mistake!
It's Kohaku!
Rin, don't go off on your own!
Lord Sesshomaru will scold me!
I was so close to
being purified.
Huh?! Rin!
She's gone!
Kohaku!
You?!
I'm so glad I get
to see you again.
Rin, why are you here?
Last time, we didn't part
in a nice way.
It bothered me.
Go back. This is no place for you!
What's the matter?
Quiet!
Go back slowly.
Before they notice you.
Kohaku...
Hurry! If they see you,
they'll kill you!
Kohaku.... What about you, Kohaku?
They won't attack me.
Now go!
Uh-huh....
Kohaku!
Die! Monk!
Not if I have my way!
Miroku!
Pay attention!
My flames of Hell
will roast you alive!
That kind of thing
won't work on me!
Naraku's poison insects!
Saimyosho!
Retreat?
Has something happened?
Don't bother me!
I want to deal with them first!
I wanted to have a
little more fun.
Inuyasha, say your prayers!
Hey, that's my line!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
You're too late!
So this is the Wind Scar?!
Bankotsu!
He did it!
Serves you right!
Damn!
You scarred my Banryu!
Good job, Ginkotsu.
You saved me.
All right! I heard you!
Inuyasha, that's all for today.
Quit joking around!
Break's over!
Damn!
Just that girl...
Kagome!
Before she says too much.
I'll shoot!
Kagome!
Renkotsu!
You won't get away!
Kagome!
This is too much!
He really wants us back quickly.
See ya!
You're not getting away!
Inuyasha, it's been a while.
N-Naraku!
I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me, Lord Sesshomaru!
Rin ran off before I could stop her....
Rin is....
inside the barrier?
No, you mustn't, Lord Sesshomaru!
If you enter sacred grounds,
you'll instantly be purifed!
Silence!
Look behind you.
Huh?!
Wha...?!
Rin!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Kohaku was inside, wasn't he?
Be honest!
Tell the truth. You can't deceive
Lord Sesshomaru's keen nose.
Does Lord Sesshomaru intend
to kill Kohaku, after all?
Umm.... Kohaku helped
me escape.
There were lots and lots
of demons in the cave.
What?
Demons?
Kohaku protected me
from the demons.
So....
Demons inside this
sacred place?
Lord Sesshomaru?
Now I understand...
Naraku's trick.
I give you credit for
coming this far.
Why you...!
Inuyasha, this Naraku is....
What else?
It's one of his demon puppets.
Buying time for the
Band of Seven to make their escape?!
Huh? What's this...?
That's a demon puppet, right?
Yes. It has to be a decoy
that Naraku created.
Why do you ask, Kagome?
This one is different
from the others he's used.
I ain't got time
for fakes!
What're you doing, Koga!
I can't let you pass.
He's gotten so big!
Kagome!
Sango!
I'll just use....
The Wind Scar!
Huh?
Can't....let you....pass....
All right!
Koga, trying to get ahead
of us?!
Shut up, Mutt!
An incompetent like you would
only let the Band of Seven get away!
They can't have gone
far yet.
They won't get away!
Hey, hold it!
Wait, Inuyasha.
Kagome, you noticed it, too?
What's up?
There's something strange
about this demon puppet.
Somehow, it seems....clean.
Whaddya mean Naraku's
puppet seems clean?!
It's similar.
It's like Mt. Hakurei.
Mt. Hakurei?
Huh? It smells nice.
This demon puppet smells of
water and flowers.
Water and flowers?
You're right.
But why does Naraku's
puppet smell like this?
Where are you?!
Where'd you go?!
What the hell....?!
A barrier?
D-Damn!
We can see it, Bankotsu.
It's Mt. Hakurei.
Geez, what's with this air?
Made me sick the last
time we came, too.
We couldn't feel it so far out before.
The barrier has been
made stronger.
This way, neither Inuyasha nor Koga
can come after us.
But it'll be tough for us, too.
Even though we're human.
Wait.
Seems we won't have to go
up to the base of the mountain.
Bankotsu....
Kohaku.
Who's this albino kid?
Kanna.
What's this?
Huh?
That's....!
You know him?
No mistake!
He's the one who killed Mukotsu!
It's Inuyasha's older brother,
Sesshomaru.
Huh? So he was Inuyasha's
older brother?
I see.
And?
You are to go after him
and kill him, too.
Hey! Is that all?
We were in the midst of
fighting Inuyasha.
If you had continued fighting,
you would have been killed.
What?!
What're you saying, kid?!
Your halberd cannot
defeat Inuyasha's sword.
You mean because of this
scratch on Banryu?
This scratch is....
It can become much stronger.
Huh?
Oh, I get it.
Hey, Renkotsu.
Hand it over.
I'm on to you.
What're you talking about?
I knew all along.
That you took Sacred Jewel shards from
that girl, Kagome, and hid them from me.
Or should I cut the shard
out of your neck?
Don't be mad, Big Brother.
I've been meaning to give it to you.
That's a wise decision, Renkotsu.
You're smart, after all.
But....
Remember that there won't be
a second chance.
I know.
All right! Suikotsu....
Huh?
And Jakotsu....
Go get this Sesshomaru.
Huh?!
Not happy? I thought you
liked handsome men?
I keep telling you,
I want Inuyasha!
It's a one-sided love.
Forget it.
I'll kill Inuyasha.
All right then.
Hmm....
This is great.
I know where Inuyasha
is headed.
Ninja are clever, after all.
I'm not a ninja.
Damn half-demon...
Wash your neck and
wait for your death.
Look for water?
Do we look for
rivers and marshes?
Yup. Until we find the same
kind of water and
the same smell of flowers....
It was the first time
I ever smelled that flower scent.
What about the Band of Seven?
If we keep following Naraku,
they'll show up.
Naraku, we'll find you
without fail.
Mt. Hakurei's barrier has
become even stronger.
The clean scent of water and flowers
lingered from Naraku's demon puppet.
Is there some connection?
Hijiri Island....a sacred place.
It's said that a century ago,
an illustrious monk became a
Living Buddha and is enshrined there.
It bothers me!
Let's just go!
Next on Inuyasha: "Floating on the Water:
The Barrier of Hijiri Island"
Why? Why can't I use
my Wind Scar?!