Woods... squirrel... lily... yellow...
Your late father's friend
lives so deep in the forest.
Huh?
Welcome... I have been waiting.
A voice... from the sky.
I don't see anyone.
I've been expecting you...
Sesshomaru.
You knew that I was coming,
Bokusen-Oh?
You've come to speak to me...
about the swords.
Inuyasha told me...
while I went in search for Kohaku...
Miroku! What're you doing?
There are poison insects!
Wind Tunnel!
Miroku!
You're sucking in
the poison insects, too!
Inuyasha, go after Sango and Kagome.
You sacrificed yourself and fought...
Yet I went after Kohaku...
Kohaku!
I'll kill you, then kill myself.
This is the only way
to get you back from Naraku!
Forgive me, Kohaku!
Stop, Sango!
I'm sorry, Miroku.
It was my fault you ended up
sucking in poison insects.
Sango...
Yes?
Don't look so sad.
There's still hope for Kohaku.
Miroku...
So keep smiling.
Thank you.
Miroku...
No! Hang on! Miroku!
Oops!
Sango, we brought water.
How is Miroku?
I think he's much better.
Is the information you seek...
about the Tetsusaiga,
your father's heirloom sword?
Or...
A tree demon!
Lord Sesshomaru, just what is that?
A 2,000-year-old magnolia tree.
Oh...
The sheaths of the swords,
the Tetsusaiga and the Tenseiga...
that belonged to Sesshomaru's father
were carved from my boughs.
The sheaths?
So the sheaths for those swords
came from this tree!
The strange power of the sheaths...
I can see why after seeing him.
Bokusen-Oh...
You would know... the link between
Inuyasha and the Tetsusaiga.
Inuyasha?
You mean your younger brother?
Inuyasha's blood changed.
The first time was when a demon
bit into the Tetsusaiga.
The second time, he had let go
of the Tetsusaiga while fighting me.
Die!
This scent!
It changed from
a half-demon's blood scent...
to the smell of a demon's blood...
like mine and my father's.
The same smell of blood?
I wonder about that.
What do you mean?
Inuyasha is a half-demon,
born between a demon and a human.
He could never become
a full-fledged demon.
Sesshomaru... there is something...
that you, a full-fledged demon,
can do...
but which Inuyasha could never do.
Inuyasha could never do?
It is to maintain oneself.
Maintain oneself?
Yes.
For example, Sesshomaru...
during a battle, if you are cornered,
you are able to remain calm.
You never lose control of yourself.
I would never get into
such a desperate situation.
Perhaps.
However, Inuyasha is different.
If backed into a corner
and his life is in danger...
in order to protect his life...
his demon blood takes control
of the body and transforms.
So that's what happened that time...
But...
the pure demon blood of his father
is too strong for a half-demon.
So what happens?
Let me see...
It could be said that the demon blood
devours the soul.
He cannot recognize himself.
He cannot differentiate between
friend or foe... He just kills.
And in that transformation
Inuyasha will eventually lose his soul.
He will become a demon
who only knows how to fight and kill.
He will continue to fight
until he is destroyed.
Your father probably did not want
such a fate for Inuyasha.
That is why he bequeathed Inuyasha
the Tetsusaiga to protect him.
The Tetsusaiga protects him?
If he lets go of that sword,
Inuyasha becomes...
Inuyasha, you've really matured.
Whaddya mean?
I'm complimenting you!
You saved Kohaku's life.
I just wanted to irritate Naraku.
If we get Kohaku back alive
that would make Naraku mad as hell.
Putting on an act again.
And besides, you were alive.
Huh?
- Did you worry?
- Of course!
I was a bit concerned, too...
since you didn't come for a long time.
Doesn't your wound hurt?
Lemme see.
Never mind.
I can take care of it myself.
Don't you know you can
make it worse with lack of care?!
- It's okay!
- It's not okay!
- I said I'm all right!
- You're not!
Am, too!
Sorry! I wanted to thank you.
- Huh?
- Thank us for what?
Thank you, Kagome and Inuyasha...
for staying with me.
We'll get out of your way.
Staying by her? Why wouldn't we?
What was that?!
It came from over there!
What's wrong?
- Gramps... My gramps!
- Is it a demon?!
Where is it, old man?!
Where'd the demon go?!
I don't sense any demons.
Over here! Over here! I tripped...
What?!
I'm saved!
Cripes! I thought a demon attacked.
Getting us all worked up over nothing.
Good thing, Gramps.
Thank you so much!
I twisted my ankle and had fallen...
And now, you even carry me like this.
No, no. It's on our way.
Nothing to worry about.
- Right, Inuyasha?
- Tsk!
Thank you very much.
Oh, the village!
Yes, I can see it.
- Take care.
- Yes.
Thanks, Sis...
And Mr. Dog-Man.
Dog-Man?!
Inuyasha...
As thanks,
I'm giving you my treasure.
'Bye!
- What did he give you?
- A snake's molted skin.
Wow! A molted skin?
Wow! Inuyasha, can I have it?
Dang! We have no time
to be saving people!
But we're walking this route anyway!
Whenever you do a good deed,
you become ill-tempered.
Ha!
Huh?
Inuyasha?
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
I smell human blood.
What?!
And I smell a lot of it.
There's smoke!
Isn't that in the direction
of that kid's village?
They've been attacked!
The boy...
Gramps...
Hang on!
Are you all right?!
Please help...
- Kagome, take care of the kid.
- Okay.
- Sango, stay and protect Kagome.
- Got it!
- Let's hurry, Miroku!
- Coming!
I like this village.
We'll camp out here
until the food runs out.
Gather the women in one place!
If you try to escape, we'll kill you!
Roving bandits!
Why you!
I'll take care of you small fry later.
Where's your leader?
Inuyasha, among the bandits.
Yeah... I smell it.
There's a demon in their midst.
Kid... you have an interesting sword.
Are you the demon...
controlling a bunch of bandits?
The leader is a demon?!
You must be kidding!
Kid... hand over that sword.
What?! What're you mumbling about?
Be careful, Inuyasha!
As if I'm gonna lose!
If you won't hand over that sword
I'll take it from you.
Sounds fun to me! Take it if you can!
Inuyasha still has difficulty
wielding that sword. Will he be okay?
I'll cut the dirty hide
off your back, demon!
- Chief!
- The Chief's giant hatchet!
Serves you right!
That's a pretty sharp sword.
You understand?
Then prepare to die!
This calls for a shield.
W-what?!
You've been showered
with my poison powder!
W-why you!
An amazing sword!
I like it more and more!
No!
Troublesome kid...
T-that's!
Chief!
What's wrong?
Afraid, now that you know
I'm a demon?
No way!
A strong demon for a leader
will make us invincible!
We'll continue to follow you!
Serves 'em right!
It's a poison cocoon.
If you touch it, you'll melt away.
The two inside
have totally disintegrated.
It's a poison cocoon.
Anyone who touches it will melt away.
Even those two inside...
Hmm?
They're still inside!
Oh... so they've created a
barrier on the inside.
Inuyasha... can you move?
Damn... Of course!
I'll rip apart this stupid cocoon!
Inuyasha!
It seems you can't move your body.
The poison powder has entered
through your wound.
It will fester slowly.
Hey... get it.
Yes... sir!
Tetsusaiga!
Here you are, Chief.
The Tetsusaiga has rejected him!
Chief?
Kid... what's the meaning of this?
Why does this sword reject me?!
My sword Tetsusaiga... is choosy
about who wields it.
It won't let a low-class demon
like you near it!
But this low-class bandit
was allowed to?
Low-class? C'mon, Chief!
I see... kid.
So you're a half-demon?
What a joke!
A half-demon like you
had the gall...
to pick a fight with me,
the demon Gatenmaru!
They're late. Something must've
happened in the village.
- Are you all right?
- I'm worried about Gramps.
Inuyasha...
Inuyasha's wound
is worsening steadily.
Damn...the bleeding won't stop.
Is it because of the poison?
This is bad.
I can barely maintain the barrier.
I can't make a move.
However...
even this barrier won't hold forever.
Ah... Chief, this sword...
Do as you please with it.
I'm not interested in a sword I can't use!
Thank you!
That sword... I must...
Get it to him somehow...
Nice!
What a great sword!
It's only a matter of time
before the barrier wears off...
and the poison cocoon
melts them away.
So I'll just sit here
and enjoy the view.
Bring on the women.
No!
Damn!
Inuyasha is badly hurt by
the poison moth demon, Gatenmaru.
But his demon blood takes over...
and slaughters even the bandits
who beg for mercy.
How can we reverse Inuyasha's
transformation?
Miroku, Sango...
We must think of something!
What?!
Why do we have to deal with
Sesshomaru at a time like this?!
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Demon's True Nature"
Don't miss it!