Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings
a group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled by
the few remaining shards of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
Demon after demon appears
at the Cultural Festival.
Taking them all on is Inuyasha-
No, wait, it's Grandpa, Mom,
Sota and even Hojo!
It's dangerous!
Don't do anything rash!
'Scuse me!
Home Economics
Classroom 2
What is it?
What's wrong?!
Huh?!
W-What happened?!
I don't know....
I was only away for a bit.
This is terrible....
Who could have done this?!
Well, we can't just
stand here!
What'll we do?
We can't use any of this.
It's too bad, but....
It's too early to give up.
But how?
Don't worry.
I have an idea.
This is all.
That'll be 1360 yen please.
35... 36...
We don't have time.
Everyone, hurry!
- How many of this?
- What else do we need?
We made it!
That's great.
But what are these anyway?
Lightly salted pickled
potato chips.
Sweet dumplings simmered
in corn soup.
Pre-made hamburger
with yogurt sauce.
Chocolate fondue with
pickled radishes, and more.
Kagome, you're amazing....
when you're under pressure.
Well, I guess I've been in
a pinch quite often.
By the way, are these things
all edible?
No idea.
What do you mean?
I guess we'll find out
soon enough.
You're probably right.
At least, that's taken
care of.
But... who did all this?
Hey Kagome!
- Over there!
- Everyone!
What is that?!
That's a Kurotengudake!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
That was close...!
Why are you here, too?!
Shaddup!
What're you doin', Kagome?!
What do you mean,
what am I doing?
You brought those dried foods
back, didn't you?
Ulp....
What?!
If you boil the dried food,
they turn back into demons?
You brought them back here
without knowing?!
I wouldn't have brought them
if I knew.
Geez! Guess it can't be helped.
So how many did you bring?
Well.... I think four including
the one just now.
Four?! No wonder they
were gone so quickly.
Hah! So I have to deal with
demons here, too?
What a pain!
Not to worry.
I'll destroy the demon with a
Higurashi Shrine sutra!
You will not.
It's too dangerous.
Don't do anything.
Just leave it to us.
What're you saying?
You have an important
presentation, don't you?
- Huh?
- It's kinda scary, but I'll help too.
Right! This is a once-in-a-lifetime
event for you, Kagome!
So just leave it to us!
- Let's do our best!
- Yeah!
Now listen, Inuyasha....
We must take care of this
before it becomes complicated.
S-Sure.
Kagome!
Ayumi....
Hey! Why can't you be
more careful?!
- What're you doing?!
- Kids shouldn't watch.
- What're you doing, Sis?
- Such a lively duo.
What'll I do? His gaudy outfit
brings enough attention...
With his ears standing up
like that,
everyone'll figure out
he's a half-demon!
What're you doing?
Err....nothing.
Geez!
Huh?
It's all over!
- C'mon, let's go.
- Huh?
The choir performance
will start.
- Oh right.
- Let's go.
- But....
- Come on!
Kagome Higurashi!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
I wonder why Ayumi hasn't
said anything about Inuyasha?
I see...
No wonder.
Well whatever....that's a relief.
Say Kagome....
Say that
after the performance.
The alto solo is
very important.
Oh....right.
I forgot all about it!
- Kagome!
- Coming!
Hah! I can handle those wimpy
dried demons without Kagome.
Three more.
Where are they hiding?
Hmm?
I guess I won't be able
to smell them out.
Huh?
Hey! That's the stuff that
burns my tongue!
Somewhere around here,
there are demons...
But if I slip away now,
I'll disappoint everyone,
after all their hard work.
What should I do?!
Damn demons!
Where'd they go?!
Cursed demons!
Where are you?!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Oh Sota....
- Thank you for waiting.
- So cute.
Oh boy...
Hey, over here!
Coming!
There's Kagome!
What can be seen over there is
the light of the Shikon Jewel....
Even in pieces,
its power remains the same.
On humans and on demons,
it slowly shows its effect....
Throughout the ages,
it lights this world.
Huh? That's... a demon!
Throughout the ages,
it lights this world.
I must do something!
Throughout the ages,
it lights this world.
I must do something!
On humans and on demons,
it slowly shows its effect....
Darn! This isn't the time
to be singing!
On humans and on demons,
it slowly shows its effect....
But I can't put Ayumi and everyone
in a bind by leaving now!
On humans and on demons,
it slowly shows its effect....
But I can't put Ayumi and everyone
in a bind by leaving now!
Throughout the ages,
it lights this world.
If I do, they'll never let me
borrow their notes again!
Throughout the ages,
it lights this world.
What can be seen over there
is the light of the Shikon Jewel....
But I can't just ignore
the demons!
What can be seen over there
is the light of the Shikon Jewel....
Notes...
What can be seen over there
is the light of the Shikon Jewel....
or demons...
What can be seen over there
is the light of the Shikon Jewel....
or demons...
Through a thousand years,
its power has been coveted.
I don't need to think!
Through a thousand years,
its power has been coveted.
I know what's more important!
Through a thousand years,
its power has been coveted.
I know what's more important!
In order to become whole,
it manipulates fate....
There it is!
In order to become whole,
it manipulates fate....
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
In order to become whole,
it manipulates fate....
Now, may the last shard,
shine over peace.
In order to become whole,
it manipulates fate....
Inuyasha!
In order to become whole,
it manipulates fate....
Thank you!
In order to become whole,
it manipulates fate....
Thank you!
Now, may the last shard,
shine over peace.
Two more!
We have to find them quickly!
Dammit! If these weird smells
didn't interfere,
I'd find them in an instant!
Kagome!
Huh?!
This voice...!
What're you doing?
It's almost time for the play.
Huh?
The only way to handle this
is to end the play early.
Kagome....
Don't worry.
Don't be nervous.
I'm not that nervous.
Listen Kagome.
When the curtain goes up,
you won't be Kagome any more.
At that moment,
you'll become Escargot Pudding.
O-Okay.
If you become the character,
your lines will come to you naturally.
Just believe in yourself.
T-Thank you....
- And....
- Huh?
If you mess up,
I'll never forgive you!
Now do your best, Kagome.
Kagome....
Hojo....
Here.
A pumpkin?
I understand eating this will take
away your stage jitters.
I thought you don't eat the pumpkin,
you think of
the audience as pumpkins...
'Kay! Eat up, Kagome!
Hojo!
Hojo...
I can't eat it raw...
Demons! Come on out!
There you are demons!
I'll vanquish you with this sacred sutra!
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Oh Sota....
- I can't wait....
- I'll say!
Josephine!
Where is Josephine?
Oh, here I am,
Lady Escargot Pudding.
What is Kagome doing?!
She just skipped seven
pages of dialogue!
I know it's sudden,
but I want to get married immediately.
You'll find someone,
won't you?
I'm so sorry.
But I have no other choice.
Oh certainly.... But isn't that
something that can wait until later?
What, Josephine?!
Are you saying you
won't obey me?
Oh no!
I'll take care of it right away!
Hey, didn't they say this was
going to be a tragic love story?
Yes.... But, so what?
It's hilarious.
I guess....
Kagome is shining
on stage.
Escargot!
You're a sole meuniére....
An oyster on the half-shell!
Or even, the freshest sashimi!
You make me so happy,
Pierre Panna Cotta!
I think I'm....
You don't have to say it!
Now come into my arms!
Pierre!
Escargot!
Hold it!
What's going on?!
l- lnuyasha...
Bastard....who the hell are you?
Err....well.... I'm....
This is bad!
I have to do something!
Stop!
Huh?
You must not fight
over me.
I beg you!
Please stop!
What're you saying?
Never mind and
just follow along with me.
Okay?
Huh?
I understand, Kagome.
Please, Hannabart Pekopon.
It's all my fault.
So please don't blame him.
Hanna....Pekopon?
Pierre, please go!
I cannot involve you
in this!
Good! Now all I do is make up
some lines to finish this!
No! I will not run!
Huh?!
Step away from Escargot!
Take your filthy hands
off her, Hannabart!
Let us fight a duel right now,
to see who is the one
that deserves Escargot!
Fine with me!
Huh?!
How did it turn out like this?!
This is....!
A demon!
So this is where you've
been hiding.
It's all over...
everyone will find out...
After I tried so hard...
- Wow! This is great!
- How'd they do that?
- Yay! Inuyasha!
- This is great! Right on!
N-No one knows yet.
Looks like our duel
has to be postponed.
Looks like you get a reprieve...
Prepare to die, demon!
What're you doing, Hojo?!
It's the REAL thing!
Inuya-I mean, Pekopon!
Do something!
You don't need to
say it!
Wind Scar!
W- Why'd you have to go
to that extreme?
Hah! How's that?!
- Let's run, Pekopon!
- Huh?
Please, take me away
right now!
Take me away beyond
that sky!
Hey...
Are you really okay?
- Just hurry it up!
- Okay!
Farewell, everyone!
I, Escargot, will be free
of all the burdens of the world
and will live happily
ever after!
Farewell....!
Bravo!
Amazing! Was this really done
by middle-schoolers?!
I can't wait for
next year's production!
You were great, Kagome!
The play was a huge success!
I was really worried there,
but I guess it turned
out okay.
What is this?
An earthquake?
No, I'm positive
it's a demon!
A demon?
If it can rattle the
earth like this,
this one's gonna
be more challenging.
You sense it?
Yup, I can see it.
The last demon is....
over there!
The roof?
Let's go, Kagome!
'Kay!
This is a demon?
Uh....
I think it's called a Yumenamazu.
Is it alive?
I guess we have our featured dish.
This was certainly
a great Cultural Festival.
Kagome, you sure worked hard.
Iron-Reaver, Soul-Stealer!
Boy, was this a long day....
I'm exhausted!
What're you saying?
This was nothing compared
to Naraku and the Band of Seven!
I wasn't talking about
the demons...
Anyway, you're all done here, right?
Well, yes....
- Then let's go back.
- Go where?
Where else?
We have to go back
and find the Sacred Jewel shards.
Sacred Jewel shards?
We can't let Naraku
keep having his way!
Right!
What took you?
I heard it.
It was very faint, but
I'm certain I heard it.
Still, it won't be easy
to lay your hands on it.
Don't dither....
or I'll kill you.
Tell me.
Where is the last shard?
The last shard....
is at the border of this
world and the netherworld.
At the border of this
world and the netherworld, you say?
A shrine is broken and the demon
sealed inside is reawakened.
Whenever he sees a pretty girl,
he asks her to bear his children
and kidnaps her!
Such a cruel thing to do!
Miroku, you should talk!
Young ladies, I promise
to protect you!
On the next Inuyasha:
"Chokyukai and the Abducted Bride"
I love pork cutlets,
but I refuse to become
a demon's bride!