Darkness and Light!
Into the chaos of
the Feudal Era,
the Sacred Jewel brings
a group of strangers together.
500 years across time,
their destinies are controlled by
the few remaining shards of the Jewel.
Feudal Fairy Tale:
Inuyasha!
According to a genealogy scroll
found at Hojo's house,
his ancestor, Akitoki Hojo,
had a wife
whose name was Kagome!
What? Could that mean me?!
The Sacred Jewel which is said
to grant one's every wish.
In order to search for the shards
of the shattered Sacred Jewel,
I began crossing between
the present and the feudal age
through the hidden well
in my family's shrine.
But at times, I return to
the present world
to attend classes like any normal
junior high-school student,
studying and doing my best
in tests.
None of my school friends
knows about my other life,
but I really don't think anyone
would believe me anyway.
Oh no!
I don't get it!
I don't understand it at all!
All right, time's up!
It's hopeless!
I was confident about history...!
Especially since it's on the feudal age.
What a shock!
Cheer up, Kagome.
You've been absent a lot lately.
It can't be helped.
I probably have to
take a make-up test.
You want me to take it
with you?
Oh, Kagome!
You're in school today!
Are you feeling better?
Hojo!
Hey, Kagome.
I found something amazing.
Huh? What's this?
It's a scroll of the
Hojo family tree.
It's so long!
And look!
By my ancestor, Akitoki Hojo,
who lived 500 years ago
during the feudal age....
Look at his wife's name.
Wife?
- Huh?!
- Is it for real?
See it?
It says, "Kagome"!
- No...!
- No way!
What a shock!
He's right! That's my name
on the Hojo family tree...
What a shock, that among
the Hojo ancestors
is someone named Kagome Hojo!
If Kagome breaks up with that
delinquent boyfriend of hers
and hooks up with Hojo,
her name'll be Kagome Hojo!
Maybe that's not just a
genealogy chart,
but a prophecy scroll.
Hojo might be thinking
just that.
What do you think, Kagome?
I'd better brush up
on history again.
Kagome isn't in the mood
to talk about it.
Oh yes.... I developed the pictures
I took at the culture festival.
Huh? Pictures?
See?
Wow, nice pictures!
I'll say!
Kagome looks so cute!
Oh no!
The real demon is also
in the picture!
Hey mister....
Leave all your belongings
and go!
Huh?
Defy us and you'll get hurt.
Give us all your money!
People will dislike you if
you're too bossy.
You men speak as though
you're robbers.
That's exactly what we are!
Stop acting so dense and
hand over the money!
Caught in a bind again?
Who the hell are you?!
You're....!
You're looking well, Akitoki!
Shippo and Inuyasha!
Thank you for coming
to my rescue.
Oh yes!
Here.
Pickled plums?
I'm told they're good for you.
Try one.
By the way, what're you
doing here?
Well, it's a long story....
but I need to ask something
of the priestess, Kaede.
What? Old Kaede?
You wanna ask her something?
Oh.... You're on a mission?
Yes.
There is something called Kenkon,
the Naginata of Heaven and Earth.
This naginata is a demonic weapon
which has a blade affixed to
either end.
A demonic weapon?
Recently, the Hojo family has
been plagued with misfortune.
And the source of the misfortune
is supposedly the blade
of this Naginata of Heaven and Earth.
Huh? This is....!
A demonic aura!
It looks so ominous!
Huh....?
T-This is not good.
Put it away!
Y-Yes!
Inuyasha!
Arghh! Snap out of it, Inuyasha!
Huh?!
What happened?
You were about to be possessed!
We were told that an exorcism
would be necessary
in order to disperse
the demonic aura.
But as you just saw,
the power of the blade
is too strong.
So it was decided to purify it
at Mt. Hakurei.
And I was chosen
to fulfill the mission.
But that mountain....
Yes.
Just recently, a natural disaster
caused the mountain to totally collapse
leaving not even a trace
of its former glory.
Hmm....
If the blade cannot be purified,
the Hojo family will continue
to be plagued with ill fortune.
And so, you came to me in search
of another solution.
Someone suggested that I seek
you out for advice.
It's that peak over yonder.
Deep in that mountain is
the sacred Shrine of Furai.
If you were to entrust
the blade to that shrine....
the demonic aura should
dissipate by itself.
The Shrine of Furai?
Around here, it is the holiest place.
But just what is
"deep in the mountain"?
That's hard to find.
A river flows to the east of the peak.
If you follow it upriver,
you will come upon Shoun Falls.
Furai Shrine is apparently
close to that.
Shoun Falls?
Please everyone, accompany me!
Huh?
What'd you say?
I was accosted by robbers earlier,
but ever since I've had possession
of that blade,
bad things continually happen
to me.
Please, help me!
Akitoki is my vassal!
It's a master's responsibility to
come to the aid of his servants.
Kagome will be returning
here soon.
Huh?! Kagome will come, too?!
Sis, are you sure
you have everything?
I'm taking my textbooks this time,
so I'll be able to study
over there, too.
I'm all ready.
Maybe this time, I'll say you
hit your head
and suffered amnesia.
Grandpa, amnesia is
a bit extreme....
Buyo....
I know! How about cat allergy?
Or you became paralyzed from
a voodoo doll that
was sent to us for
purification.
Sorry I'm late!
Kagome, here's your bento lunch.
It's so heavy!
You made so much!
You can share it with everyone.
Thanks, Mom.
I'll be on my way.
Take care now.
Hey, which one will it be?
Cat allergy or the voodoo doll?
Neither!
Kagome! Kagome!
I wish she was here!
And there!
You're Hojo's ancestor, Akitoki!
I'm so sorry. Are you all right?
Oh, it's nothing.
Here! The ninja food I promised.
Huh? Vietnamese flavor....?
I found some new products.
Where's Inuyasha?
He's sulking.
Huh?
He doesn't like the idea of
helping Akitoki and
delaying the search for
the Sacred Jewel shards.
He's so selfish!
Inuyasha!
Huh? What is it?
Are you sulking?
No I'm not!
He is sulking.
I heard the story from Old Kaede.
Hojo is in trouble.
We should help him.
And what about
the Sacred Jewel shards?!
What if Naraku gets
them first?
I understand that, but....
Because Mt. Hakurei
disintegrated,
Hojo can't carry out his mission.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
It's Naraku's fault that
the mountain collapsed.
But you can't just ignore
someone in trouble.
You're too nice to others.
Kagome is such a kind person.
Huh?
- Huh?
- Why you...!
Since Kagome asked, I'll take
you to the waterfall or shrine or whatever.
So get your business over with quickly.
He's such a hardhead!
Be careful, Kagome!
And I shall enjoy
your mother's cooking!
Looks delicious!
That's it?
Let's try going to
the foot of the mountain first.
Kirara, let's go.
It transformed!
Now, get on her back.
Huh? You mean me?
What about Kagome and
you others?
I'll ride on Inuyasha.
Miroku is pretty fast, too.
Quit dawdling!
I'll see you there.
T-They're so fast....
Now, let's get going, too.
We're off!
Huh?
Hang on tight.
O-Okay.
Hojo, are you okay?
Y-Yes!
Kagome's smile
is so cute...
Hojo's ancestor, huh?
The name, Kagome,
that was listed on
the family tree scroll
that Hojo showed me...
What if...
I couldn't return to
the modern age and
ended up marrying
Hojo here?
No way!
Huh? Look, Miroku,
a river!
Huh?
That must be the river that
flows east of the mountain.
Hey Akitoki....
Why didn't you think about
getting rid of that blade?
Then another family besides
ours would suffer misfortune.
I must have the blade purified.
That's all there is to it.
Hojo, you're quite manly,
aren't you?
You think so?
And this Inuyasha....
The guy's a wimp. He should
stop acting so brave.
- That wasn't necessary, Inuyasha.
- Are you all right?
Err.... Yes, I guess.
They're finally coming.
A teahouse!
Miroku, there's a teahouse!
Thank goodness for that.
Ohh....
What's the matter?
Oh! My sandals!
Both the thongs....!
This bodes ill....
Huh?
This blade brings so
much bad luck!
Aww man! Take a break?!
That's why humans are
such a pain to be with.
Well, don't judge us against
your brute strength.
We're made of delicate flesh.
Here you are.
Thank you!
These dumplings are delicious.
For you, too.
Oh, thank you!
Arghh! Hot!
Hojo!
Hold on.
Huh?
Do this....
Huh? It's cold!
There goes Kagome
with her ninja bag of tricks!
Kagome, what is that?
It's a cold compress.
It's just the thing to
cool your burn.
Oh yes! It's starting to
feel cool!
This is amazing!
Isn't it?
Hah!
Oh! A lunch box of goodies!
This omelet is delicious.
The simmered vegetables
are great, too.
I prefer the ninja food
you add hot water to-
Sit boy!
Well then, I shall try....
Aghh!
Wait! My rice ball!
Wait!
Huh?
This blade brings
such bad luck!
Just having it in your possession
brings misfortune, huh?
You saw what happened
just now.
Well, a lot of little mishaps
have been happening to you.
Aren't you making too
much of it?
No, this blade brings misfortune
to whoever possesses it.
A succession of small mishaps, huh?
I guess if they happen one
after another, it's hard to bear.
That blade is a demonic blade.
Humans shouldn't possess it.
He should just get
rid of it.
Not again!
Hojo is doing his best!
Even though he's weak and
gets airsick, he's doing his best.
Makes you want to help
and encourage him!
Why're you defending him
so much?
I am not.
Demon blades can only be
handled by demons,
or half-demons like me.
It's impossible for you guys!
Huh?
Humans shouldn't get involved!
You guys just don't understand!
H-Hey! Hey Inuyasha!
Here!
Health before a mission.
Eat, Akitoki.
Thank you, Shippo.
I accept with....
Huh?
Boulders!
They're coming right at us!
Hah! Leave 'em to me!
Who could have done that?
Huh?
I smell it!
The smell of explosives!
Explosives?
Look! Up in the sky!
Was that a bird?
It looked like a kite.
I've never seen a strange
kite like that.
It's coming again!
Hojo! Watch out!
Dammit!
You won't get away!
A sacred arrow!
Damn!
He got away.
He pulled up those huge boulders....?
Who was he anyway?
Miroku.... Do you think
he was after the blade?
During that last attack,
he targeted Akitoki.
So I'd guess, yes.
The blade brings misfortune....
And that's why I keep
telling you....
Just let 'em have it!
No, I will not.
If the enemy wants this blade,
then he must already
have the Kon blade.
The Kon blade?
The Naginata of Heaven and Earth,
or Kenkon, was so frighteningly powerful
that the blade was divided
into two blades, the Ken and Kon blades,
and sent away - one to the north
and one to the south.
And one of the blades was
entrusted to the Hojo family.
And what if the two blades
are joined?
Specific details weren't
passed down to us.
Huh?
Crows?
Master Inuyasha!
Old Myoga?!
How I've missed you,
Master Inuyasha!
What's up, Myoga?
Err.... Well....
Now that Mt. Hakurei
has disintegrated, Totosai said....
That holy mountain kept
many things sealed.
I fear that the Naginata of
Kenkon which was left by Kaijinbo
will appear again...
And he was quite worried.
Huh?
The Naginata of Kenkon....!
Was forged by the demon
Kaijinbo?!
And Master Inuyasha, if it's possible,
Totosai wants you to seal it.
That's why I came in
search of you.
Geez! Why me?!
Only he can do it.
And that's what he said to
tell you.
Hah!
Not "hah", Master Inuyasha.
The one after the blade is
the leader of the demon ninjas, Hoshiyomi.
Demon ninjas?
Exactly.
Demon ninjas are just that -
demons versed in the ninja ways.
And Hoshiyomi is the one who
made Kaijinbo forge the Naginata.
Sacred arrow?
Yes sir!
Interesting.
We'll reach Furai Shrine
tomorrow, Kagome.
Yes.
Huh?
Seems they haven't learned
their lesson!
They must be after
the Ken blade.
Hojo! This way! Hurry!
Hojo!
Hojo, are you all right?
Kagome!
Hojo, hang on!
K-Kagome!
Kagome! Akitoki!
Kagome! Kagome!
Kagome!
So you're Hoshiyomi, the one
after the Ken blade!
Why do you want it so badly?!
This doesn't concern you,
so there's no need to answer.
Fearsome Demon Ninjas
attack our group...
and Akitoki and I become
separated from the others.
I never imagined that just the two of us
would head towards Furai Shrine.
Oh? Just the two of us?! Wow!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Mountain of Demons: Survival of the Duo"
Now can this be called
a fortunate misfortune?