Can you kill them?
Yes, Master Naraku.
Inuyasha, Miroku and... Sango?
I made him forget.
I erased all his memories.
Bring me Tetsusaiga,
Inuyasha's sword.
And I will give Kohaku
eternal life.
What? What am I doing?
Sango, what's the matter?
Nothing... Couldn't sleep.
That's all.
I'm gonna kill him...
although I feel badly for you.
I already told you...
he is not Kohaku.
Kohaku... my kid brother...
could never slaughter
an entire village.
I will deal with him and Naraku
at the same time!
Is it that simple?
He looks exactly the same.
Can one hate and forget
so easily?
Don't underestimate me!
I am a Demon Slayer!
I don't fall for dirty tricks!
If I were in your position...
I probably couldn't do it.
Looks exactly the same...
So he can't hate or forget.
Inuyasha is speaking of Kikyo.
Inuyasha...
Be on your guard.
We are surrounded.
Kohaku!
Hey Miroku!
What're you doing?!
Your Wind Tunnel
isn't completely healed!
Yes... but...
Stop it, Miroku!
Don't hurry to death
for these small fish.
I just have to go and
get rid of their boss!
Go away, vermin!
You plan to fight me with
that level of skill?!
Finishing blow!
No! Don't kill him!
Damn!
I'm easy! Way too easy!
It's okay to kill 'im!
This is Naraku's trap!
I've got to kill him!
You're right.
I deserve to die.
What?!
I... I killed them all.
Father... our friends... the villagers...
I killed everyone.
That's why... I deserve to die.
Hey!
What're you doing?!
What're you up to?!
He's trying to extract
the Sacred Jewel fragment!
That's why he slashed
his own back...
Kohaku's life is sustained by...
the fragment of the Sacred Jewel
imbedded in his back.
If the fragment is removed,
Kohaku will die immediately!
Stop!
Huh?
Sango!
- Sango!
What're you doing?!
Sango!
Is he testing me?
Does he really believe that
I will take the Tetsusaiga to him?
I...
I... ?
Kirara!
Wait, Sango!
What're you doing?!
I have no other choice.
My only choice...
My true desire...
Let's go, Inuyasha!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Miroku, too?
How about it, Inuyasha?
I still smell it.
That boy... Kohaku's blood
is still here...
It still reeks of it.
Naraku is luring us to him.
My Wind Tunnel is sealed...
and the Tetsusaiga was stolen.
Who cares!
I still have my fists!
This castle...
Kohaku.
Kohaku!
First, put down the Hiraikotsu.
Naraku...
Good work, Sango.
You brought me the Tetsusaiga,
Inuyasha's sword, as promised.
Let me see Kohaku.
Only then will I hand over
this sword.
Naraku! Turn Kohaku back
to his former self!
Right now!
Killing me won't help.
You should know that already.
It's all the fault of
the Sacred Jewel.
Demons desiring the Sacred Jewel
attacked your village.
Your father's death...
that your brother's soul
now wanders...
are all because of the
curse of the Sacred Jewel.
Stop this nonsense!
You killed my father
and comrades!
Just because you
covet the stupid Jewel...
you did it all!
People die because of the
power of the Sacred Jewel...
and people live because
of its power.
Do not despise the
Sacred Jewel so much.
Kohaku was revived because
of the Jewel's power.
The promise was to exchange
Kohaku with the sword.
What will you do?
You despicable!
What promise?!
This is my answer!
You are...
the Young Lord of this castle!
Kagewaki was a fine lord.
He gave the slayers
proper burials.
Oh yes... I was the one who
ordered your care.
Did you kill him?
Kagewaki Hitomi...
But now, that is who I am...
the lord of this castle.
Damn you!
Die!
Kirara!
What's wrong?!
My miasma is stronger
than any poison gas.
Not even you, Sango,
can withstand it.
W-what?!
How about it?
Will you serve me in this castle
along with Kohaku?
I remember Kagewaki telling you...
"Return to the castle."
Don't make me laugh.
My only goal in life is to
destroy you!
I will avenge my father
and comrades!
I will kill you!
Kohaku, come!
Good bye... Sister.
Kohaku!
- The castle!
- Is this it?
This is where Naraku
is hiding!
Sango's voice!
Damn it!
Kohaku...
Kohaku!
Snap out of it!
Yes, Sango!
Kill him...
Kill your brother with
your own hands!
And then pray...
that you want to continue
living in this world...
that you alone want to be saved!
When you kill Kohaku...
and you are bathed in his blood...
the Sacred Jewel will glow brighter
with the power of the Dark.
The more sullied it is...
the more beautifully
the Sacred Jewel glows.
Kill you?
How could I kill you?
I...
can't kill...
Kohaku...
Sister!
- Sango!
Kirara!
Are you all right?!
He made her brother
do this?!
This is terrible...
How could he?!
Naraku... where are you?!
Come on out!
The brother who killed
his father... and comrades.
His sister says she
cannot kill him.
She loves her brother
more dearly than her own life.
I do not understand how
that can be.
Kohaku...
will regain consciousness
in a little while...
Inuyasha...
this is exactly what
happened with you!
Fifty years ago, with you...
What?!
He tried to make Sango
hate her brother...
so that she would kill him.
Then the Sacred Jewel in his back
would become more evil.
The same trick he used to make
Kikyo and Inuyasha...
hate each other,
and fight!
I can't forgive him!
I'll never forgive this!
Kikyo died so that the
Sacred Jewel would remain dormant.
In the same way, Sango refused
to fight her brother.
Naraku's such a fool!
There's no way Sango
would have done it.
Sango is a kind sister
who loves her brother.
Huh?!
A miasma!
Foolish mortals!
Drown in this sea of miasma!
Father said you're
getting better and better.
Really?
Really!
It's the first time
Father praised me!
I feel sorta awkward.
Sango, you mustn't move yet.
Sango, keep still!
I gotta lot of things to
say to you!
So don't you dare die!
It's my fault...
But...
I know!
Naraku has the Sacred
Jewel fragment!
There!
Naraku!
Prepare to die!
W- what?!
Naraku, you are sooo...
despicable!
This woman...
What is her power?
With hardly any effort...
she can purge the miasma...
the poison vapors...
This power belonged to Kikyo...!
It can't be...!
I won't let you go
even if you beg forgiveness!
That is none other than
Kikyo's sacred arrow!
That means the girl is!
She did it!
She purged the miasma
and located Naraku!
Kagome!
Do not let Kirara go!
Kohaku!
Kohaku!!
The castle disappeared!
It was a phantom castle.
Inuyasha!
Naraku got away?
Yes...
I don't see any
Sacred Jewel fragment.
I see...
I'm sorry.
I couldn't finish him off.
No need to apologize.
Without you, we'd all
be dead by now.
Kagome...
I've never seen you
so awesome before.
Inuyasha... we must
destroy Naraku.
No matter how hard it is.
We must work together...
No, Sango!
You mustn't move!
Sango!
Please stop her!
Sango intends to go somewhere.
Where in the world
do you intend to go?
I'm sorry.
I cannot stay with you any longer.
Sango...
we all know that you were
being blackmailed by Naraku...
over your brother.
That's why!
I will betray you again!
As long as Naraku has
Kohaku under his control!
Sango!
Sango, you intend to go
after Naraku alone?
That's the only way...
But that's...
We'll all save your brother.
He's not an opponent
one person can handle.
Okay? First, we must tend
to your wounds.
You... why?!
Will you stop yapping?
Just stay together!
'Cause you fight well!
Inuyasha...
See? Even Inuyasha, whose
sword you stole so easily, agrees.
Okay? So no problem.
You make me sound like
a half-wit.
No, you're just generous.
Sango, do you dislike us?
It's all my fault that this
happened...
and I may end up doing
something like this again...
and yet...
Poor Sango... How hard
it must've been for her.
It'll be all right, Sango.
We're with you now.
There's an herb that
will cure Kirara...
who was stricken with poison
when she bit into Naraku.
Inuyasha and I go in search
of this herb garden...
and we come upon a huge
demon working in the field.
He seems strong...
and he looks fierce...
but this demon has
very kind eyes.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Jinenji, Kind Yet Sad"
Don't miss it!