Half-demon Inuyasha covets
the power of the Sacred Jewel.
He was able to take possession
of Tetsusaiga, his father's sword...
and defeat Sesshomaru
in battle.
But this only makes him
more determined...
to become a full-fledged demon.
Priestess Kaede warns me
to make sure that...
Inuyasha doesn't find all
the fragments and disappear.
Not to worry!
Inuyasha may have
Tetsusaiga...
but I also have a
potent weapon.
Inuyasha, sit!
Oh, this feels so good!
Sparkling clear water
and clean, fresh air!
There's something to be said
about this age, after all!
It's been three days since
we left the village.
Maybe there aren't any fragments
of the Sacred Jewel left...
in Musashi country.
Huh?
Say, are you listening?!
Huh? Oh, you may be right.
But my, my...
the firm, luscious flesh
of young women...
Hey you!
I'm just going to
take a peek.
Stop! You'll only get whacked!
See? Master Inuyasha,
you can't resist either...
Huh?!
What?! I'm not peeking!
Get my clothes back!
A finger whistle?
Here, here... Hiyoshimaru.
Good job.
Th-this... isn't something
to eat!
Hey!
Please return my clothes!
Wh-who are you?!
You look suspicious!
That's our line!
"Potato
Chips"
You really must've
been hungry.
Want some tea?
Uh-huh...
Want something to eat
too, Inuyasha?
No thanks.
If you'd help me eat,
I'd have less to carry.
Well, why'd you bring so much stuff
each time you go back to the well?
Well, I have clothes to change into,
homework...
Listen here...
Mmmm... The dried potatoes
were delicious.
My thanks, woman.
My name is Kagome.
He's Inuyasha.
And...
This is Myoga the Flea.
Who the heck are they... ?
You said you had become
separated from your comrades.
Are you from a
high-ranking family?
For personal reasons, I cannot
reveal my lineage.
But call me Nobunaga.
Nobunaga?!
Not!
Please let me shake your hand!
And...
Please give me your autograph!
Autograph?
Oh, your name...
Please sign your full name.
Why're you so excited?
He's Nobunaga Oda!!
Don't you know him?
He's soooo famous!
His full name is
not Nobunaga Oda.
Nobunaga Amari?
No! Aren't you
Nobunaga Oda?!
I belong to the Takeda Clan
in the land of Kai.
Don't lump me with that
cretin from Owari!
Cretin?
I mean "fool"?
If you're not Nobunaga ODA,
why didn't you say so earlier?!
I got excited for nothing.
Ahem...
Thanks for the food.
I have an important mission,
so I'll take my leave.
Fare thee well.
Hey, that's...
the ledge.
Such a simpleton...
but he's not Nobunaga Oda.
Why are all the girls in the
domain being taken there?
I heard that none of the girls summoned
to the castle have ever returned.
Wh-what?
So the rumors are true!
Why do we have to keep
this guy company?
Well... He doesn't seem like
someone who can manage.
Look, we have to look for
the Sacred Jewel...
Just between us, I heard that
the lord of the castle...
has been possessed
by a demon.
What?!
Princess Tsuyu...
Have you adjusted to
castle life?
Yes, I have naught for want.
I am glad to hear that.
Err... My lord?
Yes?
I understand that you have
summoned...
many of the young village women
to the castle...
Where are you keeping them?
You do not need to know!
Please pardon me...
for being so intrusive!
I'm so frightened.
I wish I could go back
to the land of Kai.
No mistake about it...
This place reeks with the
smell of evil.
I'm sure we'll find a
Sacred Jewel fragment.
Okay, let's take a leap
up there!
Kagome, hop on my back.
'Kay.
Hey, why're you jumping
on my back?!
I have business at
this castle, too.
Then climb up yourself.
Just take him, too.
Please!
Oh well!
Hang on tight!
Such lax security...
Everyone's asleep.
Master Inuyasha, please
be careful.
They're under a hypnotic sleep.
Probably everyone here
in the castle.
Princess!
Princess Tsuyu!
Where are you?!
Nobunaga is here to
rescue you!
Princess! Princess Tsuyu!
Is it safe for him to
yell like that?
Well, everyone's under
a hypnotic sleep.
With this much noise...
I'm sure the demon will
come seeking us out.
Princess!
Princess Tsuyu!
Are you all right?!
Princess, what has
become of you?!
Say, Nobunaga...
Isn't the princess you're
looking for... over here?
Huh?
Oh!
Such a beautiful princess!
We must awaken her!
I'll taste her blood!
Princess!
Nobunaga?
Why are you here?
Princess Tsuyu...
you recognize me?
How could I forget you?
You are my childhood friend
who was ever so kind to me.
Oh... Thank you for those words!
I thought you had long forgotten a
lowly vassal like me.
You'd fall into the pond...
or slip on horse dung...
and always made me laugh.
Say, Inuyasha...
Do you think Nobunaga is in
love with the princess?
What a silly question!
I wish I could return
to those days!
Princess!
My lord husband began to
act strange...
shortly after I came here
as his bride.
He fell at the edge of
the pond in the garden...
and ran a terrible fever.
He completely changed...
Almost like he was another being.
Nobunaga, what am I to do?!
You have no choice!
You must return with me
to the land of Kai.
Even your father has heard of
this lord's derangement.
In fact, he ordered me to
come for you.
My father's orders?
Even had he not ordered it...
I would have...
Nobunaga...
Princess Tsuyu, I...
On top of your head...
Hiyoshimaru!
Hmm... It's come.
Let's go, Kagome.
Uh-huh.
Intruders!
So there you are,
you demon!
Let us...
see your true form!
A toad?!
My lord!
Princess!
Hang on!
I see it... the Sacred Jewel!
For someone with the Jewel,
he doesn't look strong.
Beware of him,
Master Inuyasha.
This demon toad is
300 years old...
the Toad of Tsukumo.
He is a formidable foe!
Hah! I'll crush him
in one blow!
Oh no! Toxic vapors!
Kagome, do not inhale it!
Okay... When'd you get here?
Princess Tsuyu!
Get back, Monster!
Fool! Just what can you do,
mortal?!
Nobunaga!
Princess!
Don't move!
You're badly wounded!
Never mind me!
Save the princess!
Nobunaga... You truly love
the princess, don't you?
How could you tell?!
Don't you know it's
pretty obvious?
That disgusting toad!
He won't get away!
I'm going on ahead!
Halt!
Hey!
Princess Tsuyu... I like you...
Let me have you!
Found you, you repulsive toad!
It's too late...
Wh-what are these?!
Princess Tsuyu!
The rumors were true...
Just like toad spawn.
The Tsukumo toad demon seals
the souls of young women...
until they mature, then eats them.
He used the magical powers
of the Sacred Jewel...
to possess the clan lord,
as well as the domain.
He intends... He intends to
devour Princess Tsuyu?!
Why you...!
A miasma!
Back away!
Die, Toad Demon!
You did it!
Ohh! You're controlling
the Tetsusaiga!
Well, he is rescuing
a mortal.
I'll use Tetsusaiga to
slit your belly...
and dig out the
Sacred Jewel!
I'll die!
Spirits!
Revival!
His wound has healed!
Why that!
Keep stabbing me!
And for each wound,
I'll eat a fresh spirit!
Princess!
Princess Tsuyu!
Nobunaga!
I now have no regrets
in life!
What're you doing to
my princess!?
Keep your mouth shut!
Princess Tsuyu!
I...
Is this all my doing?
Huh? It's too late to
act innocent!
That voice...
It's the voice of my
kind lord husband!
I see!
The real lord still lives
inside the toad!
I know it!
What a frightening thing...
I have done!
Although I was possessed
by a toad demon...
my heart was still human.
But lately, even my heart...
Kill me!
Huh?
Otherwise, I will end up
devouring Princess Tsuyu!
My lord!
I beg you!
Slay me now!
Pretty noble words...
I gotta hand it to you,
lord!
'Kay then, as you say!
Hold it, Inuyasha!
What about the real lord?!
Yes!
He still has a human heart!
Will you stop yapping?!
The REAL lord is asking
me to slay him!
This is no time
for silly sentimentality!
Stop!
Sheathe your sword, Inuyasha!
Inside this monster, the real lord's
heart still beats!
Why you...!
If you don't move,
you'll die, too!
I can't die.
Then move!
I can't do that either!
I cannot allow you to kill the monster
while the lord's heart beats!
Even if he weren't a lord,
I despise the taking of life!
Nobunaga...
This may sound naive considering
the times in which we live...
Laugh at me if you like.
But I still... still!
All right!
I won't lift another finger.
You guys can settle this.
Humph!
Inuyasha...
Thanks for sparing me.
Nobunaga!
The toad demon is back!
Inuyasha!
If I help, the lord will die.
Princess Tsuyu!
Kagome... Pay me no heed.
You must take the princess
and escape!
All right! Let's go!
Nobunaga!
Move!
Now do you see?
Do NOT kill him!
You!
Princess...
Isn't there something
we can do?!
Though a demon,
he's still just toad.
He should have an
aversion to heat.
Heat?
Throw some hot
water on him.
Hot water?
Then the toad will be in
agony and...
the real lord will be
released.
And just how do we
get hot water?!
Stop!
He's coming!
Something hot!
I know, fire!
Is there something like
a large torch?
Huh?
Hiyoshimaru!
When'd you appear?!
I'll gobble both of you!
Fire! Good work, Hiyoshimaru!
It's too small.
Wait up, repulsive toad!
Inuyasha!
Kagome, the time for
niceties is over!
I'll gonna get 'im!
Niceties?
I know... hairspray!
It'll work...
this will drive the toad out!
I'm gonna get 'im!
Sit!
Wh-whaa!
It worked!
Inuyasha, get the fragment!
I don't need you
to tell me that!
Die!
Inuyasha!
Huh?
Well done!
The lord is alive!
You waited until the toad
was driven out! Good work!
No, I...
Just let him believe that.
Nobunaga...
Princess Tsuyu!
Nobunaga!
Thank you for protecting
my lord husband!
Princess Tsuyu!
My lord, you are your
old self once more.
Forgive me for
all that has happened.
He seems like a
very kind lord.
Hah!
The toad demon's spell
was broken...
and all the women have
been saved.
I'm so glad!
Umm...
Please cheer up,
Nobunaga.
I knew it... He IS a
first-class fool!
He was almost killed...
yet he saved the life
of his bitter rival in love!
That's true...
I am the world's
biggest fool.
Oh well... But thanks to you,
many were saved.
Why not keep it at that?
Okay! I'm feeling quite chipper now!
I'm off!
Off to where?
Nobunaga, that's...
the ledge!
He really is a fool.
Beyond this well is
the age of the warring states.
Perhaps, I'll get to meet
some real-life warlords...
like Nobunaga, Hideyoshi
and leyasu!
I know my history grades
have gone up...
but these days, I don't go anywhere
without my autograph book!
I think a camera would
be useful, too!
But I don't think I'll want
to take a look...
at photos of demons and things.
Now here's a cute demon!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Shippo and the Thunder Brothers".
Don't miss it!