It comes!
From the forest!
Slayer! Please!
A Sacred Jewel fragment, after all.
Slayer, what's that?
The cause of the centipede
going berserk.
Please call me if you need me.
What about your fee?
That's okay... I'll take this instead.
Besides, the Sacred Jewel originally
came from my province.
So many stars.
I wonder which is more...
the number of stars or
the number of Jewel fragments?
The road ahead is long.
Not really.
Why?!
That Naraku has the same goal
and is gathering the fragments.
Simply put, he's saving us work.
Make him gather lots and lots,
then take them all from him.
Hah! How's that for strategy?!
Inuyasha...
The more Sacred Jewel fragments
he gathers...
the stronger Naraku becomes!
Then it'll be too late!
We must hurry and gather
lots ourselves.
Cripes! Even a kid like me
knows that!
You were really born without
a brain!
What?! Say that again!
Inuyasha, what will you do when
you gather all the fragments?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm gonna become a
full-fledged demon!
Ohh... Is that all?
Can't do a thing when you're weak.
If there's a guy you
don't care for...
what's the sense if you lose to him?
However, Inuyasha...
When you become a true demon
with the sacred jewel...
will you be able to remain
as you are?
W-what do you mean?
Have you ever seen anyone
using the Sacred Jewel fragments...
to do good deeds?
This is what I believe...
Those who seek the Sacred Jewel,
lose their hearts in the process.
Hah!
I don't remember ever saying...
that I want to become a
good demon.
However... you want to
protect Kagome.
And that's why you want power.
But when you use the Jewel's
power to become a demon...
you may just end up
devouring Shippo and Kagome.
Me, too?!
What about you, Miroku?
I would have run away
long before that.
Stupid!
All the demons I fought
until now...
were bad from the start.
That's all it is!
But I'm different!
Inuyasha...
What?! A woman had a
Jewel fragment?!
When was this?
When?! Answer me!
Another demon!
We must hire the Slayer!
A giant centipede!
Me?! A centipede?!
A Demon Slayer?
Hmm...
Someone actually makes a living
slaying demons?
And this Slayer gathers
the Sacred Jewel fragments?
Uh-huh... She says that this
Sacred Whatever...
originally appeared in her province.
Yeah...
Did you know this, Inuyasha?
Err... No.
When I first came across
the Sacred Jewel...
it was already in Kikyo's
possession.
I never even thought about...
how the Jewel was made or
where it came from.
Welcome back, Sango.
Hello.
What was your prey?
A giant centipede.
It's not much, but I brought back
the legs and skin.
You can use it for an armor.
Good girl, Kirara.
Have you been good?
Welcome home, Sister!
Hi, Kohaku.
Father... I mean the Chief
wants to see you.
I see... So you found a
fragment of the Sacred Jewel.
Good work, Sango.
Let's see...
Father, will that be enough to suppress
the evil within the Jewel?
Probably not.
I doubt it.
About fifty years ago, it was
supposedly turned over...
to a priestess with
unusual powers for purification.
But even that priestess became...
embroiled in a fight
over the Jewel and died.
All we can do is...
until someone is found who has
the power to purify the Jewel...
we must gather the fragments
and keep watch over them.
The power to purify the Jewel...?
Rest a bit. We'll be needing you
very shortly.
Okay.
Kohaku, make ready too.
Huh? Me?
You are already eleven.
It's time you got some
real battle experience.
Sister...
Hmm?
Do demons really spit out
toxins and fire?
Sometimes.
I see...
Kohaku... Are you afraid?
N-no...
Don't worry!
We slay large serpents
and spiders.
Father always says...
the demons to fear most...
are the ones pretending
to be humans.
And if such demons get a
hold of the Jewel...
terrible things would happen.
Welcome, Slayers.
Nightly, a giant spider terrorizes
this castle...
and has eaten several of
our people.
Will you be able to destroy it?
Leave it to me.
I have chosen the most skilled ones
to assist.
Oh?
Most skilled perhaps...
but a young woman... and you
even brought a child?
These two are my daughter and son.
In the province, they are
the top two fighters.
You can witness their
skill tonight.
Heard that?
Do your best, Kohaku.
F-father... you liar.
It's coming! My lord!
Slayer! There it is!
Yes!
Let's go!
The demon is here again?
That demon is also the cause of
your long illness.
But Slayers have been summoned.
We should see the last of
that beast tonight.
Then you must hurry and
get well.
Slayers?
Surround it!
Kohaku!
Take a deep breath and go, Kohaku!
Come on!
All right! Got it!
Hiraikotsu!
Awesome, Sister!
Sango is the best in the province.
Wow!
She slayed the giant spider
in one sweep!
Let's finish this up!
Crash its head!
Okay, me too!
It may've been huge,
but it was such easy prey.
It was too easy...
This spider... I don't like it...
Why?
Kohaku... why did you
slay Father and?!
Stop, Kohaku!
Don't you recognize me?!
Hey! Slayer?!
What happened?!
Let them be...
This is very entertaining.
What happened, Kohaku?!
The thread... of the spider...
Why you!
Is this your doing?!
I'll kill you!
These siblings have both gone mad!
- Kill them!
- Yes!
Damn!
S-sister!
Kohaku?!
I...
Sister!
Kohaku!
Cast your arrows at these crazed two!
K-kohaku!
S-sister! I'm scared!
It's all right. I'm with...
The siblings have made up.
So nice, so nice...
Lord!
Young Lord, what have you done?!
He is not Father.
Take a good look.
T-this is...
A demon!
I had been thinking that
Father was acting differently.
He had been possessed
by the demon.
It's too bad about those Slayers.
Bury them in a corner
of the garden.
Yes, sire!
This is not good...
no one knows where the
Village of the Demon Slayers is.
All they can say is
it's in the mountain...
Shaddup!
Just find them!
Inuyasha... You intend to steal
the Jewel fragments from them?
Of course!
Hopefully, we won't be
slayed first.
I'll say! Those people are
supposed to be pros.
But I'm curious, too...
about how the Sacred Jewel
came to be.
They claim that the Sacred Jewel
first appeared in their province.
I'm sure Inuyasha wants to
know about this, too.
What is it? This ominous wind...
Something is approaching...
Lots of them.
A hoard of demons!
What is this awful feeling?
This is really weird!
She's right... I'm starting to
feel worse and worse.
Death is in the air!
They're going to attack something!
Let's go after them!
The sibling Slayers...
They were still so young.
Poor things.
Damn!
I... will... NOT... die!
Slayer!
You are still alive?
You seem to have avenged
your long-harbored grudge.
After I told you that the Slayers
were not at this fortress...
you're going to attack me?
Such fools...
That's!
A fortress?
The demons were headed...
Here!
Wait!
T-this is!
A battlefield of demons?
No mistake...
This is the village of the
Demon Slayers.
What's the matter, Kagome?
I don't sense the presence
of Jewel fragments.
Meaning... we're too late?
If we go after them now,
we can catch up!
First, let's bury the dead.
Otherwise it'd be too cruel.
You're right.
There's something!
A demon survivor!
That voice... belongs to Inuyasha.
- Huh?
- It spoke!
Back off, Kirara.
These people are not enemies.
- W-wha!
- How cute!
It has been such a long time.
Old Myoga!
What're you doing here?!
Oh dear...
You know him?
He's Inuyasha's vassal...
or tries to be.
Precisely... this is the secret province
of the Demon Slayers.
For generations, the people of
this village...
have trained and worked
to get rid of demons.
Well then, they must've been
hated by the demons.
However...
to be attacked now of all times.
A number of the warriors had been
summoned to a castle...
and this village was left
with few to protect it.
I have this bad feeling.
I wonder if those who went to
the castle are safe?
I'm glad... at least you are alive.
You there, Slayer!
Answer the young Lord!
Old one, that's enough.
B-but...
Your name is Sango, right?
I'm sorry...
About your father and brother...
and your comrades.
Why? How did this happen?
Young Lord...
- Naraku...
- Yes...
As you ordered,
I rushed to the village to...
notify them of this terrible development.
But the village had been annihilated.
How unfortunate...
I had so many questions to ask
the villagers.
Old Myoga... you must know
something at least?
Huh?
You mean about the Sacred Jewel?
Myoga, were you perhaps looking
into the Sacred Jewel yourself?
Well... I had been bothered
for some time...
about just what this
Sacred Jewel was.
After all, anyone who had been
involved with the Sacred Jewel...
had come upon some misfortune.
I followed the rumors about
the Sacred Jewel...
and found myself here in this village.
However, one thing worried me.
During my journey, a white baboon
slipping in and out of sight.
A white baboon?!
It's Naraku! He must be near!
Tell me in detail...
what you saw at the
Slayers' village.
The slain bodies of
countless villagers...
and the half-demon who
attacked them...
His name is Inuyasha.
Inuyasha seeks the power of
the Sacred Jewel...
to turn himself into a
full-fledged demon.
Sacred Jewel?
He must have believed that he
would find the Jewel at the village...
and thus attacked it.
Sango!
Give me my weapon!
I will get the one who
attacked my village...
I will kill this half-demon
Inuyasha!
Sango is told that her village was
attacked by Inuyasha...
and attacks him
with the last of her strength!
She is in no condition to fight...
but she throws her
giant boomerang-like weapon!
A Sacred Jewel fragment glows
eerily on her back!
It's all a scheme by you-know-who!
Naraku transforms!
Inuyasha challenges him
with the Tetsusaiga!
Next, "Naraku's Insidious Plot".
Look forward to it!