Isn't there a way to destroy him?!
Why, that!
I'm getting used to
this body!
Inuyasha! Above you!
Inuyasha!
What's the matter, Inuyasha?
Can't move?
Shaddup!
Why, you!
Inuyasha!
This time, I'll shred you
into bits!
Inuyasha!
Now come.
Why, you!
Don't act too cocky!
Wind Scar!
Damn... not dead yet?
This will never end.
Huh? What's that?
A spider.
He's transforming again.
What's his body
made of, anyway?
Naraku is basically
a collection of demons
bonded into one
by Onigumo the bandit.
If Muso was created from
Naraku's flesh...
Then at that same time, several
of those demons were released?
Is he different from us?
Is he something special?
Even to Naraku?
But why is Muso able
to regenerate? Is he immortal?
Why, you!
I told you it's useless.
You bastard!
I can't watch! Isn't there
anything we can do?!
Inuyasha is getting tired.
Which is to be expected from
using the Wind Scar so many times.
He's also withstood Muso's
vicious attacks.
If this continues...
Look at you, Inuyasha!
Had enough already?
Inuyasha, use the Backlash Wave!
Use the Backlash Wave
to blow him to bits!
Shaddup! If I thought it'd work,
I'd've used it long ago!
What? You can't use it?
The Backlash Wave utilizes the
enemy's ghostly aura.
Muso doesn't have that,
so it's useless.
Wind Scar is the answer!
Inuyasha!
Miroku!
Use Wind Scar one more time
to blow Muso away!
No need to tell me that!
Wind Scar!
Well?!
Damn! Not again!
Even if I keep at it,
this is hopeless!
Inuyasha!
Muso's tentacles accumulate
towards the spider marks.
What marks?
Look... you can see
the spider scar.
Muso gathers his parts
towards that scar to regenerate.
That scar was pulsating.
Most probably,
that is where his heart is.
I get it.
It's worth a try to aim for that.
It's useless, Inuyasha.
You're starting to breathe
pretty hard.
The track of the Wind Scar that
leads to Muso...
I'll use it to make sure
it strikes straight on...
Die!
... into his heart!
Go!
Fujin!
Kagura!
Did it work?
No. Kagura used her Fujin
to divert my Wind Scar
from striking Muso's heart.
But now it's clear at least.
Muso's weakness is his heart.
Damn!
And he's not gonna hide it either.
After'em, Miroku!
Sango, protect Kagome
and the others.
Understood!
Don't worry.
I'll protect them!
Why would the Bandit Onigumo
come alive now?
I don't think Muso is just another
one of Naraku's creations.
I agree. Muso has Onigumo's heart.
But don't you think it's strange?
Huh?
Why would Naraku let Muso...
Naraku tried to get rid of
Onigumo's heart...
because it still has feelings
for Kikyo.
Then he would try to destroy
Kikyo's dead spirit.
For Naraku, Onigumo was
a liability.
Isn't that why he cast Onigumo
out of his body?
Yet Naraku is using Kagura and
the toxic wasps to protect Muso.
What's going on?
He's created others before,
then cast them out after using them.
Does it mean that Naraku still
needs Onigumo?
Damn that Inuyasha!
I almost killed him, too.
Where am I anyway?
Onigumo... No, I should
call you Muso.
Imagine confronting each
other like this.
You're... Naraku?
Are you Naraku?!
Did you enjoy the outside world
after fifty years' absence?
Fifty years?
Did you say fifty years?!
Muso, come back inside me
once more.
You've gotta be joking.
Don't think I want you inside me
any longer than necessary.
However, you were released
too early.
Too early?!
How dare you say that after
keeping me locked up for fifty years!
It must have felt like
a second to you.
I remember now!
You're the one who killed Kikyo
fifty years ago!
Your perverted greed
lured the demons.
And those demons which
devoured your flesh
wanted to kill Kikyo.
Wasn't that you!?
That was not me.
I am Naraku.
You should know that.
Shut up!
All I wanted was to
make Kikyo mine!
Damn!
Kikyo was resurrected.
Looking exactly the same
as before.
What?
Although, she's not
exactly the same.
Kikyo is alive?
Want her?
Where is she?
Where is Kikyo?!
I cannot grant your wish.
Come back, Muso.
As if I would!
This time, I'll make Kikyo mine!
Give it up.
You persistent bastard!
Just leave me alone!
I cannot.
Muso is trying to escape
from Naraku's clutches?
Is he planning to defy Naraku?
I get it!
Naraku doesn't control
Muso's life!
So that's the difference
between him and me.
You will return to my body.
What's going on, Naraku?!
Inuyasha...
You have no use for Onigumo's
human heart.
So you dug him out of your flesh
and cast him out!
So why're you trying to
take him back?
I thought Muso would be able
to kill you, but I was wrong.
That's why I'm taking him back.
That's all.
I don't think so.
Something very precious got mixed in
and was released with Muso.
Otherwise, you wouldn't try
to take back
Onigumo's heart which
you purposely threw out.
Oh? Inuyasha, you actually
use that brain of yours sometimes?
What will you do?
I can destroy Muso anytime.
I'll take care of you first!
Is he serious?
Damn!
Why, you!
Die!
What're you doing, Kagura?
Go after Muso.
Don't let him get away.
Muso and I were both
created from Naraku's flesh.
I act according
to Naraku's wishes.
But Muso is escaping...
That guy!
On guard!
Inuyasha!
You're late!
W-Why is Naraku here?!
He's trying to take Muso back.
I'll bet releasing Muso made
you weak, huh?
Isn't that so, Naraku?!
Die!
Don't underestimate me, Inuyasha.
You're nothing...
Muso!
It can't be! He killed Naraku?!
He did it! He killed Naraku!
Fool! You didn't think
I'd let you go!
My arm's being absorbed!
You saved me trouble, Muso.
I need you.
Why, you!
My body won't listen to me!
Lemme go! Lemme go!
Is that my fate, too?
If I defy him?
Damn! Lemme see Kikyo!
Kikyo! Kikyo!
Kikyo!
This bitterness... This greed.
You must give it up, Muso.
Kikyo is just like you.
Made of clay and bones.
And her soul just a phantom
of the past.
He absorbed Muso!
I need Onigumo as a link
for my body.
Your guess was quite accurate.
Link?
Then... let me ask you.
Once more, you've
swallowed Onigumo's heart.
Does that make you
a half-demon?
Why ask me that?
Awhile back, the barrier around
your castle weakened.
Inuyasha, Koga...
Anyone with a keen scent
could find it.
That wasn't on purpose.
What is Miroku trying
to find out?
I see, Priest.
You think that even I, Naraku,
have periods of weakness?
Like all half-demons.
I know that your powers had
weakened that time.
W-What?!
But when that occurs is a
half-demon's deepest secret.
Inuyasha, what about you?
What?!
Do you, like other half-demons,
lose your powers
and hide in fear of your enemies
during such times?
W-Why, you!
Judging from what Naraku just said,
Kagura hasn't told him that Inuyasha's
night of weakness is during the new moon.
Monk...
As you surmised, I have periods
when I cannot move.
However, I can choose my time,
by my own will.
What?!
As if you can do
such a thing!
You, borne from a human
and a demon,
and I, Naraku, are
vastly different.
Don't you agree, Kagura?
Naraku's appearance that time...
It looked like he was
reconstructing his body.
During that time,
I experiment.
And what is strong,
I make stronger.
And what is weak,
I cast out and become even stronger.
He can reconstruct his own body?
You!
No mistake, I am a half-demon
right now.
But I don't lose my powers
and cower in fear...
like some other pitiful half-demons!
Hah! Well, you sure
rambled on and on.
I'll make you shut up now!
Die!
W-What?!
A barrier?
It won't hold me back!
Wind Scar!
The Wind Scar doesn't work.
Naraku's barriers haven't been
as strong as this!
I told you.
I continue to grow in power.
Get back, Inuyasha!
A miasma!
Damn!
It seems Naraku was
speaking the truth.
I turn into a weak human
on the night of the new moon.
But Naraku's different?
Yes...
If Naraku is able to reconstruct
himself and get stronger...
This is very bad.
Huh? What an eerie wind.
Naraku...
You don't have to tell me.
Um, Kikyo...
Don't worry.
It's nothing.
What?!
Naraku's barrier withstood
the Wind Scar?
Hah!
It's certain that Naraku is
becoming stronger.
On top of that,
he's a half-demon,
but he's different from Inuyasha
who loses his powers during the new moon.
Instead, Naraku says he can
choose his day.
So we can't tell when Naraku's
powers will be weakened?
Yes.
If we only knew when Naraku
was powerless...
I thought we'd be able
to defeat him.
Hah! Why's everyone so serious?
We know that Naraku does
have a night of weakness.
l just have to get stronger
than him, is all.
Just leave it to me!
Inuyasha? Sometimes,
you're very positive.
Sometimes?!
Does he think
he's always positive?
I dunno.
Oh, no. I forgot my things!
Things?
By the well.
I have to go get them.
Wow!
What's the matter?
It's so beautiful!
Nothing special about stars.
In the other dimension,
you never see it this pretty.
Really?
I know.
I am Kikyo, and yet not Kikyo.
That's why I resisted.
Yet, why?
Why does my heart...
yearn so much?
Inuyasha...
Which does my heart wish for?
Listen, listen, Shippo!
Inuyasha headed out alone
to see Old Totosai!
Totosai is the one who
forged Tetsusaiga!
Inuyasha wants to learn a technique
to break through Naraku's barrier.
Huh?! Inuyasha's a fool!
It won't be so easy!
I know.
Old Totosai... he'll make it
impossible for Inuyasha!
Next on Inuyasha:
"Totosai's Rigid Training!
What?! Inuyasha has a fellow
trainee who's his superior?!