Huh?!
W-Wha...!
So you're up?
W-Why you!
So you're a half-demon, huh?
Damn! If you're gonna kill me,
do it quick!
A half-demon's power is good nourishment
for the Human-faced Fruit Tree.
Thanks to you, it'll bear
the Fruit of Longevity more quickly.
Forget it!
So hurry and get your demon
powers back.
Yeah, struggle more!
If the thorns pierce your skin,
it'll make it that much easier
to extract your juices.
Damn!
That's...
the bottle in which Kagome kept
the Shikon Jewel Shards!
Hey you!
Where's the owner of the
Sacred Jewel Shards?!
Owner?
There ain't such a person.
I found these.
Don't kid around!
You stole them from Kagome!
Kagome?
The girl who had
the Sacred Jewel Shards!
Hmm... a girl?
What great news!
Somewhere in this house
is a girl.
The Tree of Human-faced Fruit loves
women, too. The younger, the better.
Kagome... I'll be there!
Don't get caught until
I come for you!
I found the shards around here.
Hah! So you're in my box garden?
Okay!
Kagome, I'm ready over here!
All right.
Miroku!
I'm ready anytime.
What're they up to?
Fox fire!
It worked, Miroku!
Wind Tunnel!
W-What's this?!
It's coming!
We did it! It worked!
There she is!
Good, good!
A young girl...
A bit dirty, but sure to please
the human-faced tree.
Ow!
So this is the sage, Tokajin?
This has been a fine day.
An unusual half-demon and a young girl...
all in one day.
By tomorrow, I should have
the Fruit of Longevity.
Did you see Inuyasha?
Hey!
Is Inuyasha all right?
I'll never forgive you if
he's not!
Kagome is amazing!
She's talking to him
and she's not afraid at all.
Comes from experience.
Hey! Say something!
Pipe down!
Go to sleep for a while.
K-Kagome!
Shucks! My hands are covered
with dirt now!
Damn! I can't stand it!
This is why a human body
is so!
Damn! I've lost too much blood.
I'm getting dizzy.
Still alive, huh, half-demon?
Kagome's clothes!
She couldn't be!
Where's Kagome...
Where's the girl?!
Because you broke my gourd,
extracting nourishment
has become very bothersome.
Extract nourishment?!
Why that look?
W-What'd you do with Kagome?!
So you were in love with that
dirt-covered girl?
You'll see her soon...
inside my belly.
Both of you will become the
Fruit of Longevity,
and will be eaten by me!
Unforgivable!
It's useless.
Those thorny roots cannot
be torn apart.
Inuyasha!
Being this small, I don't know how
effective my Wind Tunnel will be...
But here goes!
Kagome!
Wait, Inuyasha!
Kagome is in the cellar.
Why're you?!
What's this sweet smell?
W-Where am I?!
Kagome!
Inuyasha!
She's alive!
Inuyasha, are you all right?
Hah! These are mere scratches.
It's torn up, but wear it.
Okay... Thanks.
Inuyasha!
He's a mortal right now,
yet he tried to do so much.
Err... we're here, too.
You won't get away.
Inuyasha seems to
be in bad shape.
His injuries are pretty serious.
We really shouldn't move him.
I think we can get out.
Can you walk, Inuyasha?
Out? Is it morning yet?
No, it's pitch dark.
Y-You don't intend to fight?!
'Course!
You can't!
Until your powers return,
we have to keep running!
I must protect everyone
until day breaks!
We can't jump...
...Can we?
Plus we have to get Miroku
and Shippo back to normal size.
Let's do this...
No!
I didn't say anything yet.
You want me to escape alone, right?
No way!
Is someone there?
Did you escape from
the box garden?
Who are you, old man?
I'm ashamed to admit it...
I was Tokajin's teacher.
Then you're a sage, too?
Why you...!
Why'd you make a guy like
him a sage?!
Inuyasha!
I didn't make him a sage.
It was the Tree of
Human-faced Fruit.
Tree of Human-faced Fruit?
It was about a month ago...
Oh boy... I can't stand this
training day in and day out!
Isn't there some way I can
become a sage right away?
What's this?
Hah! Nothing to eat.
Oh, a Sacred Jewel Shard!
Thank you!
Who said that?!
I am the Tree of Human-faced Fruit.
You there... Do you wish for
a sage's power?
Uh-huh...
Then eat the fruit of the
Human-faced Fruit Tree.
Eat!
Then we shall both possess
the art of Sagery!
Yes! Swallow the seed, too!
And you shall have power...
a sage's power!
However...
When one eats
the Human-faced Fruit,
you become a slave to
the Tree of the Human-faced Fruit.
Then Tokajin obeyed the order
to turn me into fertilizer for the tree,
so that it would bear
the Fruit of Longevity.
But Master Sage, why are
you in that condition?
Just the fruit isn't enough
for longevity.
The fruit must be soaked and
made into a potion.
And only I know the process.
That's why I let him live
like that!
You guys...
So this is where you escaped to.
The power of the shards is increasing!
Tokajin is no longer human.
Please slay him!
Yes, I'm no longer human!
Humans are covered with mud
and work, then grow old, then die!
My ma and pa both lived and
died like that!
I refuse to live such a
weak, senseless life!
You're not strong at all!
You sacrifice others, just so
you can have longevity!
No way you're strong!
Shut up!
I'm strong!
That's why I'll take advantage
of the weak!
Don't you even understand that?!
Watch out!
Inuyasha!
The Tree of Human-faced Fruit
made me strong.
And since I got the Sacred Jewel Shards,
I've become invincible!
And I'll have eternal life!
And turn weaklings like you
into fertilizer.
You're!
Stop, Kagome.
Inuyasha... Don't move!
He wouldn't understand your logic.
I'm a half-demon.
I know only too well how weak
mortals are...
And I understand his desire
to be strong!
However...
I'm still disgusted by you!
Huh?! You dare lecture me?
In that condition?
I ain't got...
...any words for you!
Before the Jewel Shards melt into
this punk's body...
Inuyasha!
Human-faced Fruit!
Take a swallow of that potion!
Potion?
Tokajin made it... An imitation
of the secret longevity potion.
But it's effective enough to
heal surface wounds.
But wouldn't drinking that make him
a slave to the Tree of Human-faced Fruit?
No, you just can't eat the fruit.
Now... if you want to be saved,
drink it.
Drink it.
It'll be more fun
if you had more spunk.
Forget it!
The Human-faced Fruit Tree takes
humans as fertilizer!
Who'd drink this disgusting stuff!?
Don't put me in the same class as you!
Inuyasha!
Half-demon, you'll regret
not drinking the potion.
Hah! I don't need to drink that stuff...
to beat the hell outta you!
Fool!
Hah! What's the matter?
Are you only talk?
Damn!
Inuyasha!
Ohh! He can't do a thing with
a mortal body!
And with my size, the Wind Tunnel
won't do much good either.
I'll save you right now!
It's useless. A bow and arrow won't
kill Tokajin.
I will kill him... without fail!
I'll just aim for the
Shikon Jewel Shards!
The glow of exorcism...
around the bow and arrow!
Just who is this girl!
Tokajin!
W-What... happened?!
As if the bow and arrow of
a vanquished soldier would work on me!
K- Kagome...
Don't get... too cocky!
Why you!
Please slay Tokajin...
This is my way of making amends.
He turned into a bow and arrow!
The Old Sage... He squeezed out
his last ounce of power!
Kagome!
I'll tear you into bits!
I can see it through
his back!
The glow of the Jewel Shards!
That glow is my target!
The Sacred Jewel Shards!
Thank you... Old Sage!
Woman!
How dare you!
Get down, Kagome!
Inuyasha!
Kagome!
Serves you right!
With a mortal's body,
you'll die, too.
Maybe so...
But...
At least, if Kagome is alive...
Inuyasha!
Ohh! Human-faced Fruit Tree!
You're rescuing me!
No! I just don't want to lose
precious nourishment!
W-What?!
Now I've attained it!
The freedom of movement!
I have ample shards of
the Sacred Jewel now.
And I am all-powerful!
Now then, half-demon...
become one with me!
Damn... Daybreak at last!
I never thought I'd get
a half-demon as well!
Everything will go as planned now!
No way!
Prepare to die, Tokajin!
Or should I say...
Tree of the Human-faced Fruit!
Just try, half-demon!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
Awright!
Yes! We're back to normal!
Tokajin probably died,
undoing his spells.
Those men in the box garden
have probably reverted back, too.
Tokajin is dead?
Then Inuyasha, too?!
N-No!
When Inuyasha fell, it was
still dark...
Dawn hadn't broken yet.
He probably... died...
Inuyasha is dead!
No!
Inuyasha is alive!
But he was hurt badly...
And no mortal could survive a
fall from a cliff like this!
Don't cry, Shippo.
Let us pray for his repose.
Miroku...
Inuyasha had no regrets.
He wanted to save you,
even if it cost him his life.
To save me?
As if that makes me happy!
He had no demon power,
yet he acted so foolishly!
Inuyasha was stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid Inuyasha!
What good is it
if he's dead?!
What am I to do from now?!
Yes, he was foolish!
Yes, he was!
Inuyasha was the biggest fool
in the world!
Hey!
You guys...
Just because I'm not around...
Call me "fool" and
"stupid," will ya!?
You're alive, Inuyasha!
I knew you wouldn't
die so easily.
Thank goodness!
I ain't so easy to kill!
Stop thinking rubbish!
Did you say "rubbish"?!
Of course we worried!
W-Wha...!
We knew you were
overtaxing yourself!
But I'm alive, so what's the big deal?!
Stop crying!
I'm not crying!
You are!
I'm not!
- Am not!
- You are!
Quiet! Sit!
He's dead.
Ahh, Sango...
The three days you've been gone
seem like a lifetime.
What?!
Someone who wants to be an apprentice
appeared at the village?
They want Sango to teach them
to become Demon Slayers?
What?! They're two beautiful sisters?
I envy her! Err... I mean,
seems like hard work.
Next on Inuyasha:
"The Beautiful Sister Apprentices"
Are you okay, Sango?
Owwee!
C'mon it's just your butt.