You pesky moth!
I don't remember a thing
while I was transformed.
Tetsusaiga suppresses the demon
blood that flows through him.
Tetsusaiga is merely a dog's fang.
At that moment,
Tetsusaiga was broken...
awakening the demon blood
inside Inuyasha.
Once awakened, the demon blood will
try to protect itself and retransform.
That's why you must not let go
of Tetsusaiga.
Otherwise, when your life is in danger,
you will transform, Inuyasha.
The next time I transform...
I might use these claws
and tear you apart...
Kagome...
Hey, you there, Totosai?
Huh?
We need to talk.
Hah, I was expecting you
around now.
Geez!
Where did Inuyasha go anyway?
Kagome, don't you have any ideas?
Uh-uh...
Inuyasha no doubt wants to make
Tetsusaiga lighter.
Maybe he's training somewhere.
Think so? I don't think
Inuyasha would be that diligent.
Shippo!
In any case, we'll just have to search
every place we can think of.
Yeah...
I haven't told the others...
but Inuyasha is going through
a lot of suffering now.
That's why I think it's better
to leave him alone...
but I can't just sit still
and wait.
Inuyasha...
I'm so disappointed in you, Inuyasha.
How can you let Tetsusaiga's weight
hinder you still?
Shaddup!
That's why I'm asking you
for a way to make it lighter!
There must be something!
Why don't you work it out yourself?
I'm in a hurry!
I don't want to transform anymore.
Hmm...
Just 'cuz I can't master Tetsusaiga...
I was cornered by that
petty demon...
and I lost my senses.
I never want that to happen again.
It gave me the creeps.
Hmmm...
Hey!
Master Inuyasha,
I'm glad you're fine...
Owweee... I was worried
about you.
Hah!
You've been hiding out here!
Hey, Old Myoga!
How dare you keep it
from me!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Don't act innocent!
The connection between Tetsusaiga
and my transformation!
Kagome told me...
that Tetsusaiga serves to suppress
my demon blood.
Hmm... that Kagome!
I made her promise
not to say a thing.
Hah!
So now I know...
but unless I'm strong,
my sword can be taken from me.
I have to master Tetsusaiga,
or else...
Hmm... so you've put some
thought into this.
And you've had enough
of transformations.
Yeah...
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
Huh?
Inuyasha, go and kill Ryukotsusei.
Ryukotsusei?
Ryu... You said Ryukotsusei?
Ryukotsusei, Inuyasha...
is the demon your father
battled and put under seal.
Inuyasha...why do you think this
new Tetsusaiga is so heavy?
It is because your fang
embedded in the blade...
has not yet reached
the power of your father's fang.
In other words, if I destroy the
demon my father fought...
I'll surpass my father?
Now listen, Master Inuyasha,
to "destroy"...
as Ryukotsusei still remains
under seal...
all you have to do is
stab its heart.
What? I don't have to fight him?
Of course not!
Even your father barely
managed to seal it.
He wasn't able to finish it off.
Damn... and I'm supposed to kill it
while it's asleep?
If you keep complaining,
I will not show you the way!
Who're you talking to?
- Err... well... I...
- Me?
- Hey!
- Don't!
Interesting, Kanna.
You... Kagura... Goshinki...
Juromaru... Kageromaru...
None of you were able to
kill Inuyasha.
Let's test this Ryukotsusei.
Old Myoga, aren't we there yet?
Just a little further.
You'll be able to see it soon.
Damn!
Old man!
Huh?
What do you all want?
We're looking for Inuyasha.
Do you know his whereabouts?
Inuyasha...
Hmm... Inuyasha?
Inuyasha, huh?
It involves Tetsusaiga, so we thought
he'd come to you.
What'll I do?
You know, don't you?
Where is he?!
Oh boy...
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Inuyasha has gone to
the Valley of Ryukotsusei.
The Valley of Ryukotsusei?
Master Inuyasha, over there!
So that's... Ryukotsusei.
Correct.
And look at the seal...
where your father's claw
has immobilized him.
Ryukotsusei's heart lies beneath it.
Naraku!
But, Master Totosai...
if there was such a way, why didn't you
tell it to him earlier?
That'd have been too easy.
If it's too easy, he won't learn.
But Inuyasha has suffered enough.
Kagome...
He agonized over it,
then decided to come to you.
That's true.
Even if they were bandits,
he did kill human beings.
Hmm... that's why I told him.
If he felt nothing after killing humans,
he has no right to wield Tetsusaiga.
Naraku! What're you up to?!
Huh?!
The claw that seals Ryukotsusei!
Listen, Ryukotsusei.
The one over there is the son of the
hated man who put you under seal.
Fight him to your heart's content.
N-No! Let's run for it, Master Inuyasha!
What are you blubbering?
I didn't like the idea of prickling
someone held under a seal!
I'll face him head on
and make Tetsusaiga lighter!
Come at me!
Little man! You say you'll kill
me, Ryukotsusei?
Not a bad idea for entertainment.
I'll have some fun with you.
"Fun"?!
No! It's hopeless!
Such an eyesore!
Hmm... Ryukotsusei isn't bad at all.
It should be easy for him
to kill Inuyasha.
What a good show.
I'll enjoy this.
A mere demon puppet.
It didn't even serve as
a warm-up.
So you were going after Naraku
from the start?
Hey, little man...
I hope you'll give me
more fun than that.
Be more than happy to,
Ryukotsusei!
W-what's he doing?!
What's this strong evil aura?
W-what happened?!
Old man...
could it mean Inuyasha is?
That fool!
He's awakened Ryukotsusei.
I've never felt such
a powerful evil aura.
Does that mean Inuyasha is fighting
such a formidable foe?
Kagome!
Let's go, too!
Hey, wait!
Oh boy... what a bad day
this is.
Come at me, little man!
I'll have my fun with you.
Stop talking so big!
The scar left by my father's claw...
If I pierce through it...
Tetsusaiga will become lighter!
Tetsusaiga...couldn't pierce it!
Just because it's for fun, doesn't mean
you have to go easy on me.
My body is harder than steel.
M-Master Inuyasha!
This is hopeless!
Shaddup! I just got started.
I already told you...
even your father barely managed to
put this Ryukotsusei under seal!
Not only that, the wound inflicted
upon him during the battle...
ultimately killed him.
W-what?
Oh... so he died.
Little man... you're his son, huh?
Could it be you came to avenge him
with that silly sword?
Hah! Unfortunately, I don't even
remember the old man's face!
As if I'd care about avenging him!
Hey!
You've been saved countless times
by Tetsusaiga, your father's heirloom!
Shaddup!
Ungrateful son!
I'll have nothing to do with you!
Running away, are you?!
Damn!
The reason why this new Tetsusaiga
is so heavy...
is because my fang,
used to forge it...
isn't up to par in strength
with my father's.
Yes...
I must somehow
destroy Ryukotsusei...
and surpass my father!
Such an ominous evil aura!
This is bad.
But how did Ryukotsusei's seal
get broken?
As if I'd know...
But what a problem this poses.
Huh?
If Ryukotsusei acts up once more...
this plain of Musashi will become
a field of ashes.
l-Is he that frightening a demon?
Uh-huh.
How can we defeat such a demon?
There's only one way to defeat
the reawakened Ryukotsusei.
He must use the Backlash Wave.
Backlash Wave?
What is that?
It is the ultimate technique
of Tetsusaiga.
You mean it's even stronger
than the Wind Scar?
The Wind Scar is a trick
for a beginner.
But...
Inuyasha can barely wield Tetsusaiga,
not to mention the Wind Scar!
Let alone the ultimate technique...
I guess it's impossible.
Ouch.
Master Myoga...
did you abandon Inuyasha again?
Kagome!
Inuyasha!
Stay alive!
So weak.
You're not worth tormenting.
It won't relieve my anger towards
your father for putting me under seal.
Do you not understand...
with such an inferior sword...
you cannot kill me?!
Tetsusaiga!
You must not part with Tetsusaiga.
When your life is in danger,
you will transform, Inuyasha.
Tetsusaiga...
I see them! Over there!
So easy...
Dead, already.
Huh?
W-what's with him?
Inuyasha!
Inuyasha isn't holding Tetsusaiga!
K-Kagome...
Inuyasha transforms into a demon.
If we stay here, he may come
after us as well.
What? Totosai?
You say we have to fall back?
I will not abandon Inuyasha!
He's trying all by himself so hard
to discover his true power.
Just then, Tetsusaiga begins
to pulsate.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Backlash Wave:
Tetsusaiga's Ultimate Technique"
Don't miss it!