Here we come!
It's the start of Inuyasha!
We're going to gatherall the shards
of the Sacred Jewel...
And I'll destroy Naraku
with my Tetsusaiga!
Kikyo... who was resurrected
into a body made of bones and earth
and continues to exist through
souls of the dead.
The bond she shared with Inuyasha
remains strong...
I understand that, but...
Miroku, Sango, Shippo and Kirara...
travel back in time!
To a Feudal Fairytale!
Inuyasha!
Help...
Someone... Help me!
Ayoung child?
So late at night?
You there!
Damn!
Sit!
What're you doing, Kagome?!
Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit!
Stupid Inuyasha!
Err... Kagome?
Where're you going?
Awalk! For a walk!
Kagome's so scary!
I have to be strong!
That Inuyasha!
I made it sweet just so
he could eat it, too!
I'm so mad!
I'll never cook for him again!
Maybe I was a bit harsh?
This feeling!
It's a Sacred Jewel shard!
I'm sure of it!
It's very faint.
But I feel the Sacred Jewel shard!
What's with her anyway?
What are you saying?
I'll be very blunt.
You are to blame, Inuyasha!
Why?
All I did was speak the truth.
That's where you messed up!
Kagome did herbest to cook.
How could you say such
a cruel thing!
Well then... Were you able
to eat that stuff?!
It's quite good.
- Avery distinct flavor.
- Uh-huh.
You guys are strange!
How could you eat stuff that
makes yourtongue burn?!
It's from in here.
The shard seems
pure enough.
Help...
Someone... help...
I have no choice but
to go in and see formyself.
Kikyo...
The shard of the Sacred Jewel...
she has one.
It seems you have the power
of a priestess, too.
Uh... What're you doing in
a place like this?
Is something wrong with you?
Could it be your soul spheres?
Where are the Soul Collectors?
Why're you collapsed in here
like this?
You sure talk a lot like always.
In any case, let's get out of here.
It's useless...
We're in the belly of
the Priestess Eater.
Priestess Eater?
It's the name of the demon
who devours priestesses
and absorbs their powers.
It puts up a barrier on the outside
and allows no one but
a priestess inside.
So we're inside the belly
of this demon?
A priestess' powers have
no effect in here.
It's impossible to escape.
That's!
But it looks like an
ordinary cave.
It's useless to attempt anything.
Are you kidding?!
I'm not willing to die in a place like this!
Let's go!
So which way should we go?
He's in a bad mood.
You should justgo and say
you're sorry.
Shaddup!
I REFUSE to apologize!
This girl... just what does
she intend to do?
Oh boy... why'd this have to happen?!
On top of that, why'd I have to
get stuck with Kikyo?!
Umm... Doing fine, you know.
Oh, not me. I meant Inuyasha.
He's always saying things
to make people mad,
but he's doing okay.
ljust had a fight with him earlier.
I guess when he was with you,
such things neverhappened, huh?
Stupid me! What am I saying?
Why must I say things like that
to Kikyo?
Well because...
Kikyo and Inuyasha were...
Huh?! Hey!
Inuyasha...
I will destroy Naraku!
So you don't have to fight anymore.
I will protect you!
Inuyasha!
Kikyo...
Oh dear... I'm having such
bad luck today.
Are you all right?
Why did this happen?
You are quite amazing.
Normally, a priestess wouldn't be able
to move.
Meaning I'm not normal?
Leave me!
Huh?
I am a dead person anyway.
Ratherthan being burdened
by someone like me,
you have a better chance of living
by going on alone.
In orderto escape from here,
you must destroy the heart which
you'll find deeper in the cave.
I can't do that...
I don't know about our chances.
But don't orderme around!
I will notgive up!
So you cannotgive up
so easily!
You?
I can hear something!
But Kagome is very late.
Maybe something happened?
I think you should go
and get her, Inuyasha!
Shaddup!
Who'd go afterthat!
Acting so proud.
She's right, Inuyasha.
In this world, you must
learn to accept things with grace.
Be honest with yourself.
It's also a problem if you're
toohonest.
Absolutely.
Those were just practice shots.
Take that! And that!
T-Thank you!
We are going to survive this!
Listen up!
I'm notgoing to look for Kagome!
I'm goin' for a walk! S'all!
I feel the last of my souls
starting to fade.
We must hurry!
Hurry! We must make haste!
Why does this girl?
So warm... this living body through which
blood flows.
Is this Kagome's strength?
Inuyasha must be so worried.
I really don't think so.
We just had an argument
and he probably doesn't
know about ourpredicament.
If we're to escape from here,
we have to do it
on our own strength.
Kikyo, hang in there
for a bit longer.
Kagome!
This is?
The central core of the cave.
Then...
What is it?
It's coming.
If you destroy the heart of the demon,
the barrierwill disappear.
That's... the heart?
Then there's no time to waste.
Let's destroy it and
get out of here!
It's too much even for Kagome...
W-Why?
I told you...
A priestess' power and her
arrows are useless against this demon.
T-That's!
What's that?!
How gruesome!
R-Run!
Huh?
It's too dangerous to
stay... here...
The path!
Run! It's over if you're sealed in here!
No! I will NOT leave you behind!
Kagome!
Isn't there something?!
Something?!
My arrows are useless against it...
Then... I must use something else!
I know!
If I shoot these into the heart...
Darn it!
There's no way I can retrieve
the shards!
I'm borrowing this!
Here I come, Demon!
I did it!
What?!
The Sacred Jewel shard
didn't work?!
The shards...
Give me the remaining shards...
Huh? But...
Hurry!
All right!
Kikyo!
Give me your hand!
Pray...
But what?
Believe in me...
A-All right.
The shards have become one!
I get it!
Even if one shard isn't
strong enough...
three shards combined are!
There's only one chance.
Aim well!
Go!
U-Umm...
What's wrong?
Hurry and go.
Why?
Why didn't you give up?
That moment... did you believe in me?
You're very talkative for a change.
Even I don't know the answer
to yourquestion.
Then why did you save me,
a dead person?
Because if you're gone,
someone would be very sad.
If you're gone, too.
Inuyasha...
You came for me?
Hurry, let's go!
Umm... Inuyasha...
Hey Kagome...
do you know Sesshomaru?
Sesshomaru is Inuyasha's
older brother.
Inuyasha's on bad terms with
Sesshomaru
who wields a powerful
sword named Tokijin.
He's extremely strong and
a bit cold-hearted.
Cold-hearted?
When Inuyasha and Koga fight,
they'd neverget to
the point of death.
But Sesshomaru wouldn't hesitate
to kill.
Next on Inuyasha:
"Koga and Sesshomaru:
A Dangerous Encounter"
This is bad! Koga will...
Get killed!