Customers will be here soon.
Can we get this over with?
Customers?
Ha! Nobody's coming!
Nobody wants to eat at this shit hole.
It's fine.
Everybody needs to eat.
Anyway, do you have my money?
You better not be a single yen short.
If you don't have it all,
know that you can't run away from me.
I'll ruin your life.
Fifty million yen, got it?
$43,9887 USD
Too bad, huh!
What'd you expect, lending to the poor?
The Restaurant of Murderous Intent
I'll hide her here for now.
I'll move her to the mountains at night.
You deserve this.
Who has fifty million yen?
Look at this fucking place...
A shitty guitar and an old record player.
All this country music shit?
It's not even popular here.
No wonder she needed her money.
Gah! There're rats here!
Fuck!
Yo!
Let's take a break and grab a cup of coffee.
Good idea. Let's stop here.
I dunno about this place. Looks closed.
But the sign says they're open.
Whatever.
Shit! If they come in now...
Oh, that place over there looks nicer.
You're right. Wanna go there?
Ah, that one's closed!
That's it then. We'll get our coffee here.
Really? This place?
Hi! How's it goin'?
Oh, something smells good here.
Welcome!
Please, seat yourself!
This place is actually pretty cool.
Geez!
What're you doing, Kindaichi?
My bad, old man.
I'm sorry for that scare, master.
S-Sure...
As long as you're not hurt.
Master, are you the only one here?
Y-Yes, that's right.
I can't afford anyone else.
Hey, old man. Do you smell something?
Now that you mention it...
I think I can smell some blood.
No, actually, until now I was preparing a bird.
The scent of blood's still lingering in the store.
Ah, so you're cooking a bird right now?
Stay away!
Lemme see.
T-This meat--
What about it?
Is it...?
H-He knows!?
Rib roast?
Eh?
That's high quality beef!
It sure is tasty...
And it smells so good.
What's with this guy?
This reminds me of a mystery.
This guy used frozen meat as a murder weapon.
I remember that.
Then he tried to cook it and feed it to the detective.
That's right. What an idiot.
Just who are these guys?
Are you ready to order?
Ah, sorry, I forgot.
We'll take two cups of the house blend.
I bet it's delicious!
I have a good feeling about this place.
Very well.
Are you alright, master?
A-Ah, yes. I'm fine.
I've only ever made instant coffee before.
Am I supposed to put the coffee powder in the tea strainer?
Whatever.
That's got to be too much!
It's so dark...
Hold on...
If I give them some shitty coffee, maybe they'll leave?
Sorry for the wait.
It smells really good!
Seriously?
No need for milk or sugar.
Very funny.
No good? It's not like anyone could drink that.
That's right. Hurry up and leave.
Old man? You alright? Old man?
Incredible!
This is the true taste of bitterness!
Way too freakin' bitter.
Hey, does he have no taste buds?
How could he drink that without dying?
What's with these two?
What a strange pairing.
They don't seem like family, or student and teacher...
Brothers? Couldn't be... friends?
Yes, Division One, Inspector Kenmochi here.
Division One = Homicide
Inspector!?
And he's the one in charge of homicide!
What? A woman was murdered?
He's got me!
You already made the arrest?
And you already have a full confession?
There was a threat?
It's not about me!
Looks like my day off's over.
No worries.
But I'm starting to get hungry.
Do you wanna eat something here?
Good idea.
The coffee was so good, we should grab lunch.
Master! Menu!
Why the hell won't they leave?
Alright! I'll have the special sautéed bird and rice.
Ah, actually, that's--
What? Weren't you preparing bird earlier?
That's for someone with a dinner reservation.
I can only make you beef or curry right now.
Then I'll have the curry...
I'll take the sautéed beef!
Coming right up.
Curry and beef... they're getting all the spices!
Hey, master!
Yes...?
Where's the toilet?
T-The t-toilet is...
Aha, there it is!
Please me more careful when you stand!
That was a close one!
Hey, master?
Yes, what now?
There's no TP.
Sorry, all out.
Eh! Seriously?
So sorry.
Whatever.
Check it out! They're actually stacked to the ceiling in here!
You should remember this sort of thing.
Yeah, you're right.
What was he planning to do without toilet paper?
Hello, is anyone here?
It's Ishihara, the cleaner.
I've finished laundering your uniform.
Ah, thank you very much.
That's your uniform?
I knew you wouldn't cook in a shirt like that.
Lucky it didn't get dirty.
Yes, it's a good thing it's arrived.
Ah, that's better!
Huh?
He's...
So you're like this...?
How is it? Looks good, right?
I-I've no choice but to endure this humiliation.
Sorry for the wait.
So much curry!
But there's not much meat...
Superb! This is the perfect blend of spices.
Master, you're amazing!
It really is good!
Hey old man, we should get dessert too!
Yeah, good idea.
Master, can we get the cold watermelon and petal cookies? Oh, and more coffee.
Coming right up.
They're ordering more...
So good!
It was delicious.
I hope the dessert's as good.
Thank you very much.
Just what's with these guys?
That's a lot of records.
Think they're all country?
How nostalgic. Reminds me of the good ol' days.
Hey, master!
It says on here that you'll play requests.
I'm requesting.
You want me to play the guitar?
Why'd that woman have something so unnecessary!?
Hold it, Kindaichi!
I chose this place, so I get the first request!
Eh? But I already asked!
No, it's mine!
I can't play any instruments!
I'm never gonna get outta here.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
What's wrong, master?
I cut my finger on the broken dish.
I can't play the guitar now.
I'm so sorry.
Master, we should treat that immediately. Where's your first aid box?
Ah, no, it's not that bad!
For this kind of injury, cellophane tape is the best.
See?
Really? I've never heard of that.
It's true. I saw it on TV.
What the?
Why's the bench filled with these?
That's actually where I store my vegetables.
Geez, when you yelled like that, I thought something else was gonna come out.
Me too.
Like maybe a body.
Very funny.
Well, then, here's the watermelon.
Here's your watermelon and petal cookies.
Finally!
These petal cookies are great!
It was a long battle...
You can't buy anything else.
Hurry up and go home.
This watermelon is so cold. It's delicious.
I'm so full. It's about time we left.
Master, check please.
Yes, sir.
That'll be ¥2,000.
¥2,000 = $17.62 US
¥2,000? Come on.
That's not enough for this level of service.
No, it's really alright.
I just ask that you come back.
Don't worry about it.
We were pretty lucky today to have found this place.
Come again!
Just a sec, old man.
Didn't you forget something?
I forgot something?
I've got my cell, wallet, and police notebook.
What did I forget?
You forgot...
to investigate the murder here.
What?
And I've already solved the mystery.
You're not really this shop's master.
Hey, Kindaichi.
You had a dispute with the real master.
That was right before we arrived.
You had no choice but to pretend to be the master.
Seriously?
Furthermore, the victim is hidden somewhere in the shop!
The real master is probably a woman, considering that frilly apron.
The master, rather mama-san, is quite short.
Probably about 155cm.
155cm = 5'1"
And this place is so messy...
So what if it is?
That exposed you.
For instance, when you ran into that stepladder.
You're pretty tall. Only short people need a stepladder.
That stepladder would only be used by mama-san.
That stepladder isn't the only evidence that you aren't the master.
You didn't know where the toilet paper was.
To avoid playing the guitar, you hurt your finger on purpose.
Also...
the knife and fork!
When you set the table, you put the knife on the left and fork on the right.
S-so what?
The knife and fork should be switched.
You know, I thought something was off.
Right.
I'm certain they're reversed. Miyuki told me.
A real restaurant master wouldn't make such a basic mistake.
Hey, you!
Wait! Wait!
I really am the master!
Just where is this imaginary mama-san?
You already told me.
You gave the hint while cooking.
The watermelon you served for dessert was in here.
Looking at it got me thinking.
The menu said it was cold watermelon.
It would be strange if it was cold.
And it was when it was served.
You're right.
There can only be one explanation.
Until recently, that watermelon must've been in the fridge.
Not just the watermelon, but all the vegetables in this bench.
They're cold.
You were nervous when I almost knocked over this bench.
That's because you filled it with the contents of the fridge.
In other words, you swapped the contents of the fridge and the bench.
Then inside the fridge...
The victim.
Hello! Delivery!
Asshole!
Nice one!
I've got a black belt.
Old man! She's alive!
Really?
Call an ambulance!
Right!
Hello? This is inspector--
By the way, when'd you start suspecting that guy?
When he hit the stepladder.
Oh?
And I was convinced by the calendar.
The calendar?
Yeah, just look around.
I knew something was up when I saw the calendar.
Hey old man, can't you see it?
I have no clue...
It's just a calendar.
Ha!
See how the holidays are marked with flowers?
The 15th is Respect the Aged Day.
It's on the 3rd monday in September since 2003.
The 23rd is Autumnal Equinox Day.
But there is no holiday on September 10.
So why is it marked?
Is there any reason?
When mama-san was attacked, she was probably cutting cookies.
Cookies?
My mom does the same thing.
You knead the flour and sugar,
then you cut out the shapes and bake them in the oven.
But if you do it right on the cutting board,
it'll get stuck and won't really work.
So first you need to put down paper.
That mama-san used this calendar for that.
Isn't that kinda gross?
It's fine if they're for yourself.
She was attacked while making cookies.
When mama-san was struck, she collapsed onto the counter.
That's how this hint came to be.
Because of the flower shape of the cookies.
Mama-san's blood then passed through the hole, staining the calendar.
And the result was this red flower mark on September 10.
Earlier, I saved one of these cookies to try and match it up.
See, a perfect fit.
What're the odds the bloodstain would be in the perfect spot!
With this hint, I knew there was a case here.
And, the reason why he had to hang up the calendar.
More blood.
Hey, you can't--
Who cares!
That guy didn't know what this was.
Mama-san had taken down the calendar,
because she was planning to replace it with this.
I get it.
She was just gonna use the calendar as parchment paper.
Hold on! Where's the weapon?
Ah, about that...
how to put it...
I didn't...
You did...
That fucker!
I'll flip that asshole another two or three times!
Hi, guys.
Did you solve the case?
Hajime-chan, good job!
It's thanks to the old man for treating me.
Apparently he was an assistant professor.
He wanted to marry a company president's daughter, but he had troubles with mama-san.
So how'd you end up here?
It's the usual story.
We were looking for elite coffee, but this place stunk.
Huh? The coffee was fantastic.
Old man...
That reminds me! There's a nearby shop that's known for it's really delicious coffee!
You stop there?
Did you know that, old man?
Well, actually...
Time to go!
Alright, let's do it!
Wait up! Where're you going?
Wait for me!
Why?
While camping in a deserted forest, we wandered into a shady laboratory.
There we met some strange med students and mysterious old man.
They're looking for something.
And in the basement I found traces of something strange.
It was the nameplate for Cerberus!
Could it be?
Kindaichi's Case Files:
Murder in the Devil Dog's Forest
File 1