"Doraemon" is starting!
How to Use
Nobita's Energy
"How to Use Nobita's Energy!"
Come on, you...!
Strawberry Jam
I give up! It just won't open...
We've already finished eating, so it's fine for now, Mom.
Why me...?!
I went all the way to the store on the other side of town to get a good deal on this jam...
Oh...
Well, then...
Energy Valve
Try the Energy Valve!
You see, this is a gadget that allows you to control your flow of energy.
There you go!
What's this thing?
Open the valve a little bit.
Okay, Mom. Now try the jar one more time.
This is just going to make my hand hurt again.
Hey... It opened!
Wow!
Now, isn't that great?!
What just happened there?
She used this to slightly
increase her usual flow of energy.
Her energy? So what happens to it?
It made her able to use that much more of her strength.
Hey-!
Now THIS  is handy!
Lemme borrow it!
No way! Ow...
Oh, come on!
I have a stamina test during P.E. today.
So this is perfect.
I'm borrowing it!
No! That's not how you're supposed to use it...
I'm off to school!
Nobita-kun!
All right! Next up is Nobi-kun!
Yes, sir!
Do your best, Nobita-san!
You can count on me, Shizuka-chan!
On your marks...
Oh! So Nobita's next, huh?!
Wouldn't it be better for him to race a snail?
Yeah, cuz he's got da worst record in class, 'n gets slower every time.
Get set...
Go!
What?!
H-Hey, record keeper!
How many seconds was that?
Sorry, sir!
He was so fast, I forgot to push the button!
That's amazing! It might even be a new world record-breaking time!
Hey, Nobi! I need you to run like that one more time!
Hey!
What...?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Honestly, you really crack me up, Nobita-kun!
You don't need to laugh, do you?
Just tell me what's going on.
You used up an entire day's worth of energy.
For example...
Let's say you have two cars,
both with the same 1 liter of gas.
The race car goes REALLY  fast...
And the normal passenger car travels at a regular speed.
Because of that, the race car will use up its 1 liter of gas right away.
But while the normal passenger car doesn't go very fast, it can travel a much longer distance.
To think you went and used yours up like that race car...
Man... The gadgets you pull out,
Doraemon, never do anything good.
That's because you always use them incorrectly.
If used properly, my gadgets are all very handy.
Hey... When you say I don't have any energy left...
Does that mean I'll be like this forever?
Don't worry. When you go to sleep at night, you'll be back to normal in the morning.
Thank goodness.
I'm off to school!
Have a nice day!
I'm gonna use this right, today!
But wait. If I don't know
how much energy I have left...
The same thing that happened
yesterday might happen again...
Then...
What's this?
That's the amount of energy you currently have.
If you open the valve all the way,
you can use it all in one shot...
If you close it, on the other hand,
you can make it last a long time.
Oh, I get it!
I'll be fine as long as I make sure
this doesn't get empty, right?
Exactly!
I'll try doing pull-ups to show off to Shizuka-chan when she comes.
And then she'll think better of me!
Yeah, yeah! I saw!
Oh, here she comes!
They had so many cute clothes there!
They sure do. I went and bought
new ones there yesterday, too.
Aw, you're so lucky!
What?!
I hit it!
Here it comes!
Okay!
Whoa... Take that!
What...?!
Why won't Shizuka-chan notice me...?
I sure used up a lot of energy. I'll close this a bit.
Nobita! Pass dat ta me!
Oh, no! I closed it too much...!
Ow...
Oh, are you okay?
Nobita-san?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Why...?!
I tried so hard to show her how cool I can be, too...
What do you mean "cool"?
You can't even kick a ball!
I bet yer proud of runnin'
faster den me yesterday!
Well I really did, didn't I?!
Dun getta big head
just cuz yer legs are kinda fast.
Don't get a big head, now!
It's not just my legs!
I wouldn't lose to you in strength, either, Gian!
Wut wuz dat?!
Fine, den. Let's havva dual!
What?!
Um, now's not the best time...
Git yer butt to da
vacant lot tomorrow at noon!
Tomorrow?!
Sure, that's perfect!
You're going to fight Gian?!
Why are you doing something so stupid again?!
I'll be fine as long as I have this gadget!
But you don't have any physical strength...
Which means you don't have much energy, either!
I know that! That's why...
Oh?
I'm going to sleep right now,
and save up as much energy as I can!
Oh, brother...
Man, I didn't lend you the Energy Valve
so you could use it for something stupid like this.
Aw...
Huh?
It's stuck. What should we do?
Shizuka-chan!
Oh, Nobita-san.
What's wrong?
Our shuttlecock got stuck up in those branches.
We were just going to try getting it down with a long stick or something.
No, it's fine. Let me handle it!
Here it is.
T-Thank you...
I was finally able to show
Shizuka-chan how cool I can be!
But aren't you having that duel against Gian?
Are you okay with using your
energy for something like that?
It's fine. I still have all this energy...
Wait... What?
That's because you got full
of yourself and used it without thinking.
I'd better close it a bit.
Oh, heavens. This is so heavy.
Oh, no!
I don't have enough left.
Why thank you, young man.
No problem. I can handle this.
Then could you be a deary
and get those for me, as well?
What?!
I'm on the 8th floor of that building over there.
WHAT...?!
And to top it all off, the elevator's stopped...!
Are you okay, Nobita-kun?
I can still pull through with just this, somehow...
Huh?
Agh! A mouse!
Hurry, hurry! Run!
What..?! Why me?!
I'm sorry, Nobita-kun. This is my fault.
No, you couldn't help it.
Why don't we just go home?
Yeah.
Nobita! I heard you're fighting Gian!
Huh?
That's incredible! You've sure got guts!
You're so cool!
Oh, uh... Yeah...
Do your best!
You can do it!
I'll carry you there on my back!
You get a little sleep and save your energy!
You're good at napping, right?
Yeah!
He's late.
It's Nobita, after all.
He probably got scared and chickened out.
So he ran, huh?
He did not!
Nobita-kun would never run away!
Well, they're partially right, but...
Nobita-kun, wake up. We're here.
Wut da? He looks totally wiped out.
Duz he really think he c'n fight me like dat?
You only have enough energy for one, deciding shot.
You got it?
Oh, you don't even need to nod.
It's a waste of your energy.
I've really gotta settle this fight in one shot, or...
Ya' done preparin' yerself, Nobita?
Let's do dis.
Wut da heck wuz dat?
Uh, oh. Nobita-kun used every last bit of his energy...
W-Wut's da matter? Yer done already?!
In dat case, it's ma' turn!
Doraemon, what on earth is going on?
Oh, I know!
Nobita-kun's body has absolutely no energy left, anymore.
But he's strong for that very reason.
What do you mean?
Like how the branches of a willow tree sway in the wind to keep from breaking...
Or how a balloon just keeps floating, even if you hit it...
In Nobita-kun's current condition, he can evade any attack, no matter what it is!
I don't quite get it, but it's still amazing.
Why, ya'...
Gian!
Well, he won...
Even though he used up all his energy doing it...
Are you napping again?!
Yep. Because I really should
save my energy for a rainy day.
Oh, what am I going to
do with you, Nobita-kun...?
kokoro no naka itsumo itsumo egaiteru
In my heart, I'm always, always drawing...
yume wo noseta jibun dake no sekai chizu
My very own world map, based on my dreams.
take koputaa
Bamboo 'Copter!
sora wo tonde toki wo koete tooi kuni demo
Flying through the sky, travelling through time, even distant countries...
doa wo akete hora ikitai yo ima sugu
Open the door, and look! You can go where you want right now!
dokodemo doa
Anywhere Door!
otona ni nattara wasurechau no kana?
When I grow up, I wonder if I'll forget all of this?
sonna toki ni wa omoidashite miyou
When that time comes, let's try to remember!
Sha la la la la
Sha la la la la...
uta wo utaou
Let's sing a song!
minna de saa te wo tsunaide
Everyone, hold on to each other's hands.
Doraemon
Doraemon...
sekai juu ni yume wo sou afuresasete
Yes, make the whole world overflow with dreams!
Floating Through the Sky with Nose Balloons
"Floating Through the Sky with Nose Balloons!"
Whoa!
That's Gian, for you!
It's the perfect shape and color!
He's a genius, even when it
comes to bubble gum blowing!
Ya' think so?!
What's so special about that?!
Anyone can blow bubble gum!
Oh, now dat's funny'!
Den why dun we havva li'l battle ta' see who can blow da biggest bubble?
Whoever loses gets ta pound da other 10 times.
What?!
Oh, you aren't confident you can win?
No way! That's exactly what I was wanting.
Okay, then. Face each other.
Ready, go!
Huh, this is weird...
Nobita, it's yer loss.
Ah! Help me!
Come back here, Nobita!
Doraemon...
Oh, hey. Welcome home.
Nobita-kun, you wanna give it a try?
Even you, Doraemon...?
Oh, that's so mean!
Oh, I see...
You can't do it on your own.
At this rate, Gian's gonna beat me up.
Please! Pull out a bubble
gum blowing machine for me!
You really think there's a
stupid, pointless gadget like that?
There isn't, is there?
Nope. No chance.
Even if there isn't one,
please pull one out for me!
What...?
Hey, I know!
There's no such thing as a
"bubble gum blowing machine", but...
Nose Balloons
You can blow up some Nose Balloons!
Balloons?
Yep! This makes special balloons.
And you can choose their color by turning this dial.
Which color do you want?
Red, blue, green, or yellow?
Um... Red!
Now just stick this up your nose...
It feels itchy, for some reason.
Now try breathing out through your nose.
Breath through my nose?
Wow, cool!
Isn't it?
But having it come out of my nose is kind of creepy.
If that's what you have to say, I won't let you borrow it!
No, no! Let me borrow it!
This'll be plenty good enough.
I think I'll try it with French gum, now.
Do dey really have gum in France, too?
There they are! They're still doing it!
All right, all set.
Hey!
Oh, look! Da loser's back again!
Did you come all the way
here so you can get beat up?
I just wasn't taking it seriously before.
Why don't we try that battle one more time?
No matter how many times ya' try, it'll end da same way!
We'll see about that...
Whoa! No way!
It's gigantic!
What do you think?
Mine is pretty awesome, too, right?
It's almost likka real balloon!
I'll blow some more for you.
What?!
Nobita's actually...!
Wut da heck's goin' on here?!
Looks like I'm taking the crown this time.
Wut wuz dat?!
I can do dat, too!
You can beat him, Gian!
All right! That's my Gian!
Nobita!
Alright... A battle's a battle, 'n I lost fair 'n square.
Go on, hit me!
Eh? No, that's okay...
I can't do that just because I was
able to blow up some balloons...
I ain't able ta' calm down if ya' dun't!
If yer not gonna hit me, den I'll hit myself!
Hey, wait! Gian!
He got blown away!
Now DAT's sum awesum gum.
Wow! This feels so nice!
What is that?
He's flying!
Easy as pie!
And... up I go!
Hey, Shizuka-chan!
Nobita-san!
Wow, what pretty balloons.
The word for "Nose" and "Flower" sound the same in Japanese.
They're no ordinary balloons. They're Nose Balloons.
Oh? Flower Balloons?
How do you make them?
It's better if you don't ask...
What's wrong?
My balloon!
It's stuck up there.
I know! You can have mine.
Here you go.
Yay! Thank you!
You're really kind, Nobita-san.
No, you're just saying that...
No fair! I want one, too!
Me, too!
Here.
Nobita-san, do you have any more balloons?
Yep! I can go blow them up right now!
That's great! And I'll help, too!
You want to do it, too, Shizuka-chan?
No, no, no!
I don't want to see you like that Shizuka-chan.
Nobita-san, you're a strange one.
I wonder what happened to Nobita-kun. I'm really worried.
Huh?
What's going on down there?
This is more tiring than I thought it would be.
Nobita-kun.
What are you doing?
Doraemon! Perfect timing!
Can you help me?!
Huh?
We need a whole bunch
more, so keep it up, you two!
Okay!
There's still more of them.
Don't you have an "auto nose breathing machine" or something?
Like I'd have something like that!
I can't do this anymore.
Don't complain. I'm helping, too, you know.
Let's just hurry and get this over with.
Nobita-san, Dora-chan.
There might be... 50 more kids left now?
50?! What...?!
T-This can't be happening...
We're all counting on you, Nobita-san!
U-Uh, yeah...
Here you are.
This is for you.
And here's yours.
Yay!
Isn't it great that we made everyone so happy?
My nose hurts...
Mine's red and swollen, too.
Man, that sure was tiring.
Well of course, when we had to make that many.
I never wanna see another balloon, ever again.
Come on, Gian. Just give up.
Even if you chew a lot of gum,
it's still gonna do the same thing.
Darnnit! Why ain't dis gum makin' me fly, too?!
He must've used some kind of trick.
Because I've never heard of
someone being able to fly with gum!
Huh?
Is that Nobita and Doraemon?
There are balloons coming out of their noses!
I get it! It must be one of Doraemon's gadgets!
Wut?!
'Ey, Nobita!
Gian!
Ow...
Mind tellin' me wut dat is?
Um, well... That's...
You cheated, didn't you?!
Run!
Come back 'ere!
Whoa, what? What's going on?!
Don't think, just run!
Why, ya... Come bak, come bak, come bak!
Where'd dey go?
Let's split up!
Alright! Look fer dem high 'n low!
What do we do...?
It doesn't look like we can get away from them.
That's it! Let's use the Nose Balloons to make
a really big getaway balloon, and fly off into the sky!
Hey, yeah!
Come on, faster, faster!
I know...!
Hurry, hurry!
Nobi!
What are you doing out here?
S-Sensei...
This is painful...
I'm pretty sure I assigned PLENTY of homework today.
And if you're out walking around playing, that must
certainly mean that you've already finished it all, correct?
I can't hold it in anymore...
If you've actually forgotten about tomorrow's homework...
I'm going to have to contact your mother, and...
What?! Come down here, Nobi!
How can you just fly away when
someone is in the middle of talking to you?!
I'm sorry, sir.
Hey, there's Nobita!
Nobita!
Hey, it's Gian!
Catch me if you can!
Don't you gimme dat!
Hey, I know!
We'll use my plane...
Go get 'em!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Attaboy, Suneo!
One more round should do it!
Hey, stop! That's dangerous!
Alright!
They landed behind the supermarket.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Oww...
I think they landed somewhere around here...
Huh? Dey ain't here.
Then let's try over there!
The other side is armed with an airplane.
So we can't possibly escape on a balloon.
What do we do...?
Oh?
Huh?
Unneeded cardboard: Please take and use as you see fit.
That's it! Let's use that!
Huh? Cardboard?
Yep! Doraemon, start blowing up a bunch of Nose Balloons.
Huh? But balloons won't...
It'll be fine.
Darn! Dey ain't here, either!
Gian, let's go back to the first place we looked.
'Kay!
If we take the cardboard
we gathered up, and tie it all together...
And put balloons in that...
What on Earth are we making?
Ah! There they are!
This is bad!
Doraemon, get in!
What?!
Wut da heck is dat?!
I-It's a blimp!
Nobita-kun, what is this?
It's the "Airship Nobita"!
Airship Nobita?!
Why dat cheeky li'l...
Suneo!
Okay!
We'll jus shoot 'em down!
No! I just bought that plane, too!
'Ey, Nobita! Dat's no fair!
This is amazing, Nobita-kun!
It was nothing!
I'll remember dis!
Ah, we're saved.
Yeah, looks like those two gave up.
I feel safe now that we're up this high.
Why don't we take a "stroll"
through the skies on our way home?
Hey, that sounds great!
Darn dat Nobita!
Huh?
Hey Gian, look at this!
It must be Doraemon's gadget!
Nice find, Suneo!
I guess we do dis?
Ew, that's gross.
One mo' try!
Whoa, that's Gian for you!
It wuz nuttin'.
Wait, Gian!
What a refreshing breeze.
Help us!
Sure feels good, doesn't it?
I'm scared!
S-Suneo! Are ya' okay?!
How did I get myself into this?!
How far're we gonna go?!
Mommy!
Next Episode Preview
It's finally here!
Doraemon's
Birthday Special!
So you really were  a
raccoon, huh, Doraemon?!
I am NOT a raccoon!
No matta' how I lookit 'ya,
yer a raccoon, ain'cha?
I am not!
A giant Dora-Raccoon?!
I just said I'm not a raccoon!
Wow! It's Perman!
It really is!
Wow, he's so cool!
It's Doraemon's
Birthday Special!
And the appearance of
Giant Dora-Raccoon!
Look forward to it!
I am NOT a raccoon!