Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai kara
I won't let anyone get in my way.
kajitsu ga tsugeta mirai. Yume, visou ni kaeru
The recent past tells me of the future. My ideals become my dreams.
Daremo ga nozonda owari wo...
The ending that everyone desires...
Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Itsuka boku ga misete ageru hikari kagayaku sekai wo
Someday I'll show you a world that shines in the light.