[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: DXD
Collisions: Normal
Original Script: DHR
Synch Point: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.91,0:00:07.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上次我快要死的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.05,0:00:10.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長是不是也像這樣對我做這種事？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.83,0:00:12.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.08,0:00:14.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.81,0:00:20.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,離完全治癒 看來要花些時間
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.42,0:00:24.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個「走散」驅魔師所使用的光之力量
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.00,0:00:26.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是相當濃厚的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.68,0:00:29.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「走散」不止是惡魔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.63,0:00:35.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被教會驅逐後 很多人落身與墮天使僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.63,0:00:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是說愛西亞也是那個「走散」驅魔師同一類嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.52,0:00:46.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣 你是惡魔 她是墮天使的僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.13,0:00:48.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是事實
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.93,0:00:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.10,0:00:52.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太弱…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.20,0:00:55.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我太弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.33,0:00:57.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歸根究底「兵卒」是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.33,0:00:57.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(457,435)}Pawn
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.21,0:01:01.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連一個女孩都救不了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.61,0:01:02.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.25,0:01:04.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不該這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.01,0:01:08.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果弱小 那就鍛鍊變強就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.59,0:01:12.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.54,0:01:21.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是不行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.07,0:01:27.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 她正在跟瘋子神父在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.69,0:01:29.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在這期間也會…愛西亞正在被…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.34,0:01:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.20,0:01:38.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Comment: 0,0:01:56.50,0:02:03.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.47,0:02:02.41,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.57,0:02:08.06,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.29,0:02:13.78,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.09,0:02:20.10,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.30,0:02:26.94,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:32.66,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.03,0:02:35.74,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.92,0:02:38.79,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.95,0:02:50.76,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:00:41.05,0:00:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.47,0:02:02.41,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.57,0:02:08.06,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.29,0:02:13.78,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.09,0:02:20.10,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.30,0:02:26.94,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:32.66,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.03,0:02:35.74,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.92,0:02:38.79,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.95,0:02:50.76,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Comment: 0,0:03:08.82,0:03:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.82,0:03:18.44,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU  後期:KoU
Comment: 0,0:02:37.34,0:03:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.75,0:03:14.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,389)}第4話 「要去救朋友！」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.21,0:03:14.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 愛西亞醬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.60,0:03:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像這樣吃 公主
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.59,0:03:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然有這種吃法 好厲害！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.79,0:03:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.16,0:03:43.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起這個 為什麼你在公園？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.45,0:03:46.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.01,0:03:50.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為是休息時間 想在城裡散步一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.10,0:03:55.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 之後 見到了一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.59,0:03:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.30,0:03:57.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.25,0:04:00.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就盡情的玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.82,0:04:01.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.70,0:04:04.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.12,0:04:19.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.85,0:04:22.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是…什麼事也沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.29,0:04:25.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡拉丘君啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.19,0:04:28.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不是…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.68,0:04:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.57,0:04:32.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再怎麼說在回家社的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.55,0:04:35.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還跟松田和元濱橫掃附近的遊樂場了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.89,0:04:39.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.72,0:04:43.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個拉丘是與一誠先生的相遇帶來的寶貝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.45,0:04:47.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 下一個玩哪一個呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.31,0:04:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 這個相遇是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.99,0:04:52.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只限於今天的貴重的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.66,0:04:57.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我出生以來第一次這麼開心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.84,0:05:00.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞真什麼事都說得好誇張
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.94,0:05:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛…愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.21,0:05:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那個時候的傷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.12,0:05:06.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.69,0:05:18.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過還真可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.01,0:05:21.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我記得你的腿也…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.73,0:05:22.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.83,0:05:30.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.32,0:05:33.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看看…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.92,0:05:35.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全沒問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.96,0:05:37.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,腿也好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.63,0:05:39.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好厲害啊愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.16,0:05:47.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一出生就被父母拋棄了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.43,0:05:47.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.82,0:05:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在歐洲一個小農村的教會裡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.74,0:05:53.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽說我在那門口哭鬧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.24,0:05:56.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在那裡長大
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.44,0:06:03.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,八歲的時候 受傷快要死的小狗迷路走進教會裡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.70,0:06:05.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一個人拼命為牠祈禱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.98,0:06:09.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那時 奇蹟發生了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.24,0:06:13.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那之後我很快就被帶到很大的教會
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.16,0:06:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被吩咐治療來自世界各地的信徒的病和傷
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.06,0:06:25.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很高興自己的力量可以幫上別人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.92,0:06:31.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但在某一天 我與一個受傷倒下了的男人見面了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.70,0:06:35.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是偶然相遇的那個人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.99,0:06:38.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然是可以治療惡魔的能力？！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.37,0:06:40.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔女啊 治療惡魔的魔女
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.54,0:06:47.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他們說擁有連惡魔都能治療的能力的人是異教徒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.63,0:06:51.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後墮天使就把沒有了去處的愛西亞給…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.27,0:06:57.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過我從沒忘過對神祈禱以及感謝之心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.16,0:07:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,何況那些人還全都做那麼過分的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.20,0:07:08.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這也一定是神之試煉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.48,0:07:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,熬過這個試煉 總有一天神一定會實現我的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.42,0:07:17.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我這麼相信著
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.88,0:07:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夢想？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.43,0:07:22.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交到很多朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.51,0:07:27.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟朋友們一起買花啦 買書啦 聊天啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.32,0:07:30.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這種夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.36,0:07:34.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我 沒有朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.29,0:07:43.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.94,0:07:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我來當愛西亞的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.30,0:07:49.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話說我們已經是朋友了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.50,0:07:54.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看 我們已經在一起玩一起聊天了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.78,0:07:58.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呃 雖然沒有花和書什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.30,0:08:01.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣不可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.68,0:08:08.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 不是 不是 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.70,0:08:12.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過…這樣會給一誠先生帶來麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.95,0:08:14.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,管他是惡魔還是修女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.45,0:08:17.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朋友就是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.15,0:08:20.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.73,0:08:23.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好高興
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.71,0:08:27.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.57,0:08:29.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.10,0:08:31.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷娜蕾大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.90,0:08:34.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.35,0:08:36.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是墮天使
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.55,0:08:41.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說你墮落成惡魔苟且偷生…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.47,0:08:42.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.49,0:08:45.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 逃了也沒用哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.58,0:08:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要 我不要回到傷害他人的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.65,0:08:54.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 其實我是從那個教會逃了出來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.28,0:08:55.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種事我早知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.74,0:09:02.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞不可能跟這種不正經的傢伙們一夥嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.15,0:09:04.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墮天使來這幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.49,0:09:09.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,憑你一個髒兮兮的下級惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.43,0:09:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別跟我套近乎行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.16,0:09:15.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果妨礙我的話
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.87,0:09:19.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光之…槍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.07,0:09:23.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次可要完全消滅掉你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.86,0:09:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,｢神器」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.86,0:09:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(419,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.32,0:09:29.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.61,0:09:37.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我以為什麼呢 只是個二級危機
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.61,0:09:37.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(570,436)}<Twice Critical>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.34,0:09:39.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全期待落空嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.44,0:09:40.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,二級？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.70,0:09:42.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又稱「龍之手」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.12,0:09:46.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有個能在一定時間將力量強化一倍的能力的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.27,0:09:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到處都有的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.91,0:09:49.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量強化一倍？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.72,0:09:52.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說你的「神器」很危險…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.72,0:09:52.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(409,434)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.32,0:09:55.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就因上頭這麼說…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.51,0:09:57.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我還演了那麼無聊的戲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.45,0:10:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡你 請跟我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.29,0:10:05.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙你的啦 那個時候你那麼色瞇瞇的可真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.77,0:10:08.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.84,0:10:11.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,憑那種東西可贏不了我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.49,0:10:15.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖把愛西亞交出來給我滾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.44,0:10:16.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.44,0:10:17.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.79,0:10:20.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連個朋友都保護不了怎麼行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.33,0:10:24.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我動啊 不是能強化一倍的力量嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.68,0:10:25.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.27,0:10:28.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量…流進體內了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.99,0:10:35.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.30,0:10:40.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白沒 力量從一變成二可沒什麼區別
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.64,0:10:42.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.15,0:10:44.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.53,0:10:47.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.07,0:10:53.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,厲害 因為這光痛楚在漸漸消失
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.74,0:11:01.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 乖乖跟我一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.78,0:11:07.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的「聖母的微笑」跟那傢伙的｢神器」比 可要珍貴得多了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.78,0:11:07.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(198,436)}<Twilight Healing>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.97,0:11:12.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然你們…只是想要我的能力而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.68,0:11:18.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要你肯回來 那惡魔的命可以留著
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.50,0:11:20.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.15,0:11:22.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰讓你施捨了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.21,0:11:28.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞危險
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.12,0:11:33.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.08,0:11:37.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 跟之前那支槍比完全不同
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.01,0:11:40.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的是故意射偏的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.48,0:11:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,命中的話身體就四分五裂了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.47,0:11:46.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞的治癒也未必來得及
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.66,0:11:49.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.11,0:11:58.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子 今晚的儀式一結束
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.34,0:12:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就能從一切煩惱與痛苦中解脫了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.69,0:12:04.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再見囉 一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.21,0:12:05.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.16,0:12:08.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永別了 一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.77,0:12:17.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼…我這麼弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.39,0:12:32.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要說幾次你才能懂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.08,0:12:34.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行就是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.78,0:12:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忘掉她吧 你可是吉蒙里家的眷屬
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.22,0:12:42.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…就把我從眷屬裡去除掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.08,0:12:44.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後我就一個人…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.11,0:12:46.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能做到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.89,0:12:48.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是西洋棋的「兵卒」不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.89,0:12:48.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(471,438)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.13,0:12:51.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一個小兵卒被吃了也沒大礙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.57,0:12:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.98,0:12:58.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠覺得「兵卒」是最弱的棋子嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.98,0:12:58.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(379,439)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.42,0:13:07.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我應該說過惡魔之棋跟實際的西洋棋特徵相同
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.42,0:13:07.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(328,438)}Evil Piece
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.88,0:13:10.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,實際的…「兵卒」的特徵是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.88,0:13:10.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(410,440)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.00,0:13:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「升級」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.00,0:13:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(426,438)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.09,0:13:23.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs35}「兵卒」只要走到敵陣最深處就能升格為國王以外的其他棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.09,0:13:23.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(73,435)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.17,0:13:27.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是說我…可以擁有大家的能力嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.81,0:13:31.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要身為主人的我認可那個是敵陣就行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.72,0:13:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 就比如教會
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.14,0:13:37.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,順便一提你的「神器」嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.14,0:13:37.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(503,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.88,0:13:39.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是可以強化一倍力量是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.13,0:13:40.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從夕麻…唔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.86,0:13:43.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從墮天使那聽到的…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.61,0:13:45.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想像吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.94,0:13:52.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,｢神器」是靠主人的想像產生變化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.98,0:13:57.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想像越強烈力量越大 它就一定會回應你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.01,0:13:59.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想像之力…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.59,0:14:07.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出了點急事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.48,0:14:10.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和朱乃稍微出去一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.66,0:14:12.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 還沒商量完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.44,0:14:15.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽好 即使用了「升級」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.46,0:14:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(524,438)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.47,0:14:18.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墮天使也沒弱到可以用一個棋子戰勝他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.33,0:14:23.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種事…我也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.03,0:14:25.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.74,0:14:28.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你阻止我也沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.86,0:14:29.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會被殺掉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.27,0:14:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使我死也要讓愛西亞逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.31,0:14:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我想說你的覺悟不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.94,0:14:37.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是太魯莽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.34,0:14:38.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了臭帥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.56,0:14:40.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.61,0:14:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.83,0:14:45.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長不是跟你說「即使用了『升級』…」什麼的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.37,0:14:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.53,0:14:50.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長已經認可教會是敵陣了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.68,0:14:51.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.70,0:14:56.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然 同時那也是要我們輔助兵藤君的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.30,0:14:58.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪醬也是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.66,0:15:00.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就你們兩個我會不安
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.50,0:15:03.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好無聊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.04,0:15:05.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要我來監視啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.45,0:15:09.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.52,0:15:15.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,免貴 人稱墮天使蜜特露特~
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.31,0:15:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 您可真有禮貌
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.87,0:15:20.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,僕人剛探查到了你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.98,0:15:24.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們攻過去的話腸胃受不了是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.43,0:15:25.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.56,0:15:29.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果被惡魔破壞了重要的儀式會有點困擾而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.25,0:15:31.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.02,0:15:35.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才我們家欲求不滿的孩子們已經過去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.79,0:15:38.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒 真的？討厭 真的假的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.67,0:15:41.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 從正面堂堂正正地~
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.17,0:15:45.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了 以為會從後門偷偷出來的說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.52,0:15:49.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過反正是雜種 去幾個都沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.45,0:15:51.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,決定了 沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.32,0:15:58.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正 真正麻煩的只有你們兩個而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.40,0:16:02.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還特地來一趟 真有勞你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.49,0:16:03.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你多心了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.95,0:16:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我不跟他一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.10,0:16:09.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說要放棄他們嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.19,0:16:12.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大的殺氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.02,0:16:15.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來神父也聚集地相當多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.45,0:16:17.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是真的嗎 一起來真是幫我大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.32,0:16:19.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們不是夥伴嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.83,0:16:24.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有 我個人而言 不喜歡墮天使和神父
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.55,0:16:26.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以說恨他們
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.49,0:16:28.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.58,0:16:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 小貓？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.01,0:16:34.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對方也肯定注意到我們了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.99,0:16:44.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太殘忍了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.20,0:16:48.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呀 呀 呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.68,0:16:51.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們又再會了 真是感動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.01,0:16:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,菲利德
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.45,0:16:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說 不會想到會有第二次見面的惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.50,0:17:00.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看 因為我是超級超超級的強
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.93,0:17:05.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一碰見惡魔 就立即是這個了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.52,0:17:08.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以說 很讓人惱火
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.73,0:17:13.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我蒙受羞恥的你們這些狗屎惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.66,0:17:15.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞在哪兒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.39,0:17:19.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那個被惡魔迷惑住的狗屎修女的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.08,0:17:24.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在從這個祭壇通向的地下的祭祀場裡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.97,0:17:25.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是地下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:28.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前提是你們能去得了那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.46,0:17:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「神器」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.46,0:17:29.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(426,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.48,0:17:32.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,壓碎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.58,0:17:36.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你太礙事了 這個小不點
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.66,0:17:38.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小不點？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.16,0:17:44.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,煩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.34,0:17:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真煩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:48.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看著就很煩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.50,0:17:50.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不賴嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.44,0:17:51.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也是簡直太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.52,0:17:54.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓我真的想殺你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.02,0:17:59.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來他不只是臉長得帥而已
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.35,0:18:03.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 我也稍微動點真格了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.44,0:18:11.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼東西？ 這是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.91,0:18:12.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「食光劍」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.85,0:18:13.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(425,435)}<Holy Eraser>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.83,0:18:15.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吞噬光的黑暗之劍
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.72,0:18:17.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙也是｢神器」使用者啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.78,0:18:19.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也能用「神器」的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.80,0:18:19.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(458,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.45,0:18:20.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤君
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.61,0:18:21.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.73,0:18:22.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.48,0:18:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說你很煩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.60,0:18:27.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之就是這意思吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.84,0:18:33.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要幹掉作為主人的你 其他僕人也就完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.56,0:18:36.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出來吧 卡拉瓦娜 特蘭西克
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.19,0:18:44.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在得意什麼  真不巧 又相見了 吉蒙里大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.22,0:18:47.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟你的僕人還有個帳要算呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.16,0:18:49.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 都聚齊了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.07,0:18:53.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「升級」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.07,0:18:53.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(424,435)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.02,0:18:57.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Rook是戰車 其特性是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.45,0:18:58.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可喻的防禦力和
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.27,0:18:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不是真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.75,0:19:03.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無比強大的攻擊力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.52,0:19:04.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.63,0:19:14.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟敢對愛西亞那麼粗暴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.91,0:19:16.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有點出氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.72,0:19:17.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.28,0:19:19.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了 一個狗屎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.57,0:19:21.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好疼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.75,0:19:26.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對於我來說 可不想被你們惡魔殺掉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.06,0:19:27.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.19,0:19:29.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給這個 拜拜了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.55,0:19:32.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓他逃掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.81,0:19:33.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之先前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.33,0:19:42.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們要妨礙我們計劃的意圖 已經是我們的麻煩了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.36,0:19:44.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們就好好掙扎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.15,0:19:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.98,0:19:47.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.38,0:20:10.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼 你要跟我比Cosplay嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.29,0:20:17.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然是結界！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.18,0:20:19.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是不是很不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.41,0:20:24.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從這個籠子裡是逃不掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.06,0:20:27.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們一開始就打算…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.86,0:20:31.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 一開始就為了消滅你們而來的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.43,0:20:33.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.87,0:20:35.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.74,0:20:37.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖的消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.97,0:20:40.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼 你們就先悠哉悠哉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.90,0:20:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等儀式結束了 就會變成連你也贏不了的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.07,0:20:50.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎 惡魔的各位
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.17,0:20:52.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來的挺晚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.02,0:20:56.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.88,0:21:01.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠…先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.53,0:21:03.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 我現在就去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.79,0:21:04.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤君 危險！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.71,0:21:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是感動的會面 可是很遺憾 儀式馬上要結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.18,0:21:16.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想對愛西亞做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.89,0:21:19.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 墮天使的目的是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.10,0:21:26.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 墮天使是想奪走修女的「神器」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.10,0:21:26.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(634,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.37,0:21:29.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要奪走「神器」？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.37,0:21:29.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(457,435)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.55,0:21:31.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那愛西亞會怎樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.61,0:21:32.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.15,0:21:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然擁有者的性命也…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.48,0:21:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞…要死了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.44,0:21:49.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「聖母的微笑」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.44,0:21:49.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(425,436)}<Twilight Healing>
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.96,0:21:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,終於到手了
Comment: 0,0:21:58.30,0:22:00.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Comment: 0,0:23:25.06,0:23:27.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.59,0:23:30.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是作為來到這兒的獎賞
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.41,0:23:32.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎能讓你逃掉 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.09,0:23:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不要小瞧一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.58,0:23:38.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為那孩子是我最強的「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.58,0:23:38.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs22\pos(580,438)}<Pawn>
Comment: 0,0:23:38.54,0:23:40.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.85,0:23:41.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(417,210)}第5話 ｢幹掉原女朋友！｣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.86,0:23:51.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
