[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:漫遊字幕
Original Script:漫遊字幕組
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer:100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: DXD
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這莫非是胸罩 為什麼在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.46,0:00:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 這是愛西亞的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.02,0:00:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是犯罪 一誠學長
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.82,0:00:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.33,0:00:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.60,0:00:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷內衣是不折不扣的犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.63,0:00:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯罪？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.75,0:00:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 只是偶然碰在我的臉上 所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.78,0:00:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 本來是想在大家來之前收起來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.20,0:00:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 再說愛西亞現在去處只有這裡了…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.22,0:00:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長說會在上學之前會給我找好住處
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.34,0:00:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早晨特訓？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.26,0:01:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在跟墮天使的戰鬥中我明白了 你有必要提高基礎體力
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.76,0:01:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會在早上五點之前去接你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.17,0:01:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五點之前？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.64,0:01:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 那我去發傳單了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.62,0:01:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.98,0:01:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.53,0:01:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.41,0:01:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於寄宿的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.67,0:01:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Comment: 0,0:01:41.63,0:01:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.58,0:01:47.52,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.68,0:01:53.17,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.40,0:01:58.89,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.20,0:02:05.21,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.41,0:02:12.05,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.34,0:02:17.77,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.14,0:02:20.85,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.03,0:02:23.90,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.06,0:02:35.87,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:01:21.09,0:01:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.58,0:01:47.52,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.68,0:01:53.17,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.40,0:01:58.89,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.20,0:02:05.21,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.41,0:02:12.05,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.34,0:02:17.77,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.14,0:02:20.85,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.03,0:02:23.90,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.06,0:02:35.87,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Comment: 0,0:02:54.02,0:03:03.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.72,0:03:03.41,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:希美亞 後期:KoU  BDrip: ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.73,0:02:59.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,388)}第6話 「正在當惡魔！」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.32,0:02:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…已經早上了…請快起來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了…快起來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.45,0:03:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快起來吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.57,0:03:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 才四點半啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.36,0:03:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社…社長 我現在就去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.19,0:03:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別跑得像個老爺爺
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.60,0:03:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我要成為後宮王
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.36,0:03:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出乎意料的惡魔竟然是屬於體育系的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.33,0:03:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別發牢騷
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.84,0:03:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我絕對不能容忍我的僕人這麼弱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.02,0:03:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我會努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.16,0:03:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好 在惡魔的世界力量是絕對的發言權
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.55,0:03:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 特別是像你這種情況
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.90,0:03:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.41,0:03:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部 胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.43,0:03:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好 對於你的能力 你的基礎體力越強就越有意義
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.06,0:03:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 十一 十二…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.32,0:04:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長臀部的觸感太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.69,0:04:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你腦子裡摻有邪念 腰部的動作變得猥瑣了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.12,0:04:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可以這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.39,0:04:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種情況下我的YY已經MAX了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.34,0:04:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是快來了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.77,0:04:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有誰要來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.95,0:04:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 一誠先生 社長 我遲到了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.19,0:04:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼會摔倒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.42,0:04:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.34,0:04:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.57,0:04:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 為什麼來這裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.61,0:04:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長讓我來的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.68,0:04:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 為什麼要讓愛西亞來？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.68,0:04:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.77,0:04:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.46,0:04:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 和愛西亞一起出發吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.42,0:04:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒? 去哪兒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.64,0:04:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 一誠的家哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.77,0:05:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.40,0:05:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的私人用品 沒想到會有這麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.04,0:05:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是愛西亞的？ 到底怎麼回事 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.42,0:05:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 從今天起愛西亞要在你家裡住
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.85,0:05:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.80,0:05:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.80,0:05:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問她希望寄宿在哪裡 她說想住在你的家裡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.25,0:05:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你突然這麼說我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.18,0:05:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是愛…愛西亞同學是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.09,0:05:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 父親
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.32,0:05:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要找家庭寄宿的話 比起我們這樣的 應該還有更好的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.51,0:05:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生是我的恩人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.86,0:05:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩人？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.82,0:05:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.75,0:05:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從外國一人來到這裡 一誠是最讓我承蒙照顧的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.46,0:05:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是一誠先生家的話 我也能安心的度過
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.29,0:05:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.30,0:05:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 如果覺得麻煩的話我會放棄的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.43,0:05:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可沒說不可以啊 又不是沒有空房 只是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.44,0:05:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我家有個可以說是性慾的化身的兒子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.83,0:06:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對對
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.47,0:06:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對著兒子怎麼能這麼說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.22,0:06:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼這次的家庭寄宿也兼是個新娘修行的話怎樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.84,0:06:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新…新娘修行？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.89,0:06:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩…孩子他媽 看兒子是這副德行 \N我還以為我這一生見不著孫子的臉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.17,0:06:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子他爸 我也是啊 這種沒出息的兒子竟然會…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.98,0:06:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 給我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.49,0:06:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父親 母親 一誠可不是沒出息的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.49,0:06:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多…多麼好的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.42,0:06:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲同學 愛西亞同學我們收留了 不 請務必讓我們收留
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.71,0:06:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝 父親 母親
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.19,0:06:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣已經決定了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.76,0:06:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…新娘修行和做新娘是完全不一樣的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.23,0:06:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新娘嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.65,0:06:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.26,0:07:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫愛西亞·阿基多 不足的地方請多多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.88,0:07:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金髮美少女
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.36,0:07:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸圍82 腰圍55  臀圍81 Good!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.75,0:07:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 來了這個班級啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.31,0:07:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也是社長…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.77,0:07:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在寄宿在一誠先生的家裡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.35,0:07:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.14,0:07:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼情況 為什麼你會和金髮美少女在同一屋簷下？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.56,0:07:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這樣的Flag條件只出現在你跟前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.50,0:07:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我決定的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.20,0:07:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 看來和大家相處的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.25,0:07:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}{\an8}那你說是誰決定的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.97,0:07:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞的房間有鎖嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.72,0:07:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.63,0:07:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡和上洗手間的時候要嚴密檢查哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.22,0:07:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,檢查嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.54,0:07:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對對 說不定會裝有攝影機
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.99,0:07:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攝影機？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.94,0:07:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你們啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.26,0:08:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天累了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.83,0:08:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡 班上的人都很親切
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.59,0:08:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有一誠先生的朋友松田和元濱也是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.38,0:08:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們對你做了什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.78,0:08:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說下次紳士的聚會裡邀請我什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.31,0:08:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那個無視掉也無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.55,0:08:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.81,0:08:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.19,0:08:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.81,0:08:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…去下一個地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.80,0:08:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.91,0:08:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 我們回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.01,0:08:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…社長？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.94,0:08:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 剛才稍微發了呆
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.00,0:08:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.08,0:09:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.37,0:09:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.35,0:09:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想讓愛西亞今晚出首場
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.71,0:09:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首場？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.67,0:09:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從魔法陣傳送到契約者身邊 然後做契約協議
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.95,0:09:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說來 這是不是太早了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.14,0:09:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞作為惡魔才幾天而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.61,0:09:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.54,0:09:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據我的調查 愛西亞作為眷屬惡魔持有的魔力僅次於我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.24,0:09:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.32,0:09:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.25,0:09:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為「主教」能充分發揮其實力了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.28,0:09:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(317,434)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.67,0:09:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很厲害啊 愛西亞小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.98,0:09:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.35,0:09:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是件好事 不過有些沮喪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.46,0:09:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 只談經驗的應該我更上一層樓
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.12,0:09:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞必須得由我來保護
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.17,0:09:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.40,0:09:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.29,0:09:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被授予的任務…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.02,0:09:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.95,0:09:56.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.03,0:09:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次就讓我去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.01,0:10:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.75,0:10:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞來這個國家還沒幾天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.51,0:10:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多多習慣現在的生活之後也不遲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.60,0:10:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說實話 我自己也是很不安啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.10,0:10:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到召喚者是個危險人物的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.83,0:10:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要跟你締結契約 不管什麼要求都會聽從我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.06,0:10:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可以這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.67,0:10:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我知道自己多慮了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.34,0:10:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在 請進喵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.61,0:10:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.06,0:10:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵是個什麼情況？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.26,0:10:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨喵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.61,0:10:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是美露碳喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.01,0:11:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…你是不是召喚了惡魔古裡莫利的眷屬什麼的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.94,0:11:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.66,0:11:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有願望才叫惡魔的喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.46,0:11:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.44,0:11:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你把美露碳變成魔法少女喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.65,0:11:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就穿越到異世界什麼的就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.77,0:11:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那已經試了喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.60,0:11:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經試了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.69,0:11:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.22,0:11:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.15,0:11:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請給美露碳魔幻力量吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.69,0:11:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已經夠魔幻了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.39,0:11:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美露碳很需要魔法的力量喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.20,0:11:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請冷靜 在這裡吵鬧的話會對近鄰不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.84,0:11:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到裡面去吧 吶？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.03,0:11:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會讓我成為魔法少女喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.24,0:11:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少會陪你談心的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.35,0:11:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那跟我一起 看「魔法少女蜜兒琪螺旋7二選一」唄
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.26,0:12:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有從這裡開始施展的魔法呦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.09,0:12:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是這種的啊 在某種意義上也是超危險的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.09,0:12:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我去的地方全是怪胎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.06,0:12:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.00,0:12:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了 工作好像完事了呢 有何成果
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.80,0:12:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.20,0:12:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好 集中精神的話 一定能把燈籠褲看成內褲的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.74,0:12:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到啊 元濱 我也能看到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.29,0:12:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深藍色燈籠褲不知何時變成了白色
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.62,0:12:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又沒契約成功嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.14,0:12:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被推薦的動畫意外的很好看…不小心看到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.09,0:12:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.32,0:12:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 沒成功也沒辦法了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.90,0:12:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長的聲音聽起來就像超級失望的說
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.93,0:13:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這個笨蛋笨蛋笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.58,0:13:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陽光這麼強 逃課睡覺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.35,0:13:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社…社長？！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.85,0:13:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手擅自…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.87,0:13:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊 我的右手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.16,0:13:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還差一點點…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.27,0:13:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.43,0:13:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…這是什麼情況
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.36,0:13:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有點累 想打個盹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.88,0:13:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來這一看一誠先睡在這裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.72,0:13:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.91,0:13:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妨礙到你了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.08,0:13:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不 不過全裸打盹有點太刺激了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.50,0:13:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不裸睡就睡不著
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.81,0:14:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠你喜歡女生的胸部嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.80,0:14:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.24,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要摸摸我的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.23,0:14:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要摸摸我的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.56,0:14:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到日語裡有這麼美妙的語句
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.03,0:14:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我個忙就可以讓你摸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.30,0:14:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 儘管吩咐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.01,0:14:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 契個約給我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.25,0:14:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…真的要一起去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.05,0:14:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是說過這次我要作為監督跟著一誠去嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.94,0:14:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 跟社長一起的話肯定不會失敗的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.08,0:14:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.36,0:14:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油哦 一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.71,0:14:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦~ 我加油 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.92,0:14:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就傳送了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.24,0:14:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點像公寓呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.84,0:15:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過這麼多個戰國裝備到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.58,0:15:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是惡魔先生嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.19,0:15:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…冒昧問一下 您是女士嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.35,0:15:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.85,0:15:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫蘇珊 是個憧憬日本文化來這裡的留學生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.92,0:15:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那個裝扮是？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.72,0:15:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 深夜會很危險 就這麼穿加強防備
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.36,0:15:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那樣有點奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.09,0:15:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過來的是溫柔的惡魔太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.60,0:15:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是可怕的惡魔 這個「鬼神丸-國重」就不得不
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.83,0:15:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得不拔了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.73,0:15:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經拔了拔了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.32,0:15:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼蘇珊小姐 你的願望是？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.65,0:15:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗚嗚 跟我一起去我上的大學取下筆記
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.13,0:15:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那點事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.46,0:15:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深夜的校舍 太恐怖了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.35,0:15:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最恐怖的是你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.87,0:16:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 為什麼叫我的全是這種怪胎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.06,0:16:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.25,0:16:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉 晚上小鎮太恐怖了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.69,0:16:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說你最恐怖了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.78,0:16:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.69,0:16:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們就先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.97,0:16:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實現和社長的約定了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.13,0:16:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣我就能毫不客氣地揉社長的咪咪了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先是右乳 彷彿畫圈一樣摸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.65,0:16:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左邊也是放在手心搖來搖去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.10,0:16:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.29,0:16:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底要幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.75,0:16:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…還有個願望想實現的說
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.36,0:16:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那有點困擾呢 願望一次只能一個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.08,0:16:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 沒關係哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.42,0:16:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.73,0:16:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡的男生？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.72,0:16:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我太晚熟關係拉不近 是非常帥氣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.22,0:16:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是滿臉鬍鬚像戰國武將一樣的男人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.94,0:17:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他喜歡上你就行了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.37,0:17:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的話 不用惡魔之力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.11,0:17:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用自己的努力讓他喜歡上我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.50,0:17:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就沒必要我們上嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.56,0:17:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 你直接當面跟他告白怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.09,0:17:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事…突然叫我做 絕對不可能的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.48,0:17:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫個信什麼的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.72,0:17:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫信嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.21,0:17:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對呢 情書也不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.35,0:17:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Love letter
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.69,0:17:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用文字傳達心意也很不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.70,0:17:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 我試試
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.92,0:17:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之至候差儀二而 無之候之條可
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.92,0:17:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}{\an8}摘自「森亂直筆書狀」 戰國時期 \N森蘭丸寫給團平八忠直的感謝信 森亂是指森蘭丸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.43,0:17:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被御心安候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.30,0:17:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣就只能是詭異文章吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.10,0:17:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Yes？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.68,0:17:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.54,0:17:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的不是形式而是心意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.78,0:17:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個心意能好好傳給對方嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.76,0:17:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 不是形式
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.25,0:17:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是形式哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.58,0:17:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.40,0:17:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.70,0:18:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,箭書有點太荒唐了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.89,0:18:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽 那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.55,0:18:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不能看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.98,0:18:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是在幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.90,0:18:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.95,0:18:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,箭！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.50,0:18:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蘇珊小姐 箭插進去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.98,0:18:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我想了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.52,0:18:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻想不出除了箭書以外的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.90,0:18:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過…那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.91,0:18:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信我讀了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.29,0:18:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是非常美的箭書
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.77,0:18:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然疏忽之時被箭射穿…真是厲害的箭書啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.59,0:19:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會呢 我只是一心想著好好射箭而已 堀井君
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.22,0:19:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腦袋快要瘋掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.56,0:19:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以的話 好想和你交往啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.04,0:19:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.51,0:19:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.31,0:19:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堀井君 好…好高興
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.64,0:19:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蘇珊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.22,0:19:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個鎧甲真美
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.84,0:19:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有 堀井君的盔甲也好硬好強壯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.01,0:19:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是像畫一樣般配的情侶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.57,0:19:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是呢 在某種意義上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.53,0:19:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.62,0:19:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.47,0:19:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得像這樣和喜歡的人在一起怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.08,0:19:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼怎樣 不是很幸福嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.86,0:19:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福…是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.66,0:19:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.38,0:19:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不喜歡還去交往是絕對不該做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.68,0:19:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事絕對不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.86,0:19:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.96,0:19:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？我在說什麼呢 真抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.75,0:20:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 謝謝你告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.95,0:20:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說一誠 你不是有話要說嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.94,0:20:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.16,0:20:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 誰也不在 這次一定要實現那個約定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.61,0:20:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次 上次約定好的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.86,0:20:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次的約定？我有跟你約定什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.38,0:20:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…是那個…咪咪！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.88,0:20:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我記得哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.04,0:20:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒必要擺那麼嚴肅的表情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.06,0:20:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 現在開始5秒的時間內 這個咪咪是你的了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.31,0:20:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.98,0:20:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然那麼說也…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.92,0:20:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.61,0:20:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 在我心理準備做好前會…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.47,0:20:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.52,0:20:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷靜 我要冷靜啊 要右邊還是左邊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.47,0:20:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.91,0:20:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話 兩邊一起揉啊揉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.53,0:20:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 你先來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.99,0:21:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們來晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.44,0:21:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.19,0:21:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5 好 結束~ 真可惜啊 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.56,0:21:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 怎麼了一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.35,0:21:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.11,0:21:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠你真太有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.79,0:21:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那麼想摸我的胸部嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.18,0:21:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…就給你補償一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.36,0:21:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…大家都在看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.17,0:21:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次也要加油哦 我可愛的一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.20,0:21:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.06,0:21:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲 你難道…
Comment: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ、こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}わたしキミのハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけスゴイのホントのところは? Naked soul, Wake UP↑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチぽいんだけど だまされてあげない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形やるしかないでしょ Don't you know? Baby
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今きゅんとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル キミは何も知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:47.87,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.71,0:22:49.65,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}NO-NO-NO トップシークレット 内緒ナイショです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.68,0:22:51.40,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}言えるワケがなーい!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.79,0:22:54.90,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}STUDY NOW!! 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ケシゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸にチョクで書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第!? 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Boy meets Girl きっとウンメイ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}STUDY×STUDY 恋はキマグレ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:23.54,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Boy meets Girl さぁご一緒に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.62,0:23:25.05,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}はじめよっ

Comment: 0,0:21:56.54,0:21:58.54,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這麼下去你會很糾結吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢？ Naked soul, Wake UP↑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然看起來還是生疏 但我是不會故意讓你騙到我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在是進行式 只能做了吧 Don't you know? Baby
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}因為剛剛心跳一下 3秒後可沒什麼保障哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你是不會知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:47.87,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它正在轉變為我的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.71,0:22:49.65,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}NO-NO-NO 這是最高機密 保密的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.68,0:22:51.40,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼可能說得出來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.79,0:22:54.90,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}STUDY NOW!! 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}用橡皮擦是擦不掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}因為是直接寫在你胸口上的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}以後的發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Boy meets Girl 這一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}STUDY×STUDY 戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:23.54,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Boy meets Girl 來我們一起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.62,0:23:25.05,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}開始吧
Comment: 0,0:23:33.36,0:23:36.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.34,0:23:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.12,0:23:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位是？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.72,0:23:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接看簡直是神級的！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.15,0:23:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太下流了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.61,0:23:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.73,0:23:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(417,210)}第7話「我要得到使魔！」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.60,0:23:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多麼美妙的情節啊！
