[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Original Script: DHR
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer:100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: DXD
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.31,0:00:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離遊戲開始還有1小時啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.73,0:00:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他對手是菲尼克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.99,0:00:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要讓他們領會到莉雅絲‧吉蒙里的眷屬的厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.48,0:00:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也拼命修行過了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕不能輸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.38,0:00:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 可以進來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.32,0:00:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.12,0:00:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.99,0:00:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個打扮是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.87,0:00:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來覺得穿修女服不適宜…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.02,0:00:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是社長說把自己打扮成認為自己最好的樣子來…所以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.51,0:00:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞果然最適合修女服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.78,0:00:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 可以坐在你身邊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.70,0:00:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.89,0:01:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.17,0:01:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來將要開始可怕的戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.54,0:01:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只要一誠君在的話 我就不擔心了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.61,0:01:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後也能一直待在一誠君的身邊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.88,0:01:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 一直在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.17,0:01:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間到了 準備好了嗎 起床…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.33,0:01:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 愛西亞
Comment: 0,0:01:45.41,0:01:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.45,0:01:51.39,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.55,0:01:57.04,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.27,0:02:02.76,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.07,0:02:09.08,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.28,0:02:15.92,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.21,0:02:21.64,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.01,0:02:24.72,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.90,0:02:27.77,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.93,0:02:39.74,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:01:24.96,0:01:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.45,0:01:51.39,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.55,0:01:57.04,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.27,0:02:02.76,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.07,0:02:09.08,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.28,0:02:15.92,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.21,0:02:21.64,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.01,0:02:24.72,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.90,0:02:27.77,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.93,0:02:39.74,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:10.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:10.06,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU 後期:KoU BDrip:ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.44,0:03:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,388)}第10話 「決戰開始了！」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.33,0:03:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是我們的姐姐大人 好冷靜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.14,0:03:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.76,0:03:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好 蒼那
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.64,0:03:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.50,0:03:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會長和副會長？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.54,0:03:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼來這
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.16,0:03:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,評估遊戲會轉播到跟參戰兩方有關係的人們那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.02,0:03:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們就是轉播人員
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.75,0:03:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是自願的 因為是莉雅絲的第一次戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.97,0:03:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能讓身為對手的你看到丟臉的戰鬥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.31,0:03:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都準備好了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.21,0:03:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 隨時可以
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.67,0:03:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了觀察時間 從這個魔法陣傳送到戰鬥用空間
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.75,0:03:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥用空間？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.44,0:04:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了遊戲而製造出的異次元空間
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.49,0:04:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為是製造出來的空間 做出任何華麗的事情都不要緊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.07,0:04:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,華麗…嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.65,0:04:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先回作為轉播的學生會室了 祝你好運 莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.58,0:04:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 轉播要公平點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.08,0:04:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然 不過就個人而言
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.91,0:04:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是認為那位大人配不上你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.08,0:04:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便一提這次戰鬥 魔王路西法也會看的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.04,0:04:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 哥哥要看…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.80,0:04:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 那個 剛才叫了哥哥？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.38,0:04:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我聽錯了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.21,0:04:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 社長的哥哥就是魔王大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.85,0:04:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔王？！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.03,0:04:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長的哥哥是魔王嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.38,0:04:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.57,0:04:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「紅髮魔王」 瑟傑克斯‧路西法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.00,0:05:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是現在社長的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.21,0:05:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑟傑克斯大人繼承了上屆大戰死去的魔王路西法一職
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.80,0:05:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以社長才要繼承吉蒙里家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.34,0:05:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.96,0:05:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是吉蒙里家的女兒 一直背負著吉蒙里這個名字
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.98,0:05:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多到時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.90,0:05:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出發吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.42,0:05:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和剛剛一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.73,0:05:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傳送失敗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.13,0:05:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道又是因為我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.78,0:05:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.21,0:05:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是這次被授予了吉蒙里家和菲尼克斯家的裁判一職的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.27,0:05:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉蒙里家的佣人葛雷菲亞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.05,0:06:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的戰鬥場地是參考莉雅絲大人和萊薩大人的意見
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.09,0:06:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,複製了莉雅絲大人所上的人間的學校 駒王學園
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.91,0:06:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,複製？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.29,0:06:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去看看外面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.90,0:06:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.34,0:06:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這裡是異次元
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.45,0:06:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這裡把學校原模原樣再現出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.99,0:06:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔的力量到底有多厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.74,0:06:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩方注意聽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.94,0:06:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被傳送後的目的地就是大本營
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.90,0:06:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人的大本營是舊教學樓超自然研究會部室
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.47,0:06:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,椿姬
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.29,0:06:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.04,0:06:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩大人的本陣是新教學樓校長室
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.68,0:06:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以各自能潛入到對方的教學樓
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.68,0:06:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以使用「兵卒」的「升級」技能
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.68,0:06:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(395,437)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.68,0:06:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(545,435)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.65,0:06:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能侵入到新教學樓裡我就能升級到最強「皇后」的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.65,0:06:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(637,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.68,0:06:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 沒這麼簡單的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.91,0:07:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反過來對方入侵到舊教學樓時也能升級
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.86,0:07:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要知道大本營的防禦是最堅不可破的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.32,0:07:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 確實
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.69,0:07:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.43,0:07:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在戰場上用這個連繫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.15,0:07:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,類似通訊器的東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.63,0:07:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 遊戲開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.15,0:07:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然對你們來說是輕鬆的活 但是不要留情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.50,0:07:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹底擊潰他們
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.61,0:07:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs35}不把那紅頭髮公主的自尊心擊潰的話 這場鬧劇根本沒有意義
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.36,0:07:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敵人的本陣是新教學樓
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.92,0:07:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從校園中庭去是最快的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.88,0:07:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是從新教學樓看的話 我們就完全暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.69,0:07:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風險太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.60,0:07:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼要進入新教學樓的話 可以從後面的用於田徑競技的運動場
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.19,0:07:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕這個應該也在敵人的意料當中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.70,0:08:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs32}估計會在這運動部室裡安排數名機動性高的「騎士」和「城堡」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.70,0:08:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(595,440)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.70,0:08:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(725,440)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.16,0:08:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是常規的做法 但這也是確實的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.31,0:08:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 先佔領和新舊教學樓連在一起的體育館如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.80,0:08:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我們的大本營很近 更何況能牽制他們
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.48,0:08:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(637,438)}{\fs23}<Center>
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.48,0:08:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體育館的位置按國際象棋來說是中心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.72,0:08:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先占領了 從戰術來說比較有利
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.22,0:08:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決定了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.62,0:08:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為是室內 所以比起機動性高的「騎士」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.62,0:08:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(644,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.50,0:08:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更具破壞力的「城堡」能更加發揮其特性
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.50,0:08:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(396,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.40,0:08:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥很複雜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.71,0:08:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們只要相信社長 聽她指揮就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.60,0:08:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.49,0:08:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先先確定防禦陣線
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.15,0:08:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佑斗 小貓咪先去樹林裡設下陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.11,0:08:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 了解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.76,0:08:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出來 小白
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.09,0:08:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我們去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.30,0:09:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃 陷阱設置完後
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.18,0:09:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就在樹林的周圍包括天空裡施幻術
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.61,0:09:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.18,0:09:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 社長 我們呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.21,0:09:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治療的愛西亞就和我一起在這裡待機
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.64,0:09:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒下了就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.43,0:09:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠的話 躺到這裡來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.68,0:09:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.44,0:09:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 難道是傳說中的膝枕？！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.78,0:09:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點過來！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.93,0:09:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.12,0:09:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該怎麼形容這感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.68,0:09:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又軟又嫩 就那樣 被緊緊包裹著
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.57,0:09:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明在重要的比賽裡 這真的殺必死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.87,0:10:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.35,0:10:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓社長為我膝枕 感動的眼淚停不下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.57,0:10:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活著真好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.77,0:10:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小題大作呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.65,0:10:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就膝枕而已 以後再給你做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.48,0:10:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.68,0:10:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以快把鼻水眼淚擦了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.03,0:10:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 我稍微解開下曾在你身上施放的咒術
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.83,0:10:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 去下一處
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.56,0:10:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.06,0:11:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量從身體深處…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.68,0:11:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說過讓你重生需要八個棋子的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.17,0:11:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.66,0:11:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛重生好的你的身體還承受不了這個力量
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.29,0:11:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以分幾階段把你的力量封印起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.24,0:11:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛稍微解除了點封印
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.30,0:11:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼剛剛在我體內沸騰的這個力量
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.05,0:11:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你本來的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.06,0:11:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}在這之前需要能承受「赤龍帝之籠手」和這個力量的強壯的身體是必須的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.06,0:11:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(346,441)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.18,0:11:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然還有很多不足之處
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.42,0:11:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個艱苦的修行原來為了這個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.86,0:11:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我卻在心裡喊著魔鬼社長什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.59,0:11:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這人 我這人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.20,0:11:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到社長如此深思謀慮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.72,0:12:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主啊 請原諒剛剛吃醋的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.99,0:12:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好一誠 就算對手是女孩子 你一定要去打到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.14,0:12:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕不可以手軟 因為對方是毫不留情的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.55,0:12:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 我一定會讓社長贏得勝利的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.91,0:12:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會期待的 我可愛的一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.35,0:12:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 聽得見嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.19,0:12:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 能聽得到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.36,0:12:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備完畢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.18,0:12:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 開始說明作戰計劃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.86,0:12:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人有所行動了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.21,0:12:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為缺少棋子 所以完全守住本營是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.09,0:12:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼一來 只能以速攻推進
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.38,0:12:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好 一旦進入體育館 戰鬥將無法避免
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.67,0:12:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千萬記住要按照指示行動
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.27,0:12:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.27,0:12:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佑斗 準備好沒？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.43,0:13:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.75,0:13:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃就看準時機行動
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.68,0:13:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.55,0:13:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作戰開始！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.22,0:13:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可愛的僕人們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.33,0:13:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs32}對手是連不死身‧菲尼克斯家族也認為很有前途的人才萊薩‧菲尼克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.89,0:13:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 去消滅他們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.96,0:13:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 大家 請加油
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.57,0:13:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連裡面都再現的這麼完美
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.15,0:13:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有敵人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.46,0:13:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你們在那裡 吉蒙里家的僕人們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.83,0:13:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來偷偷摸摸的行動是不管用的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.58,0:13:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是「城堡」和…看起來格外有精神的「兵卒」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.58,0:13:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(199,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.58,0:13:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(653,435)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.27,0:13:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是之前被妮亞秒殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.45,0:13:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是尼亞 屬性是「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.45,0:13:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(536,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.05,0:13:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是「城堡」修艾爾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.05,0:13:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(411,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.24,0:13:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是「兵卒」妮露 同樣是「兵卒」美露
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.24,0:13:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(284,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.24,0:13:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(567,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.23,0:14:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個「城堡」 等級相當高
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.23,0:14:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(377,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.59,0:14:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.73,0:14:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,論戰鬥力的話是「女王」級別
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.73,0:14:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(504,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.85,0:14:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.19,0:14:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也好 我對自己的不利情況一開始就心知肚明
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.21,0:14:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能拼了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.45,0:14:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.74,0:14:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.78,0:14:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對付「城堡」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.78,0:14:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(473,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.53,0:14:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠學長對付這些「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.53,0:14:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(546,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.00,0:14:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打不過的話 至少要逃竄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.56,0:14:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用擔心我 我是有勝算的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.06,0:14:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 上了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.39,0:14:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是從中央廳攻打過來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.60,0:14:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突擊隊情況如何
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.43,0:14:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.49,0:14:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修莉亞 瑪麗歐 格蘭特
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.95,0:14:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三名「兵卒」正在潛入
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.93,0:14:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(395,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.33,0:14:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水霧怎麼冒出來這麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.13,0:14:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陷阱？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.29,0:14:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不怎麼樣嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.37,0:14:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的只能騙騙小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.51,0:14:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這菜鳥樣 真可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.65,0:15:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.25,0:15:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺能幹…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.51,0:15:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是何方神聖
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.42,0:15:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是莉雅絲大人的僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.11,0:15:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肢解你～ 肢解你～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.28,0:15:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你逃也沒用的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.08,0:15:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖地被解體吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.24,0:15:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用那種明朗的聲音 說出那樣的話是不可以的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.13,0:15:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說我可不想被解體
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.10,0:16:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.46,0:16:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次可避開了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.54,0:16:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肢解你～ 肢解你～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.03,0:16:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是這行得通
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.56,0:16:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讓人火大
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.49,0:16:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼打不中啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.97,0:16:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是經過拼命的修煉的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.30,0:16:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輕而易舉地輸掉話就對不起社長和夥伴了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.14,0:16:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.38,0:16:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要上了「赤龍帝之籠手」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.38,0:16:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(471,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.37,0:16:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Explosion!!」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.76,0:16:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先從你們開始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.04,0:16:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.61,0:16:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.88,0:16:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.89,0:16:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把我的棍棒…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.93,0:16:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.46,0:16:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 這樣一來條件齊全了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.03,0:17:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若輸給這種男人 會讓萊薩大人生氣的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.89,0:17:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下絕不原諒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.12,0:17:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對讓你支離破碎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.03,0:17:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是現在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.29,0:17:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.49,0:17:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的必殺技
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.34,0:17:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「洋服崩壞」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.37,0:17:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(426,436)}<Dress Break>
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.92,0:17:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.21,0:17:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何 見識到了沒？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.78,0:17:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在腦中不停地妄想著 把女孩子的衣服轟飛…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.04,0:17:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…對 就是不停的妄想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.05,0:17:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把我擁有的魔力才能 全都用在把女孩子弄成裸體上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.30,0:17:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我的必殺技「洋服崩壞」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.30,0:17:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(546,436)}<Dress Break>
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.01,0:17:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真下流
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.37,0:17:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是在接觸女人的瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.66,0:17:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把自己的腦中的形象化作魔力注入了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.12,0:17:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然具有獨創性…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.08,0:17:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差勁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.85,0:17:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禽獸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.54,0:17:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人的公敵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.49,0:18:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.32,0:18:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.23,0:18:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.95,0:18:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 愛西亞 再來一次
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.85,0:18:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那我去換衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.16,0:18:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.60,0:18:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣不行 光是衣服話是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.29,0:18:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然屢次讓你為難
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.01,0:18:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的 我有很多別人送的舊衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.83,0:18:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.65,0:18:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你的功勞 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.93,0:18:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看錯你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.91,0:18:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.78,0:18:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把敵方「城堡」…不愧是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.78,0:18:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.44,0:18:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓 一誠 戰況如可
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.20,0:18:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 我和小貓咪都沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.49,0:18:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如說現在很有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.78,0:18:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.50,0:19:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃已經準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.89,0:19:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照作戰計劃來 拜託你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.43,0:19:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想逃跑嗎 還沒分出勝負啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.22,0:19:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算放棄自己的陣地嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.54,0:19:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩大人的「兵卒」三名 「城堡」一名
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.54,0:19:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(376,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.54,0:19:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(567,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.73,0:19:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥不能
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.93,0:19:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.66,0:19:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐的通稱是「雷之巫女」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.43,0:19:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據說其名稱和力量 只有真正懂的人才會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.69,0:19:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「雷之巫女」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.09,0:19:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若被那樣的一擊受教訓的話 那必死無疑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.57,0:19:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放棄重要陣地 反而利用它用於攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.02,0:19:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不讓人以為是頭一次的大膽性
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.80,0:19:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.54,0:19:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是 這樣一來萊薩大人就不得不拿出真實力了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.73,0:19:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 真正可怕的現在才開始
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.79,0:19:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在數量上還是對方佔優勢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.51,0:20:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到朱乃能放使出第二波為止是需要時間的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.88,0:20:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦朱乃魔力復原 我們也到前線去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.07,0:20:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前 你們各自為下一步計劃展開行動
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.02,0:20:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一個是？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.22,0:20:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田徑競技運動場附近跟佑斗學長會合
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.45,0:20:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後殲滅之後的敵人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.40,0:20:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說回來 木場他沒問題吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.44,0:20:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們真以為這樣的陷阱能保護你們嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.78,0:20:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是敵人的大本營
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.78,0:20:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.98,0:20:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遺憾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.29,0:20:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們已經從這出不去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.08,0:20:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你們正在我們「女王」佈置的結界當中
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.08,0:20:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(440,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.92,0:20:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 被這些陷阱分神了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.99,0:20:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人手不足的話就拿智慧去彌補
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.88,0:20:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你算是我喜歡的類型 所以本想不想說的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.88,0:20:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非你以為3對1能贏得了我們嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.20,0:21:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要試一試嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.83,0:21:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是他的話 會以清爽的表情好好幹的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.46,0:21:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪 我們也走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.70,0:21:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.81,0:21:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用擔心了 又不用在自己人身上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.17,0:21:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣 那是很低級的招數
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.45,0:21:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來真被她討厭了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.37,0:21:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.41,0:21:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.27,0:21:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓 小貓怎麼了 回答我 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.89,0:21:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲 你可別小看我這萊薩‧菲尼克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.06,0:21:55.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(424,436)}<Take>
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.06,0:21:55.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「擊破」
Comment: 0,0:21:57.99,0:22:00.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「紅髮滅殺姬」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.92,0:23:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(426,436)}<Ruin Princess>
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.54,0:23:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「聖母的微笑」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.54,0:23:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Twilight Healing>
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.20,0:23:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「雷之巫女」還有 「魔劍製造」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.20,0:23:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(551,436)}<Sword Berth>
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.19,0:23:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝之籠手」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.19,0:23:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.62,0:23:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是一排聽起來很厲害的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.47,0:23:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們是菲尼克斯 不死之身
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.77,0:23:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(417,210)}第11話 「絕讚，決戰進行中！」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.06,0:23:52.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
