[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 4
Video Position: 20338
Last Style Storage: DXD
Collisions: Normal


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.19,0:00:06.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吶吶 一誠 快點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.32,0:00:08.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水很甜哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.30,0:00:09.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.04,0:00:13.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…我要不要也拿一點行李…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.58,0:00:16.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧 一誠才不會被那點行李壓倒的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.46,0:00:18.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先走一步了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.74,0:00:20.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡啊 木場那混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.65,0:00:21.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然在我面前表現得這麼游刃有餘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.81,0:00:23.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.92,0:00:28.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我輸了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.76,0:00:32.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.87,0:00:35.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,時間定為十天後
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.01,0:00:36.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,十天後…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.67,0:00:39.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從萊薩大人與莉雅絲大人的以往交鋒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.20,0:00:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及現有戰力來看
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.96,0:00:44.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的結果是理所當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.51,0:00:46.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很不甘
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.79,0:00:48.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但也不得不接受啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.78,0:00:50.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我們就感激地接下他們給予的期限
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.88,0:00:53.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來作為這期間的修行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.23,0:00:59.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 在這次的合宿裡讓你變得更強
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.02,0:01:01.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更加強…更加強
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.36,0:01:03.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我讓你…
Comment: 0,0:01:21.43,0:01:29.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.43,0:01:27.37,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.53,0:01:33.02,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.25,0:01:38.74,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.05,0:01:45.06,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.26,0:01:51.90,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.19,0:01:57.62,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.99,0:02:00.70,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.88,0:02:03.75,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.91,0:02:15.72,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:01:00.94,0:01:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.43,0:01:27.37,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.53,0:01:33.02,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.25,0:01:38.74,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.05,0:01:45.06,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.26,0:01:51.90,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.19,0:01:57.62,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.99,0:02:00.70,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.88,0:02:03.75,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.91,0:02:15.72,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Comment: 0,0:00:02.85,0:00:12.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:10.03,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU 後期:KoU BDrip:ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.50,0:02:39.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,388)}第9話「修行開始了 ！」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.01,0:02:42.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太漂亮了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.42,0:02:45.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 趕快進去開始修行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.31,0:02:46.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就開始！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.18,0:02:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長你果然是惡鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.05,0:02:51.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是惡魔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.96,0:03:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吶 木場
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.39,0:03:07.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說啊 之前在教會戰鬥的那次
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.40,0:03:11.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好像說過你很恨墮天使和神父之類的啊…那是什麼情況
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.99,0:03:14.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,個人不太喜歡墮天使和神父…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.31,0:03:16.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說恨也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.22,0:03:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無論是一誠你還是愛西亞 你們都是被社長所救之人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.76,0:03:23.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們也是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.35,0:03:27.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們必須為了社長而奔走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.16,0:03:28.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說的對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.10,0:03:30.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這肯定的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.56,0:03:31.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且是絕對的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.91,0:03:32.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Lession 1
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.06,0:03:34.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話是這樣說啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.70,0:03:38.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是這樣揮的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.04,0:03:40.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不僅要看清劍的路線
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.23,0:03:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且還要注意對手與周圍環境
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.13,0:03:47.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是騎士啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.13,0:03:47.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(474,438)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.86,0:03:49.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說你啊 別掉以輕心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.58,0:03:52.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Lession 2
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.32,0:03:56.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔力是讓深藏於全身的氣引出來從而收集的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.53,0:04:01.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,集中精神
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.39,0:04:03.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感知魔力的波動
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.00,0:04:05.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.15,0:04:14.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦啊啦 搞不好愛西亞醬很有魔法天賦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.06,0:04:19.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 只要愛西亞能變強 我也能那個啥了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.26,0:04:23.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.62,0:04:29.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要習慣了 就能從無中生出火 水 甚至是雷
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.25,0:04:32.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞來練習這個吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.02,0:04:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.40,0:04:35.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠要繼續練習魔力的冥想哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.27,0:04:39.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔力的泉源是想像
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.38,0:04:40.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是…是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.98,0:04:47.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之最重要的是要把腦中所想之物具現化
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.76,0:04:50.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,腦中想的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.43,0:04:51.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.94,0:04:56.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有沒錯 集中精神 集中精神
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.96,0:05:03.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我究竟在想什麼啊 我這個人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.27,0:05:05.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 一誠？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.88,0:05:08.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.65,0:05:09.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.10,0:05:11.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Lession 3
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.59,0:05:15.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弱爆了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.65,0:05:18.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒完啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.37,0:05:23.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻擊要瞄準身體的中心部位
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.20,0:05:26.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓敵人無法還擊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.77,0:05:35.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打又打不過木場和小貓咪 魔力又在愛西亞之下…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.10,0:05:36.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不就一點好處都沒嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.14,0:05:39.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特性因人而異
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.29,0:05:40.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特性？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.74,0:05:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你覺得我的特性是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.31,0:05:44.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,H之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.17,0:05:47.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有一點
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.07,0:05:50.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很努力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.98,0:05:52.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.51,0:05:54.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會努力的了 小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.96,0:05:55.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.78,0:06:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Lession 4
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.93,0:06:02.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次是使用魔力！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.87,0:06:04.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做料理嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.52,0:06:06.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要在允許的範圍就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.11,0:06:08.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你們要努力了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.40,0:06:11.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,熱水先生 請沸騰起來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.76,0:06:21.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在朱乃的課程上 拼了老命也才只做出個小米粒般的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.37,0:06:27.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但即便如此啊 只要能回想起朱乃的咪咪我就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.46,0:06:36.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒 馬鈴薯也只是小菜一碟啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.35,0:06:39.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.03,0:06:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才是碰巧不在狀態 這就是我的真正實力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.38,0:06:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.19,0:06:49.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺這之前也有發生過…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.21,0:06:52.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 就是那個時候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.11,0:06:55.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是第一次發動「神器」的時候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.11,0:06:55.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(457,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.96,0:06:57.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.95,0:07:00.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能會讓我變得…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.82,0:07:04.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無敵！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.36,0:07:09.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生…這個…該怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.66,0:07:18.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔力的泉源是想像
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.97,0:07:23.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之最重要的是要把腦中所想之物具現化
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.26,0:07:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特性因人而異
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.83,0:07:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,H之類的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.56,0:07:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總感覺一副下流的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.05,0:07:33.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有這樣的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.30,0:07:36.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.41,0:07:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.47,0:07:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,覺得今天的修行怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.07,0:07:44.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊…我是這裡最弱的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.46,0:07:46.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這也沒錯呢 這確實是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.92,0:07:50.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}但是啊 愛西亞的回復 還有你的「赤龍帝之籠手」都是很重要的戰力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.94,0:07:50.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(472,440)}Boostet Gear
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.97,0:07:52.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然也是寶貴的戰鬥力
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.03,0:07:55.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對方也應該了解這一點
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.56,0:08:00.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了不拖同伴後腿 最少也要有逃跑能力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.70,0:08:02.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 了解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.65,0:08:06.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 把愛西亞捲進這場戰鬥的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.10,0:08:11.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要習得能保護愛西亞的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.77,0:08:12.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.20,0:08:16.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼晚飯也吃完了 去洗澡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.45,0:08:17.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡？！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.12,0:08:21.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉 一誠 想要偷看我們洗澡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.57,0:08:24.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼一起洗吧  我是無所謂的～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.66,0:08:25.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.60,0:08:30.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真想給這位大人擦背呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.68,0:08:34.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞的話 是喜歡的一誠的話沒關係吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.92,0:08:37.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.18,0:08:38.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.76,0:08:40.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就不行了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.25,0:08:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遺憾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.74,0:08:45.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偷看的話就揍你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.17,0:08:50.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然溫泉是好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.76,0:08:55.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣能消除大家修練的勞累就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.91,0:08:59.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肯定消除啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.60,0:09:06.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是奢侈的咪咪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.11,0:09:13.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.44,0:09:19.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 做那種事情有什麼意義
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.46,0:09:21.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴 這也是修行的一環
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.24,0:09:25.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠想要透視能力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.94,0:09:30.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得我的特性是什麼呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.21,0:09:31.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,H之類的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.97,0:09:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 這就是我的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.47,0:09:36.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的能力！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.65,0:09:56.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.55,0:09:57.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.81,0:10:00.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真像莉雅絲的作風呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.22,0:10:02.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐有機會贏嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.75,0:10:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.00,0:10:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您知道這點卻…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.30,0:10:09.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只不過給了她選擇權
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.75,0:10:12.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是莉雅絲自己的決定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.13,0:10:15.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作為吉蒙里的下任當家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.35,0:10:16.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.51,0:10:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.15,0:10:33.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.47,0:10:35.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼晚了抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.35,0:10:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情只能拜託愛西亞了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.42,0:10:42.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.68,0:10:47.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能行的 絕對能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.25,0:10:55.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.00,0:10:58.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞  想向你借衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.52,0:11:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 那麼認真的態度
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.37,0:11:03.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底想幹嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.80,0:11:17.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我們惡魔和墮天使和跟著神的天使
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.58,0:11:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很久以前在永恆的時間裡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.63,0:11:23.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發動過三次大戰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.57,0:11:27.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,結果沒人勝利或失敗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.63,0:11:31.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為所有戰鬥力都戰死了  戰爭結束
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.71,0:11:37.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔雖然有永恆的時間 出生率卻十分的低
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.13,0:11:41.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為大戰的原因演變成了種族危機
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.93,0:11:50.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs32}大戰過後 關係到純血惡魔 被稱為七十二柱魔的名門基本上都斷絕了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.51,0:11:57.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我「吉蒙里家」 蒼那「支取家」萊薩「菲尼克斯家」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.78,0:12:00.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以說是七十二柱魔僅剩的幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.87,0:12:06.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是惡魔讓人類變成眷屬的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.96,0:12:09.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,評估遊戲就是這樣由來的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.26,0:12:19.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根據遊戲運用眷屬的實戰經驗 也能展示眷屬主人的實力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.81,0:12:24.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算現在遊戲的成績對爵位和土地也有很大的影響
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.76,0:12:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,稍微休息會兒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.38,0:12:32.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家也都累了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.99,0:12:34.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我去倒茶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.13,0:12:36.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我也幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.14,0:12:39.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 昨晚對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.96,0:12:44.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事 很厲害一誠  那麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.48,0:12:47.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這件事是我們二人的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.86,0:12:48.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,二人的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.54,0:12:53.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒完成 要在後天的實戰裡實用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.96,0:12:59.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 在一誠的必殺技完成前我會幫你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.92,0:13:00.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必殺技？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.89,0:13:02.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.41,0:13:06.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想聽聽原修女的你的意見
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.89,0:13:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.96,0:13:15.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驅魔師擁有的道具有二種
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.56,0:13:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一種是這個 聖水
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.42,0:13:21.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身為惡魔的大家絕對不要去碰
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.37,0:13:23.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,碰到了的話會怎麼樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.27,0:13:25.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會變成很麻煩的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.21,0:13:27.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很麻煩？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.53,0:13:30.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,含糊的說明 反而感到害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.20,0:13:34.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞你也是哦 因為也是惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.72,0:13:36.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恩 是這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.39,0:13:39.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道有沒有幫到你們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.91,0:13:42.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用方法等下告訴你們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.25,0:13:43.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後另一種是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.58,0:13:45.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聖書
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.01,0:13:48.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小時候開始一直讀的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.58,0:13:53.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是現在只要讀一頁就會變成很可怕的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.31,0:13:54.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,煩惱著
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.75,0:14:01.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為是惡魔嘛X4
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.01,0:14:05.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是但是這一頁是十分出色的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.67,0:14:07.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,額 頭痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.26,0:14:12.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,主啊 原諒不能讀聖書的我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.99,0:14:15.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.93,0:14:21.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是真的天然還是裝傻真的很難分辨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.33,0:14:25.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我沒有愛西亞這樣的才能
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.66,0:14:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.26,0:14:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.89,0:14:39.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 這麼晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.22,0:14:44.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正好 我們聊會兒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.31,0:14:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是作戰計劃嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.05,0:14:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,照這麼下去的話 勝率十分的小
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.76,0:15:01.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有這樣的事 社長這麼晚了還在努力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.55,0:15:05.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是這次的對手是菲尼克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.64,0:15:07.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.07,0:15:09.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被稱為不死鳥的神鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.11,0:15:15.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是惡魔但是擁有神獸的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.09,0:15:19.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,七十二柱魔的公爵家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.76,0:15:22.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且能力和神獸也是一樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.32,0:15:23.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不死
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.00,0:15:27.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不死之身什麼的 這種事可能嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.37,0:15:30.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 基本上是無敵的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.25,0:15:33.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使被攻擊了 也能馬上再生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.97,0:15:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩的戰績是8勝2敗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.96,0:15:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是這2敗是因為考慮到家系的問題所以故意敗北
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.69,0:15:48.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自從評估遊戲開始盛行起來後
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.88,0:15:54.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,菲尼克斯家就急劇擴大其勢力範圍 就像暴發戶似的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.22,0:15:57.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是理所當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.66,0:16:01.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是不死之身的話是絕不會輸的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.38,0:16:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.90,0:16:04.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.13,0:16:09.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是因為我當時跟萊薩頂撞 才變得不得不跟他戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.01,0:16:11.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 倒不如說
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.47,0:16:14.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多虧因為你才能讓談話進行的更快 幫我大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.41,0:16:20.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從一開始父親就預料到我會輸 所以才謀劃了這次遊戲
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.20,0:16:24.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用國際象棋用語來說是「詭計棋譜」應該是詐騙戰術吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.20,0:16:24.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(669,438)}<Swindle>
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.16,0:16:29.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…社長為什麼要拒絕此次婚事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.36,0:16:37.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36}我是吉蒙里家的女兒 不管走到哪裡 都不會作為莉雅絲我個人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.91,0:16:40.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使變成惡魔也是莉雅絲‧吉蒙里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.28,0:16:45.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉蒙里這名一直糾纏著我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.82,0:16:48.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然這對我來說是一種自豪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.43,0:16:52.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但至少希望與我相伴一生的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.55,0:16:56.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡的是作為莉雅絲的我 而不是作為吉蒙里家女兒的我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.45,0:16:58.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我希望跟喜歡我這個莉雅絲的人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.56,0:17:02.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然這思念有矛盾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.93,0:17:06.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使這樣我還是希望擁有這小小的願望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.02,0:17:10.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡社長跟這些事無關
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.16,0:17:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉蒙里家 惡魔的社會什麼的 說實話我完全不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.46,0:17:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在在這…像這樣…在我眼前的莉雅絲學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.33,0:17:22.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說是最重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.38,0:17:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說了什麼奇怪的話嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.16,0:17:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.03,0:17:33.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之既然戰鬥就要拿出全實力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.31,0:17:40.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}之前從木場聽說 社長是「Ruin Princess」都被稱為「滅殺公主」的天才
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.48,0:17:43.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長初次上陣的對手竟然是如此厲害的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.28,0:17:44.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.93,0:17:53.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的能力不是上天賜予的 而是歷代吉蒙里家培養出來的結晶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.35,0:17:56.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是屬於吉蒙里家和我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.94,0:17:59.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我絕不能輸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.02,0:18:01.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然戰鬥就要贏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.70,0:18:03.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只能贏下去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.15,0:18:07.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然社長很厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.41,0:18:11.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反過來我 多麼沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.80,0:18:13.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.07,0:18:17.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到這一步讓我痛徹地認識到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.95,0:18:19.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自己是最沒用的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.39,0:18:25.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是很厲害的「神器」到了我這兒就沒什麼意義
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.39,0:18:25.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(364,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.34,0:18:28.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我還是只憑一時衝動猛衝過去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.16,0:18:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,結果只是給社長添麻煩而已
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.73,0:18:33.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像我這種人 像我這種人…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.98,0:18:35.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全派不上用場
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.54,0:18:38.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是想要自信是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.61,0:18:39.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.45,0:18:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以 我可以讓你有自信
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.46,0:18:45.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自信…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.53,0:18:47.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.19,0:18:49.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以現在就先休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.57,0:18:52.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓身心得到休息 哪怕是一會兒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.48,0:18:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到你入睡為止 我會一直在你身旁的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.79,0:19:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安心吧 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.06,0:19:05.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定會讓你有自信的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.61,0:19:12.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用「Boostet Gear」 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.11,0:19:17.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是社長曾說過 合宿中是禁止使用的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.24,0:19:19.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是指沒有我許可的情況
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.64,0:19:22.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佑斗 你來當對手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.51,0:19:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.26,0:19:25.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不會手下留情的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.43,0:19:31.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Boostet Gear」！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.16,0:19:33.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.40,0:19:34.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.54,0:19:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.79,0:19:36.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.96,0:19:37.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.11,0:19:39.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.18,0:19:40.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.35,0:19:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還不夠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.43,0:19:42.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.66,0:19:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.92,0:19:44.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來一次
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.89,0:19:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.01,0:19:47.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.15,0:19:47.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多來點
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.18,0:19:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost Boost Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.19,0:19:52.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.23,0:19:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣力量一共翻倍了12次
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.11,0:19:55.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.54,0:19:57.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 你能明白嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.38,0:20:02.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是之前的你的話 是承受不了這樣的強化的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.10,0:20:09.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,修煉的成果都不漏的體現在了你身上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.16,0:20:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.61,0:20:11.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開始
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.52,0:20:12.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我上了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.43,0:20:14.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Boostet Gear!」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.62,0:20:15.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Explosion!!」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.25,0:20:18.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.38,0:20:25.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的聲音可以讓一誠一定時間內保持強化的狀態下去戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.37,0:20:26.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佑斗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.00,0:20:36.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 射出魔力能量束
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.39,0:20:39.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然就這點而已嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.85,0:20:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快射出
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.52,0:20:45.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.61,0:20:59.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一座山…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.69,0:21:03.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…沒了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.02,0:21:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我的技能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.61,0:21:09.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.76,0:21:12.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來是力量用盡了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.89,0:21:14.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佑斗 他表現得如何
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.15,0:21:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說實話 剛才那一擊簡直就是上級惡魔級別
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.66,0:21:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠是這場遊戲的關鍵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.20,0:21:30.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕一誠的攻擊力 會在很大程度上掌控局勢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.56,0:21:33.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要相信我們…比什麼都更要相信自己
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.51,0:21:38.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相信大家…相信自己
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.37,0:21:43.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.28,0:21:47.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡社長跟這些事無關
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.46,0:21:50.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲學姐對我來說是最重要的
Comment: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:06.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.60,0:22:00.99,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.99,0:22:05.12,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.52,0:22:21.13,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.20,0:22:26.80,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.83,0:22:32.47,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know? Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.47,0:22:37.36,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.36,0:22:43.91,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.09,0:22:48.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.33,0:22:51.51,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.93,0:22:54.96,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.12,0:22:57.97,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:00.89,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.04,0:23:03.20,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.37,0:23:09.10,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.39,0:23:13.33,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.37,0:23:15.38,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.38,0:23:18.00,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.03,0:23:20.73,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.93,0:23:25.28,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:22:00.99,0:22:00.99,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.60,0:22:00.99,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.99,0:22:05.12,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.52,0:22:21.13,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.20,0:22:26.80,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.83,0:22:32.47,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know? Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.47,0:22:37.36,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.36,0:22:43.91,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.09,0:22:48.32,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.33,0:22:51.51,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.93,0:22:54.96,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.12,0:22:57.97,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:00.89,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.04,0:23:03.20,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.37,0:23:09.10,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.39,0:23:13.33,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.37,0:23:15.38,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.38,0:23:18.00,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.03,0:23:20.73,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.93,0:23:25.28,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.09,0:23:33.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明處在很重要的遊戲當中 但這實在是太殺必死了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.48,0:23:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你在哭什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.16,0:23:41.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(417,210)}第10話 「決戰開始了！」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.65,0:23:39.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.94,0:23:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,時間到了 準備好了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.06,0:00:02.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
