[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Original Script: DHR
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: DXD
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.52,0:00:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好紅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.44,0:00:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同那個人的髮色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.94,0:00:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好紅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.70,0:00:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比Strawberry blonde更加鮮紅的頭髮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.32,0:00:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猶如被染紅的這隻手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.29,0:00:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美麗的紅艷長髮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.70,0:00:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 就是那個人的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.42,0:00:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為我而活吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.39,0:00:11.40,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀  校譯:小囈  時軸:希梅亞&KoU  後期:konataメ夏汐  BDrip:ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.84,0:00:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,400)\fs35\fsp2\pos(253,125)\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1}第1話 「交到女朋友啦!」

Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.05,0:00:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想揉揉咪咪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.18,0:00:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同意兵藤一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.85,0:00:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說了 太不現實了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.64,0:00:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松田 元濱 我們怎麼來這間學校了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.65,0:00:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們私立駒王學園才剛從女子高中變成男女合校
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.28,0:00:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 女生數量極其龐大
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.20,0:01:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來自海外的美少女留學生也不在少數
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.49,0:01:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 男生極其稀少
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.29,0:01:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.12,0:01:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你再不顯眼 也超級受歡迎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.04,0:01:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直就是理想鄉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.92,0:01:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是傳說中的 後宮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.51,0:01:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 等待著我們的是波濤洶湧的現充生活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.34,0:01:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,fight fight…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.89,0:01:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但實際上是 一直沒有交到女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.18,0:01:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就快到第二年的春天了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.23,0:01:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.40,0:01:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越說越空虛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.82,0:01:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能輕易言棄啊 機會還有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.95,0:01:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木場君
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.41,0:01:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來準備去哪裡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.78,0:01:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 一起去卡拉OK好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.66,0:01:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我還有社團活動
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.75,0:01:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒…真可惜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.71,0:01:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得你們來邀請我 真是非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.29,0:01:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二年級C班 木場祐斗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.46,0:01:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為全校女生的愛慕對象
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:01:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們全體男生的最大敵人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.39,0:02:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.97,0:02:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不過是稍微長得帥了些 頭腦過人 性格溫順而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.89,0:02:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這麼多女生上鉤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.47,0:02:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說了 越說越悲劇
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.85,0:02:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界真不公平啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.65,0:02:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕 快到時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.86,0:02:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.61,0:02:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村山的咪咪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.36,0:02:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超級大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.28,0:02:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,82-70-71
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.28,0:02:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片瀨 好腿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.79,0:02:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,78.5-65-79
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.00,0:02:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上體育課時偶然發現的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.25,0:02:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說啊 也給我瞧瞧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.51,0:02:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個別獨佔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.68,0:02:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有誰在?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.85,0:02:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹什麼啊 喂 松田
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.14,0:02:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,元…濱…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.56,0:02:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.61,0:02:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.40,0:02:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死色狼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.70,0:03:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.20,0:03:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般也不會用竹劍揍的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.53,0:03:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是災難啊 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.45,0:03:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然拋下兄弟自己跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.08,0:03:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是讓我看到了咪咪也沒什麼話說了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.79,0:03:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但現在什麼都沒看到就直接揍我一頓…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.35,0:03:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舊校舍裡有人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.73,0:03:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮啊 那鮮紅的長髮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.15,0:03:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲·吉蒙里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.23,0:03:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,99-58-90
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.57,0:03:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年級兼神秘學研究社社長
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.95,0:03:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傳聞北歐人氏
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.75,0:03:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.12,0:03:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.33,0:03:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中間那個
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.92,0:04:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二年級B班的 記得好像叫兵藤來著
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.17,0:04:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那男生怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.13,0:04:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼 錯覺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.51,0:04:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將軍
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.94,0:04:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡單的問題呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.40,0:04:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的問題來多少都能簡單對付呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.70,0:04:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 那就期待下次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.28,0:05:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是黑暗的青春啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.99,0:05:15.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再這樣下去我的學生時代就要在平凡無奇
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.54,0:05:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就連咪咪也不能摸摸的日常中結束啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.17,0:05:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.05,0:05:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是駒王學園的兵藤一誠同學嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.60,0:05:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.39,0:05:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒見過的制服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.02,0:05:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪間學校呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.23,0:05:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.64,0:05:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.15,0:05:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.36,0:05:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤現在有正在交往的人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.32,0:05:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒…沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.62,0:05:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.08,0:05:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 能跟我交往嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.04,0:06:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛才說…什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.09,0:06:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前看到過你路過這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.09,0:06:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後就…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.93,0:06:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對兵藤…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.14,0:06:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 這不就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.22,0:06:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請跟我…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.65,0:06:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請跟我交往！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.11,0:06:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.91,0:06:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快給我起來 快給我起來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.95,0:06:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不起來我就要親下去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.25,0:06:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快給我起來 快給我起來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.26,0:06:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.51,0:06:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.55,0:06:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位女生是 天野夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.60,0:06:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這班傢伙是我的死黨松田和元濱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.89,0:06:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.64,0:07:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑且算是我的 女·朋·友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.19,0:07:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 你們也要趕快交到女朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.15,0:07:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走吧 夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.36,0:07:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.74,0:07:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約會?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.87,0:07:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 這週星期天 不行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.71,0:07:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有說不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.33,0:07:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.21,0:07:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.80,0:07:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.63,0:07:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.72,0:07:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很期待約會呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.89,0:07:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.39,0:07:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約會約會
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.81,0:07:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽起來真爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.77,0:07:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.62,0:07:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.24,0:08:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部長果然沒猜錯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.54,0:08:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡要而言
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.62,0:08:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你去監視果然是正確的選擇呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.96,0:08:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部長你準備怎麼做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.34,0:08:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們先做好準備吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.34,0:08:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 最終還是要看他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.56,0:08:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就快到約定時間了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.77,0:08:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.65,0:08:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下不自覺就收了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.44,0:08:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫您實現您的願望
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.03,0:08:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可疑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.53,0:08:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.53,0:08:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.99,0:08:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起呢 等了很久吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.58,0:08:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也剛到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.12,0:08:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就想說一次了 這句台詞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.83,0:09:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.33,0:09:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.92,0:09:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真是開心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.38,0:09:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 今天真是棒極了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.43,0:09:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在該是男人主動出擊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.10,0:09:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.82,0:09:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.99,0:09:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了紀念我們的第一次約會
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.03,0:10:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能聽聽我的一個請求嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.37,0:10:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這難道就是傳說中的…ki…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.83,0:10:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什麼呢 那請求
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.05,0:10:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能給我去死嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.51,0:10:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 那個是…咦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.72,0:10:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬 抱歉了 能再說一遍嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.47,0:10:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的耳朵好像出了點問題
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.93,0:10:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能給我去死嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.56,0:10:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.02,0:10:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才看到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.44,0:10:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然只是一瞬間 但確實是真正的咪咪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.53,0:10:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於能第一次如此近距離的接觸咪咪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.95,0:10:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還是這麼可愛的女生的咪咪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.32,0:10:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這時候該用什麼詞彙來形容啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.41,0:10:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是大飽眼福嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.24,0:10:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不是說這個的時候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.91,0:10:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是說這個的時候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.41,0:10:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翅膀?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.83,0:10:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是愉快啊 雖然只是那麼短暫的交往
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.46,0:10:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你玩的這個天真爛漫的扮家家酒交往
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.97,0:11:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你買給我的這個 我會好好珍惜的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.72,0:11:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.68,0:11:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.85,0:11:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.86,0:11:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起呢 你對於我們來說 是過於危險的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.16,0:11:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須盡快抹殺掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.95,0:11:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怨就怨把神器寄宿於你身上的神吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.46,0:11:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神…? 那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.67,0:11:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是美妙的回憶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.71,0:11:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.51,0:11:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.01,0:11:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這麼寒酸的公園裡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.51,0:11:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為莫名其妙的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.89,0:11:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…要死了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.56,0:11:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要殺我的話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.10,0:11:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也讓我揉揉咪咪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.24,0:12:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然沒有認真看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.49,0:12:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是對不錯的咪咪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.24,0:12:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.50,0:12:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真紅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.54,0:12:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好紅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.96,0:12:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同那個人的髮色
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.59,0:12:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好紅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.67,0:12:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比Strawberry blonde更加鮮紅的頭髮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.84,0:12:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猶如被染紅的這隻手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.22,0:12:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在說些什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.18,0:12:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明就快要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.77,0:12:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.90,0:12:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體已經完全不能動彈了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.03,0:12:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.36,0:12:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會是這種不明所以的死法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.20,0:12:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說這還真是悲劇的人生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.45,0:12:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是還有來生 我要…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.92,0:12:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲學姐嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.54,0:12:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那漂亮的紅色長髮 那個人的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.80,0:12:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正都要死
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.34,0:13:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望能死在那種美女的胸前啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.90,0:13:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.28,0:13:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼喚我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.22,0:13:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.33,0:13:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正都要死 何不讓我拾回你的狗命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.42,0:13:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是…翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.60,0:13:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的生命 為我而活吧
Comment: 0,0:13:47.01,0:13:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.59,0:13:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不起來就把你殺掉…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.06,0:14:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪這傢伙 讓我做惡夢了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.09,0:14:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.44,0:14:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們真的不記得夕麻醬這個人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.98,0:14:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說 不知道有這個人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.44,0:14:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要說多少次你才明白
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.36,0:14:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本沒有介紹過這樣的女生給我們
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.40,0:14:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說你根本不可能有女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.32,0:14:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.70,0:14:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明有交換過郵箱地址的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.90,0:14:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.39,0:14:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論是夕麻醬的電話號碼還是郵箱地址
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.15,0:14:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都沒有了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.92,0:14:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.05,0:14:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.05,0:14:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是莉雅絲學姐哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.72,0:14:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論何時都是如此完美呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.28,0:14:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是美女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.51,0:14:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那難以接近的感覺讓人欲罷不能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.74,0:15:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老是妄想些工口的東西 腦子沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.33,0:15:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別把我跟你們混為一談
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.58,0:15:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我確實是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.46,0:15:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 今天來我家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.79,0:15:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給大家看看我珍藏多年的好東西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.38,0:15:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工口DVD…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.34,0:15:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是討厭呢 那些傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.80,0:15:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿腦子糟糕物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.55,0:15:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真差勁 變態
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.51,0:15:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對 還有親子圓盤的新作哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.60,0:15:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那還真是棒極了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.10,0:15:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 這可是通向真正工口的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.89,0:15:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.68,0:15:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變身
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.60,0:15:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是桃子醬的新作 假面騎士Binky
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.48,0:15:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是費我不小的功夫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.58,0:15:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.58,0:15:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這幾天的記憶全是夢?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.46,0:15:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.13,0:15:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這段時間的記憶究竟去哪裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.30,0:15:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你怎麼了 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.18,0:15:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是桃園桃的粉絲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.68,0:15:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了更好地觀賞還是把燈關了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.44,0:15:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.27,0:15:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Comment: 0,0:15:59.15,0:15:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.98,0:16:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 沒關啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.69,0:16:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.99,0:16:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房間的燈沒關吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.32,0:16:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥 你在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.95,0:16:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不對 燈關了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.58,0:16:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺不到光線
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.37,0:16:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 能看見
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.08,0:16:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.00,0:16:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.63,0:16:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 身體哪裡不舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.26,0:16:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然比白天看得要清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.10,0:16:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這究竟是什麼情況
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.85,0:16:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像力量在不斷湧現一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.27,0:16:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要不要 我就要買我就要買
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.15,0:16:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再這麼任性我就不管你了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.61,0:16:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.03,0:16:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼那麼遠的聲音也能聽到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.33,0:16:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.04,0:16:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的身體太奇怪了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.58,0:17:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這公園
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.30,0:17:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 就是這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.34,0:17:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這裡跟夕麻醬約會了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.59,0:17:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.55,0:17:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想相信 那是一個夢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.77,0:17:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.90,0:17:32.70,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可真是不幸 在郊區遇上你這樣的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.08,0:17:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼情況 身體止不住地顫抖
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.12,0:17:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想退後一點而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.25,0:17:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要逃嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.42,0:17:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫名其妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.88,0:17:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羽毛?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.85,0:17:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.35,0:18:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說低級的存在是如此礙事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.11,0:18:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是夢嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.24,0:18:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既沒有主人的氣息也沒有同伴的氣息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.53,0:18:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺不到要隱藏起來的意圖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.49,0:18:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就連魔法陣也沒有展開
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.66,0:18:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據以上分析
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.54,0:18:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是「走散」嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.08,0:18:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 殺了也沒有問題
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.00,0:18:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要真是同一個夢的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.38,0:18:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起死在這個大叔手下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.25,0:18:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死在美女身上要強上千倍萬倍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.97,0:18:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.30,0:18:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼死了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.35,0:18:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬那時候可沒有這麼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.23,0:18:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很疼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.81,0:18:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光對於你們來說相當於猛毒般的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.57,0:18:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還以為能一擊斃命呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.65,0:18:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想不到你這麼頑強啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.07,0:18:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.03,0:18:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就讓你解脫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.45,0:18:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.99,0:18:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有誰…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.87,0:19:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.25,0:19:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你的小伎倆嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.46,0:19:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像並不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.24,0:19:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把那孩子還給我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.97,0:19:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮紅長髮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.38,0:19:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲…學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.93,0:19:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何方神聖
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.02,0:19:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.20,0:19:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮紅長髮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.59,0:19:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.97,0:19:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉蒙里家族的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.99,0:19:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲·吉蒙里 晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.33,0:19:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墮天使先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.00,0:19:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到這座城市是吉蒙里家族的下任當家的領地啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.64,0:19:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙是您的眷屬嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.06,0:19:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是敢對這孩子動手的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.92,0:19:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不會輕饒你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.55,0:19:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我為今天的事道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.03,0:20:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但還請不要讓下僕四處亂跑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.22,0:20:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的話會被像我那樣的人散步順便而獵捕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.72,0:20:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝你的忠告
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.98,0:20:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是下次還敢做出這樣的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.56,0:20:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就毫無猶豫地把你幹掉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.15,0:20:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來就想這麼幹的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.36,0:20:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這句台詞原封不動還給你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.74,0:20:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉蒙里家族的下任當家喲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.91,0:20:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾之名為 特蘭西克
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.28,0:20:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待不要再次相見
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.82,0:20:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大意了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.42,0:20:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到居然會遇到墮天使
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.13,0:20:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再這樣下去就會死掉了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.72,0:20:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會讓他死的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.30,0:20:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為 這孩子是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.43,0:20:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人 請起床
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.35,0:20:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.86,0:20:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 又做了奇怪的夢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.32,0:21:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼晚晚都…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.90,0:21:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎麼沒穿衣服?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.03,0:21:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內褲 在哪裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.81,0:21:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.08,0:21:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲學姐?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.55,0:21:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上了?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.14,0:21:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咪咪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.17,0:21:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.43,0:21:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這究竟是怎麼回事 莉雅絲學姐會…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.61,0:21:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說這是夢吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.64,0:21:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 一定是那個夢的後續
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.19,0:21:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是現實哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.52,0:21:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所經歷的事情全部都是真實的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.69,0:21:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是莉雅絲·吉蒙里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.07,0:21:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是惡魔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.36,0:21:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後還是你的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.91,0:21:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多多指教了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.33,0:21:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤一誠君
Comment: 0,0:22:13.52,0:22:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.27,0:22:20.19,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.36,0:22:25.86,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.07,0:22:31.58,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.87,0:22:37.92,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.08,0:22:44.76,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.01,0:22:50.47,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.85,0:22:53.56,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.72,0:22:56.60,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.73,0:23:08.57,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:21:53.79,0:21:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.27,0:22:20.19,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.36,0:22:25.86,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.07,0:22:31.58,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.87,0:22:37.92,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.08,0:22:44.76,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.01,0:22:50.47,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.85,0:22:53.56,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.72,0:22:56.60,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.73,0:23:08.57,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.09,0:23:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回想起你最想做的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.64,0:23:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後宮王
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我當定了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.81,0:23:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賜予我力量
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.06,0:23:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 算是收到一個笨蛋小弟了嗎
Comment: 0,0:00:02.01,0:00:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.93,0:23:41.97,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fsp2\fs38\pos(380,165)\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1}第2話 「我不做人類了!」




