[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: DXD
Collisions: Normal
Original Script: DHR
Synch Point: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.60,0:00:04.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金色女郎的白色春天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.21,0:00:06.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是稀有動物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.86,0:00:08.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不是說這個的時候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.29,0:00:10.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.58,0:00:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝您
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.18,0:00:21.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.02,0:00:23.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.18,0:00:26.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.00,0:00:33.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,簡直就是我理想中的女生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.29,0:00:36.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金髮少女版
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.17,0:00:38.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是太感謝你了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.54,0:00:40.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.24,0:00:43.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要趕緊想辦法接下話去…我想想
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.63,0:00:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話題啊話題
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.57,0:00:48.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…今天的天氣很不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:00:50.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是附近的老婆婆嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.73,0:00:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…迷路…我迷路了 正困惑著呢
Comment: 0,0:01:15.42,0:01:21.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.42,0:01:21.36,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.52,0:01:27.01,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.24,0:01:32.73,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.04,0:01:39.05,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.25,0:01:45.89,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.18,0:01:51.61,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.98,0:01:54.69,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.87,0:01:57.74,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.90,0:02:09.71,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:00:54.93,0:00:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.42,0:01:21.36,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.52,0:01:27.01,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.24,0:01:32.73,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.04,0:01:39.05,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.25,0:01:45.89,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.18,0:01:51.61,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.98,0:01:54.69,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.87,0:01:57.74,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.90,0:02:09.71,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.07,0:02:37.34,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU  後期:Ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.46,0:02:33.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(552,391)}第3話 「交到朋友了！」
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.58,0:02:30.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,旅行?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.61,0:02:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.42,0:02:35.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是來這座城市的教會任職
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.67,0:02:36.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來是修女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.18,0:02:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得這身打扮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.88,0:02:41.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能遇到您這麼好的人真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.80,0:02:43.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這一定是主的指引呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.22,0:02:51.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.29,0:02:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.36,0:02:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼突然間…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.37,0:03:00.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等…等等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.89,0:03:06.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子不能因為這點小傷就哭了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.91,0:03:14.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,傷被…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.77,0:03:23.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦…剛剛明明很疼的啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.52,0:03:26.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了  傷口已經好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.17,0:03:28.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經沒事了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.28,0:03:32.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思…不知不覺就…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.23,0:03:40.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的左手起了反應
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.96,0:03:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.49,0:03:43.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嚇了一跳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.41,0:03:48.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒啊 你有很厲害的力量呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.90,0:03:51.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是神主賜予給我的非常美妙的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.55,0:03:56.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 美妙…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.08,0:03:59.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.75,0:04:04.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要說這座城市的教會 就只有那間了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.85,0:04:07.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 太感謝你的幫助了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.09,0:04:14.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 沒見過有誰待過在那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.25,0:04:19.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能跟我一起前往教會嗎 我想回禮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.39,0:04:22.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 剛好有點急事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.91,0:04:28.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 我叫愛西亞·阿基多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.55,0:04:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫我愛西亞就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.30,0:04:31.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫兵藤一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.29,0:04:33.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫一誠就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.99,0:04:40.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 剛來到日本就遇到像一誠您這麼溫柔親切的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.27,0:04:42.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真是太幸福了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.07,0:04:44.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,客氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.81,0:04:49.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有空的話 請一定要來教會作客
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.61,0:04:50.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,約定好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.28,0:04:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那就這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.87,0:04:58.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次再見
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.69,0:05:01.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是個好孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.51,0:05:06.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能再接近教會了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:10.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,教會對於我們惡魔來說 就是敵陣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.58,0:05:15.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,擅自踏足的話 就將會上升到神界與惡魔界間的大問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.17,0:05:18.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可不能保證你什麼時候又會吃上一記光之槍
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.22,0:05:20.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.09,0:05:24.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那接近教會時候的惡寒是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.80,0:05:27.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你的惡魔本能察覺到了危險
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.74,0:05:30.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在你跟教會的人走在一起的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.87,0:05:32.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,附近肯定有使徒的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.19,0:05:35.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特別是隸屬於教會的驅魔師
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.35,0:05:40.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驅魔師之中也是有人擁有神器的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.63,0:05:44.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.74,0:05:45.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.12,0:05:49.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被驅魔師淨化的惡魔是會被完全消滅其存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.44,0:05:53.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說 什麼都沒有 什麼都感覺不到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.28,0:05:55.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼都做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.74,0:05:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是多麼嚴重的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.77,0:05:58.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明白嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.54,0:06:01.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.55,0:06:05.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 我說的太重了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.58,0:06:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之 今後給我注意點
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.36,0:06:10.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.35,0:06:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唉 怎麼感覺我好像總是在惹社長生氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.25,0:06:20.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起了 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.11,0:06:23.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,估計我要爽約了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.86,0:06:26.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長真是太過溺愛一誠了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.89,0:06:28.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.08,0:06:33.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃 我還以為你回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.05,0:06:36.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛從大公那裡收到聯絡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.49,0:06:37.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大公那裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.78,0:06:40.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這座城鎮裡貌似還有 走散惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.69,0:06:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它們原本是惡魔的僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.29,0:06:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像我們這樣的？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.48,0:06:53.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾背著主人 為所欲為地殘害人類
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.71,0:06:55.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是 走散惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.43,0:07:01.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,報告上稱那位走散惡魔先生引誘人類到那間屋子裡進行吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.72,0:07:02.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.42,0:07:05.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對其進行討伐就是今晚的工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.77,0:07:09.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,利用主人的無限魔力為媒介
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.26,0:07:11.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,創造出這個醜陋的結界嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.26,0:07:13.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.75,0:07:15.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.87,0:07:17.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你會玩西洋棋嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.96,0:07:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是指桌遊的那個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.19,0:07:23.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作為主人的我是國王
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.19,0:07:23.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(534,432)}<King>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.37,0:07:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女王  騎士  城堡  主教  兵卒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.37,0:07:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(273,430)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.37,0:07:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(352,430)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.37,0:07:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,430)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.37,0:07:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(502,430)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.37,0:07:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(580,430)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.96,0:07:38.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上位惡魔可以賜予這些棋子的特性給自己的下僕
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.39,0:07:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,棋子的特性？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.10,0:07:44.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們稱之為惡魔之棋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.10,0:07:44.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(489,435)}<Evil Piece>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.83,0:07:46.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要特地告訴我這些
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.17,0:07:51.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之你今晚就在旁邊好好看看什麼叫惡魔間的戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.73,0:07:52.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊…是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.12,0:07:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.10,0:07:57.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有看起來很難吃的味道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.29,0:08:01.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過也有看起來很好吃的味道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.47,0:08:03.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會甜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.85,0:08:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是會苦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.66,0:08:07.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咪咪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.47,0:08:09.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(520,435)}<Vice>
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.47,0:08:09.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「走散」惡魔 罪惡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.48,0:08:15.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃出主人的手掌為了滿足欲望暴走的不倫之輩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.40,0:08:17.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那罪孽應予以萬死
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.92,0:08:19.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我以吉蒙里公爵家之名
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.39,0:08:22.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,揍飛你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.73,0:08:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂妄自大的小丫頭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.08,0:08:30.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要我用鮮血將你的身體渲染成你那頭髮的顏色嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.14,0:08:34.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,越是小嘍囉越能說時髦的話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.13,0:08:36.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是「走散」惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.52,0:08:40.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只覺得是個裸露癖的大姐姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.01,0:08:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說過吧 心身都會變得很醜陋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.75,0:08:50.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明有著極品咪咪 太遺憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.19,0:08:53.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.76,0:08:55.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那不是魔法陣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.70,0:09:08.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,的確是個怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.53,0:09:10.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能大意哦 祐斗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.82,0:09:12.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.96,0:09:14.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因為太快了看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.69,0:09:17.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(521,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.69,0:09:17.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐斗的職位是「騎士」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.87,0:09:18.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特性是速度
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.49,0:09:21.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後他最強武器為劍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.37,0:09:28.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危險 小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.89,0:09:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.12,0:09:48.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪是「城堡」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.12,0:09:48.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(488,435)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.76,0:09:52.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特性相當單純 巨大的力量和防禦力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.20,0:09:54.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那點程度傷不到一根寒毛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.96,0:09:56.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,扔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.09,0:10:07.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我決定在小貓咪前面乖一點
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.39,0:10:08.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.40,0:10:10.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.83,0:10:13.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 該怎麼辦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.74,0:10:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.76,0:10:21.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神器
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.76,0:10:21.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(426,435)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.34,0:10:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.76,0:10:32.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事 身體不自覺地就…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.89,0:10:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃 幹掉她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.21,0:10:44.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對社長出手的淘氣壞小孩可要好好調教一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.06,0:10:47.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她是「皇后」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.06,0:10:47.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(458,438)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.68,0:10:52.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,結合了其他棋子所有能力的無敵副社長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.51,0:10:55.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 還很有精神嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.40,0:10:58.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那接下這招如何
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.73,0:11:02.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,擅長利用魔力的攻擊 而且她…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.01,0:11:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 還這麼有精神
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.02,0:11:09.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究極的 虐待狂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.28,0:11:11.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道能堅持多久呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.25,0:11:14.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她在笑…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.47,0:11:16.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃 差不多點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.42,0:11:23.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼快就完了 有點遺憾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.32,0:11:31.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你還有什麼遺言嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.49,0:11:33.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,殺了我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.18,0:11:37.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 那就被我揍飛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.18,0:11:39.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,將軍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.53,0:11:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完事了 走 回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.18,0:11:55.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.79,0:11:57.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…社長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.17,0:11:58.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.15,0:12:00.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.52,0:12:05.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的棋子…作為僕人的職位是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.47,0:12:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「兵卒」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.47,0:12:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(410,435)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.79,0:12:09.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兵卒…難道是？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.58,0:12:12.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 一誠 你是士兵
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.57,0:12:14.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,士兵？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.47,0:12:17.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最下級的？！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.81,0:12:35.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若想擁有僕人必須成為上級惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.32,0:12:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,與一開始就是上級惡魔的社長不同
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.93,0:12:42.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們轉世者需要實力被認可後升級才行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.32,0:12:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我是士兵 最弱的棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.90,0:12:47.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不就是棄子嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.76,0:12:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,離成為後宮王還真遙遠
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.52,0:13:01.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不鎖門太危險了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.32,0:13:05.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是吉蒙里大人的惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.29,0:13:07.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,委託人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.09,0:13:12.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺…剛才有種不好的預感…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.30,0:13:14.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您在家嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.39,0:13:22.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪的召喚又重複了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.41,0:13:24.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今晚還能拜託你其中一個活嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.82,0:13:25.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.49,0:13:28.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次可要完成契約哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.96,0:13:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要辜負我的期待
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.34,0:13:34.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是…是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.75,0:13:39.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這麼回去的話就更加沒臉見社長了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.44,0:13:45.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了哈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.29,0:13:51.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還真有氣氛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.82,0:13:54.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.17,0:13:57.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼灑在地上…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.78,0:14:02.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這難道…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.44,0:14:11.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.05,0:14:16.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「惡人要受懲罰哦」…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.67,0:14:20.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我借用了一下聖人的話試了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.16,0:14:28.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 這不就是惡魔同學嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.71,0:14:31.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是菲利德‧賽路斯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.62,0:14:36.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是所屬於某驅魔組織的少年神父
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.53,0:14:38.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神父？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.07,0:14:42.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 我能確定我不是惡魔那種狗屎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.84,0:14:45.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是你幹的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.55,0:14:47.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,依靠惡魔這種行為作為人類已經完了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.68,0:14:50.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,END哦 END！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.15,0:14:53.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以就殺了他哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.29,0:14:57.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驅除像狗屎惡魔和被狗屎弄髒的臉的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.44,0:15:00.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是本大爺的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.05,0:15:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光之劍？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.61,0:15:05.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在要把這劍插進你胸口
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.15,0:15:12.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用這帥槍必殺必中Fall in love…掉你了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.40,0:15:15.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射擊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.86,0:15:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驅魔師禁制伏魔彈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.79,0:15:24.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,味道如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.70,0:15:26.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.19,0:15:30.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.03,0:15:34.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣我驅魔才起勁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.28,0:15:37.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慘目忍睹
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.70,0:15:42.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 華而不實嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.56,0:15:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最不爽那種東西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.45,0:15:52.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀 這不是助手小愛西亞嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.91,0:15:55.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佈置好結界了沒？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.64,0:15:57.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這…這是？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.58,0:16:00.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對了 對了 我忘了你原來是個新手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.31,0:16:02.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我們的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.40,0:16:06.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是像這樣解決掉依靠惡魔的廢物們
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.29,0:16:08.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.64,0:16:11.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.03,0:16:12.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.46,0:16:15.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 什麼 你們倆是熟人？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.34,0:16:17.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你會是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.93,0:16:23.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起…我…是惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.58,0:16:24.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.12,0:16:26.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生竟然是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.60,0:16:28.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是想騙你的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.62,0:16:35.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以說 我本來已經決定不再和你見面的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.45,0:16:36.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.97,0:16:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很遺憾 小愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.97,0:16:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔和人類是…無法相容的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.20,0:16:43.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更何況我們是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.65,0:16:48.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有了墮天使的保護就沒法生存下去的半吊子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.13,0:16:49.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墮天使？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.22,0:16:52.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 該盡快完成我們的任務了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.17,0:16:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做好覺悟了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.68,0:16:57.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算沒做好 我也開殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.58,0:17:00.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.59,0:17:04.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂 這不是真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.38,0:17:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,菲利德神父大人求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.72,0:17:08.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請原諒這位先生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.88,0:17:10.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請放他一條生路
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.63,0:17:14.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明白自己正在幹什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.96,0:17:18.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是惡魔 一誠先生是很好的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.99,0:17:20.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再說 這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.66,0:17:22.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真主是不可能會原諒的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.61,0:17:24.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.15,0:17:26.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別犯傻了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.18,0:17:31.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.22,0:17:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這臭婊子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.06,0:17:37.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在夏天你腦袋裡是不是長了條蟲子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.90,0:17:40.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.21,0:17:45.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然墮天使姐姐叮囑我不要傷害你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.85,0:17:48.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來這次可需要調教呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.57,0:17:52.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.11,0:17:59.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,清潔的修女被神父盡情地玩弄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.06,0:18:01.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是不是很棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.85,0:18:02.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.27,0:18:03.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我住手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.78,0:18:09.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.08,0:18:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,免費觀看是不允許的哦 客人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.51,0:18:14.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把愛西亞…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.39,0:18:16.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放開
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.73,0:18:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.64,0:18:22.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要和我戰鬥嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.41,0:18:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你會痛苦的死去的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.03,0:18:25.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生 不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.05,0:18:27.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼勝算
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.53,0:18:31.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然可能會死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.20,0:18:34.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是在庇護過我的這女孩面前
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.69,0:18:37.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有退路了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.85,0:18:39.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.55,0:18:40.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.62,0:18:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.34,0:18:50.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉能剁碎成什麼程度
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.40,0:18:53.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,由我來挑戰金氏紀錄如何！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.24,0:19:01.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔法陣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.13,0:19:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.49,0:19:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤君 來幫你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.58,0:19:11.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 這可真是不得了了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.95,0:19:12.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驅魔師
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.63,0:19:14.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.60,0:19:18.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔團隊駕到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.28,0:19:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 他可是我們的夥伴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.83,0:19:25.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 不錯嘛 那份熱情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.09,0:19:26.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.93,0:19:28.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是攻 他是受？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.16,0:19:31.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種沒品的話 不像是神父能說的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.73,0:19:33.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別裝樣了 醜惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.86,0:19:36.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,獵殺像你們這些臭蟲是我人生最大的樂趣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.05,0:19:39.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖的讓我殺了就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.98,0:19:42.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是惡魔也會選擇對方的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.75,0:19:44.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 不錯 那個火熱的視線
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.99,0:19:47.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 這是戀愛？ 不 是殺氣？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.29,0:19:51.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管受到殺氣還是投放殺氣 都讓人興奮不已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.68,0:19:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你消失了不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.18,0:19:58.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可愛的僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.34,0:20:00.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來受了你不少的疼愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.15,0:20:01.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.05,0:20:04.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這又是新夥伴登場了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.13,0:20:07.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 是 我是疼愛了他 所以呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.27,0:20:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.71,0:20:11.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.22,0:20:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛被你訓斥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.33,0:20:15.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又這樣了…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.13,0:20:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼遍體鱗傷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.36,0:20:20.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.32,0:20:23.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到竟然來了狩獵走散的驅魔師
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.06,0:20:28.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛為止 因為有結界沒能察覺到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.41,0:20:31.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞毛啊 臭婊子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.78,0:20:33.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佈置結界不是你的工作嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.07,0:20:34.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.91,0:20:38.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經決定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.95,0:20:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,絕不原諒弄傷我的僕人的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.94,0:20:44.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特別是像你這種沒品至極的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.99,0:20:47.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弄傷我的所有物
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.43,0:20:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,實在是讓人無法忍受
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.82,0:20:52.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這股力量有點不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.72,0:20:53.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如說相當的不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.75,0:20:56.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有多個墮天使
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.16,0:21:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這下情勢逆轉了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.73,0:21:02.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要把你們通通送上西天
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.85,0:21:04.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.02,0:21:07.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在是回收一誠最要緊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.79,0:21:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃 準備傳送
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.76,0:21:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.83,0:21:12.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓 一誠就拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.56,0:21:13.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.05,0:21:17.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臭惡魔們 怎能讓你們逃掉…啊 好痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.12,0:21:27.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.37,0:21:29.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩也一起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.36,0:21:31.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是無法辦到的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.79,0:21:35.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個魔法陣只能傳送我的眷屬
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.64,0:21:36.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼會
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.67,0:21:38.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.43,0:21:40.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.55,0:21:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要去救愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.96,0:21:42.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.00,0:21:44.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.81,0:21:45.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.01,0:21:50.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再…再… 在某地方再見吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.79,0:21:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！
Comment: 0,0:21:58.56,0:22:04.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.58,0:22:00.97,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.97,0:22:05.10,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.50,0:22:21.11,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.18,0:22:26.78,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.81,0:22:32.45,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.45,0:22:37.34,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.34,0:22:43.89,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.07,0:22:48.30,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.31,0:22:51.49,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.91,0:22:54.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.10,0:22:57.95,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.18,0:23:00.87,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:03.18,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.35,0:23:09.08,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.37,0:23:13.31,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.35,0:23:15.36,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.36,0:23:17.98,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.01,0:23:20.71,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.91,0:23:25.26,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:22:00.97,0:22:00.97,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.58,0:22:00.97,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.97,0:22:05.10,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.50,0:22:21.11,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.18,0:22:26.78,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.81,0:22:32.45,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.45,0:22:37.34,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.34,0:22:43.89,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.07,0:22:48.30,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.31,0:22:51.49,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.91,0:22:54.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.10,0:22:57.95,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.18,0:23:00.87,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:03.18,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.35,0:23:09.08,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.37,0:23:13.31,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.35,0:23:15.36,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.36,0:23:17.98,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.01,0:23:20.71,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.91,0:23:25.26,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Comment: 0,0:00:01.76,0:00:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.93,0:23:29.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖的消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.75,0:23:33.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感謝你特地來一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.98,0:23:35.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 這次的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.48,0:23:38.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是只屬於今天的…珍貴的…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.56,0:23:41.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(423,213)}第4話 ｢要去救朋友！｣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.59,0:23:40.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連朋友都沒法保護 怎麼能行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.94,0:23:42.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
