[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Original Script: DHR
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer:100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: DXD
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.85,0:00:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.52,0:00:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們去發傳單了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.08,0:00:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.26,0:00:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.05,0:00:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.87,0:00:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發傳單到這週為止就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.67,0:00:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.76,0:00:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是之前說過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.47,0:00:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然那是作為修行的一環 但發傳單原本是使魔的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.48,0:00:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那已經不用發傳單了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就需要你們先找到自己的使魔
Comment: 0,0:00:47.46,0:00:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.40,0:00:53.34,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.50,0:00:58.99,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.22,0:01:04.71,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.02,0:01:11.03,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.23,0:01:17.87,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.16,0:01:23.59,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.96,0:01:26.67,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.85,0:01:29.72,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.88,0:01:41.69,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:00:26.91,0:00:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.40,0:00:53.34,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.50,0:00:58.99,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.22,0:01:04.71,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.02,0:01:11.03,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.23,0:01:17.87,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.16,0:01:23.59,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.96,0:01:26.67,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.85,0:01:29.72,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.88,0:01:41.69,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:09.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:08.05,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:希美亞 後期:KoU BDrip: ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.39,0:02:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,388)}第7話「我要得到使魔！」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.14,0:02:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我的使魔 一誠以前見到過吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.82,0:02:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.92,0:02:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那個時候的女孩就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.88,0:02:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的使魔是這個
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.94,0:02:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小「鬼」？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.33,0:02:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牠叫小白
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.60,0:02:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.46,0:02:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你的就不用看了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.88,0:02:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真夠冷淡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.93,0:02:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這對惡魔來說是基本的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.53,0:02:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從輔助惡魔到 情報傳達 也能用於追蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.42,0:02:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那這些使魔如何才能得到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.49,0:02:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就要…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.37,0:02:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.03,0:02:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾各位了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.09,0:02:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位大人物是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.05,0:03:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…她們是哪位？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.09,0:03:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這個學校的學生會長 支取蒼那學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.53,0:03:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁邊的是副會長 真羅椿姬學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.36,0:03:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說學生會成員全聚齊了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.41,0:03:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼出動全部成員 有什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.33,0:03:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此間都增加了僕人 所以覺得該打一下招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.07,0:03:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說僕人 難道…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.83,0:03:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位的真名是蒼那·西迪 上級惡魔西迪家的下任當家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.24,0:03:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這學院竟然還有其他惡魔…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.91,0:03:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲學姐 難道沒跟他提起我們的事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.30,0:03:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然覺得 明明同樣是身為惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.55,0:03:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻沒能察覺到的這傢伙也有些問題
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.98,0:03:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匙 我們規定彼此之間是互不干涉的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.95,0:03:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤不知道也是理所當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.23,0:03:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是最近作為書記新加入學生會的…記得是二年C班的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.68,0:03:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匙‧元士郎是「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.68,0:03:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(509,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.10,0:03:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「兵卒」 兵藤一誠 「主教」愛西亞·阿基多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.10,0:03:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(199,437)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.10,0:03:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(453,435)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.06,0:03:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 你也是「兵卒」啊 而且還是同年級
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.06,0:03:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(364,435)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.58,0:04:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說 跟你這種「變態三人組」的一員是同一個類別
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.89,0:04:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這非常損我的尊嚴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.66,0:04:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼！ 你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.33,0:04:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 要幹一場嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.63,0:04:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}雖然我剛剛變成惡魔 但別看我這樣 我可是消耗了四個棋子的士兵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.42,0:04:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匙 別說了 還有對方的他可是消耗了八個哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.28,0:04:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八個！ 這不是全部嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.76,0:04:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢相信 這麼沒志氣的傢伙竟然會…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.15,0:04:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,囉嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.35,0:04:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉 兵藤君 阿基多小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.54,0:04:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的話 作為新人惡魔彼此間友好相處吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.71,0:04:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.43,0:04:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.88,0:04:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.95,0:04:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.32,0:04:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這才是 我非常歡迎像你這樣可愛的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.65,0:04:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.01,0:04:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匙君 對我也多多關照啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.23,0:04:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說你敢對愛西亞出手的話 我可真會宰了你的匙君
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.30,0:04:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想獨享金髮美少女啊 不愧是好色畜牲君啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.97,0:04:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真夠麻煩的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.23,0:04:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那邊也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.65,0:05:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一出道就被允許擁有使魔 我聽說你還在發傳單呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.32,0:05:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別小看我 我也剛剛被社長允許擁有使魔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.81,0:05:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 你那邊也是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.61,0:05:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 計劃是要在下週的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.96,0:05:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 他每月只接受一次承辦…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.49,0:05:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 這裡就以公平的方式用實力分勝負如何
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.41,0:05:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝負？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.27,0:05:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,獲勝的一方獲得去找他的權力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.40,0:05:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非是評估遊戲？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.21,0:05:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會呢 首先這是得不到許可的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.46,0:05:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.66,0:05:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說 對現在的你來說「身體」很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.16,0:05:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟這沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.91,0:05:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒼那 作為高中生就以體育來決勝負吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.52,0:05:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊 社長 朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.10,0:05:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長 請拿下勝利吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.38,0:05:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃 這場勝負 要來真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.85,0:05:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.28,0:06:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上了 蒼那
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.25,0:00:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒 儘管來吧 莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.64,0:06:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 沒問題 儘管來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.66,0:06:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然希望社長勝利 但是好想就這麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.43,0:06:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直觀賞下去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.09,0:06:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好風景啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.77,0:06:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 你們！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.28,0:06:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我校頂級美少女們 穿著閃亮的純白迷你短裙打網球
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.54,0:06:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事怎能不以光的速度向全校擴散啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.83,0:06:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且網球技能全都是專業選手級別
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.99,0:06:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加上相貌身姿的話是神級別
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.75,0:06:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贊同
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.19,0:06:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不覺觀眾變這麼多了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.41,0:06:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.41,0:06:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.42,0:06:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一來就沒法使用魔力了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.91,0:06:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃我這招 「西迪流回旋球」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.47,0:07:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太天真了 接我「吉蒙里流扣球」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.31,0:07:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,15:30
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.16,0:07:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.86,0:07:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 不愧是我們的會長
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.97,0:07:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是都在用魔力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.63,0:07:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有點過火了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.20,0:07:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是魔球啊 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.87,0:07:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們以為那是魔球呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.28,0:07:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼和平不是很好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.73,0:07:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣才是我的競爭對手 但我是絕對會贏的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.87,0:07:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的魔球可是有八百式呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.09,0:07:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會全部接下呢 這就是我對戰鬥的愛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.47,0:07:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最終結果是 哪邊都一直沒能決出勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.03,0:07:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,團體賽？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.30,0:07:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就為這個 會長和朱乃學姐正在學生會商議中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.28,0:07:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽項目定為躲避球
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.04,0:07:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽時間是明晚 地點是體育館
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.55,0:08:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了一誠和愛西亞大家加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.92,0:08:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.47,0:08:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.63,0:08:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.44,0:08:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 睡了沒？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.80,0:08:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.43,0:08:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進請進
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.65,0:08:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…那個…因為都這麼晚了…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.30,0:08:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說愛西亞 你那裡有針和線嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.35,0:08:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.01,0:08:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為對方多出兩人 所以請了裁判
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.67,0:08:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上次玩躲避球還是小學呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.64,0:08:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為目的是分出勝負 所以規則越簡單越好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.44,0:08:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞也馬上會了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.80,0:08:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.85,0:08:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再努力一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.43,0:08:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.70,0:09:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著她們 不由得讓我…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.42,0:09:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs30}加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.29,0:09:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意淫起來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.48,0:09:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纏頭帶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.49,0:09:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 很棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.59,0:09:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是通宵製作的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.31,0:09:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒睡嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.37,0:09:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長和朱乃學姐為我們那麼努力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.49,0:09:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天又有小貓咪和木場也幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.99,0:09:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以想為大家至少做一件有用的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.92,0:09:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 纏頭帶是不是有點土了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.28,0:09:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 做的很精緻
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.52,0:09:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很棒啊 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.39,0:09:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡 不是那麼好的東西啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.93,0:09:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出乎意料的出色表現
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.97,0:09:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纏上這個 讓我們團結一心加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.37,0:09:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.06,0:09:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你們久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.96,0:10:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出局
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.73,0:10:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.88,0:10:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.96,0:10:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「追憶之嘆息」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.99,0:10:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是你啊 從正面就把椿姫的球給…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.27,0:10:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為我是誰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.57,0:10:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.76,0:10:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.46,0:10:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 不可以大意哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.46,0:10:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 一不小心就…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.14,0:10:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「追憶之嘆息」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.71,0:10:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲避球原來是這麼可怕的競技項目啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.37,0:11:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這已經搞不清是啥比賽了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.49,0:11:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長 先做掉兵藤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.17,0:11:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「西迪流爆裂投擲」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.14,0:11:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.33,0:11:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.07,0:11:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 躲開
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.30,0:11:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了 什麼都完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.12,0:11:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會用「聖母的微笑」治療的 讓我看看傷處
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.12,0:11:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(329,434)}<Twilight Healing>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.74,0:11:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.78,0:11:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是看不到患部的話就沒法好好的去治療
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.76,0:11:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,患部…O部的話…會讓我各方面為難啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.44,0:11:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 真心饒了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.85,0:11:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就沒辦法了 那就隔著衣服…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.52,0:11:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺得疼嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.18,0:11:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讓人難以啟齒的場面啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.18,0:11:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也…那麼覺得
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.66,0:11:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞就先給一誠治療
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.98,0:11:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.25,0:12:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 這是為一誠的復仇戰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.16,0:12:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不能把一誠君的死…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.27,0:12:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白白浪費掉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.77,0:12:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.31,0:12:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…我才沒死呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.08,0:12:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治好吧 能治好的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.27,0:12:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.87,0:12:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只剩你一個了 覺悟吧 蒼那
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.63,0:12:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝負才剛剛開始
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.28,0:12:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.94,0:12:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贏了 贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.55,0:12:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們做到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.48,0:12:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就按照約定 就讓我們先契約使魔了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.64,0:12:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那當然 雖然很遺憾 不過還算玩得開心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.76,0:12:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 如果不是這種遊戲而是評估遊戲 我才不會輸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.45,0:12:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 可不能輸給你這個青梅竹馬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.22,0:12:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 這也得是很久以後的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.27,0:12:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 那麼辛苦你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.82,0:12:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,評估遊戲？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.78,0:12:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乾杯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.65,0:13:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮地打敗了學生會 我們神秘學研究社的勝利了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.22,0:13:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這都是託大家的福
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.15,0:13:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我在中途退場了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.62,0:13:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這個大家士氣也上升了 一誠的功勞也很大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.03,0:13:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.14,0:13:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.00,0:13:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木場 雖然是帥哥不過偶爾 真的是偶爾挺能說好話啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.34,0:13:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 不能再磨蹭了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.11,0:13:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去抓使魔去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.96,0:13:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 現在就去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.27,0:13:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是滿月之夜就見不到他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.85,0:13:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.37,0:13:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使魔專家哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.85,0:13:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.29,0:13:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是製作使魔的森林
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.05,0:13:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也是在這裡得到使魔的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.55,0:13:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確 什麼東西蹦出來也不奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.73,0:13:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.39,0:13:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.19,0:13:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.63,0:14:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是使魔專家札頭基
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.83,0:14:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使魔…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.87,0:14:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,專家？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.45,0:14:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚也是漂亮的滿月 最適合抓使魔了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.60,0:14:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我抓的話任何使魔都能100%抓到的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.52,0:14:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是抓使魔的專家哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.67,0:14:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.92,0:14:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 你們想要什麼樣的使魔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.98,0:14:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強的？快的？還是有毒的？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.35,0:14:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 有沒有可愛的使魔呢 美眉系之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.05,0:14:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才說外行不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.80,0:14:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使魔得又有用又強大才行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.66,0:14:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即是說要掌握其能力並彌補自己的特性
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.56,0:14:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 我也想要可愛的使魔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.09,0:14:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道咯～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.71,0:14:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝您
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.21,0:14:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.23,0:14:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個湖裡住著叫溫蒂尼的水精靈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.45,0:15:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水精靈啊 從名字來看肯定是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.63,0:15:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為未來的後宮王都想放在身邊的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.93,0:15:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把挖耳屎當藉口躺在膝蓋上 然後輕輕伸出手…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.11,0:15:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸那個神秘無窮無比的…咪咪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.92,0:15:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湖水…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.55,0:15:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,溫蒂尼要露臉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.03,0:15:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是溫蒂尼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.75,0:15:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 怎麼看那都是來洗澡的格鬥家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.41,0:15:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運氣不錯啊少年 那可是超稀有的物種
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.44,0:15:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻擊力高的水精靈也不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.40,0:15:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,錯了 這不是治癒系而是殺人系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.38,0:15:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 那就是美眉系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.03,0:15:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我最不想知道的事實…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.96,0:15:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那孩子有著清澈的眼神呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.71,0:15:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是心靈善良的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.23,0:15:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別把那個說成女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.79,0:16:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.76,0:16:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.76,0:16:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.75,0:16:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.99,0:16:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖精龍 能用藍雷的龍之幼崽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.66,0:16:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是相當高級別的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.75,0:16:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是第一次見到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.29,0:16:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要抓的話趁現在哦 長大就抓不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.57,0:16:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠君有著赤龍的力量 相性應該不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.47,0:16:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.50,0:16:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖精龍 決定是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.26,0:16:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.36,0:16:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.35,0:16:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史萊姆？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.38,0:16:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.40,0:16:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.34,0:16:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太下流了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.66,0:17:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.95,0:17:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好丟臉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.83,0:17:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黏糊糊 好噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.53,0:17:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.02,0:17:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多麼美妙的劇情！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.97,0:17:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.39,0:17:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使你那麼說 我也不能不顧大家的危機
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.65,0:17:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣連魔力也用不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.57,0:17:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 這可真糟糕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.81,0:17:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.48,0:17:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁現在 腦內保存 腦內保存
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.20,0:17:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是專門吃布料的史萊姆
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.96,0:17:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了會溶化掉女人的衣服以外沒有害處
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.55,0:17:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,溶掉衣服的史萊姆？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.42,0:17:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 我要抓這個史萊姆當使魔用
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.25,0:17:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 那裡不能碰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.92,0:18:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙才是 是我追求的逸才啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.22,0:18:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你啊一誠 使魔對惡魔來說是很重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.25,0:18:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好考慮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.53,0:18:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我考慮過了 我還是把這個當使魔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.34,0:18:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真對不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.65,0:18:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓開 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.43,0:18:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種生物必須得燒掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.18,0:18:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.22,0:18:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這隻史萊姆簡直是為了與我相遇才出生於此世的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.41,0:18:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這簡直是命運 已經不是外人了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.79,0:18:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生竟然會抱住我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.71,0:18:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史萊太郎 我的夥伴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.43,0:18:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經取上名字了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.00,0:19:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次見到這麼想要森林的累贅的惡魔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.83,0:19:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個世界還真是廣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.30,0:19:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平時是個好孩子 只是他的體質太忠實於欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.81,0:19:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 不要用那種憐憫的眼神看我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.56,0:19:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要用這個來展翅高飛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.77,0:19:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生什麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.72,0:19:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖精龍的雷擊？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.79,0:19:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史萊太郎 你這小子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.31,0:19:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.21,0:19:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙只會攻擊自己認為是敵人的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.13,0:19:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說牠以為少年和史萊姆襲擊金髮美少女了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.73,0:19:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說的話 也就是說
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.70,0:19:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.76,0:19:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決定了吧 美少女 抓到使魔了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.19,0:19:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以…以愛西亞·阿基多之名命令
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.02,0:20:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汝…汝作為吾之使魔回應契約吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.66,0:20:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 這樣就完事了 做得很好哦 愛西亞醬
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.84,0:20:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好癢啊 雷誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.92,0:20:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷誠？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.02,0:20:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 這孩子能放雷擊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.56,0:20:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後…我再把一誠先生的名字用上了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.52,0:20:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 請多指教啊 雷誠
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.19,0:20:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘記說了 雄龍最討厭其他雄性了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.00,0:20:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷誠真調皮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.18,0:20:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼死了 吾之友史萊太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.59,0:20:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那偉大的力量我一定要得到手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.96,0:20:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色狼死之也
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.28,0:20:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖精龍好像只對心靈清澈的人敞開心扉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.35,0:20:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般都不會接近惡魔的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.26,0:21:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是因為愛西亞以前是修女吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.55,0:21:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷誠你小子對愛西亞做什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.54,0:21:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說雷誠君 不能淘氣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.80,0:21:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就晚安咯 雷誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.47,0:21:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞學妹作為惡魔居然更像樣…真沮喪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.41,0:21:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 總有一天我要抓到讓大家大吃一驚的使魔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.16,0:21:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會期待的 那麼 辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.48,0:21:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.60,0:21:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠還差的遠呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.29,0:21:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才剛開始起步呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.65,0:21:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.34,0:21:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Comment: 0,0:21:57.93,0:21:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know? Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know? Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.17,0:23:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玫瑰色的時刻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.59,0:23:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生不是喜歡看裸體嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.96,0:23:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(417,210)}第8話「要吵架了！」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.61,0:23:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉蒙里家下任當家的女婿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.40,0:23:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奪走我的處女吧 快點拜託了！
