[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: DXD

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.43,0:00:02.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！
Comment: 0,0:00:20.49,0:00:25.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.45,0:00:26.39,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.55,0:00:32.04,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.27,0:00:37.76,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.07,0:00:44.08,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.28,0:00:50.92,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:56.64,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.01,0:00:59.72,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.90,0:01:02.77,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.93,0:01:14.74,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.45,0:00:26.39,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.55,0:00:32.04,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.27,0:00:37.76,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.07,0:00:44.08,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.28,0:00:50.92,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:56.64,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.01,0:00:59.72,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.90,0:01:02.77,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.93,0:01:14.74,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Comment: 0,0:01:33.03,0:01:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.03,0:01:42.37,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU  後期:KoU  BDrip:ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.69,0:01:38.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(421,393)}第5話 「幹掉原女朋友！」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.28,0:01:36.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這才是我多年來一直想要的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.60,0:01:41.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要有了這個我就能…得到愛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.14,0:01:52.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最強的力量 這樣我就能變成最強的墮天使
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.57,0:01:55.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以讓那些小瞧我的傢伙們給點顏色看了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.53,0:01:57.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.07,0:01:59.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死惡魔 滅了你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:02:01.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滾開 沒空理你們
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.97,0:02:10.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.07,0:02:14.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場 小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.89,0:02:16.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Thank you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.75,0:02:21.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.57,0:02:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.30,0:02:34.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是作為來到這兒的獎賞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.13,0:02:40.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.59,0:02:44.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 沒事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.49,0:02:48.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.19,0:02:51.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來接你了 打起精神
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.30,0:02:53.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.02,0:02:57.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子就給你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.01,0:03:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了 快把她的「神器」還給她
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.03,0:03:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(392,434)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.54,0:03:08.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別說傻話了 我可是瞞著上頭偷實行了這個計劃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.79,0:03:12.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很遺憾你們要成為我的代罪羔羊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.30,0:03:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過不是很好嗎 你們兩個可以一起消失
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.00,0:03:19.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤君 在這裡很不利
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.56,0:03:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是我第一次交到的女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.56,0:03:26.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 看你還真純真無邪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.21,0:03:30.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不懂女人的男人玩起來真有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.51,0:03:33.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本來想要好好珍惜的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.58,0:03:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要我顯得很困擾 馬上就開始擔心起來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.88,0:03:43.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過那全是我故意裝出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.60,0:03:47.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為你緊張的樣子 超級好笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.11,0:03:50.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我 真的很喜歡夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.62,0:03:53.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,初次約會真的是非常用心的去設計
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.50,0:03:56.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了弄成最好的約會…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.28,0:04:02.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對呢 真的是好老套的約會呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.51,0:04:05.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多虧你我快無聊死了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.50,0:04:08.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.92,0:04:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還算幹的不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.40,0:04:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那點程度的障壁能撐到何時呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.39,0:04:22.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們自己設的結界反倒妨礙你們了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.35,0:04:26.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不你們解開結界放跑我們如何
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.43,0:04:29.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,NoNoNoNo~反倒是我們不會放跑你們
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.53,0:04:33.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的小僕人現在估計也燒成灰燼了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.60,0:04:37.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是那個 對雷娜蕾姐姐大人死心塌地的色小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.06,0:04:39.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙肯定早就…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.85,0:04:41.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不要小瞧一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.57,0:04:45.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為那孩子是我最強的「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.59,0:04:45.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(436,434)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.89,0:04:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻…對 為了在夕陽底下殺掉你才取的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.36,0:04:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相當有情調吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.24,0:04:59.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,結果你死也不好好死那麼快就交了個金髮女友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.10,0:05:02.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好過分好過分一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.06,0:05:06.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是又邀她去超無聊的約會去了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.93,0:05:11.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過對於農村長大的小姑娘來說很新鮮也說不定呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.56,0:05:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是說了「我出生以來第一次這麼開心」之類的？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.40,0:05:18.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷娜蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.12,0:05:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臭小鬼不要隨便叫我名字
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.66,0:05:22.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會弄髒的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.85,0:05:25.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙才是真正的惡魔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.64,0:05:32.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.22,0:05:33.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.52,0:05:35.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.09,0:05:39.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兵藤君快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.85,0:05:43.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和小貓咪給你擋著
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.85,0:05:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這邊交給我們
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.03,0:05:46.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點逃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.76,0:05:48.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.76,0:05:50.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點去吧 兵藤君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.86,0:05:57.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場 小貓咪 回去以後一定要稱呼我為一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.52,0:05:59.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,約好了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.51,0:06:04.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽好 我也是你們的夥伴！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.29,0:06:06.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「兵卒」？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.29,0:06:06.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(309,433)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.52,0:06:10.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們把僕人比喻為西洋棋來著是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.62,0:06:13.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「兵卒」不是擺一堆在前排的那個嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.62,0:06:13.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(183,434)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.46,0:06:16.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是棄子唄
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.47,0:06:20.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 我們部長可不用什麼棄子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.59,0:06:30.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 堅持住 出了這裡愛西亞你就自由了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.20,0:06:33.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能隨時和我…一起玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.21,0:06:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…即使時間不長…能交上朋友…很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.18,0:06:43.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼呢 我還有很多要帶你去的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.33,0:06:47.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,KTV啦 遊樂場啦 保齡球啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.95,0:06:50.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉丘君也可以再多抓幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.29,0:06:54.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有對了 還有那個啊那個 你想想
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.43,0:06:57.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊對了 還得介紹給我的死黨
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.73,0:07:02.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,松田和元濱雖然有點好色但都是非常好的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.45,0:07:05.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定會和愛西亞做朋友的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.74,0:07:08.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以和大家一起吃喝玩樂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.78,0:07:11.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像白痴一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.99,0:07:16.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果出生在這個國家後…能和一誠先生上同一所學校的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.28,0:07:18.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那該有多好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.24,0:07:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上唄 不 你必須得上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.09,0:07:22.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.82,0:07:28.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你會為了我而哭…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.90,0:07:32.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經…什麼也…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.47,0:07:35.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.67,0:07:46.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛…西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.28,0:07:51.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼啊 為什麼要非死不可啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.18,0:07:57.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她可是只要有人受傷即使是惡魔也會去治好的溫柔的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.84,0:08:00.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 神 你在那裡吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.70,0:08:05.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別把她帶走啊 求你了 求求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.96,0:08:09.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她什麼壞事也沒做 只是想要朋友而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.37,0:08:13.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因為我變成了惡魔所以不行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.48,0:08:17.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為她的朋友是惡魔所以不管了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.61,0:08:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 求求你了神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.42,0:08:23.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔在教會懺悔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.30,0:08:26.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這玩笑可真不好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.32,0:08:27.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷娜蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.42,0:08:32.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來你特別看好那小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.41,0:08:35.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但不說能力如何他是贏不了雷娜蕾大人的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.34,0:08:38.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再說是原女朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.68,0:08:42.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我從雷娜蕾大人聽說了關於他的事 真逗死我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.40,0:08:47.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別說了蜜特露特 光是想起來就讓我笑破肚皮了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.37,0:08:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 倒是給我們的酒席助興了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.47,0:08:54.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.37,0:08:57.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,彈開了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.32,0:09:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘲笑了？竟敢嘲笑了我的僕人是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.39,0:09:10.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 看來你們惹怒了不該惹怒的對手 小白痴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.05,0:09:19.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看看這裡 來這裡的途中被「騎士」傷著了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.05,0:09:19.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(418,433)\fs23}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.45,0:09:20.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場和小貓咪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.60,0:09:26.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,厲害吧 不管受到多少傷都能治好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.65,0:09:31.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對於失去神之加護的我們墮天使來說 這可是至上的禮物
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.16,0:09:34.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一來我作為墮天使的地位就無憂了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.44,0:09:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偉大的阿撒塞勒大人 歇穆赫撒大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.63,0:09:40.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我能為你們二位效力了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.49,0:09:41.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,關我屁事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.14,0:09:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墮天使也好惡魔也好 那些跟她完全沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.82,0:09:51.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是被神看中寄宿了「神器」的人的宿命
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.82,0:09:51.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(390,435)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.90,0:09:55.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宿命個屁！她也是可以過著安祥的日子的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.82,0:09:56.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.92,0:09:57.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.86,0:10:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「神器」對於人來說是太過神聖的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.86,0:10:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(171,434)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.26,0:10:04.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管多麼神奇的力量 神秘的東西都會被恐懼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.15,0:10:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後被排斥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.24,0:10:11.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他們說擁有連惡魔都能治療的能力的人是異教徒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.82,0:10:15.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我 沒有朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.87,0:10:19.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法啊 人類這種生物就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.33,0:10:22.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明是這麼美妙的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.52,0:10:25.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過我…我是愛西亞的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.70,0:10:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作為朋友我要保護愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.86,0:10:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過她不是死了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.85,0:10:34.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她已經死了哦 不是保護不保護的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.57,0:10:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你沒能保護好她 那個時候 而且現在也是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.30,0:10:40.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.83,0:10:42.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才不能原諒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.65,0:10:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不原諒你 然後連我自己也全都不能原諒！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.74,0:10:50.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想像吧 「神器」是靠主人的想像產生變化
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.74,0:10:50.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(231,434)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.92,0:10:51.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還給我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.93,0:10:55.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想像越強烈力量越大 它就一定會…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.28,0:10:57.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把愛西亞還給我！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.66,0:10:58.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回應你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.80,0:11:01.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Dragon Booster！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.01,0:11:11.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不是說了嘛 力量從一變成二也贏不了我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.08,0:11:12.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.05,0:11:17.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量稍微變強了
Comment: 0,0:11:16.02,0:11:18.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.17,0:11:36.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光對於惡魔來說是猛毒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.90,0:11:42.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光是碰一下就會燒傷 那劇痛對於惡魔來說是最難忍的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.40,0:11:46.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你這種下級惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.84,0:11:48.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.74,0:11:53.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種東西…比起愛西亞的痛苦…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.72,0:11:57.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本就算不上什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.80,0:11:59.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.31,0:12:05.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不賴啊 憑一個下級惡魔能奮鬥到這地步 值得稱讚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.26,0:12:08.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒力氣了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.97,0:12:10.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但那已經是極限了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.10,0:12:14.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是下級惡魔的話 早就死了也沒什麼奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.22,0:12:16.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,意外地還挺結實的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.04,0:12:22.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然神…是不行的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.81,0:12:25.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為是惡魔 所以是魔王才對
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.46,0:12:27.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔王是應該有的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.76,0:12:33.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我姑且算是個惡魔 能聽一下我的請求嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.81,0:12:35.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一個人在自言自語什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.92,0:12:37.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不會是因為太疼崩掉腦袋了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.61,0:12:39.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我求您了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.85,0:12:44.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別的我什麼都不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.65,0:12:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能…這是騙人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.86,0:12:48.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以讓我…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:51.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛毆這傢伙一拳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.92,0:12:53.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能會站得起來的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.06,0:12:56.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整個身體正在被光從裡面開始燒焦著啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.36,0:13:01.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有緩解光的能力的下級惡魔 是不可能忍受得了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.85,0:13:03.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 很痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.77,0:13:05.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.65,0:13:08.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在意識都快要消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.16,0:13:15.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是…你讓我生氣得…這些都無所謂了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.21,0:13:17.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Explosion！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.59,0:13:22.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個波動是中級？…不 是那以上的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.91,0:13:25.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是不可能的 你那「神器」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.91,0:13:25.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(414,436)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.06,0:13:28.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是個「二級危機」為什麼能…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.06,0:13:28.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(298,434)}<Twice Critical>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.39,0:13:40.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼能讓你逃 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.84,0:13:43.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是…我是最強的…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.55,0:13:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我滾蛋 狗屎天使
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.70,0:13:52.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,活該
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.16,0:13:56.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然一個人打倒了墮天使
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.66,0:13:58.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太晚了 帥哥王子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.91,0:14:01.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長叫我不要插手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.26,0:14:03.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長她…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.21,0:14:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他說的沒錯 因為我相信你能打倒她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.08,0:14:07.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.22,0:14:10.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我的私事辦完了 所以通過傳送來到這個地下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.37,0:14:15.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後看見祐斗和小貓咪正在和神父們周旋著
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.28,0:14:17.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多虧社長得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.45,0:14:20.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 害我白擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.88,0:14:23.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 我帶來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.14,0:14:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,初次見面 墮天使雷娜蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.37,0:14:33.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是莉雅絲·吉蒙里  是吉蒙里家下屆掌門
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.51,0:14:36.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吉蒙里一族的女兒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.73,0:14:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,望你好好記住 雖然相處時間很短
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.80,0:14:48.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有 到我那裡拜訪的你的夥伴們 已經被我轟飛了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.38,0:14:50.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,轟飛了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.02,0:14:55.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長是「紅髮滅殺姬」 有著「滅殺姬」這個別名
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.24,0:14:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滅殺？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.16,0:14:59.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我成了這麼厲害的人的眷屬了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.36,0:15:03.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 弄得這麼亂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.92,0:15:08.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉蒙里的女兒竟敢…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.39,0:15:11.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我從之前一誠被特蘭西克襲擊開始就察覺到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.54,0:15:16.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個城鎮裡有很多墮天使在策劃著什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.05,0:15:20.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實只要不把我們捲進來就會視若無睹…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.66,0:15:22.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 那麼是為了我…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.91,0:15:26.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠…你那「神器」…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.91,0:15:26.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(367,435)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.88,0:15:29.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知什麼時候形狀就變了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.22,0:15:33.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,紅色的龍…原來是那麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.91,0:15:35.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墮天使雷娜蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.96,0:15:40.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠的「神器」不是單純的「二級危機」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.96,0:15:40.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(228,434)}<Sacred Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.96,0:15:40.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(459,436)}<Twice Critical>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.99,0:15:41.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.07,0:15:44.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,據說它會使擁有者的力量每十秒翻一倍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.13,0:15:49.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,致使其能一時超越魔王和神的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.23,0:15:52.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,十三種「神滅具」之一
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.14,0:15:55.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝之籠手」…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.11,0:15:57.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Boostet Gear」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.81,0:16:01.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,據說連神都能滅掉的可怕的神器…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.71,0:16:02.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟在這種小孩子身上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.49,0:16:07.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管多強大 提升力量是需要時間的 並不是萬能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.58,0:16:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以說是因為對方輕敵了才能贏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.07,0:16:13.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你準備消失吧 墮天使…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.16,0:16:14.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.36,0:16:19.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救救我 雖然我說了那些話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.87,0:16:22.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但那是為了盡作為墮天使的職責迫不得已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.14,0:16:23.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夕麻醬…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.32,0:16:27.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看 作為證據 這個我一直帶著沒扔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.93,0:16:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你沒忘記吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.63,0:16:32.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你給我買的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.49,0:16:35.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你還帶著那種東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.10,0:16:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我無論如何都丟不下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.63,0:16:42.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為是你給我…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.76,0:16:45.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不妙 小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.34,0:16:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救救我吧 一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.15,0:16:55.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…到底要…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.13,0:16:59.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.18,0:17:07.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然誘惑我可愛的僕人 轟飛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.07,0:17:18.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…能和我交往嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.74,0:17:21.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.11,0:17:35.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把這個還給她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.69,0:17:40.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.66,0:17:49.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 對不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.57,0:17:54.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說了那麼過分的話 社長和大家卻都幫了我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.52,0:18:00.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我…沒能保護好愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.05,0:18:07.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 你只是缺少作為惡魔的經驗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.35,0:18:10.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰也不會責備你的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.31,0:18:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是…可是…我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.21,0:18:17.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然前所未聞 可還是值得一試
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.78,0:18:20.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個 你覺得是什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.71,0:18:22.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是西洋棋子…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.81,0:18:25.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正確答案是「主教」之棋哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.81,0:18:25.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(344,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.99,0:18:26.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.06,0:18:31.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「主教」的能力是掩護眷屬的惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.06,0:18:31.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(196,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.16,0:18:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這女孩子的回復之力能當我的僧侶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.77,0:18:37.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 難道…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.92,0:18:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我讓這個修女轉生為惡魔看看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.55,0:18:46.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吾以莉雅絲·吉蒙里之名下令
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.95,0:18:48.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,汝名 愛西亞·阿基多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.55,0:18:54.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,令靈魂重歸此地 成為我的惡魔僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.52,0:18:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,汝作為我的僧侶 以嶄新的生命歸來吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.34,0:19:04.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 愛西亞她…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.34,0:19:06.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.56,0:19:14.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.88,0:19:15.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.12,0:19:17.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.23,0:19:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是需要連惡魔都能治癒的力量才讓她轉生的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.71,0:19:25.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今後由你來保護了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.40,0:19:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟你是學長惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.85,0:19:32.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.79,0:19:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們回去吧 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.59,0:19:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,起來啊 已經早晨了哦 快·起·來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.37,0:19:48.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭…你摸哪裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.97,0:19:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.13,0:19:55.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 來得正好的呢 傷勢怎麼樣了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.92,0:19:58.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 多虧了愛西亞的治療神力 已經痊癒了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.37,0:20:02.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作為「主教」這麼快就派上用場了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.37,0:20:02.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(229,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.18,0:20:04.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能明白墮天使為什麼那麼需要她了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.47,0:20:05.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…社長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.50,0:20:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.58,0:20:10.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是…有跟西洋棋子數量相當的「惡魔之棋」？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.59,0:20:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(482,436)}<Evil Piece>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.04,0:20:11.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.77,0:20:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說…像我一樣的「兵卒」還會增加七人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.87,0:20:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(345,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.02,0:20:19.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我想…如果「競爭對手」再增加的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.25,0:20:24.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是個玩笑而已 小小的玩笑…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.42,0:20:27.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的「兵卒」只有一誠一人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.42,0:20:27.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(263,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.92,0:20:29.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒 那就是說…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.52,0:20:31.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在把人類轉生為惡魔的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.48,0:20:36.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根據轉生者的能力 消耗掉的「惡魔之棋」的數量也不同
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.56,0:20:36.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(393,436)}<Evil Piece>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.56,0:20:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒 消耗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.33,0:20:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我剩下的棋子還有「騎士」「城堡」「主教」各一個
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.33,0:20:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(287,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.33,0:20:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(380,434)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.33,0:20:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(469,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.13,0:20:49.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有八個「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.13,0:20:49.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(367,435)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.68,0:20:52.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒用掉八個全部棋子的話是無法讓你轉生的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.02,0:20:56.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一個人就用掉了八個了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.49,0:21:00.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了這事後 就決定讓你成為我的僕人了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.66,0:21:04.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能擁有這麼多潛力的人是非常少見的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.62,0:21:06.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就賭在這個可能性上了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.30,0:21:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就因為是擁有神滅具之一「赤龍帝之籠手」的一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.30,0:21:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(413,435)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.48,0:21:13.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才會消耗那麼多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.33,0:21:17.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Boostet Gear」…赤龍帝之龍手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.17,0:21:21.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「紅髮之滅殺公主」和「赤龍帝之龍手」…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.60,0:21:24.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,紅色和紅色 是絕配相性呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.79,0:21:26.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.17,0:21:29.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要以最強「兵卒」為目標
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.17,0:21:29.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(344,434)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.45,0:21:31.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是你的話可以辦到的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.65,0:21:33.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為你是我可愛的僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.10,0:21:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最強的「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.10,0:21:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(355,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.54,0:21:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽起來真令人興奮啊 這下向野心又邁進一步…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.65,0:21:46.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個是魔法 你要變強哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.71,0:21:49.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 我會加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.00,0:21:52.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,疼愛你如果不到此為止的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.87,0:21:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就要被新人嫉妒起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.88,0:21:56.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嫉妒？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.77,0:21:58.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.32,0:22:00.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.32,0:22:04.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想起來也是 莉雅絲學姐…不…莉雅絲社長很漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.63,0:22:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以一誠先生也肯定會喜歡上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.03,0:22:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 不可以 不可以想這些事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.29,0:22:14.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真主 請原諒我罪孽的心靈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.77,0:22:15.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.40,0:22:17.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然頭痛了起來…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.15,0:22:20.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然了 你現在已經變成惡魔了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.61,0:22:25.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 我變成惡魔了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.63,0:22:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你後悔嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.06,0:22:29.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 謝謝你了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.39,0:22:31.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管是什麼樣的形式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.82,0:22:35.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像這樣能跟一誠先生見面我就無比幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.51,0:22:37.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話說 你那身裝扮…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.71,0:22:39.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,適合我嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.42,0:22:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 愛西亞要上這個學院？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.98,0:22:47.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的父親也參與這個學校的營運 這種算小事一樁了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.38,0:22:49.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我之前不知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.81,0:22:52.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.60,0:22:54.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 一誠學長
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.36,0:22:58.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 大家都到齊了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.67,0:23:01.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 這是新人的歡迎派對哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.28,0:23:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.40,0:23:06.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是最棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.06,0:23:09.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝…謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.64,0:23:16.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是個好結局啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.10,0:23:18.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…騙你們的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.42,0:23:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想摸摸我的胸嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.54,0:23:32.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胸部 胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.11,0:23:38.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想…我想讓美露炭變成魔法少女
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.12,0:23:41.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那可是犯罪 一誠學長
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.72,0:23:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(322,212)}第6話 ｢正在當惡魔！｣
Comment: 0,0:21:52.90,0:21:58.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.65,0:21:47.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.04,0:21:51.17,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.57,0:22:07.18,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.25,0:22:12.85,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.88,0:22:18.52,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know? Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.52,0:22:23.41,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.41,0:22:29.96,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.14,0:22:34.37,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.38,0:22:37.56,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.98,0:22:41.01,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.17,0:22:44.02,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.25,0:22:46.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.09,0:22:49.25,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.42,0:22:55.15,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.44,0:22:59.38,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.42,0:23:01.43,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.43,0:23:04.05,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.08,0:23:06.78,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.98,0:23:11.33,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:21:47.04,0:21:47.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.65,0:21:47.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.04,0:21:51.17,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.57,0:22:07.18,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.25,0:22:12.85,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.88,0:22:18.52,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know? Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.52,0:22:23.41,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.41,0:22:29.96,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.14,0:22:34.37,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.38,0:22:37.56,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.98,0:22:41.01,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.17,0:22:44.02,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.25,0:22:46.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.09,0:22:49.25,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.42,0:22:55.15,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.44,0:22:59.38,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.42,0:23:01.43,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.43,0:23:04.05,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.08,0:23:06.78,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.98,0:23:11.33,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.44,0:23:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
