[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Original Script: DHR
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer:100.0000
Last Style Storage: DXD
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 4
Video Position: 34091
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.70,0:00:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是萊薩的「女王」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.70,0:00:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(486,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.07,0:00:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.49,0:00:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.92,0:00:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還想…多幫點社長忙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.92,0:00:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有事的 這點傷愛西亞會馬上治療…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.72,0:00:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.89,0:00:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小…
Comment: 0,0:00:45.52,0:02:10.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.52,0:00:51.46,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.62,0:00:57.11,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.34,0:01:02.83,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.14,0:01:09.15,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.35,0:01:15.99,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.28,0:01:21.71,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.08,0:01:24.79,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.97,0:01:27.84,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.00,0:01:39.81,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:00:25.03,0:00:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.52,0:00:51.46,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.62,0:00:57.11,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.34,0:01:02.83,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.14,0:01:09.15,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.35,0:01:15.99,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.28,0:01:21.71,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.08,0:01:24.79,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.97,0:01:27.84,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.00,0:01:39.81,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:09.60,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU 後期:KoU BDrip:ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.84,0:02:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,388)}第11話 「絕讚，決戰進行中！」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.09,0:02:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人的一名「城堡」出局
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.09,0:02:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(518,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.25,0:02:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 你竟敢把小貓咪…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.03,0:02:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快給我下來 我來對付你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.27,0:02:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷靜 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.39,0:02:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥不能者會被傳送到指定的地點接受治療
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.80,0:02:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓沒死
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.97,0:02:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請冷靜一點
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.54,0:02:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.46,0:02:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放棄吧 小男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.39,0:02:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管如何掙扎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.46,0:02:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們是贏不了我們的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.76,0:02:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.22,0:02:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.33,0:02:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 這裡就交給我 你就先走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.21,0:02:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必擔心 我會全心全意 為小貓報仇雪恨的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.76,0:02:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.90,0:02:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以來想著有朝一日能跟你單挑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.56,0:02:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「雷之巫女」小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.32,0:02:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 那真是我的榮幸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.81,0:02:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「爆彈王妃」小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.81,0:02:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(396,436)}<Boom Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.88,0:02:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩大人的三名「兵卒」 出局
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.88,0:02:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(499,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.98,0:03:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.19,0:03:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.14,0:03:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.32,0:03:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才所說的三人難道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.90,0:03:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧了朱乃學姐的結界 收拾她們讓我輕鬆了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.90,0:03:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼一來 現在所剩的棋子變為
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.22,0:03:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩大人九個 莉雅絲大人五個
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.63,0:03:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不能大意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.96,0:03:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木場 抱歉 小貓咪她…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.15,0:03:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.50,0:03:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來是很內向的女孩子 可今天卻幹勁十足
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.02,0:03:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她心裡肯定很怨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.53,0:03:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去贏得勝利 絕對
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.17,0:03:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.80,0:03:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佑斗 一誠 能聽得到嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.66,0:03:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和愛西亞去奇襲他們大本營
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.65,0:03:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你們盡可能的牽制住他們 為我們爭取時間
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.19,0:03:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇襲？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.45,0:03:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也迫不得已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.15,0:03:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來是計劃是 等朱乃的魔力復原後 一個一個去擊破
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.19,0:04:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是對方直接派出了「女王」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.19,0:04:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(560,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.10,0:04:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是社長 「王」親自出擊大本營 是不是風險太大？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.10,0:04:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(259,436)}<King>
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.61,0:04:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敵人也會這麼認為吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.81,0:04:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是抓住這個破綻
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.74,0:04:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎麼強調菲尼克斯是不死之身
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.69,0:04:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是未必內心也是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.74,0:04:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他嚐到足以讓他失去戰鬥意志的攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.59,0:04:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就有可能打敗萊薩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.85,0:04:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我親自去挫敗萊薩的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.10,0:04:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然這麼決定了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.12,0:04:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就以我們神祕學研究社男子搭檔組合
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.88,0:04:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來一場華麗的戰鬥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.70,0:04:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我知道你們藏起來的 堂堂正正地滾出來決勝負吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.30,0:04:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是萊薩大人的手下「騎士」 卡拉米爾
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.30,0:04:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(502,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.58,0:04:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然大搖大擺地從正面出來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.08,0:04:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像是神智清醒的人的所作所為
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.33,0:04:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我倒是很喜歡 像你們這樣的笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.14,0:05:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是莉雅絲大人的手下「騎士」 木場佑斗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.14,0:05:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(517,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.38,0:05:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「騎士」（Knight）間對決
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.80,0:05:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直盼著這天到來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.59,0:05:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說得很好 莉雅絲‧吉蒙里的「騎士」！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.59,0:05:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(615,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.65,0:05:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 話說沒有我出場的機會
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.86,0:05:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不一定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.01,0:05:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡拉米爾 這人真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.45,0:05:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿腦子都是劍 劍 劍
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.33,0:05:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犧牲己方棋子時也擺出憤憤不平的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.81,0:05:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了她土裡土氣的性格
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.20,0:05:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還以為難得找到了可愛的男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.00,0:05:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到他也是劍痴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.24,0:05:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真夠不走運
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.89,0:05:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把剩下的棋子全部投入是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.17,0:05:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長猜對了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.45,0:06:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 莉雅絲看男人的眼光這麼差嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.37,0:06:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長著一副可愛的臉蛋 沒想到是個吐毒舌的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.27,0:06:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝之籠手」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.27,0:06:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.08,0:06:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.20,0:06:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.04,0:06:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不戰的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.28,0:06:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊莎貝拉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.28,0:06:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是伊莎貝拉 萊薩大人的手下「城堡」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.28,0:06:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(629,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.38,0:06:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.72,0:06:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲點‧吉蒙里的「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.72,0:06:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(578,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.30,0:06:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 那傢伙到底算什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.97,0:06:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不戰鬥到底是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.15,0:06:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然作為「主教」參戰
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.15,0:06:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(454,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.58,0:06:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本只是觀戰的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.59,0:06:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.78,0:06:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她…不 那位大人是蕾維兒‧菲尼克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.89,0:06:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尼克斯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.09,0:06:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然現在是作為眷屬 但她是萊薩大人的親妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.72,0:06:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.59,0:06:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這叫做萌自己妹妹？ 不是有很多人羨慕或憧憬有妹妹的人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.98,0:06:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 我不萌自己妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.11,0:07:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是形式上作為我的眷屬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.28,0:07:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.68,0:07:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來那鳥混蛋 真的是個白痴變態
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.91,0:07:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我能夠充分理解 他想把自己妹妹拉入後宮的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.03,0:07:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我預計的還強啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.85,0:07:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那當然 我也不是白白跟小貓和佑斗接受訓練的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.32,0:07:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話雖這麼說 把力量強化到一定程度之前 只有逃跑這一策
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.29,0:07:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.40,0:07:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是第五次強化
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.25,0:07:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是「兵卒」（Pawn）的話 也許足夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.42,0:07:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是對手是「城堡」的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.44,0:07:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(457,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.78,0:07:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 跟以前被米菈襲擊時完全不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.58,0:07:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來莉雅絲‧吉蒙里把你鍛鍊地訓練有素嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.02,0:07:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 我被社長狠狠地訓練了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.73,0:07:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是莉雅絲社長的僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.74,0:07:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以絕不能輸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.78,0:07:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算只為了社長…也要把你打到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.44,0:08:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.15,0:08:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親愛的莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.97,0:08:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的食光劍被…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.45,0:08:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遺憾 那種攻擊對我是不管用的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.05,0:08:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 這個如何呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.91,0:08:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我凍起來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.40,0:08:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙竟然擁有兩件神器
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.61,0:08:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.68,0:08:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們高貴的菲尼克斯眷屬 掌管著 火焰 風 生命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.69,0:08:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會輸給你這種傢伙的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.38,0:08:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙到底有幾件神器？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.15,0:08:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我並不是擁有多件神器 只是製造出來了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.48,0:08:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「魔劍製造」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.48,0:08:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Sword Birth>
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.24,0:08:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.79,0:09:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以按照我的意願製造出魔劍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.12,0:09:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.32,0:09:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.45,0:09:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來他有那種能力…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.31,0:09:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你 戰鬥中別東張西望
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.42,0:09:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 差不多該來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.00,0:09:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.42,0:09:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.20,0:09:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Explosion!!」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.56,0:09:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威力不及「龍之波」的「龍之魔彈」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.56,0:09:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(380,436)}<Dragon Waves>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.56,0:09:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(576,436)}<Dragon Shot>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.93,0:09:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說說看的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.42,0:09:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這已經算是保留了我相當多的力量的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.58,0:09:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個神器很危險
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.84,0:09:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須由我來當場解決掉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.15,0:09:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逮著了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.96,0:09:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為這樣就打中我了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.77,0:09:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我綻開！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.65,0:09:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「洋服崩壞」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.65,0:09:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Dress Break>
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.63,0:09:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.34,0:09:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在腦內存儲器裡貼上名片保存
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.44,0:09:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保存完畢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.17,0:10:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 開始
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.58,0:10:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊莎貝拉被…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.67,0:10:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩大人的「城堡」一名出局
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.69,0:10:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(443,436)}<Rook>
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.09,0:10:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.38,0:10:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過這招數真夠粗暴的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.23,0:10:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對 應該說對女人來說是恐怖的招數
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.96,0:10:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是頭一次看到…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.27,0:10:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…該怎麼說好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.99,0:10:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉  我們的一誠是個色狼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.46,0:10:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 別這麼毫無掩飾的跟人家道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.66,0:10:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木場！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.34,0:10:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊的士兵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.06,0:10:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 你已經注意到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.14,0:10:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.63,0:10:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算主動出擊 這也太快了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.85,0:10:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的詭計被他們拆穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.43,0:11:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說早就預料到我會來是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.23,0:11:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個處女 可不能小看老練者哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.87,0:11:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.03,0:11:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一成不變 說話還是這麼下流
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.04,0:11:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「紅髮滅殺姬」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.04,0:11:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(426,436)}<Ruin Princess>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.69,0:11:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「聖母的微笑」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.69,0:11:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(424,436)}<Twilight Healing>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.07,0:11:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「雷之巫女」還有 「魔劍製造」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.07,0:11:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(551,436)}<Sword Birth>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.69,0:11:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝之籠手」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.69,0:11:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(424,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.40,0:11:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是一排聽起來很厲害的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.48,0:11:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們是菲尼克斯不死鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.97,0:11:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不死之身哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.80,0:11:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能明白嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.52,0:11:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這情況對於你們來說多麼的絕望
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.21,0:11:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小蜜 小麗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.54,0:11:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些「兵卒」 你可別光用外表來判斷她們的實力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.54,0:11:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(225,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.55,0:11:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝之籠手」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.55,0:11:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(427,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.01,0:11:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.27,0:11:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是差勁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.44,0:11:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用下半身思考問題
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.64,0:11:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愚蠢之極
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.65,0:11:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給他狠狠一擊 司雷絲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.55,0:12:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下真危險了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.80,0:12:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.16,0:12:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.70,0:12:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你們能多陪我玩玩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.32,0:12:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是難得的婚前交涉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.03,0:12:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見鬼去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.72,0:12:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.71,0:12:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.82,0:12:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的事先不說 現在對付眼前的敵人要緊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.19,0:12:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.13,0:12:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我信賴著你 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.71,0:12:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他們瞧瞧吉蒙里眷屬的厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.51,0:12:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 我是社長的僕人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.76,0:12:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然把司雷絲劍…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.07,0:12:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用手臂…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.73,0:12:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼可考慮的 就只為了社長 我要把你們打到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.36,0:12:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.89,0:12:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤龍帝啊 如果聽得見的話 請回應我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.01,0:12:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請賜予我力量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.78,0:12:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Dragon Booster」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.48,0:12:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來點
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.35,0:12:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更猛烈地回應於我的心意吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.82,0:13:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝之籠手」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.82,0:13:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.67,0:13:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Dragon Booster Second Liberation」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.48,0:13:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.69,0:13:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形狀變了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.15,0:13:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到「雷之巫女」竟然如此的厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.11,0:13:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過你的魔力 應該早就空了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.55,0:13:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不著你為我擔心 因為只要稍微休息一會兒就能恢復
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.97,0:13:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為你有那個時間嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.06,0:13:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.01,0:13:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上鉤了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.36,0:13:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 這是我的新能力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.38,0:13:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木場！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.93,0:13:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快釋放你的神器的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.53,0:13:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,釋放？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.63,0:13:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.76,0:13:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「魔劍製造」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.76,0:13:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Sword Birth>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.60,0:14:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Transfer!!」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.97,0:14:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認輸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.61,0:14:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33}萊薩大人的「兵卒」二名 「騎士」二名  「主教」一名 出局
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.61,0:14:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(253,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.61,0:14:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(434,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.61,0:14:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(616,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.24,0:14:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「騎士」的能力 被「赤龍帝之籠手」強化了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.24,0:14:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(193,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.24,0:14:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(505,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.62,0:14:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 赤龍帝贈予的新能力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.09,0:14:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝的贈禮」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.09,0:14:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(424,436)}<Boostet Gear Gift>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.74,0:14:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人的「女王」一名 出局
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.74,0:14:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(451,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.21,0:14:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.23,0:15:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.97,0:15:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐她…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.51,0:15:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像損失了讓你引以自豪的左膀右臂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.59,0:15:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還有佑斗和一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.32,0:15:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那樣就好…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.10,0:15:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐居然被打敗了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.31,0:15:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木場！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.03,0:15:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木場！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.76,0:15:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「擊破」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.78,0:15:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(424,436)}<Take>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.26,0:15:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.49,0:15:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人的「騎士」一名 出局
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.49,0:15:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(453,436)}<Knight>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.70,0:15:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佑斗！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.54,0:15:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放棄遊戲（Resignation）吧 莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.88,0:15:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.64,0:15:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還不明白嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.85,0:15:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去 只會傷害你那「主教」和
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.85,0:15:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(566,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.25,0:15:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所疼愛的「兵卒」而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.25,0:15:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(473,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.47,0:15:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.59,0:15:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你來晚了 尤貝露娜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.83,0:15:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如傳說一樣 那個「女王」確實厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.86,0:15:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(476,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.08,0:15:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最終還是借助了它的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.85,0:16:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贏就是贏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.67,0:16:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然你就是最靠得住的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.62,0:16:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.40,0:16:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那瓶子是什麼東西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.56,0:16:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尼克斯的眼淚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.16,0:16:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管什麼傷 都能讓其瞬間痊癒的 吾家一族的秘寶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.28,0:16:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這都有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.71,0:16:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 這在遊戲裡是被准許的哦 最多可以使用兩個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.20,0:16:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們那也不是有擁有「聖母的微笑」的「主教」嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.20,0:16:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(470,436)}<Twilight Healing>
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.20,0:16:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(653,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.53,0:16:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由於我家一族才有能力製造這個 所以可以高價賣出
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.99,0:16:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不死之身加上眼淚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.39,0:16:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自從評估遊戲開始以來 菲尼克斯家就好事不斷
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.35,0:16:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 無視我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.33,0:16:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「升級」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.36,0:16:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(423,436)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.67,0:16:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請賜予我「女王」的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.67,0:16:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(439,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.61,0:16:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我 我一定會讓社長贏得勝利的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.56,0:17:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 兵藤一誠 此刻參上！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.89,0:17:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.78,0:17:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.17,0:17:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小男孩「兵卒」和小姐「主教」就由我來對付…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.17,0:17:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(258,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.17,0:17:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(472,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.70,0:17:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必了 還是我來把他們一網打盡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.96,0:17:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣才能讓他們口服心服
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.68,0:17:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別胡說
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.89,0:17:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些話 先打倒我再說
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.33,0:17:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放棄遊戲吧 莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.58,0:17:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已經陷入困境了 我早就料到會這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.89,0:17:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已被「將軍」了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.62,0:17:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我閉嘴 萊薩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.43,0:17:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逼入困境？預料？別說笑了 我這「王」還健在呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.43,0:17:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(581,436)}<King>
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.37,0:17:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下我也無可奈何了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.96,0:17:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去實行那個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.28,0:17:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.59,0:17:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是那麼激烈的戰鬥 你竟然挺過來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.58,0:17:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是跟你約好的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.19,0:17:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.19,0:17:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.30,0:17:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞是我們的生命線 你先退一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.22,0:18:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞！ 一誠！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.72,0:18:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.90,0:18:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞她…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.30,0:18:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫髮無傷 她只是受刺激暈了過去而已
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.73,0:18:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 沒想到他會用身體去抵擋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.59,0:18:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 也好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.01,0:18:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 這樣一來「聖母的微笑」的力量就已經封住了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.01,0:18:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(383,436)}<Twilight Healing>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.25,0:18:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.45,0:18:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明從正面接受了我的攻擊…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.60,0:18:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是「女王」的防禦力吧 你被「升級」得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.60,0:18:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(237,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.60,0:18:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(579,436)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.40,0:18:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長 這場比試還繼續的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.90,0:18:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.71,0:18:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我是個笨蛋 所以不懂什麼是揭穿詭計和陷入困境
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.17,0:18:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我還可以戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.82,0:18:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我這個拳頭還能握得住就可以繼續戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.03,0:18:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.02,0:18:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一起打到萊薩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.90,0:18:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.86,0:18:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等等 愛西亞 我們絕對會贏的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.94,0:18:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後一起回去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.60,0:18:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.35,0:19:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.44,0:19:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一遍 「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.30,0:19:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.35,0:19:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二遍 「Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.45,0:19:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Burst」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.56,0:19:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.76,0:19:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝之籠手」所帶給寄宿的身體負荷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.76,0:19:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(272,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.94,0:19:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大到其他神器無法與之相比
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.03,0:19:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如說 強化力量這麼多次 還能繼續戰鬥這本身
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.46,0:19:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經很接近奇蹟了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.36,0:19:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔力都落空了 還受到了尤貝露娜的直擊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.69,0:19:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的負荷已經超過了肉體所能承受的極限
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.02,0:19:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.36,0:19:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.74,0:19:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.83,0:19:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也只剩下這點魔力了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.56,0:19:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老老實實地承認敗北 趕緊放棄遊戲如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.95,0:19:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼才要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.35,0:19:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事的 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.92,0:19:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會不惜任何代價也要去贏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.39,0:20:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要成為最強的「兵卒」 我已經跟社長約好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.39,0:20:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(391,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.82,0:20:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長還訓練了我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.75,0:20:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你個打不死的活屍
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.08,0:20:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還能戰鬥的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.64,0:20:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會遵守約定的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.90,0:20:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.54,0:20:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還能戰鬥 因為我是社長的「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.54,0:20:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(611,436)}<Pawn>
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.67,0:20:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還能戰鬥的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.54,0:20:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會贏的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.43,0:20:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 退下！ 快退下！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.77,0:20:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.99,0:20:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 我什麼你不聽我的命令…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.70,0:20:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.84,0:20:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能讓社長笑出來的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.41,0:20:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡社長跟其他事沒有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.00,0:20:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為莉雅絲學姐對我來說是最重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.17,0:20:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 你…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.35,0:20:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很讓人不爽…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.95,0:20:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,區區一個僕人而已 硬是要跟我這萊薩‧菲尼克斯對抗嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.60,0:20:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩 你想幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.42,0:21:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼 我只是順著他的意思 把他燒成灰而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.79,0:21:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燒到讓治療失去意義
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.14,0:21:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遊戲中的死亡可以被當做事故來處理
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.51,0:21:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.22,0:21:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.21,0:21:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一誠！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你住手 萊薩
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.89,0:21:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我輸了 我放棄遊戲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.23,0:21:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「將軍」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.53,0:21:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.80,0:21:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確認莉雅絲大人放棄遊戲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.64,0:21:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場遊戲 萊薩‧菲尼克斯取得勝利
Comment: 0,0:21:56.74,0:21:59.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:00.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.93,0:22:05.06,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.46,0:22:21.07,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.14,0:22:26.74,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.77,0:22:32.41,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.41,0:22:37.30,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.30,0:22:43.85,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.03,0:22:48.26,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:51.45,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:54.90,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.91,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.14,0:23:00.83,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.14,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.31,0:23:09.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.33,0:23:13.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.31,0:23:15.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.32,0:23:17.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.97,0:23:20.67,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.87,0:23:25.22,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.59,0:23:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是訂婚派對 但這不就是婚紗嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.43,0:23:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好弱…我為什麼這麼弱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.66,0:23:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的皇后 莉雅絲‧吉蒙里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.19,0:23:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒結束呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.01,0:23:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fsp2\fs38\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(417,210)}第12話 「前來履行諾言！」
D
