[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 4
Video Position: 34139
Last Style Storage: DXD
Collisions: Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.52,0:00:09.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,STAFF
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.52,0:00:09.55,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR製作 DMG協力  僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯:朱雀、Amanda、堀秀正  校譯:牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU 後期:KoU BDrip:ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.98,0:00:03.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.84,0:00:07.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你現在所揮舞的力量 並不是其原本的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.27,0:00:08.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.53,0:00:09.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在哪裡聽過…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.65,0:00:13.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話無論過多久你都不會變強的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.29,0:00:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,記起來了…你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.92,0:00:16.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之前也在夢裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.38,0:00:19.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是寄宿著龍的異常存在
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.98,0:00:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別露出這麼丟人的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.12,0:00:24.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會被那「白色傢伙」嘲笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.02,0:00:26.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,白色傢伙是…誰！？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.23,0:00:28.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天會出現在你面前的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.53,0:00:32.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯…你跟他是命中注定的對手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.23,0:00:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為此 你必須要變強
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.44,0:00:36.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我無論何時都可以借予你力量
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.82,0:00:40.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧 付出的代價 會得到相應的回報
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.63,0:00:43.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在他們面前展現真正的龍之力量
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.43,0:00:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龍？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.25,0:00:44.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.42,0:00:48.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,, 「Welsh Dragon」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.87,0:00:51.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝」德萊格
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.23,0:00:52.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,德萊格？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.43,0:00:54.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你左手的寄宿之物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.75,0:01:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎？我怎麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.25,0:01:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,388)}第12話 「前來履行諾言！」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.49,0:01:05.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,醒來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.49,0:01:07.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葛瑞菲雅小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.89,0:01:10.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勝負呢？社長她怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.34,0:01:14.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遊戲是以萊薩大人的勝利收場
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.23,0:01:15.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,輸了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.18,0:01:18.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人宣布認輸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.33,0:01:20.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長她…投降了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.78,0:01:21.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.25,0:01:23.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不是真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.41,0:01:27.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能認輸呢…這不可能是社長說出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.72,0:01:30.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為萊薩大人就要把你殺掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.23,0:01:34.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那時候的事…我記得不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.77,0:01:38.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無論被打倒多少次 你都重新站起來對抗萊薩大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.10,0:01:42.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 你已經做得很好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.61,0:01:44.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經夠了 你真的做得很好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.41,0:01:48.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你了 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.86,0:01:51.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來那是這樣的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.52,0:01:53.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全都是因為我…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.84,0:01:56.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虧我還在社長面前表現出勝券在握的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.86,0:01:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,結果卻在她的面前被整的這麼慘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.20,0:02:02.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其他…其他人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.51,0:02:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有愛西亞小姐 遵照莉雅絲大人的指示
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.83,0:02:08.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而留在這裡照顧一誠大人您
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.72,0:02:10.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除此之外的其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.55,0:02:13.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟隨莉雅絲大人一同去了冥界
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.21,0:02:14.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一同…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.07,0:02:17.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,婚禮Party…萊薩大人與莉雅絲大人的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.41,0:02:19.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.67,0:02:23.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只想跟只把我當做莉雅絲來愛的人一起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.59,0:02:26.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想擁有這小小的願望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.84,0:02:28.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.87,0:02:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以最強的「兵卒」為目標吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.87,0:02:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Pwan>
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.00,0:02:33.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你一定能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.34,0:02:35.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為你是我最可愛的僕人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.37,0:02:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變強吧 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.60,0:02:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我變不強…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.77,0:02:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弱小…因為我可是如此的弱小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.76,0:02:49.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來你不能接受呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.17,0:02:52.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人這可是遵循了家族的決議
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.47,0:02:56.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來 決勝的結果也是出自其本人的願望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.31,0:02:58.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 我可是知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.93,0:03:00.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但就算是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.33,0:03:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不甘地認許所討厭的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.92,0:03:06.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不情願但也只能死心遵循家長所言的社長
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.51,0:03:07.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要看到這樣的社長
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.28,0:03:11.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被那個混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.88,0:03:16.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真是一個有趣的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.21,0:03:19.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼多年來我見識過無數惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.91,0:03:23.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你這樣把心裡所想之事都如實地表現在自己臉上的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.17,0:03:25.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想做什麼就做什麼的惡魔 還是第一次見到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.38,0:03:30.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瑟傑克斯大人也曾經說過你很有趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.75,0:03:32.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔法陣？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.02,0:03:35.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個魔法陣可以傳送到婚禮現場
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.91,0:03:38.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是要我去社長身旁見證那場婚禮嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.42,0:03:41.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「要是想搶回我妹妹的話 就給我去攪場」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.12,0:03:45.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是把這個魔法陣給我的瑟傑克斯大人說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.83,0:03:54.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那邊是…奪回大小姐之後才派得上用場的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.72,0:04:02.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無需多想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.77,0:04:05.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.88,0:04:11.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.02,0:04:12.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 突然…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.18,0:04:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.08,0:04:18.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明傷都痊癒了 但這兩天裡你都一直昏迷不醒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.63,0:04:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不禁想到你會不會就這樣一睡不醒呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.85,0:04:25.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了 又讓愛西亞你擔心了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.39,0:04:29.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡…只要一誠先生你能好起來 這點小事完全無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.94,0:04:31.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你聽我說 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.37,0:04:32.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.90,0:04:34.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我這就要去社長那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.85,0:04:38.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是去祝賀…的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.92,0:04:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 去把社長奪回來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.92,0:04:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.48,0:04:44.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.61,0:04:47.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 愛西亞你留在這
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.35,0:04:51.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要 我也要跟一誠先生一同戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.34,0:04:55.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也變得能使用魔法了 我不甘願一直被他人保護著
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.13,0:04:58.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧 我一定痛扁萊薩一頓 然後把他打倒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.62,0:05:00.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才不是這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.81,0:05:04.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會再次變得 血流不止 遍體鱗傷
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.81,0:05:07.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓你承受很多痛苦…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.70,0:05:10.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不想再看到這樣的一誠了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.40,0:05:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不會死的 絕對
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.20,0:05:19.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想想 救愛西亞你的時候我不還是活的好好的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.75,0:05:22.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你就要跟我做約定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.27,0:05:23.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,約定？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.39,0:05:27.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要和社長一起回來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.51,0:05:28.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.62,0:05:32.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且我有點事想要愛西亞你幫幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.04,0:05:37.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這事只能拜託愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.66,0:05:38.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.62,0:05:40.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.07,0:05:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然一誠先生都說到這個份上了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.51,0:05:45.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:49.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你都聽到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.69,0:05:51.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我找你有事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.91,0:05:54.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出來把 「赤龍帝」德萊格
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.97,0:05:58.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 小鬼 找我有什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.93,0:06:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想要跟你做個交易
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.40,0:06:06.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明是訂婚Party 但怎麼是一身婚紗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.92,0:06:08.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.29,0:06:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 萊薩大人 這裡男士禁止入內
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.52,0:06:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別這麼死板嘛 我可是今天的主角哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.80,0:06:20.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 主角可是新娘子啊 這可真是失敬了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.58,0:06:22.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我還不是你的正式新娘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.82,0:06:24.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這身衣裝是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.38,0:06:25.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.98,0:06:30.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33}這樣才能更好的向冥界展示 吉蒙里家族與菲尼克斯家族喜結連理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.75,0:06:34.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿了這身衣裝 也能更加的讓你死心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.10,0:06:36.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對吧 哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.62,0:06:37.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心放心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.89,0:06:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到正式的婚禮上 會準備好比這身好上千萬倍的婚紗的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.37,0:06:46.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用我們菲尼克斯家族傳統的火之羽所點綴的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.09,0:06:49.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全冥界最矜貴的衣裝哈~
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.46,0:06:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一聽就像是惡趣味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.36,0:06:53.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是暴發戶一族
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.98,0:07:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.63,0:07:03.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.39,0:07:05.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.57,0:07:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…是不會輸的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.50,0:07:12.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長…我一定會贏給你看的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.77,0:07:16.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明就連魔力的使用方法都還沒有銘記在心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.94,0:07:19.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,實戰的經驗也幾乎為零
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.48,0:07:23.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卻仍要為我而全力奔波著
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.42,0:07:25.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是個笨蛋啊 做到這個地步
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.82,0:07:28.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我才是傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.55,0:07:32.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差一點就失去這孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.45,0:07:35.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最可愛的最重要的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.46,0:07:39.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯…非常重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.00,0:07:41.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.26,0:07:43.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人 時間到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.87,0:07:51.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥大人真是的 通過評估遊戲就賺來一個新娘
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.15,0:07:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我早就猜到勝負結局了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.04,0:07:57.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本來還想著要弄出些更精彩的場面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.12,0:07:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是暢所欲言啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.75,0:08:02.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忘記了在轉播中的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.47,0:08:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蒼那會長
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.52,0:08:06.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先不說結果 雙方各平分秋色
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.13,0:08:10.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 你們的表現更好 誰也看的一清二楚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.01,0:08:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你了 但不用您擔心了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.51,0:08:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概還沒有結束
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.09,0:08:19.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們是這樣想的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.23,0:08:20.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒結束
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.44,0:08:26.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,譽冥界的各位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.41,0:08:31.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我僅代表菲尼克斯家族由衷感謝大家能前來參加這場婚禮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.15,0:08:34.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今日由大家來共享
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.68,0:08:39.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我萊薩·菲尼克斯與名門吉蒙里的下任當家
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.97,0:08:46.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲·吉蒙里的訂婚 這個歷史瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.66,0:08:49.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 由我來介紹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.27,0:08:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的皇后 莉雅絲·吉蒙里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.31,0:09:00.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.33,0:09:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.76,0:09:04.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 混帳 你知道這裡是哪裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.44,0:09:06.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是駒王學園神秘學研究社的兵藤一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.94,0:09:10.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 莉雅絲·吉蒙里的處女是我的！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.51,0:09:12.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混帳！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.46,0:09:14.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個男人究竟在想什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.37,0:09:15.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把他抓住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.16,0:09:19.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 我們也該出場了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.35,0:09:19.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.89,0:09:20.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.35,0:09:25.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 這裡就交給我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.02,0:09:26.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來的真慢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.64,0:09:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場 小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.50,0:09:31.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 你總算來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.19,0:09:32.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.67,0:09:34.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.20,0:09:34.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.87,0:09:36.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這究竟是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.21,0:09:38.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莉雅絲大人 這究竟是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.25,0:09:40.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是我準備的餘興節目哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.17,0:09:42.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.16,0:09:43.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄長大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.57,0:09:44.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是說…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.74,0:09:47.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瑟傑克斯·路西法大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.01,0:09:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個人就是…魔王！？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.52,0:09:52.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瑟傑克斯大人 餘興到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.90,0:09:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩君 那場評估遊戲真的很有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.63,0:10:03.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊 以毫無遊戲經驗 \N就連戰力的半數也不足的妹妹來作對手稍微有點…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.25,0:10:05.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您對那場戰鬥有所不滿嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.69,0:10:09.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 我不出來主持一下的話
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.22,0:10:13.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,評估遊戲 就會失去其原有的意味了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.89,0:10:16.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更何況這次事出有因
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.45,0:10:19.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不給點面子給老家裡那幾個老傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.26,0:10:25.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可愛的妹妹的訂婚Party 他們也希望能熱鬧隆重些
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.72,0:10:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那邊的少年
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.53,0:10:29.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你所擁有龍的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.70,0:10:32.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想親眼看看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.51,0:10:35.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從葛瑞菲雅那裡稍有耳聞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.93,0:10:37.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 也就是說…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.77,0:10:40.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龍對不死鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.02,0:10:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同樣擁有傳說力量的同類間的決鬥…讓會場變得更為熱鬧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.89,0:11:03.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄長大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.98,0:11:08.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是魔王大人啊 總能想出一些有趣的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.52,0:11:10.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,操龍君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.66,0:11:11.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.54,0:11:17.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能在我和在場所有的上級貴族惡魔們面前展現出你那力量嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.36,0:11:18.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.11,0:11:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.60,0:11:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼由我萊薩 成家立業前向大家展示最後的火焰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.75,0:11:27.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 操龍君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.78,0:11:29.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什麼獎勵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.94,0:11:31.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瑟傑克斯大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.18,0:11:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼能對下級惡魔提獎勵呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.40,0:11:36.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下級也好 上級也好 他都是惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.15,0:11:39.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然是由我這邊首先提出的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.19,0:11:41.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就必須要給予其相應的代價
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.91,0:11:43.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.31,0:11:46.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爵位？還是說 絕世美女？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.42,0:11:49.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 說說你的願望
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.05,0:11:50.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.56,0:11:53.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 把莉雅絲·吉蒙里大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.06,0:11:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還給我！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.59,0:11:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.05,0:12:01.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 給我用10秒時間 讓我解決他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.73,0:12:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然想用10秒 解決哥哥大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.48,0:12:06.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此話當真？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.80,0:12:10.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 我就用5秒的時間讓你閉上你那臭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.58,0:12:12.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓你無法再口出狂言
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.36,0:12:16.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 請求許可 讓我使用「升級」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.36,0:12:16.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(583,436)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.97,0:12:19.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 你到底打算做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.61,0:12:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「升級」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.61,0:12:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(424,436)}<Promotion>
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.28,0:12:24.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「女王」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.28,0:12:24.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(424,436)}<Queen>
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.61,0:12:25.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒用的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.71,0:12:27.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.66,0:12:31.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有像木場那樣的使劍才能
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.70,0:12:34.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是像朱乃學姐那樣的魔力天才
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.65,0:12:36.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也沒有小貓一樣的怪力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.95,0:12:40.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不像愛西亞那樣 擁有實用的治癒能力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.40,0:12:43.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使這樣 我還是要成為最強的「兵卒」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.40,0:12:43.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(627,436)}<Pwan>
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.46,0:12:47.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要為了社長 哪怕是神 我也會去打倒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.37,0:12:51.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放出光芒 「Over Boost」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.61,0:12:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Welsh Dragon Over Booster」 ！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.36,0:13:11.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是龍帝的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.51,0:13:15.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「禁手」、「赤龍帝之鎧」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.56,0:13:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(304,436)}<Balance Breaker>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.56,0:13:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21\pos(499,436)}<Boostet Gear Scale Mail>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.78,0:13:18.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「禁手」？ 也就是說禁忌？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.79,0:13:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(316,436)}<Balance Breaker>
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.41,0:13:22.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被禁忌的可怕的邪門歪法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.07,0:13:24.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我做個交易
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.96,0:13:28.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有意思 你有覺悟嗎 小子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.07,0:13:30.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,囉嗦 你是要幹 還是不幹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.69,0:13:35.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我應該說過 我會賦予你跟你所做出犧牲相符合的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.48,0:13:37.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過 你要記住一點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.05,0:13:38.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,倒數10秒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.79,0:13:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再多的話 你的肉體會受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.40,0:13:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就已經足夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.16,0:13:46.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把那混蛋揍飛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.47,0:13:47.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ten
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.76,0:13:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.17,0:13:57.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Nine
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.27,0:14:02.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事 這股力量和速度
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.96,0:14:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是令人不爽的臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.20,0:14:08.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在的你只是個怪物 臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.15,0:14:11.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被譽為火鳥和鳳凰 還有不死鳥的菲尼克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.37,0:14:15.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其我家一族的地獄之火 讓你的身體焚燒殆盡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.79,0:14:16.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Eight
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.61,0:14:21.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那微不足道的火焰 怎能燒得了我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.48,0:14:29.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是沒了這盔甲的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.06,0:14:32.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是那傢伙的實力嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.68,0:14:33.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Seven
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.68,0:14:36.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怕了嗎 怕我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.06,0:14:38.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒了「赤龍帝之籠手」 你就只是個垃圾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.08,0:14:38.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(345,436)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.96,0:14:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Six
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.55,0:14:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這點實力…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.83,0:14:55.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你這混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.89,0:14:57.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你做了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.10,0:14:59.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,十字架？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.09,0:15:04.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Five
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.32,0:15:06.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然是十字架…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.87,0:15:10.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(380,436)}<Bishop>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.87,0:15:10.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我家的「主教」原本是個修女
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.50,0:15:13.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我拿出來借用了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.64,0:15:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}就算是你 在「赤龍帝之籠手」強化的神聖的力量面前也招架不住了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.66,0:15:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(276,441)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.76,0:15:19.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Four
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.28,0:15:23.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能 十字架會沉重打擊惡魔的守備
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.30,0:15:27.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是穿上龍之鎧甲 不可能拿在手上的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.18,0:15:30.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道說…你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.23,0:15:33.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把自己的手臂獻給了寄宿於護手上的龍？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.55,0:15:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Three
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.14,0:15:37.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是 龍的手臂 就不受惡魔的弱點的影響
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.26,0:15:40.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這手臂已經不是我自己的了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.46,0:15:47.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你看 連十字架也能拿得住
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.64,0:15:53.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你瘋了嗎 這麼做 你的手臂再也回不來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.49,0:15:54.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Two
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.73,0:15:55.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.32,0:16:00.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不惜獻出自己的手臂 這樣的一誠先生是不會輸的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.51,0:16:04.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請一定要贏 把社長奪回來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.27,0:16:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,One
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.04,0:16:08.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只不過是一隻手臂 能奪回社長的話根本不值一提
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.59,0:16:14.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,倒數結束
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.50,0:16:19.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很遺憾 時間到了 小子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.95,0:16:22.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了 就只差一點了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.59,0:16:24.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次需要付給你什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.44,0:16:25.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛 腳？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.64,0:16:27.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管什麼都可以給你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.43,0:16:30.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以目前你的基礎能力 這已經是極限了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.51,0:16:32.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我弱嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.33,0:16:35.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 為什麼要在這種緊要關頭…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.22,0:16:38.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在解除的瞬間 我把僅剩的一點力量轉移到了寶玉上面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.33,0:16:41.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那只是暫時性的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.59,0:16:46.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很遺憾 那可能還不夠應付菲尼克斯的再生能力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.37,0:16:51.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使這樣 我是絕不放棄的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.73,0:16:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:57.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你該睡覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.85,0:17:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等你醒來的時候 大概儀式也結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.32,0:17:01.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒完
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.68,0:17:05.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要滅火應該用水是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.47,0:17:06.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聖水
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.39,0:17:10.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 對於像萊薩這種級別的惡魔 區區聖水恐怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.68,0:17:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「赤龍帝的贈禮」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.68,0:17:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(425,436)}<Boostet Gear Gift>
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.24,0:17:15.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Transfer！！」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.92,0:17:23.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萊薩的火焰被…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.44,0:17:25.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能是被強化的聖水
Comment: 0,0:17:25.34,0:17:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.04,0:17:30.98,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}悪戯に微笑む 白い棘のマリア
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.14,0:17:36.63,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}刻まれた傷跡 埋めていく彩(いろ)
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.86,0:17:42.35,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}ほんの少しの夢を背に受けたなら
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.66,0:17:48.67,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}守り抜ける 加護よりも強く
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.87,0:17:55.51,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}悩める世界の果て 鼓動が高鳴っていく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.80,0:18:01.23,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}結ばれし生の願い
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.60,0:18:04.31,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}涙に濡れる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.49,0:18:07.36,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}希望の弧描くから
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.52,0:18:18.78,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯 きっとこの名はかけがえない
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.13,0:18:25.15,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.15,0:18:30.54,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.79,0:18:36.80,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶を揺らす Draw×Delete 光に立ち向かおう
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.80,0:18:48.54,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}さぁ 戦いの幕開け そっと胸に伝う紅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.02,0:17:28.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正在讓萊薩的體力和精神異常的消耗下去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.38,0:17:31.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是變成了灰也能復活的菲尼克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.06,0:17:33.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唯獨精神是不能瞬時恢復
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.97,0:17:34.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精神
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.97,0:17:39.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精神 也就是說 他的內心還不是不死的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.05,0:17:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞說過 惡魔害怕十字架和聖水
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.72,0:17:46.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把這兩個同時強化 同時使用的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.41,0:17:49.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,應該會給惡魔相當大的損傷的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.37,0:17:53.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木場說過 開闊自己的視野 觀察對手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.78,0:17:57.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Transfer！！」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.79,0:17:59.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐說過
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.21,0:18:02.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔力要從環繞全身的靈氣中流水般收集
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.84,0:18:06.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,集中精神 去感受魔力的波動
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.93,0:18:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓咪說過
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.75,0:18:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打擊敵人要瞄準中心線 要準確挖入打擊部位
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.60,0:18:15.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你明不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.98,0:18:18.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次婚約對惡魔的未來來說是必須的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.57,0:18:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且很重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.88,0:18:23.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是像你這種屁都不懂的小鬼 想怎樣就怎樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.74,0:18:25.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些難懂的我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.44,0:18:32.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是被你打暈的時候 我隱約記得
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.93,0:18:35.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長在哭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.03,0:18:40.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我打你的理由 這就足夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.56,0:18:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就憑這些…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.14,0:18:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本尊…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.10,0:18:49.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.39,0:18:54.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼怨言的話來找我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.85,0:18:56.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我隨時都能奉陪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.51,0:19:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 你真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.04,0:19:02.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.35,0:19:07.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勝負已分
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.78,0:19:19.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 小貓咪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.44,0:19:20.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.67,0:19:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你成功了 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.12,0:19:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.24,0:19:24.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要投了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.14,0:19:32.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.18,0:19:33.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.22,0:19:34.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.75,0:19:36.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.23,0:19:46.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.84,0:19:48.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是Griffon
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.99,0:19:53.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,機會難得 一誠送社長如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.28,0:19:55.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.38,0:19:58.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是 能拜託你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.17,0:20:01.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長的命令樂意效勞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.73,0:20:05.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們先去部室等你們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.22,0:20:18.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那隻Griffon原本是為了應對最壞情況而準備的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.93,0:20:22.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若變成那樣 處理後事有我們受的了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.94,0:20:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和父親 還有菲尼克斯家正在為很多事反省
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.64,0:20:31.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很遺憾 此次婚約的解除已成定局
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.51,0:20:33.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是很遺憾嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.86,0:20:35.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可你臉上沒那麼寫著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.97,0:20:37.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「Welsh Dragon」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.78,0:20:41.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我萬萬沒料到赤色龍會轉到我們一方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.99,0:20:47.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30}說不定與「Vanishing Dragon」－白色龍相遇的時刻 也應該為期不遠了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.97,0:20:53.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.84,0:20:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.12,0:20:58.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了我…做出這樣的事來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.14,0:20:59.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很划算啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.97,0:21:02.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為像這樣把社長奪回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.89,0:21:05.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次的婚約也許解除成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.45,0:21:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過還有可能迎來下一場婚約
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.08,0:21:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次是右臂 再下一次是眼睛 吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.08,0:21:13.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.28,0:21:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管多少次我都會去救你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.75,0:21:22.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟我是莉雅絲·吉蒙里大人的「兵卒」嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.76,0:21:22.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(639,436)}<Pwan>
Comment: 0,0:21:24.67,0:21:25.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.67,0:21:27.06,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.06,0:21:31.19,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.59,0:21:47.20,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}お手並みハイケン努力の成果は？（Naked soul, 覚醒！）
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.27,0:21:52.87,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}平常心のピンチ イキナリで焦る
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.90,0:21:58.54,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}逆転シーソーゲーム押されちゃシャクだよ （Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.54,0:22:03.43,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だってさっきムッとしてナンダカンダ許してしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.43,0:22:09.98,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}見つめたらぎゅっとアツくなる 変わっていくのワカル
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.16,0:22:14.39,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}こんな時はなんて言えばいいの？（シシシ Thinking time）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.40,0:22:17.58,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}待って待ってよ スキ！で正解？？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.00,0:22:21.03,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}HURRY UP！！ 恋愛力強化中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.19,0:22:24.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}レッスン1(ワン)から進めない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.27,0:22:26.96,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}このままじゃキミのこと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.11,0:22:29.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}誰かにとられちゃいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.44,0:22:35.17,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}タイミングはこっちで作りたい この次なんて来ないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.46,0:22:39.40,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追試希望 会いたいね STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.44,0:22:41.45,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしなくちゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.45,0:22:44.07,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）ずっと必然
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.10,0:22:46.80,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）教科書はない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.00,0:22:51.35,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）お手上げなんて アリエナイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.54,0:21:42.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Morning Stand Up
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.52,0:21:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是初吻哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.16,0:21:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在日本女孩子很珍惜初吻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.44,0:21:52.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那倒是沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.22,0:21:53.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？ 初吻
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.99,0:21:55.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事嗎 跟我這種人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.82,0:21:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為你對我一直以來的所做的事有那個價值
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.56,0:22:00.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是獎勵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.62,0:22:03.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光有這個獎勵 我之前的努力沒白費了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.89,0:22:04.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從今以後…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.68,0:22:05.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.71,0:22:08.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也決定在你家裡住
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.79,0:22:09.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.91,0:22:12.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想加深與僕人之間的交流嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.51,0:22:36.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快跑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.05,0:22:41.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變態 變態 變態 變態！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.66,0:23:05.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想保護那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.10,0:23:11.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,與契約或者誓約不同
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.47,0:23:14.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隨風飄動的玫瑰色紅髮
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.69,0:23:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她必須以威風凜凜的身姿存在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.61,0:23:22.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是我所憧憬的…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.11,0:23:32.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個人
