[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 4
Video Position: 23029
Last Style Storage: Default
Collisions: Normal
Original Script: DHR
Synch Point: 0


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: CR main,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0056008C,&H30000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,DFMaruGothic-Lt,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,128
Style: ED-CH,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H64FF7AFE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-JP,DFPHSMincho-W9,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP-CH,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,28,&H00212FFB,&HF0000000,&H0000CDFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.35,0:00:09.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你這傢伙 站住
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.20,0:00:22.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 跑得真快
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.29,0:00:25.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.15,0:00:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦啊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.52,0:00:36.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.31,0:00:37.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.90,0:00:42.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼一直盯著我的…胸部呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.93,0:00:46.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是因為那個胸部大得太顯眼了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.50,0:00:49.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.13,0:00:54.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 逼到絕路了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.48,0:01:01.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貴安 「走散惡魔」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.19,0:01:05.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對你的討伐命令已經下達了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.34,0:01:09.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從主人身邊逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.03,0:01:12.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了滿足自身的慾望而鬧事的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.62,0:01:16.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其罪 罪該萬死
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.05,0:01:19.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以吉蒙里公爵之名
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.82,0:01:21.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把你轟飛
Comment: 0,0:01:39.56,0:01:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.56,0:01:45.50,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交わり合う線と　遠く呼びかける空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.66,0:01:51.15,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字の下で舞う　戦慄の声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.38,0:01:56.87,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弱さなど君に見せたくないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.18,0:02:03.19,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}風を受けて振り切って進め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.39,0:02:10.03,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}衝動を解き放て！駆け巡り積もる意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.32,0:02:15.75,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}その眼を忘れはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.12,0:02:18.83,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}記憶の揺らす Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.01,0:02:21.88,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}明日に代える今を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.04,0:02:33.85,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}また輪廻する灯　そっと頬を伝う紅
Comment: 0,0:01:19.07,0:01:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.56,0:01:45.50,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}交錯相遇的線 呼喚遠處的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.66,0:01:51.15,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}十字下起舞的戰慄之聲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.38,0:01:56.87,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}不想被你看到我的軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.18,0:02:03.19,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}承受著風並掙脫它前進吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.39,0:02:10.03,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}解放你的衝動 充滿全身那蓄勢待發的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.32,0:02:15.75,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}那雙眼我絕不會忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.12,0:02:18.83,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}弄亂記憶的Draw x Delete
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.01,0:02:21.88,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}可改為明天的現在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.04,0:02:33.85,OP-CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,50)}再次輪回的燈光 輕輕略過臉頰的紅暈
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,STAFF,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(300,300)}本字幕由DHR動研字幕組製作 僅供交流使用 請於下載後24小時內刪除 有愛請支持正版\N翻譯：狼と香欣料  校譯：牧瀨氏  時軸:KoU 後期:KoU ripper
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.62,0:02:57.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,400)\fs35\fsp2\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H6F6F6F&\bord1\pos(574,388)}第13話 「胸部，開花結果！」
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.73,0:02:56.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒用的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.87,0:03:03.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐斗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.72,0:03:04.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.44,0:03:16.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 啊啦 已經結束了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.59,0:03:19.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃學姐 小貓
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.35,0:03:21.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們這邊也結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.23,0:03:23.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.92,0:03:25.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弱爆了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.04,0:03:32.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是這傢伙的使魔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.50,0:03:33.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.84,0:03:39.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個蟲 不知道為什麼一直專注於我的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.53,0:03:40.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胸部？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.79,0:03:42.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像是一誠學長一樣的蟲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.09,0:03:45.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起啊 我的存在就像個蟲一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.88,0:03:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.92,0:03:50.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事嗎 愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.10,0:03:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是…是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.67,0:03:56.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多虧了兩位保護著我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.30,0:03:59.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 「走散惡魔」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.27,0:04:00.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,將軍了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.71,0:04:04.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是說你有不投降 直接面對我們的覺悟呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.47,0:04:06.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我還是投降吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.24,0:04:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以那個吉蒙里家的公主為對手 實在是太不利了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.03,0:04:16.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,長了對不錯的奶子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.27,0:04:17.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你個混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.35,0:04:18.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你對社長說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.75,0:04:21.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像一誠學長一樣的惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.10,0:04:24.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像我一樣真是對不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.06,0:04:27.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱乃 將他拘束了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.28,0:04:30.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後通過魔法陣轉送到冥界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.08,0:04:32.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.14,0:04:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能再抵抗一下的話 我也能盡興了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.25,0:04:54.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接受冥界的制裁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.05,0:04:59.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 該做的工作都已經做完了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.31,0:05:06.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚沒我的什麼事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.36,0:05:10.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然比起木場還有朱乃 我還早得很呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.02,0:05:16.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,該做的工作都已經做完了…嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.90,0:05:19.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這…這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.52,0:05:22.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,研究室 的樣子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.11,0:05:27.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根據報告所說 是在這裡趁半夜重複著某種實驗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.40,0:05:31.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正因為看起來是很重要的資料 所以處置也很簡單明快
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.15,0:05:34.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把留下的東西全部破壞掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.61,0:05:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個「走散惡魔」 到底在幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.02,0:05:42.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺沒由得讓人在意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.53,0:05:43.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你說「胸部」！？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.53,0:05:43.80,Comment,,0000,0000,0000,,註：讓人在意的字面即為「拘泥於胸部」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.82,0:05:45.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.74,0:05:47.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你們一下子幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.77,0:05:48.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你個混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.83,0:05:52.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近和莉雅絲學姐一起上下學的次數是不是太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.69,0:05:56.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至還有傳言說你們手挽著手回家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.13,0:05:57.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這簡直是前所未聞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.87,0:06:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吶 冷靜點 松田 元濱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.40,0:06:02.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼說得出口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.08,0:06:06.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說不僅是愛西亞 就連社長也住在我家裡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.92,0:06:08.15,Comment,,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回家 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.15,0:06:09.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.89,0:06:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有那種事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.11,0:06:12.08,Comment,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.75,0:06:13.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.56,0:06:14.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說得出口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.38,0:06:17.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 因為是我的姐姐大人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.43,0:06:19.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一副勝利者的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.11,0:06:24.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那剛才一定是在反芻莉雅絲學姐豐滿的胸部吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.04,0:06:27.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰說是社長的胸部啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.22,0:06:28.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「胸部」！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.40,0:06:29.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你果然！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.57,0:06:31.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不是你說的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.99,0:06:35.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說到胸部 一誠 你知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.22,0:06:35.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.25,0:06:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近 女生不明原因的早退和缺席很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.41,0:06:42.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有奇怪的流行病啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.78,0:06:46.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 據說診斷結果只是貧血而已的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.57,0:06:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貧血？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.76,0:06:49.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來才是問題所在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.75,0:06:52.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些女生都有一個共同點
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.38,0:06:54.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部都是巨乳
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.51,0:06:56.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨…巨乳？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.56,0:06:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 這可是握有全學園女生數據的我所說的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.88,0:07:01.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不會有錯的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.06,0:07:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去的話
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.08,0:07:04.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就要面臨學園的巨乳女生驟減的危機啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.03,0:07:09.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有巨乳才會生的病啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.49,0:07:12.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.73,0:07:18.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.82,0:07:21.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.98,0:07:23.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在口中擴散的美味
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.72,0:07:25.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有適當的鹹淡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.64,0:07:26.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超級好吃的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.03,0:07:29.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 那真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.69,0:07:32.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 啊啦 大白天就這麼火熱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.66,0:07:38.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直打擾你家 做個便當之類的是理所當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.22,0:07:42.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我也做了便當帶來…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.32,0:07:44.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連愛西亞也做了我那份？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.08,0:07:49.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 既然已經有社長的了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.16,0:07:52.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當…當然也會吃愛西亞親手做的便當啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.04,0:07:54.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 這可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.09,0:07:58.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.73,0:08:00.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.52,0:08:03.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說回來 這個是…媽媽的味道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.80,0:08:05.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你讓她教你了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.15,0:08:06.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.15,0:08:11.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 讓媽媽教你了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.34,0:08:15.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好高興 練習都有價值了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.73,0:08:19.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞也很能幹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.95,0:08:23.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為…不想輸給社長
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.88,0:08:25.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然看起來會輸…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.93,0:08:29.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然比你拙手 但我也不會輸的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.50,0:08:37.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 社長 這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.65,0:08:38.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.61,0:08:41.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葛瑞菲雅小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.25,0:08:48.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 就是說那個「走散惡魔」是與魔物有關的煉金術士吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.36,0:08:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 有關此事 發現了一個問題
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.94,0:08:54.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,問題？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.32,0:08:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在研究室做出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.31,0:09:00.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冥界的觸手植物和龍的合成獸
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.40,0:09:01.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被放到這個鎮上了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.16,0:09:04.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個 合成獸是指…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.39,0:09:09.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是合成了各種各樣的動物的特徵的怪物哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.42,0:09:11.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪…怪物？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.47,0:09:13.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觸手植物先姑且不談
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.08,0:09:15.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龍倒是很麻煩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.81,0:09:21.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龍是和惡魔、天使不同的 力量的聚合體
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.39,0:09:24.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葛瑞菲雅小姐以前也有說過
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.64,0:09:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以上就是通信內容
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.43,0:09:30.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一旦有新的情報 會再行聯繫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.05,0:09:32.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.80,0:09:36.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.79,0:09:37.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.57,0:09:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.80,0:09:43.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個表情就是說有什麼收穫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.93,0:09:45.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我們找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.08,0:09:49.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕盯上這個學園的女生的東西也找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.54,0:09:50.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女生？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.07,0:09:55.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 很多女生突然身體不適是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.62,0:09:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事實
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.69,0:10:01.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,問題是 那些女生身上都留下了魔力的波動
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.42,0:10:02.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔力？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.67,0:10:06.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後就有些在意 讓祐斗和小貓暗中活動了下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.32,0:10:11.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是植物魔物嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.87,0:10:14.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.56,0:10:21.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龍！？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.56,0:10:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葛瑞菲雅所說的 應該就是這個了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.03,0:10:38.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,省下麻煩了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.64,0:10:41.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快躲起來 有人來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.05,0:10:47.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 這不是我班上的片瀨和村山嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.92,0:11:08.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它在動…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.69,0:11:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來是在吸收生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.77,0:11:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.19,0:11:12.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.56,0:11:13.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.11,0:11:18.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根據之前的事例來看 也不會有性命之憂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.84,0:11:22.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 所以再多觀察一會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.56,0:11:34.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搖搖晃晃的 但看起來應該沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.66,0:11:39.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來對盯上的女生施下法術 讓她們趁半夜裡過來這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.98,0:11:43.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後像那樣吸收生氣 作為養分
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.36,0:11:46.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種事也可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.94,0:11:50.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無論如何 總之是被我們發現了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.71,0:11:53.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,運氣也到頭了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.71,0:11:58.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.67,0:12:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要大意 攻擊開始
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.01,0:12:02.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.09,0:12:17.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,揍飛你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.21,0:12:21.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要打倒你這個破壞學園和平的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.97,0:12:25.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我上了 「赤龍帝的手甲」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.97,0:12:25.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23\pos(491,435)}<Boostet Gear>
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.65,0:12:28.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.41,0:12:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙意外的聰明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.16,0:12:45.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去會沒完沒了的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.73,0:12:48.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再生速率超越了我們的攻擊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.21,0:12:51.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發揮出了超越原有的力量呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.25,0:12:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來十分適應人間界的空氣和土地還有學園學生的生氣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.24,0:13:00.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家 沒事吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.23,0:13:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.70,0:13:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.37,0:13:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是怎樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.21,0:13:10.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是這種展開
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.28,0:13:14.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 啊啦 真是H的觸手呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.05,0:13:16.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連朱乃學姐和小貓也都…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.18,0:13:19.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這下不能冒然攻擊了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.61,0:13:21.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 該怎麼做才好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.51,0:13:25.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 啊啦 真是困擾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.78,0:13:28.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滑滑的 感覺真不好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.36,0:13:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滑滑的把衣服都…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.09,0:13:37.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這滑滑的也好黏黏的也好 會把衣服溶解了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.89,0:13:40.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長能用魔力逃脫嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.69,0:13:44.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 毀滅的魔力不怎麼能發動
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.96,0:13:47.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也無法發動雷擊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.14,0:13:51.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓 你的力量也無法逃脫嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.71,0:13:53.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黏黏的滑滑的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.49,0:13:55.45,Comment,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 啊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.23,0:13:56.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這黏液會擾亂魔力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.61,0:13:58.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.41,0:14:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都會全裸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.20,0:14:05.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是何等幸福…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.59,0:14:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 糟糕的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.62,0:14:10.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 不要在看了 你也去戰鬥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.29,0:14:12.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Dragon…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.94,0:14:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.61,0:14:25.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼只放了愛西亞和小貓
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.02,0:14:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只攻擊胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.31,0:14:34.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來是從這裡吸取生氣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.60,0:14:39.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是下流的方式呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.73,0:14:40.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.63,0:14:46.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多麼美妙…下流…不不 多麼可怕的攻擊方式啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.33,0:14:50.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貼著女性的胸部吸取生氣什麼的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.17,0:14:52.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是為什麼是胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.30,0:14:53.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要明知故問
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.29,0:14:58.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我也想貼著社長和朱乃學姐的胸部吸取生氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.15,0:15:00.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要和怪物產生共鳴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.50,0:15:04.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是共鳴 我現在極度嫉妒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.94,0:15:06.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 合成獸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.86,0:15:08.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嫉妒也不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.64,0:15:13.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話說身體不適的女生都是胸部都很大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.42,0:15:18.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 就是說這傢伙的獵物是巨乳限定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.18,0:15:21.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別分析了 快做點什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.21,0:15:26.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身為上級惡魔 不能發出這種淫穢的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.21,0:15:32.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葛瑞菲雅 比起這個有沒有什麼新的情報 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.81,0:15:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 上次說的合成獸 從巨乳的女性中吸取生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.94,0:15:42.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的啊 現在就在被它吸取啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.42,0:15:50.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有另一個特殊能力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.34,0:15:52.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特殊能力？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.56,0:15:55.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,食用這個合成獸的果實的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.75,0:16:00.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無論是多麼貧乳的女升 胸部也能變得很堅挺豐滿
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.47,0:16:01.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.65,0:16:03.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「走散惡魔」這麼說的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.36,0:16:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「世上女性都是巨乳的話 女性的心靈也會變得美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.58,0:16:10.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,男性也能向著夢想展翅高飛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.20,0:16:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貧乳有罪啊太殘酷了 世界上只有巨乳就夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.16,0:16:18.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奶子和肉體」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.63,0:16:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.52,0:16:21.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 啊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.62,0:16:25.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奶子和肉體
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.19,0:16:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多麼…多麼遠大的夢想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.61,0:16:34.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼美妙的野望實現的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.06,0:16:39.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了煩惱胸部大小的女性而生的究極生物
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.16,0:16:43.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個惡魔盯著社長的胸部看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.61,0:16:46.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使魔也盯著朱乃學姐的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.94,0:16:50.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正因為對著胸部有如此執念才有的的行動理念
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.29,0:16:54.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算背叛主人也要實現夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.51,0:16:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太佩服了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.87,0:17:01.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貧乳有罪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.46,0:17:04.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貧乳是殘酷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.90,0:17:06.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小…小貓
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.40,0:17:09.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,揍飛你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.95,0:17:13.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓大人生氣了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.88,0:17:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正我沒有像社長和朱乃學姐一樣大的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.89,0:17:22.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長她們由我來救出
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.55,0:17:24.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 帥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.61,0:17:25.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.58,0:17:26.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.32,0:17:29.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請放過這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.65,0:17:34.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它是能實現全男性的夢想的最美麗的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.08,0:17:36.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.59,0:17:40.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 這種時候一誠的H開關居然開啟了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.33,0:17:42.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 啊啦 真困擾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.24,0:17:47.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛 只要有它的話 貧乳的煩惱就能解決了…啊痛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.26,0:17:53.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就像「走散惡魔」說的那樣\N看著胸部 男性也就能興奮起來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.85,0:17:54.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.67,0:17:57.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我明明拼死地在為你辯護耶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.23,0:17:59.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請讓開
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.17,0:18:02.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個合成獸是我的敵人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.01,0:18:05.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕 但是我不能退縮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.55,0:18:06.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快看 小貓
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.92,0:18:10.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看 只要吃了那個 小貓也能變成堅挺豐滿的巨乳…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.98,0:18:17.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 木場 你在幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.22,0:18:21.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠真是讓人困擾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.34,0:18:26.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 我是為了世上的女性和未來…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.14,0:18:27.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夠了 聽好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.44,0:18:28.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.98,0:18:30.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要打倒那個合成獸的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.71,0:18:33.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和朱乃的胸部一整晚都讓你隨意玩弄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.53,0:18:38.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隨意玩弄…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.80,0:18:42.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有…有過這種日本語嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.56,0:18:45.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.31,0:18:51.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,世上的女性都是巨乳 光是想像一下的話生活就是玫瑰色的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.62,0:18:54.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我啊 好好思考啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.82,0:18:59.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算世上女性都是巨乳 那我恐怕也只能欣賞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.41,0:19:03.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只能那樣斜眼看著的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.81,0:19:06.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.84,0:19:11.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 無法承受眼前胸部的誘惑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.63,0:19:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然在這裡比起摸不到的胸部還是摸得到的好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.93,0:19:23.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我現在就來打倒你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.03,0:19:27.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,受死吧 你這合成獸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.85,0:19:29.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.40,0:19:32.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一誠 借我點力量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.73,0:19:33.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.33,0:19:34.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.64,0:19:38.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.47,0:19:39.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還不夠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.35,0:19:40.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.03,0:19:40.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還不夠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.55,0:19:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.50,0:19:44.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再加把勁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.57,0:19:45.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.81,0:19:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 就是現在
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.99,0:19:50.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長 這力量就交給你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.88,0:19:53.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Boost！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.68,0:20:08.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,確實可能解決一部分女性的煩惱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.62,0:20:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是不能為了這個而產生犧牲者
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.72,0:20:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.33,0:20:26.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,結束了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.10,0:20:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.14,0:20:38.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等！ 社長 朱乃學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.36,0:20:42.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,履行約定你們兩位那美妙的胸部讓我整晚隨意玩弄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.32,0:20:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長或朱乃學姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.32,0:20:48.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪個奶子比較好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.99,0:20:49.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.56,0:20:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 因為你前面的任性 扯平了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.63,0:21:00.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.79,0:21:03.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為那種怪物辯護
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.69,0:21:05.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小貓
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.01,0:21:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最差勁了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.66,0:21:15.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.04,0:21:18.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在這反省一晚上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.50,0:21:21.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大家回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.26,0:21:23.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛西亞 救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.01,0:21:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,社長說一誠需要反省一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.51,0:21:30.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 回去吧 愛西亞學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.81,0:21:35.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了 一誠 先走一步
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.15,0:21:37.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙 就這麼棄之不顧了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.71,0:21:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胸部先寄放在這裡了呢 一誠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.41,0:21:49.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要丟下我啊 大家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.16,0:21:51.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 社長
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.24,0:21:56.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不會再這麼做了啦
Comment: 0,0:21:57.54,0:21:58.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.54,0:21:59.93,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}冴えないでしょ？こんなんじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.93,0:22:04.06,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}私、君のハートを指導しちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.46,0:22:20.07,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}どれだけすごいの ホントのところは（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.14,0:22:25.74,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}イマイチ強引だけど騙されて（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.77,0:22:31.41,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行形 やるしかないでしょ（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.41,0:22:36.30,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}だって今キュンとして3秒後の保証はないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.30,0:22:42.85,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}予想外キャッチしたシグナル 君はなにも知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.03,0:22:47.26,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキへと進化しているのは（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.27,0:22:50.45,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ナイショナイショです 言えるわけがない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.87,0:22:53.90,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 恋愛的カリキュラム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.06,0:22:56.91,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}入門編でつまずかないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.14,0:22:59.83,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}消しゴムじゃ消せないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.98,0:23:02.14,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸に直で書いちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.31,0:23:08.04,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}展開は気分次第 覚悟して 相性なんて信じない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.33,0:23:12.27,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}瞬間が大事なんだ STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.31,0:23:14.32,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}もっとしたいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.32,0:23:16.94,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）きっと運命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.97,0:23:19.67,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）恋は気まぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.87,0:23:24.22,ED-JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）さあご一緒に（始めよう ）
Comment: 0,0:21:59.93,0:21:59.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.54,0:21:59.93,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}這樣的話很糾結對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.93,0:22:04.06,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我要指導一下你的心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.46,0:22:20.07,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}其實到底有多厲害呢（Lackey so wake up！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.14,0:22:25.74,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雖然是被迫的不過被騙了（I can't lie）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.77,0:22:31.41,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}現在進行時 只能做了吧（Don't you know？ Baby）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.41,0:22:36.30,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}畢竟現在心跳一下3秒後可沒有保障啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.30,0:22:42.85,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}意外收到的信號 你怎麼也不會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.03,0:22:47.26,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}它轉變為我的心跳的事（Non non non Top secret）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.27,0:22:50.45,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是秘密是秘密 不可能跟你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.87,0:22:53.90,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Study now 戀愛課程
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.06,0:22:56.91,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}別在入門篇就受挫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.14,0:22:59.83,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}橡皮擦是擦不掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.98,0:23:02.14,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}會直接寫在胸口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.31,0:23:08.04,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怎麼發展要看心情 做好覺悟 別相信什麼相性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.33,0:23:12.27,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}重要的是時機 STUDY×STUDY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.31,0:23:14.32,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}好想多學一學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.32,0:23:16.94,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）一定是命運
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.97,0:23:19.67,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（STUDY×STUDY）戀愛反復無常
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.87,0:23:24.22,ED-CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}（Boy meets girl）來我們一起（開始吧）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.15,0:23:31.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 帥哥 把我埋在那裡一個人回去 太過分了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.89,0:23:35.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 你們是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.27,0:23:39.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔高校DXD 第二季決定！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.66,0:23:41.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 胸部
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,
