HELMET CONFIDENT
Phụ Đề bởi DMFS & MonFansub
Timer & Translator : Thái Tuấn & Trần Thanh An
Encode & Edit : Derby Manches Fansub
Website : www.derbymanches.com
Hahha…｡Hahaha
Yeah？
Ahahahhaa
Yes, it's funny!
Ừ!
I'm an idiot
Why are you angry
I'm watching comedy on TV
Everyone laughed at you??
That's right
But why do they laugh?
Story is ......
I was eating Zero again on the test
And the whole class knows
Well, that's it ... ｡
Anyway, I'm an idiot anyway
Too bad??
I hate everyone
If you hate that, how can you grow up??
Huh!?
Your point is
I have to talk to myself again
You have to be confident! Confidence up
That would be worth living
I can not do that
Yes also
You go try it
Is it like a helmet too?
This team on you will become confident
Các bạn đang xem phim Doraemon được Vietsub bởi MonFansub - Timer : Thái Tuấn - Translator : Thái Tuấn - Encode & Edit : Derby Manches - Trụ sở : www.derbymanches.com
You go try it
Is it like a helmet too?
As you will see this life full of joy
Um!! Naturally I find myself filled with confidence
useless ...
Why are you so useless?
I'm just so useless
Looks like the confidence is not enough
Try to increase slightly see
How do you feel?
Overwhelmed confidently
Now I feel very happy with joy
That's right
Do not know now should do it?
I feel I can do everything
Now try to use it in learning
Torch!
Can I do all the exercises?
This exercise is as easy to eat porridge
Happiness too
Oh my god !! Today I sit at my desk?
Yes!! Today I will definitely study
Nobita to study the dream is not it?
Aiiiiiiii ... is not a dream
Try to go up
Yeah !!? Dessert is Dorayaki cake
Hey Nobita
To support that confidence
You and me each one a little
Are you giving me two? Thank you
Ah, my donut! No too
Study finished !! I'll go for a bit
Looks like his confidence is too high
and then Akko has ...
Hahahah I do not care about those rumors where hahaha
Hi Jaian, Suneo
Hi, Nobita hahhahahha
Everyone sees my smile?
Have fun not?
huh ..? Nobita you suffer
point 0 and still laugh lah
Hahhah? Are you jealous?
If you are jealous
then let's try to be like me! Hahaha
What's up with him?
Hi salute you
Teacher
Do you do homework?
Yes ... Yes, I do you
What a !! Have you done your homework?
I do it !! The article is easy to understand
I'm done with nothing
Really?
If you study hard, you will lose point zero.
Please say this again
I will not lose 100 points in the near future
so please come up with a difficult topic?
ah
Star nobita today is not like every day?
Haha ..... Happy to be born in this world
What are you doing?
It is true that Jaian does not know anything.
now I can do anything
Then you can go up against this wall?
He can not do it! Hahhahahha
I'll make you watch
One ... two
Get off !!
EEEEEEE...? IIII
How can I do that?
Seeing I have not done it
say what? You are sitting on our back
Back pain too
Me too
playing with, playing with
Hahha baseball is a small affair
I can play like a pro
So you hit the ball?
Nobita that hit sure raining too?
Hahahha you are too easy Jaian
Ready to be Nobita?
Throw away
Then I throw all my strength
E? Of course
Hhaha some stories this child is easy
Can not you do that?
Is not Nobita right?
These are the kids !! Mau made room for us to play ball
We need to practice
Secondary school students
we !! Jaian .... im quiet
Why? What do you want ??
They are tigers middle school students
E ...
Who here?
I am
Nobi Nobita
Huh Nobi Nobita
True Nobi Nobita
Who is that?
Probably the celebrity then has the name repeat 2 times
Or is the Karate Championship of Elementary Students?
I heard that
Round eye ...
He is full of confidence
His eyes also feel confident
Really can not do ...
What is it doing?
l run out
Or too! You're so Nobita
Okay! Everybody play football anyway
See here !! Haiz
are you back now
Are you guys again?
I'm sorry, dear
-Never
Every time you broke my glass
sincerely sorry sincerely sorry
Are you guys scolded by him?
He scolded or scolded many
This is not a joke.
Huh? He said very well but let me go offline
Sorry now keep on scolding me more
we Nobita?
Sao cậu lại nói thêm chứ ông tức giận bây giờ
Cái gì? Vui thêm hả?
go away
I'm sorry
Nobita only full trouble
so that we have a good exercise
Good something good run tired to die
If not at the ball
then this is not the case
Saying again is the world is reviving
What is the end?
- Bear
That's right !!
Enter Shizuka's house
play a bit then about
Do not know she is home?
Are you drawing?
Is Nobita ah
You entered my house at that time?
Các bạn đang xem phim Doraemon được Vietsub bởi MonFansub - Timer : Thái Tuấn - Translator : Thái Tuấn - Encode & Edit : Derby Manches - Trụ sở : www.derbymanches.com
Are you praising me?
Oh, I do not dare to receive that praise?
Woa ... Wait Nobita
Painting fruit for me to draw with
Do not you draw, do not you paint the worst school?
You wait and see my work !!!!
Done! Huh..?/
What are you doing Nobita, go away
Huh? Are you praising me for being beautiful?
I'm afraid too
What's up Shizuka?
I'm drawing him to destroy your work
eructate!! Shizuka did not find it great
Nobita you can go home
Uncle invited the grandfather to stay in dinner
Okay I'll be here tonight
Yes! Nobi house please listen
Huh? Nobita ah Sorry
Of course, the confidence is so strong that you need to adjust to the new
Nobita go home soon
I really hate you Nobita
A, thank you everyone
Huh? What did I do?
Look .... do you do this?
This one really made me?
Haiizzz ... sure their families are angry at me
They will not understand where you are.
But that is so ...
Huh? What the ...?
Fail to do it again
It's nothing at all
I'm right for you Nobita
Gia sư mặt nạ là ai vậy?
Phụ Đề bởi DMFS & MonFansub
Timer & Translator : Thái Tuấn & Nguyễn Minh Cường
Encode & Edit : Derby Manches Fansub
Website : www.derbymanches.com